<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00262_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>47082112</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="de"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Plads...<BR><BR>Menneskeheden er brudt med deres nye plads krydsere i en fjern galakse. Men hvad der venter dem der vidste ingen. En enorm sort hul er dukkede op. Fra den sorte farlige fremmede rumfartøjer stream og at beskytte vores homeland asteroider i uendelig række på den stjerne flåde!<BR>Ødelægge fjenden ved hjælp af power-ups, lave comboer at formere dine point! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 45 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Der Weltraum...<BR><BR>Die Menschheit ist mit ihren neuen Raumkreuzern in eine weit entfernte Galaxie vorgestoßen. Aber was sie dort erwartet konnte niemand ahnen. Ein riesiges schwarzes Loch ist aus dem nichts erschienen. Aus dem schwarzen nichts strömen gefährliche Außerirdische Raumschiffe und Asteroiden in unendlicher Zahl auf die Sternenflotte zu, beschütze unsere Heimat!<BR>Zerstöre die Gegner mit Unterstützung von PowerUps, mache Combos um deine Punkte zu vervielfachen! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 45 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>The space...<BR><BR>Humanity is broken with their new space Cruisers in a distant galaxy. But what awaits them there knew nobody. A huge black hole is the nothing appeared. From the black nothing dangerous alien spacecraft stream and to protect our homeland asteroids in infinite number on the star fleet!<BR>Destroy the enemy with the help of power-ups, make combos to multiply your points! <BR><BR>Package size: 45 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>El espacio...<BR><BR>La humanidad se rompe con su nuevo espacio de cruceros en una galaxia lejana. Pero lo que les espera allí conocía a nadie. Un enorme agujero negro es la nada apareció. Desde la nada negra corriente peligrosa nave extraterrestre y proteger nuestros asteroides patria en número infinito de la flota.<BR>Destruir al enemigo con la ayuda de power-ups, hacer combos para multiplicar sus puntos! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 45 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Tilaa...<BR><BR>Ihmiskunta on rikki uuden tilansa risteilijät kaukaisessa galaksissa. Mutta heitä odottaa että tiesin kukaan. Valtava musta aukko on mitään ilmestyi. Päässä musta mikään vaarallinen ulkomaalainen avaruusalus stream ja suojella meidän kotimaa asteroidit lukemattomia star fleet!<BR>Tuhota vihollisen lisävoimia auttaa, tehdä comboja moninkertaistuvat pisteesi! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 45 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>L'espace...<BR><BR>L'humanité est rompue avec leur nouvel espace croiseurs dans une galaxie lointaine. Mais ce qui les attend là personne ne savait. Un immense trou noir est le rien est apparu. Depuis le noir rien flux dangereux vaisseau alien et pour protéger nos astéroïdes patrie en nombre infini sur la flotte de star !<BR>Détruisez l'ennemi à l'aide de power-ups, faire des combos pour multiplier vos points ! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 45 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Lo spazio...<BR><BR>L'umanità è rotto con il loro nuovo spazio incrociatori nella galassia. Ma ciò che li attende non ci conosceva nessuno. Un enorme buco nero è il nulla è apparso. Dal nulla nero flusso pericoloso astronave aliena e per proteggere i nostri asteroidi patria in numero infinito sulla flotta star!<BR>Distruggere il nemico con l'aiuto di power-up, fare combo per moltiplicare i tuoi punti! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 45 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>スペース.<BR><BR>人類はその新しいスペース巡洋艦遠い銀河で壊れています。しかし、誰も知っていた何がそれらを待っています。巨大なブラック ホールは、何も登場します。黒の何も危険な異星人の宇宙船のストリームと私たちの故郷小惑星星の艦隊の無限数を保護するために ！<BR>電源 ups の助けによって敵を破壊する、あなたのポイント乗算するコンボを作る ！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 45 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Plassen...<BR><BR>Menneskeheten er brutt med sin nye plass kryssere i en fjern galakse. Men hva som venter dem det visste ingen. Et stort svart hull er ingenting virket. Fra svart ingenting farlig fremmed romskip strøm og beskytte våre hjemland asteroider i uendelig antall på star flåten!<BR>Ødelegge fienden ved hjelp av oppgraderinger, lage kombinasjoner å multiplisere dine poeng! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 45 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>De ruimte...<BR><BR>Menselijkheid is gebroken met hun nieuwe ruimte kruisers in een verre sterrenstelsel. Maar wat hen er wacht niemand wist. Een enorm zwart gat is het niets verscheen. Van de zwarte niets gevaarlijk alien ruimteschip stream en ter bescherming van ons vaderland asteroïden in oneindig veel op de ster vloot!<BR>Vernietigen van de vijand met behulp van power-ups, Maak combo's te vermenigvuldigen uw punten! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 45 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Przestrzeń...<BR><BR>Ludzkość jest zajmować się maklerstwem rezygnować ich nowe miejsce krążowników w odległej galaktyce. Ale to, co czeka ich nie wiedział nikt. Ogromną czarną dziurę to nic pojawił się. Z czarnym nic strumień niebezpieczne obcych statków kosmicznych i do ochrony naszej ojczyzny asteroidy w nieskończonej ilości na flocie gwiazdy!<BR>Zniszczyć wroga przy pomocy power upy, combo, aby pomnożyć swoje punkty! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 45 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Utrymmet...<BR><BR>Mänskligheten är bruten med deras nya utrymme kryssare i en avlägsen galax. Men vad väntar dem det visste ingen. Ett stort svart hål är ingenting dök upp. Från svart ingenting farligt främmande rymdfarkoster ström och för att skydda vårt hemland asteroider i oändligt antal på star flottan!<BR>Förstöra fienden med hjälp av power-ups, göra combos att multiplicera din poäng! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 45 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Shooter"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
