<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00163_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>4418272</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks er en online musik radiostation software, som giver den bedste musik, som du kan lytte til alle typer af musik når som helst, hvor som helst. <BR>De fleste musik albums produceret af musikentusiaster, så det er bedst at give til din spilleliste, der lader dig finde den bedste musik. Uanset om du kan lide rock, jazz eller punk, eller hip hop, klassisk, etc., kan findes her. <BR>Software funktioner: <BR>1 kan følge de nyeste, hotteste, mest populære album listen for at se. <BR>2 kraftige søgefunktion opsøge din foretrukne type musik. <BR>3.. Samling / bekymringer stødt favorit album til straks samlinger, oh. <BR>PS: den musik, der anvendes i denne software understøtter ikke M4A formater fra 8tracks.com musik, så en lille del af albummet kan ikke afspilles. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 4315 KB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - forenklet/Kinesisk - traditionelt<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks ist ein Musik Radio Software über Internet und es kann die beste Musik anbieten. Sie können jederzeit verschiedene Musik hören.<BR><BR>Das meiste Teil von Musikalbum wird von Musiklieber produziert, deshalb kann diese Software die beste Playlist anbieten. Hier können Sie die schönste Musik finden. Egal Sie Rock, Jazz, Punk oder hip hop, classical lieben, können Sie es hier finden.<BR><BR>Die Funktion von Software:<BR>1. Sie können nach den Neusten, Heißesten und Populärsten die Alben-Liste lesen.<BR>2. Nach der starken Suchensfunktion können Sie ihre Lieblingsmusik finden.<BR>3. Sammlung / Anliegen, wenn Sie das Lieblingsalben getroffen haben, sammeln Sie es.<BR>PS: Die Musik aus dieser Software kommt aus 8tracks.com. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 4315 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch/Vereinfachtes Chinesisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks is network music radio software, which provides the best music that can let you listen to various kinds of music at any time any where. <BR> <BR>The majorities of music albums are made by music fanciers, so it offers you the best playlist that can let you find the most pleasant music. No matter you like Rock, Jazz or Punk, or hip hop, classical, etc, you can find it here. <BR><BR>Software function: <BR>1. Checking album list as per the latest, hottest, and most popular;<BR>2. Powerful searching function, you can search your most favorite music category;<BR>3. Collection/concern, you can immediately collect when you meet the favorite album. <BR>PS: Music used in this software comes from 8tracks.com. m4a music format is not supported, so a small part of the album can not be played. <BR><BR>Package size: 4315 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks is network music radio software, which provides the best music that can let you listen to various kinds of music at any time any where. <BR> <BR>The majorities of music albums are made by music fanciers, so it offers you the best playlist that can let you find the most pleasant music. No matter you like Rock, Jazz or Punk, or hip hop, classical, etc, you can find it here. <BR><BR>Software function: <BR>1. Checking album list as per the latest, hottest, and most popular;<BR>2. Powerful searching function, you can search your most favorite music category;<BR>3. Collection/concern, you can immediately collect when you meet the favorite album. <BR>PS: Music used in this software comes from 8tracks.com. m4a music format is not supported, so a small part of the album can not be played. <BR><BR>Package size: 4315 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks is network music radio software, which provides the best music that can let you listen to various kinds of music at any time any where. <BR> <BR>The majorities of music albums are made by music fanciers, so it offers you the best playlist that can let you find the most pleasant music. No matter you like Rock, Jazz or Punk, or hip hop, classical, etc, you can find it here. <BR><BR>Software function: <BR>1. Checking album list as per the latest, hottest, and most popular;<BR>2. Powerful searching function, you can search your most favorite music category;<BR>3. Collection/concern, you can immediately collect when you meet the favorite album. <BR>PS: Music used in this software comes from 8tracks.com. m4a music format is not supported, so a small part of the album can not be played. <BR><BR>Package size: 4315 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks is network music radio software, which provides the best music that can let you listen to various kinds of music at any time any where. <BR> <BR>The majorities of music albums are made by music fanciers, so it offers you the best playlist that can let you find the most pleasant music. No matter you like Rock, Jazz or Punk, or hip hop, classical, etc, you can find it here. <BR><BR>Software function: <BR>1. Checking album list as per the latest, hottest, and most popular;<BR>2. Powerful searching function, you can search your most favorite music category;<BR>3. Collection/concern, you can immediately collect when you meet the favorite album. <BR>PS: Music used in this software comes from 8tracks.com. m4a music format is not supported, so a small part of the album can not be played. <BR><BR>Package size: 4315 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Blue tracks es un software de internet de estación de radio musical,lo cual ha ofrecido la mejor música y usted podría escuchar todos los tipos de música en cualquier momento.<BR>La mayoría de la colección musical es elaborada por los fanes,por eso lo que le ofrecen es la mejor lista musical y es fácil para usted encontrar la música más bonita.Tanto Rock,jazz o punk que le gusta como hip hop o classical que le aficiona aquí los conseguirán gozar.<BR>Función del software:<BR>1.Se puede registrar la lista según el carácter de la música última o más popular.<BR>2.Contiene una función maravillosa de búsqueda para facilitarle el tipo de música que le gusta.<BR>3.La función de guardar /La función de seguir con atención.Si coincide con la colección que le interesa,guárdela! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 4315 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés/Chino simplificado/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks on online-musiikin radio station ohjelmisto, joka tarjoaa parasta musiikkia, että voit kuunnella kaikki tyyppistä musiikkia missä ja milloin tahansa. <BR>Useimmat musiikkialbumit tuottaman musiikin harrastajille, joten on parasta antaa oman soittolistan, jolla voit etsiä paras musiikki. Pidit Rock, jazz tai punk tai hip hop, klassinen, jne., löytyy täältä. <BR>Ohjelmiston ominaisuuksia: <BR>1 voi seurata viimeistään kuumin, suosituin albumiluettelona katsella. <BR>2 tehokas hakutoiminto, etsiä suosikki tyyppistä musiikkia. <BR>3. Collection / koskee kohdannut suosikki albumin heti kokoelmat, oh. <BR>PS: musiikkia käytetään tässä ohjelmisto ei tue m4a formaattien 8tracks.com musiikkia, joten pieni osa albumin ei voi toistaa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 4315 Kt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Kiina - yksinkertaistettu/Kiina - perinteinen<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks est un logiciel de radio musicale sur Internet. Il vous offre les musiques les plus bonnes, vous pouvez écouter toujours et partout des musiques de tous les genres.<BR><BR>La plupart de l’album est fabriquée par les amateurs de musique, il donc vous présente la liste des musiques la plus bonne afin de trouver les musiques les plus belles. Que vous aimiez le Rock, le Jazz ou Punk, même le hip-hop, classique, etc. Vous pouvez les trouver tous ici.<BR><BR>Fonctions du logiciel :<BR>1. consulter la liste des albums selon leurs dates et popularités.<BR>2. recherches les genres de musique que vous aimez avec une grande puissance.<BR>3. collecter / intéresser. Collectes les album que vous adorez !<BR>Note : toutes les musiques utilisées dans ce logiciel viennent de 8tracks.com <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 4315 Ko - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks est un logiciel de radio musicale sur Internet. Il vous offre les musiques les plus bonnes, vous pouvez écouter toujours et partout des musiques de tous les genres.<BR><BR>La plupart de l’album est fabriquée par les amateurs de musique, il donc vous présente la liste des musiques la plus bonne afin de trouver les musiques les plus belles. Que vous aimiez le Rock, le Jazz ou Punk, même le hip-hop, classique, etc. Vous pouvez les trouver tous ici.<BR><BR>Fonctions du logiciel :<BR>1. consulter la liste des albums selon leurs dates et popularités.<BR>2. recherches les genres de musique que vous aimez avec une grande puissance.<BR>3. collecter / intéresser. Collectes les album que vous adorez !<BR>Note : toutes les musiques utilisées dans ce logiciel viennent de 8tracks.com <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 4315 Ko - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Bluetracks è un programma per ascoltare la musica online , ti offre le migliori canzoni, puoi ascoltare la musica di tutti i tipi in qualsiasi momento.<BR><BR>Gli album sono creati principalmente dagli appassionati della musica, saranno i migliori playlist e vi aiutaranno a scoprire le canzoni più belle.  Qui puoi trovare tutti i generi di musica che ti piacciono: rock, jazz, punk, hip hop, classical, ecc.<BR><BR>Funzionalità del programma:<BR>1. Visualizzazione della lista degli ultimi album, la lista degli album più venduti, e la lista degli album più popolari.<BR>2. Potente funzione di ricerca, puoi cercare la musica preferita.<BR>3.Funzione Aggiungi ai preferiti, non dimenticare di aggiungere gli album che ti piacciono nella lista dei Preferiti!<BR>PS: Le musiche del programma sono da 8tracks.com <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 4315 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese/Cinese semplificato/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracksはネットワーク音楽放送sソフトウェアで、これは最もいい音楽を提供します。いつでもどこでも様々な音楽を聴かれます。<BR>音楽アルバムの大部分は音楽熱狂的なファンによって制作されたので、最もいいプレイリストがあります。最も美しい音楽を発見られます。Rock，jazzまたはpunkが好くか、それともhip hop，classicalが好くか、全部ここで発見られます。<BR>ソフトウェア功能：<BR>1. ここで最も新しい、最も人気がある、最も流行っていることによって、アルバムリストを調べられる。<BR>2. 強大な捜索功能は君様の好きな音楽類型を捜索できる。<BR>3. 収集/注目　好きなアルバムリストに会ったら、すぐ収集してください。<BR>PS：本ソフトウェアに使っている音楽は8tracks.comからの音楽である。M4A形式の音楽をサポートしていないため、アルバムのごく一部を再生することはできません。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 4315 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語/中国語(簡体字)/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks er en elektronisk musikk radiostasjon programvare, som gir den beste musikken som du kan lytte til alle typer musikk når som helst, hvor som helst. <BR>De fleste musikkalbum produsert av musikkentusiaster, så det er best å gi til din spilleliste som lar deg finne den beste musikken. Enten du liker Rock, jazz eller punk eller hip hop, klassisk, etc., finner du her. <BR>Software funksjoner: <BR>1. kan følge den nyeste, hotteste, mest populære albumliste å vise. <BR>2. kraftige søkefunksjonen, søke ut din favoritt type musikk. <BR>3. Collection / bekymringer støtt favorittalbumet til umiddelbart samlinger, oh. <BR>PS: musikken som brukes i denne programvaren støtter ikke M4A-format fra 8tracks.com musikk, så en liten del av albumet kan ikke spilles. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 4315 KB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - Forenklet/Kinesisk - Tradisjonell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks is een online muziek-radiostation software, die de beste muziek die je op elk moment om alle soorten muziek kan luisteren, overal biedt. <BR>De meeste muziek albums geproduceerd door liefhebbers van muziek, dus het is best om te geven aan uw afspeellijst waarmee je de beste muziek te vinden. Of u nu van rock, jazz of punk of hiphop, klassiek, etc., kunt u hier vinden. <BR>Software features: <BR>1 kunnen de nieuwste, heetste, meest populaire album lijst te bekijken volgen. <BR>2 krachtige zoekfunctie, zoeken op uw favoriete soort muziek. <BR>3. Collectie / problemen ondervonden favoriete album onmiddellijk collecties, oh. <BR>PS: de muziek die in deze software niet ondersteunt m4a-formaten van 8tracks.com muziek, dus een klein deel van het album kan niet worden afgespeeld. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 4315 KB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Chinees - Vereenvoudigd/Chinees - Traditioneel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[BlueTracks är en online musik radiostation programvara, vilket ger den bästa musik som du kan lyssna på alla typer av musik när som helst, var som helst. <BR>De flesta musikalbum producerat av musikentusiaster, så det är bäst att ge till din spellista som låter dig hitta den bästa musiken. Oavsett om du gillar rock, jazz eller punk eller hip hop, klassisk, etc, finns här. <BR>Programvara funktioner: <BR>1 kan följa den senaste, hetaste, mest populära albumlistan för att visa. <BR>2 kraftfull sökfunktion, söka upp din favorit typ av musik. <BR>3. Samling / oro stött favoritalbum till omedelbart samlingar, oh. <BR>PS: den musik som används i detta program har inte stöd för m4a format från 8tracks.com musik, så en liten del av albumet kan inte spelas. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 4315 KB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Kinesiska - förenklad/Kinesiska - traditionell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Music"/><genre value="Apps:Audio"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Language.png</contentDescriptor></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
