<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00027_00">

  <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>54448624</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[EcoFish ist ein Unterwasser-Arcade-Erlebnis, wo Du Spiel-Szenarien von einer toxischen Ölpest bereinigen musst, die all deine Freunde in mörderische Wahnsinnige mutiert hat.<BR><BR>Mit einer einfachen und verständlichen Touchscreen Oberfläche, musst Du dieses ozeanische Durcheinander durch 90 Levels, mit den unterschiedlichsten Feinden, Hindernissen und grafischen Szenarien lösen.<BR><BR>Wirst Du in ter Lage sein, die Schönheit in die Tiefen des Ozeans zurückzubringen? Jetzt ist deine Chance mit EcoFish... <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 52 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Eclipse Games S.C. 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[EcoFish is an underwater arcade experience where you have to clean the game scenarios from a toxic oil spill which has turned all your little friends into maniacs!<BR><BR>With a simple and accessible interface adapted to the touchscreen, you'll have to solve this ocean mess through up to 90 levels and lots of enemies, obstacles and different graphic scenarios.<BR><BR>Will you be able to turn the beauty back to the depths of the ocean? Now it's your turn with EcoFish... <BR><BR>Package size: 52 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Eclipse Games S.C. 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[EcoFish es una experiencia arcade submarina donde tienes que limpiar los escenarios del juego de un vertido tóxico de petróleo que ha transformado a todos tus amiguitos ¡en unos maníacos homicidas!<BR><BR>Con un interfaz simple y accesible adaptado a las pantallas táctiles, tendrás que resolver este lío oceánico a través de 90 niveles con múltiples enemigos, obstáculos y diferentes escenarios gráficos.<BR><BR>¿Serás capaz de devolverle la belleza a las profundidades del océano? Ahora es tu oportunidad con EcoFish... <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 52 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Eclipse Games S.C. 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[EcoFish est une expérience arcade sous-marine où tu as à nettoyer les diferentes scènes du jeu d´un rejet toxique de pétrole qui à transformé tous tes amis dans... des maniaques homicides!<BR> <BR>En utilisant une interface simple et accessible adapté à des écrans tactiles, tu auras à résoudre ce paquet océanique à travers de quatre-vingt-dix niveaux avec des ennemis multiples, des obstacles et des différentes scènes graphiques.<BR> <BR>Seras-tu capable de lui rendre la beauté aux profondeurs de l'océan? maintenant c'est ton opportunité avec EcoFish... <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 52 MB – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Eclipse Games S.C. 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Ecofish e' un'avventura arcade sottomarina in cui dovrai salvare i tuoi amici impazziti per una fuoriuscita di petrolio tossico!<BR><BR>Con una interfaccia semplice e accessibile, perfetta per il touchscreen, risolvi questo pasticcio subacqueo ripulendo 90 livelli e incontrando nemici, sfide e scenari sempre diversi!<BR><BR>Riuscirai a riportare la bellezza nelle profondita' dell'oceano? Adesso tocca a te, gioca EcoFish! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 52 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Eclipse Games S.C. 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[EcoFishは水中アーケードの経験です。あなたは、有毒な石油流出からゲームのシナリオをきれいにする必要があります。この石油流出はマニアにすべてのあなたの小さな友達を回す！<BR><BR>    あなたは90レベルと敵、障害物と異なるグラフィックシナリオの多くにまで通ってこの海の混乱を解決しなければならない。このゲームは、iOSに適応シンプルかつアクセス可能なインターフェースを持っている。<BR><BR>    あなたは海の深さに美しさを返すことができるのだろうか。<BR>    今度はそれはEcoFishとあなたの番です... <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 52 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Eclipse Games S.C. 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
