<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00169_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>14991280</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk er et netværk disk software, Log ind med din Dropbox-konto, kan du gennemse dine Dropbox netværk disk filer, og tillader alle dokumenter til at udføre den linje. <BR>features: <BR>1 billede browsing. Du kan direkte gennemse PNG, JPG-format billeder. <BR>2 musikafspilning. Du kan afspille MP3-format musikfiler, du kan lytte til musik, mens du læser en roman, mens oh. <BR>3.. Text læse. Txt-format kan læse tekstfiler, understøtter font justering, tilføje bogmærker, mv. <BR>4 billede upload. Kan altid uploade dit fotoalbum til netværket disk. <BR>5. Gem de offlinefiler. Bare downloadet filen gemmes automatisk lokalt, selv efter intet netværk kan også ses på ethvert tidspunkt. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 15 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Kamera<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - forenklet/Kinesisk - traditionelt<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk ist eine Netzlaufwerk-Software. Sie können mit ihrer Dropbox-Nummer anmelden, dann können Sie die Dokumente in ihrem Dropbox-Netzlaufwerk durchsuchen. Beim Ausgehen können Sie alle Dokumente mitnehmen.<BR><BR>Funktionen:<BR>1. Fotos durchsuchen. Sie können die Fotos mit png, jpg-Format direkt durchsuchen.<BR>2. Musik spielen. Sie können die Musikdokumente mit mp3-Format spielen. Sie können beim Lesen eines Romans Musik hören.<BR>3. Texte lesen. Sie können Textdokumente mit txt-Format lesen. Es unterstützt Schriftartenpassen, Lesezeicheneinfügen.<BR>4. Bilder hochladen. Sie können jederzeit ihre Fotos im Album auf dem Netzlaufwerk hochladen.<BR>5. Offline-Dateien speichern. Die schon aufgeladenen Dokumente sind automatisch im Lokal gespeichert. Dann können Sie sie jederzeit ohne Internet auch lesen. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 15 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Kamera<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch/Vereinfachtes Chinesisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk is network disk software, and you can browse the files in Dropbox network disk when you log with your Dropbox account. You can let all files accompany you when you go out. <BR><BR>Functions: <BR>1. Picture browse: you can directly browse png and jpg format pictures.<BR>2. Music playing: it can play mp3 format music files, so you can listen to music while reading novels.<BR>3. Text reading: you can read txt format text files, and it supports font set and the adding of bookmark, etc. <BR>4. Picture uploading: you can upload pictures in photo album to network disk at any time. <BR>5. Off-line file saving: the downloaded files can be automatically saved in the local, and you can check at any time even if there is no networking. <BR><BR>Package size: 15 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk is network disk software, and you can browse the files in Dropbox network disk when you log with your Dropbox account. You can let all files accompany you when you go out. <BR><BR>Functions: <BR>1. Picture browse: you can directly browse png and jpg format pictures.<BR>2. Music playing: it can play mp3 format music files, so you can listen to music while reading novels.<BR>3. Text reading: you can read txt format text files, and it supports font set and the adding of bookmark, etc. <BR>4. Picture uploading: you can upload pictures in photo album to network disk at any time. <BR>5. Off-line file saving: the downloaded files can be automatically saved in the local, and you can check at any time even if there is no networking. <BR><BR>Package size: 15 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk is network disk software, and you can browse the files in Dropbox network disk when you log with your Dropbox account. You can let all files accompany you when you go out. <BR><BR>Functions: <BR>1. Picture browse: you can directly browse png and jpg format pictures.<BR>2. Music playing: it can play mp3 format music files, so you can listen to music while reading novels.<BR>3. Text reading: you can read txt format text files, and it supports font set and the adding of bookmark, etc. <BR>4. Picture uploading: you can upload pictures in photo album to network disk at any time. <BR>5. Off-line file saving: the downloaded files can be automatically saved in the local, and you can check at any time even if there is no networking. <BR><BR>Package size: 15 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk is network disk software, and you can browse the files in Dropbox network disk when you log with your Dropbox account. You can let all files accompany you when you go out. <BR><BR>Functions: <BR>1. Picture browse: you can directly browse png and jpg format pictures.<BR>2. Music playing: it can play mp3 format music files, so you can listen to music while reading novels.<BR>3. Text reading: you can read txt format text files, and it supports font set and the adding of bookmark, etc. <BR>4. Picture uploading: you can upload pictures in photo album to network disk at any time. <BR>5. Off-line file saving: the downloaded files can be automatically saved in the local, and you can check at any time even if there is no networking. <BR><BR>Package size: 15 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk es un software de disco de red,usted puede hojear los archivos en disco de red Dropbox,utilizando su cuenta de la área de cliente,Asimismo lleva los documentos acompañando contigo al salir. <BR>Características: <BR>1 Hojea los imagenes. Usted puede ver directamente imagen en formato de png, jpg . <BR>2 Reproducción de música. Usted puede reproducir archivos de música en formato de mp3, se puede escuchar la música mientras leyendo una novela.<BR>3 Leutura de txtos.Usted puede leer archivos de texto de formato de txt, se adapta el ajuste de la fuente, añadir marcadores,etc. <BR>4 Sube los imágenes. Usted puede subir su álbum de fotos al disco de red cuandoquiera. <BR>5Guarde los archivos sin conexión. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 15 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Cámara<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés/Chino simplificado/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk on verkon levylle ohjelmisto, kirjaudu sisään käyttäen Dropbox-tilin, voit selata Dropbox verkon levylle tiedostoja, ja mahdollistaa kaikkien asiakirjojen suorittaa linja. <BR>ominaisuudet: <BR>1 kuva selailu. Voit suoraan selata png, jpg-muodossa kuvia. <BR>2. musiikin toistoa. Voit soittaa mp3-muodossa musiikkitiedostoja, voit kuunnella musiikkia lukiessasi romaani, kun oh. <BR>3. Teksti lukea. Txt-muodossa voi lukea tekstitiedostoja, tukee fontin säätö, lisätä kirjanmerkkejä, jne.. <BR>4 kuvanlähetystä. Voi aina ladata valokuva-albumin verkon levylle. <BR>5 Tallenna offline-tiedostot. Juuri ladannut tiedosto tallennetaan automaattisesti paikallisesti, jopa sen jälkeen ei verkkoa voidaan tarkastella milloin tahansa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 15 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Kamera<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Kiina - yksinkertaistettu/Kiina - perinteinen<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Le ClouDisk est un logiciel de network disk. Vous pouvez parcourir les courriers dans votre network disk Dropbox par vous connecter en utilisant votre compte de Dropbox. Tous les courriers peuvent être portés toujours et partout avec vous.<BR><BR>Fonctions :<BR>1. parcourir les photos. Vous pouvez parcourir les photos en format png, jpg.<BR>2. écouter de la musique. Vous pouvez écouter des morceaus de musique en format mp3 tout en lisant les romans.<BR>3. lire les textes. Vous pouvez lire les textes en format txt, ajuster les types de caractère, ajouter les signets, etc. <BR>4. télécharger les photos. Vous pouvez télécharger à tout moment les photos de vos albums  dans le network disk.<BR>5. conserver les courriers en votre absence. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 15 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Appareil photo<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Le ClouDisk est un logiciel de network disk. Vous pouvez parcourir les courriers dans votre network disk Dropbox par vous connecter en utilisant votre compte de Dropbox. Tous les courriers peuvent être portés toujours et partout avec vous.<BR><BR>Fonctions :<BR>1. parcourir les photos. Vous pouvez parcourir les photos en format png, jpg.<BR>2. écouter de la musique. Vous pouvez écouter des morceaus de musique en format mp3 tout en lisant les romans.<BR>3. lire les textes. Vous pouvez lire les textes en format txt, ajuster les types de caractère, ajouter les signets, etc. <BR>4. télécharger les photos. Vous pouvez télécharger à tout moment les photos de vos albums  dans le network disk.<BR>5. conserver les courriers en votre absence. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 15 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Appareil photo<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk è un software di disco di rete, accedere via il tuo conto di Dropbox, è possibile sfogliare i documenti del disco di rete Dropbox, si può portare tutti i documenti quando stare fuori. <BR><BR>1. Sfogliare le pitture. È possiblie di sfogliare direttamente le immagine di png e jpg.<BR>2. Giocare la musica. È possiblie di giocare i documenti musicali di mp3, è possibile di ascoltare la musica durante la lettura di un romanzo. <BR>3. Leggere il testo. È possiblie di leggere il testo di txt, supportare la regolazione di font, aggiunger segnalibri, ecc. <BR>4. Caricamento delle immagini. È possiblie di caricare le foto del tuo album sul disco di rete. <BR>5. Salvare i documenti offline. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 15 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Fotocamera<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese/Cinese semplificato/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[CloudDiskはネットハードディスクで、Dropboxアカウントでログインすると、Dropboxネットハードディスクのファイルを閲覧することができます。外出する時に、すべてのファイルを身につけることができます。<BR>機能：<BR>1. 画像閲覧。直接にpng、jpgフォーマットの画像を閲覧することができます。<BR>2. 音楽放送。 mp3フォーマットの音楽ファイルが放送可能で、歌を聞きながら小説を読むことができます。<BR>3. テキスト閲覧。 txtフォーマットのテキストファイルを読むことができ、フォント調整、しおり添加などができます。<BR>4. 画像アップロード。 いつでもアルバムの写真をネットハードディスクアップロードすることができます。<BR>5. オフラインファイルの保存。　ダウンロードしたファイルが自動的にローカルに保存するので、ネットワークがなくても、いつでも調べることができます。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 15 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- カメラ<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語/中国語(簡体字)/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk er en nettverksdisk programvare, logg inn med din Dropbox-konto, kan du bla gjennom disk filer Dropbox nettverk, og gjør at alle dokumenter for å utføre linjen. <BR>funksjoner: <BR>1 bilde surfing. Du kan direkte bla png, jpg format bilder. <BR>2 musikkavspilling. Du kan spille mp3-format musikkfiler, du kan lytte til musikk mens du leser en roman mens oh. <BR>Tre. Text lese. Txt-format kan lese tekstfiler, støtter justering skriften, legge til bokmerker, osv.. <BR>4 bildeopplasting. Kan alltids laste fotoalbumet til nettverksdisk. <BR>5 Lagre frakoblede filer. Bare lastet ned filen vil automatisk bli lagret lokalt, selv etter noe nettverk kan også ses når som helst. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 15 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kamera<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - Forenklet/Kinesisk - Tradisjonell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk is een netwerk schijf software, inloggen met behulp van uw Dropbox-account, kunt u uw Dropbox netwerkschijf bestanden bladeren, en kunnen alle documenten voor het uitvoeren van de lijn. <BR>kenmerken: <BR>1 foto browsen. U kunt direct zoeken png, jpg-formaat foto's. <BR>2 afspelen van muziek. U kunt mp3-formaat muziekbestanden af ​​te spelen, kunt u luisteren naar muziek tijdens het lezen van een roman, terwijl oh. <BR>3. Tekst lezen. Txt formaat kan tekstbestanden lezen, ondersteunt aanpassing lettertype, bladwijzers, enz. toe te voegen. <BR>4 afbeelding uploaden. Kunt altijd uw fotoalbum uploaden naar de netwerkschijf. <BR>5 Sla de offline bestanden. Net gedownload het bestand wordt automatisch lokaal worden opgeslagen, zelfs na geen netwerk ook op elk gewenst moment kan worden bekeken. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 15 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Chinees - Vereenvoudigd/Chinees - Traditioneel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[CloudDisk är en nätverksdisk mjukvara, logga in med ditt Dropbox-konto, kan du bläddra dina Dropbox nätverksdiskfiler, och låter alla handlingar för att genomföra linjen. <BR>Funktioner: <BR>1 bildvisning. Du kan direkt bläddra png, jpg-format bilder. <BR>2 musikuppspelning. Du kan spela mp3-format musikfiler, du kan lyssna på musik medan du läser en roman medan oh. <BR>3. Text läser. Txt-format kan läsa textfiler, stöder teckenjustering, lägga till bokmärken, osv. <BR>4 bilduppladdning. Kan alltid ladda upp ditt fotoalbum till nätverksdisk. <BR>5 Spara offlinefiler. Precis laddat ner filen sparas automatiskt lokalt, även efter det nätverket också kan ses när som helst. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 15 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Kamera<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Kinesiska - förenklad/Kinesiska - traditionell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Utilities"/><genre value="Apps:Productivity"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
