<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00308_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>15383872</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>50 billion years ago...(i.e. long time ago), the earth was born. Since then, numerous species had its adventure in their lives. <BR>"Life Born" brings back memories from when we were a just microorganism and lets you experience the feeling of gods guiding them to live through hard environments!<BR><BR>In hard, wavy ocean, guide those small guys to out of the ocean by tilting your device (and yourself!).<BR>They are SOOO fragile that they die when they touch anything so watch out!<BR><BR>They don't move smoothly like you expect from characters in next-gen games? <BR>OFCOURSE THEY DON'T! <BR>what do you expect from little microorganisms?<BR><BR>It's all up to you on whether they can evolve into something.<BR>Can you keep them alive to see the future? <BR><BR>Package size: 15 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 D Team.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>５０億年前、地球が誕生した。それから現在まで生命は様々な冒険を重ね今日に至っただろう。<BR>この『lifeBorn』は私達が微生物だったころの記憶を辿ると共に<BR>神になった気分で、その命を誘導する感覚を味わえる。<BR>私達がまだ海に漂っていた頃、偶然と必然と大いなる冒険とが重なり合って始まったのだろう。<BR>より多くの微生物がゴールである砂浜に上陸すれば…そこには素敵な何かが待っている。<BR>その何かを見るのは、"LIFE BORN"を見届けた者にしかできない…。<BR><BR>新感覚！？ゆらゆら揺れる海の中、ちっさい奴らを誘導してゴール（陸地）を目指そう！<BR>デバイスを傾けて、障害物を避けながら進もう！<BR>風呂桶を傾けて動かすイメージ！？思うとおりになかなかいかない、あ　わ　て　感覚がクセになる！<BR>微生物はあまりに無力で、障害物に触れると即死！<BR>微生物一匹でもゴールはできるが、より多くの微生物をゴールに連れて行った方がいい。<BR>途中アイテムの「ハート」をとると仲間が増える。<BR>微生物達が進化する日は来るのであろうか！？ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 15 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR>- モーションセンサー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2015 D Team.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Unique"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
