<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00147_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>80834928</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Find dine våben frem! Lad det regne død og ødelæggelse! Beskyt dine dyrebare, forældreløse børn! Nedkæmp enorme og utrolige bosser! Gunhouse er delvist puzzlespil, delvist tower defense, hvor du med kæmpe kombinationer affyrer byger af kugler og specielle angreb mod fjender, som kun har én ting i tankerne: at sætte tænderne i dine delikate, forældreløse venner. Med en unik stilart, musik fra Fez-komponist Disasterpeace, kode af ham fyren fra Frog Fractions og design af en eller anden gut med navnet Brandon Sheffield, lever og ånder Gunhouse for Necrosoft Games’ firmamotto “dumme spil for idioter som os”. Er *du* en idiot ligesom os? <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 78 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Laden Sie Ihre Waffen! Lassen Sie Tod vom Himmel regnen! Beschützten Sie Ihre wertvollen Waisen! Besiegen Sie riesige, unglaubliche Endgegner! Gunhouse ist zur Hälfte Puzzle-, zur Hälfte aktives Tower-Defense-Spiel. Nutzen Sie Combos, um Kugelhagel und Spezial-Attacken gegen Ihre Gegner zu entfesseln, die nichts lieber machen würden, als Ihre köstlichen Waisenkinder zu fressen. Gunhouse bietet einen einzigartigen Grafikstil, Musik vom Fez-Komponisten Disasterpeace, Code vom Frog-Fractions-Typen und wurde von einem Chaoten namens Brandon Sheffield entworfen. Gunhouse trifft dabei das Firmenmotto von Necrosoft Games im Kern: "Dumme Spiele für Blödmänner wie wir!" Sind SIE ein Blödmann wie wir? <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 78 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Load your guns! Rain death from above! Protect your valuable orphans! Defeat giant, improbable bosses! Gunhouse is part puzzle, part active tower defense, as you make big combos to launch a hail of bullets and special attacks at the enemies who would like nothing better than to consume your delicious orphan friends. With a unique art style, music by Fez composer Disasterpeace, code by that Frog Fractions guy, and design by some yahoo named Brandon Sheffield, Gunhouse stays true to Necrosoft Games' company motto; "stupid games for jerks like us." Are *you* a jerk like us? <BR><BR>Package size: 78 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Load your guns! Rain death from above! Protect your valuable orphans! Defeat giant, improbable bosses! Gunhouse is part puzzle, part active tower defense, as you make big combos to launch a hail of bullets and special attacks at the enemies who would like nothing better than to consume your delicious orphan friends. With a unique art style, music by Fez composer Disasterpeace, code by that Frog Fractions guy, and design by some yahoo named Brandon Sheffield, Gunhouse stays true to Necrosoft Games' company motto; "stupid games for jerks like us." Are *you* a jerk like us? <BR><BR>Package size: 78 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Load your guns! Rain death from above! Protect your valuable orphans! Defeat giant, improbable bosses! Gunhouse is part puzzle, part active tower defense, as you make big combos to launch a hail of bullets and special attacks at the enemies who would like nothing better than to consume your delicious orphan friends. With a unique art style, music by Fez composer Disasterpeace, code by that Frog Fractions guy, and design by some yahoo named Brandon Sheffield, Gunhouse stays true to Necrosoft Games' company motto; "stupid games for jerks like us." Are *you* a jerk like us? <BR><BR>Package size: 78 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Load your guns! Rain death from above! Protect your valuable orphans! Defeat giant, improbable bosses! Gunhouse is part puzzle, part active tower defense, as you make big combos to launch a hail of bullets and special attacks at the enemies who would like nothing better than to consume your delicious orphan friends. With a unique art style, music by Fez composer Disasterpeace, code by that frog fractions guy, and design by some jerk named Brandon Sheffield, Gunhouse stays true to Necrosoft Games' company motto; "stupid games for jerks like us." Are *you* a jerk like us? <BR><BR>Package size: 78 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Carga tus armas! Siembra muerte desde arriba! Protege tus queridos huérfanos! Derrota bosses gigantescos! Gunhouse es medio juego de puzzle, medio torre de defensa activa: haz combos espectaculares para lanzar una lluvia de balas y ataques especiales contra los enemigos que no quieren nada más en el mundo que devorar tus deliciosos amigos huérfanos. El estilo único del arte, la música del compositor de Fez - Disasterpeace, el código del tipo de Frog Fractions y el diseño de un "yahoo" llamado Brandon Sheffield - Gunhouse se mantiene fiel al lema de Necrosoft Games: "juegos tontos para cabrones como nosotros". Y *tú*, eres un cabrón como nosotros? <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 78 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Lataa aseesi! Kuolemaa taivaalta! Suojele arvokkaita orpojasi! Tuhoa käsittämättömiä jättiläis bosseja! Gunhouse on yksi osa puzzle peliä, toinen aktiivista tower defenseä samalla, kun teet isoja komboja laukaistaksesi luoti raesateen ja erikoishyökkäykset vihollistesi niskaan, vihollisten jotka eivät himoitse mitään niin paljon kuin hotkia herkulliset orpo kaverisi. Ainutlaatuisella visuaalisella tyylillä, muusikeilla Fezin säveltäjältä Disasterpeaceltä, koodilla Frog Fractions tyypiltä ja pelisuunnittelulla joltain random Brandon Sheffieldiltä, Gunhouse pysyy uskollisena Necrosoft Gamesin tunnuslauseelle: "tyhmiä pelejä meidän kaltaisille mänteille." Oletko *sinä* meidän kaltainen mäntti? <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 78 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Chargez les canons! Faites pleuvoir la Mort sur vos ennemis! Protégez vos précieux orphelins! Triomphez de boss absurdément gigantesques! Gunhouse est un mix entre puzzle et tower defense où les gros combos font tomber un déluge de feu, balles et autres attaques sur les méchants (pas beaux) qui ne veulent qu'une chose: manger vos succulents amis orphelins.<BR><BR>Avec un style graphique unique, une musique par Disasterpeace (le mec de Fez), codé par le type qui a fait Frog Fractions, et réalisé par un maboule du nom de Brandon Sheffield, Gunhouse ne fait pas mentir la devise de Necrosoft Games: "Des jeux débiles pour des crétins comme nous." Alors, êtes-VOUS un crétin comme nous? <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 78 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Chargez les canons! Faites pleuvoir la Mort sur vos ennemis! Protégez vos précieux orphelins! Triomphez de boss absurdément gigantesques! Gunhouse est un mix entre puzzle et tower defense où les gros combos font tomber un déluge de feu, balles et autres attaques sur les méchants (pas beaux) qui ne veulent qu'une chose: manger vos succulents amis orphelins.<BR><BR>Avec un style graphique unique, une musique par Disasterpeace (le mec de Fez), codé par le type qui a fait Frog Fractions, et réalisé par un maboule du nom de Brandon Sheffield, Gunhouse ne fait pas mentir la devise de Necrosoft Games: "Des jeux débiles pour des crétins comme nous." Alors, êtes-VOUS un crétin comme nous? <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 78 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Ricarica le armi! Fai piovere morte dal cielo! Proteggi quei preziosi orfani! Sconfiggi boss tanto giganteschi quanto improbabili!<BR><BR>Gunhouse è parte puzzle, parte tower defense d'azione. Crea combo sempre più grandi e scatena una grandine di proiettili e attacchi speciali contro nemici che non hanno niente di meglio da fare che masticare i tuoi deliziosi amici orfani!<BR><BR>Con una direzione artistica unica, musiche del compositore di FEZ Disasterpiece, codice di quel tizio chiamato Frog Fractions e design di quello zoticone di Brandon Sheffield, Gunhouse tiene fede al motto di Necrosoft Games: "Giochi stupidi per cretini come noi". E tu, sei un cretino come noi? <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 78 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[パズル!タワーディフェンス！この間はGunhouse.あほなゲーム好きか？これやって見て。やらないと僕が泣きます。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 78 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Klargjør dine våpen! Regn død fra oven! Beskytt dine verdifulle foreldreløse barn! Beseir gigantiske, usannsynlige bosser! Gunhouse er delvis et puslespill, delvis et aktivt "tower defense"-spill, hvor du setter sammen store komboer for å skyte ut et hagl av kuler og spesielle angrep mot dine fiender som helst vil spise dine lekre foredreløse venner. Med en unik grafikkstil, musikk fra Fez-komponisten Disasterpeace, kode fra han Frog Fractions-fyren, og design fra en tufs som heter Brandon Sheffield, så er Gunhouse tro mot Necrosoft Games' bedrifts-motto; "dumme spill for duster som oss." Er *du* en dust som oss? <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 78 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Laad je geweren! Laat de dood naar beneden klateren! Bescherm je kostbare wezen! Versla gigantische, onwaarschijnlijke bazen! Gunhouse is deels puzzel, deels actieve torenverdediging. Maak combo’s van kogels en speciale aanvallen om de vijanden te belagen die niets liever willen dan je heerlijke weeskindjes op te peuzelen. Gunhouse heeft een unieke visuele stijl, muziek van Fez-componist Disasterpiece, code van die gast van Frog Fractions, en een ontwerp van een of andere snuiter genaamd Brandon Sheffield. Het blijft trouw aan het motto van Necrosoft Games: “Domme games voor eikels zoals wij.” Ben *jij* een eikel zoals wij? <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 78 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Załaduj swoją broń! Deszcz śmierć z góry! Ochrony cennych sieroty! Pokonaj olbrzym, nieprawdopodobne bossów! Gunhouse jest częścią układanki, część aktywna tower defense, jak zrobić duże combo, aby uruchomić grad kul i specjalnych ataków na wrogów, którzy chcą nic lepszego niż zużywają swoje pyszne osieroconych przyjaciół. Dzięki unikalnym stylu sztuki, muzyka Fez kompozytora Disasterpeace, kod frakcje przez ten facet, Żaba i projektowania przez jakiś yahoo nazwie Brandon Sheffield, Gunhouse pozostaje wierny firmy motto Necrosoft Games; "głupich gier dla takich jak my. szarpnięć" Czy ci * a * szarpnięcie jak my?<BR><BR>Tłumaczone z głupim komputerze, przepraszam! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 78 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA["Ladda dina vapen! Regna död från ovan! Skydda dina värdefulla föräldralösa! Besegra gigantiska, sanslösa bossar! Gunhouse är till hälften pussel, hälften tower defence, allt eftersom du gör stora combos för att lansera en skur av kulor och specialattacker på fiender som inget hellre vill än att förtära dina smaskiga föräldralösa vänner. Med en unik grafisk stil, musik av Fez-kompositören Disasterpeace, programmering av den där Frog Fractions-killen, och design av någon grobian vid namn Brandon Sheffield, så är Gunhouse trogen Necrosoft Games företagsmotto; “Korkade spel för idioter som oss." Är *du* en idiot som oss?" <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 78 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska<BR><BR>Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
