<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00003_00">
 <appVersion>1.05</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>30404944</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[Twist Pilotはハマってしまうこと間違いなしのパズルアクションゲームです。回転を続ける「フィル」を操作して、72もあるステージをクリアしていきます。壁に触れないように気をつけながら、ちょっかいを出してくるスパイダーや面倒なトリック、罠を避けていきましょう。<br>各ステージに散らばっているゴールデンリングを集めていかなければなりません。リングを集めたり、制限時間内にゴールに着くとスターがもらえます。パワーアップを上手く利用しましょう。<br>操作は直感的で正確さが求められます。フィルが回転するタイミングを上手く合わせて画面をドラッグしていって、狭い隙間を通り抜けていきましょう。このゲームのルールと目的は非常にシンプルなので、幅広い年齢層に楽しんでいただけます。<br><br>コンテンツ容量:29 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語/日本語/韓国語/中国語(簡体字)<br><br>著作権等:<br>(c) 2012 Crash Lab Limited. All rights reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Twist Pilot is a fiendishly addictive puzzle action game. You guide the constantly rotating Phil through 72 action-packed levels, making sure not to touch the sides while avoiding the mischievous Spiders and their troublesome tricks and traps.<br>You need to collect the Golden Rings that are littered throughout the levels. Stars are awarded for collecting rings and reaching the destination in time. Power-ups help you along the way.<br>The control system is intuitive and precise. By dragging the screen and timing the rotation correctly, Phil can be squeezed through the narrowest of gaps. The game rules and objectives are simple and easy to understand and the game is accessible to all ages and abilities.<br><br>Package size: 29 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese/Korean/Simplified Chinese<br><br>(c) 2012 Crash Lab Limited. All rights reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Twist Pilot est un passionnant jeu d’action à énigmes. Guidez Phil, personnage en constante rotation, à travers 72 niveaux pleins d’action, en évitant de toucher les bords et les araignées malfaisantes qui tenteront de vous piéger.<br>Ramassez les anneaux dorés parsemés à travers les niveaux. Des étoiles vous sont décernées lorsque vous ramassez des anneaux et atteignez votre destination à temps.  Les bonus vous aideront en chemin.<br>Les commandes sont intuitives et précises. Glissez le doigt sur l’écran, calculez correctement vos rotations et faites passer Phil à travers les espaces les plus étroits. Les règles et les objectifs sont simples et faciles à comprendre, et le jeu convient à toute les générations et tous les niveaux.<br><br>Taille du paquet: 29 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Japonais/Coréen/Chinois simplifié<br><br>(c) 2012 Crash Lab Limited. All rights reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Twist Pilot è un gioco rompicapo diabolico e coinvolgente. Phil è in rotazione costante e dovrai guidarlo attraverso 72 livelli pieni d'azione, facendo attenzione a non toccare i bordi e ad evitare i ragni e le loro trappole.<br>Devi raccogliere gli anelli dorati sparsi nei livelli. Guadagna stelle, raccogliendo anelli e raggiungendo in tempo la destinazione.  I potenziamenti t'aiutano a fare strada.<br>Il sistema di comandi è intuitivo e preciso. Trascinando il dito sullo schermo e prendendo bene il tempo per le rotazioni, Phil può infilarsi nei varchi più stretti.  Le regole e gli obiettivi del gioco sono semplici e facili da capire. Il gioco è adatto a tutte le età ed abilità.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 29 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Giapponese/Coreano/Cinese semplificato<br><br>(c) 2012 Crash Lab Limited. All rights reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Twist Pilot es un juego rompecabezas de acción diabólicamente adictivo. En él, tendrás que guiar a Phil (quien no para de dar vueltas) por los 72 niveles plagados de acción, sin tocar los laterales, al tiempo que evitas a las malvadas arañas y sus molestas trampas.<br>Tendrás que recoger los anillas de oro desperdigados por los niveles. Conseguirás estrellas si recoges el número suficiente de anillas y si llegas al destino a tiempo. Los potenciadores te ayudarán.<br>El sistema de control es intuitivo y preciso. Mueve la pantalla y coordínala con la rotación de Phil para conseguir que entre incluso por los huecos más estrechos. Las reglas del juego y los objetivos son simples, ya que el juego es ideal para cualquier edad y destreza.<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 29 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Japonés/Coreano/Chino simplificado<br><br>(c) 2012 Crash Lab Limited. All rights reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Twist Pilot ist ein Action-Knobelspiel, das höllisch süchtig macht. Du führst Phil, der sich andauernd um sich selbst dreht, durch 72 actiongeladene Levels, ohne dabei die Seiten zu berühren oder den hinterhältigen Spinnen mit ihren gemeinen Tricks in die Falle zu gehen.<br>Du musst die Goldenen Ringe einsammeln, die verstreut herumliegen. Sterne verdienst du mit dem Einsammeln von Ringen und dem Erreichen des Ziels in der vorgegebenen Zeit. Powerups helfen dir auf deinem Weg.<br>Die präzise Steuerung ist vollkommen intuitiv. Wenn du über das Display streichst und Phils Drehungen richtig abpasst, kann er sich durch den engsten Spalt quetschen. Die Spielregeln und -ziele sind leicht zu verstehen und das Spiel ist für alle Altersgruppen geeignet.<br><br>Paketgröße: 29 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Japanisch/Koreanisch/Vereinfachtes Chinesisch<br><br>(c) 2012 Crash Lab Limited. All rights reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Twist Pilot is a fiendishly addictive puzzle action game. You guide the constantly rotating Phil through 72 action-packed levels, making sure not to touch the sides while avoiding the mischievous Spiders and their troublesome tricks and traps.<br>You need to collect the Golden Rings that are littered throughout the levels. Stars are awarded for collecting rings and reaching the destination in time. Power-ups help you along the way.<br>The control system is intuitive and precise. By dragging the screen and timing the rotation correctly, Phil can be squeezed through the narrowest of gaps. The game rules and objectives are simple and easy to understand and the game is accessible to all ages and abilities.<br><br>Package size: 29 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese/Korean/Simplified Chinese<br><br>(c) 2012 Crash Lab Limited. All rights reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Twist Pilot est un passionnant jeu d’action à énigmes. Guidez Phil, personnage en constante rotation, à travers 72 niveaux pleins d’action, en évitant de toucher les bords et les araignées malfaisantes qui tenteront de vous piéger.<br>Ramassez les anneaux dorés parsemés à travers les niveaux. Des étoiles vous sont décernées lorsque vous ramassez des anneaux et atteignez votre destination à temps.  Les bonus vous aideront en chemin.<br>Les commandes sont intuitives et précises. Glissez le doigt sur l’écran, calculez correctement vos rotations et faites passer Phil à travers les espaces les plus étroits. Les règles et les objectifs sont simples et faciles à comprendre, et le jeu convient à toute les générations et tous les niveaux.<br><br>Taille du programme: 29 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Japonais/Coréen/Chinois simplifié<br><br>(c) 2012 Crash Lab Limited. All rights reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Casual"/>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
