<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00187_00">

  <appVersion>2.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>96054784</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Jage og besejre Dinosaurs til mad og DNA i de store smukke omgivelser! <BR>Tag ned masser af Dinosaur arter, rovdyr og byttedyr. <BR>Saml DNA til at låse tilpasninger såsom Hoveder, Farver, kæledyr og møbler til Hub (hjemme). <BR>Dekorer din Hub med ved at skubbe dekorationer og spiselige genstande, bord, lejrbål, frugt, ananas og meget mere! <BR>Særlig slutningen boss Mecha T-Rex, kæmpe på månen i lav tyngdekraft! <BR>Bær lederne af dine besejrede Carnivore rivaler, Spinosaurus og Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Farver, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Hub dekorationer, 9 arter af dinosaurer! <BR><BR>Touch screen forenelig, men ikke nødvendigt. <BR>Engelsk ikke afgørende for at nyde spillet. <BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 92 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Jagen und zu besiegen Dinosaurier für Lebensmittel-und DNA in den großen, schönen Umgebungen! <BR>Nehmen Sie sich viel Dinosaurier-Arten, Raubtieren und Beute. <BR>Sammeln DNA-Anpassungen wie Köpfe, Farben, Haustiere und Möbel für den Hub (zu Hause) zu entsperren. <BR>Dekorieren Sie Ihr Hub mit, indem Sie Dekorationen und essbare Objekte, Tisch, Lagerfeuer, Obst, Ananas und vieles mehr! <BR>Sonder Endgegner Mecha T-Rex, kämpfen auf dem Mond in geringer Schwerkraft! <BR>Tragen Sie die Köpfe Ihrer besiegt Carnivore Rivalen, Spinosaurus und Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Farben, 9 Köpfe, 9 Haustiere, 9 Hub Dekorationen, 9 Arten von Dinosaurier! <BR><BR>Touch-Screen-kompatibel, aber nicht notwendig. <BR>Englisch Sprache nicht wichtig, das Spiel zu genießen. <BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 92 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Hunt down and defeat Dinosaurs for food and DNA in the large beautiful environments! <BR>Take down lots of Dinosaur species, predators and prey. <BR>Collect DNA to unlock customizations such as Heads, Colours, Pets and furniture for the Hub (home). <BR>Decorate your Hub with by pushing decorations and edible objects, table, campfire, fruit, pineapples and more! <BR>Special end boss Mecha T-Rex, battle it on the Moon in low gravity! <BR>Wear the heads of your defeated Carnivore rivals, Spinosaurus and Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Colours, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Hub decorations, 9 species of Dinosaurs!<BR><BR>Touch screen compatible but not necessary.<BR>English language not vital to enjoy the game.<BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Package size: 92 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Hunt down and defeat Dinosaurs for food and DNA in the large beautiful environments! <BR>Take down lots of Dinosaur species, predators and prey. <BR>Collect DNA to unlock customizations such as Heads, Colours, Pets and furniture for the Hub (home). <BR>Decorate your Hub with by pushing decorations and edible objects, table, campfire, fruit, pineapples and more! <BR>Special end boss Mecha T-Rex, battle it on the Moon in low gravity! <BR>Wear the heads of your defeated Carnivore rivals, Spinosaurus and Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Colours, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Hub decorations, 9 species of Dinosaurs!<BR><BR>Touch screen compatible but not necessary.<BR>English language not vital to enjoy the game.<BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Package size: 92 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Hunt down and defeat Dinosaurs for food and DNA in the large beautiful environments! <BR>Take down lots of Dinosaur species, predators and prey. <BR>Collect DNA to unlock customizations such as Heads, Colours, Pets and furniture for the Hub (home). <BR>Decorate your Hub with by pushing decorations and edible objects, table, campfire, fruit, pineapples and more! <BR>Special end boss Mecha T-Rex, battle it on the Moon in low gravity! <BR>Wear the heads of your defeated Carnivore rivals, Spinosaurus and Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Colours, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Hub decorations, 9 species of Dinosaurs!<BR><BR>Touch screen compatible but not necessary.<BR>English language not vital to enjoy the game.<BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Package size: 92 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Hunt down and defeat Dinosaurs for food and DNA in the large beautiful environments! <BR>Take down lots of Dinosaur species, predators and prey. <BR>Collect DNA to unlock customizations such as Heads, Colours, Pets and furniture for the Hub (home). <BR>Decorate your Hub with by pushing decorations and edible objects, table, campfire, fruit, pineapples and more! <BR>Special end boss Mecha T-Rex, battle it on the Moon in low gravity! <BR>Wear the heads of your defeated Carnivore rivals, Spinosaurus and Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Colours, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Hub decorations, 9 species of Dinosaurs!<BR><BR>Touch screen compatible but not necessary.<BR>English language not vital to enjoy the game.<BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Package size: 92 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Perseguir y derrotar a los dinosaurios para la alimentación y el ADN en los grandes escenarios de gran belleza! <BR>Derriba un montón de especies de dinosaurios, depredadores y presas. <BR>Recoger ADN para desbloquear personalizaciones como Jefes, colores, animales domésticos y muebles para el Eje (casa). <BR>Decora tu Hub empujando decoraciones y objetos comestibles, mesa, hoguera, las frutas, la piña y más! <BR>Jefe final especial Mecha T-Rex, batalla en la Luna en baja gravedad! <BR>Use las cabezas de sus rivales derrotados Carnivore, Spinosaurus y Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 colores, 9 jefes, 9 Mascotas, 9 decoraciones Hub, 9 especies de dinosaurios! <BR><BR>Pantalla táctil compatible, pero no es necesario. <BR>Idioma Inglés no es vital para disfrutar del juego. <BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 92 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Metsästämään ja voita Dinosaurukset ruokaa ja DNA suuri kauniita ympäristöjä! <BR>Ottaa alas paljon Dinosaur lajien saalistajia ja saalista. <BR>Kerää DNA avata räätälöinnit kuten Heads, Värit, Lemmikit ja kalusteet Hub (koti). <BR>Koristele napa työntämällä koristeet ja muut syötävät esineitä, pöytä, nuotiopaikka, hedelmät, ananas ja enemmän! <BR>Special loppuun pomo Mecha T-Rex, kamppailu Kuussa matalan painopisteen!<BR>Käytä päämiehet oman voitti Carnivore kilpailijat, Spinosaurus ja Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Värit, 9 päämiehet, 9 Lemmikkieläimet, 9 Hub koristeet, 9 lajin dinosaurukset! <BR><BR>Kosketusnäyttö yhteensopiva, mutta ei välttämätöntä. <BR>Englanti kieli ei välttämätöntä nauttia pelistä. <BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 92 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Traquez et vaincre dinosaures pour l'alimentation et l'ADN dans les grands environnements magnifiques! <BR>Descendez de nombreuses espèces de dinosaures, les prédateurs et les proies. <BR>Collecter de l'ADN pour déverrouiller personnalisations telles que les chefs, couleurs, animaux domestiques et des meubles pour le Hub (à domicile). <BR>Décorez votre Hub en poussant des décorations et des objets comestibles, table, feu de camp, des fruits, ananas et plus! <BR>Fin spécial patron Mecha T-Rex, s'affrontent sur ​​la Lune en basse gravité! <BR>Porter la tête de vos rivaux vaincus Carnivore, Spinosaurus et Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 couleurs, 9 chefs, 9 Animaux, 9 décorations Hub, 9 espèces de dinosaures! <BR><BR>Écran tactile compatible mais pas nécessaire. <BR>Langue anglaise pas indispensable pour apprécier le jeu. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 92 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Traquez et vaincre dinosaures pour l'alimentation et l'ADN dans les grands environnements magnifiques! <BR>Descendez de nombreuses espèces de dinosaures, les prédateurs et les proies. <BR>Collecter de l'ADN pour déverrouiller personnalisations telles que les chefs, couleurs, animaux domestiques et des meubles pour le Hub (à domicile). <BR>Décorez votre Hub en poussant des décorations et des objets comestibles, table, feu de camp, des fruits, ananas et plus! <BR>Fin spécial patron Mecha T-Rex, s'affrontent sur ​​la Lune en basse gravité! <BR>Porter la tête de vos rivaux vaincus Carnivore, Spinosaurus et Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 couleurs, 9 chefs, 9 Animaux, 9 décorations Hub, 9 espèces de dinosaures! <BR><BR>Écran tactile compatible mais pas nécessaire. <BR>Langue anglaise pas indispensable pour apprécier le jeu. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 92 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Scovare e sconfiggere i dinosauri per il cibo e il DNA nei grandi ambienti bellissimi! <BR>Tira giù un sacco di specie di dinosauri, predatori e prede. <BR>Raccogliere DNA per sbloccare personalizzazioni come teste, colori, animali e mobili per l'hub (home). <BR>Decora il tuo Hub con spingendo decorazioni e oggetti commestibili, tavolo, falò, frutta, ananas e molto altro ancora! <BR>Boss finale speciale Mecha T-Rex, battaglia sulla Luna in bassa gravità! <BR>Indossare i capi delle vostre rivali Carnivore sconfitti, Spinosaurus e Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Colori, 9 Heads, 9 Animali domestici, 9 decorazioni Hub, 9 specie di dinosauri! <BR><BR>Touch screen compatibile, ma non necessario. <BR>Lingua inglese non vitale per godersi il gioco. <BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 92 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>追い詰めると大きな美しい環境での食品やDNAのための恐竜を倒す！ <BR>恐竜種、捕食者と獲物の多くを倒す。 <BR>このようなヘッド、色、ペットとハブ（ホーム）のための家具などのカスタマイズをアンロックするためにDNAを収集します。 <BR>装飾や食用オブジェクト、テーブル、キャンプファイヤー、フルーツ、パイナップルなどを押すことで、あなたのハブを飾る！ <BR>特別な最後のボスメカT-レックスは、低重力の月でそれを戦う！ <BR>あなたの敗北肉食のライバル、スピノサウルスとティラノサウルスレックスの頭を着用！ <BR><BR>9色、9ヘッド、9ペット、9ハブの装飾、恐竜の9種！ <BR><BR>互換性が、必要ではない画面をタッチします。 <BR>ゲームを楽しむために不可欠ではない英語。 <BR>60fpsの+ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 92 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Jakte ned og beseire dinosaurer for mat og DNA i de store vakre omgivelser! <BR>Ta ned massevis av Dinosaur arter, rovdyr og byttedyr. <BR>Samle DNA for å låse opp tilpasninger som Heads, Farger, kjæledyr og møbler til Hub (hjemme). <BR>Dekorer Hub med ved å skyve dekorasjoner og spiselige gjenstander, bord, bål, frukt, ananas og mer! <BR>Spesial slutten sjefen Mecha T-Rex, kjempe på månen i lav gravitasjon! <BR>Bruk hodene til dine beseiret Carnivore rivaler, Spinosaurus og Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Farger, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Hub dekorasjoner, ni arter av dinosaurer! <BR><BR>Berøringsskjerm kompatibel, men ikke nødvendig. <BR>Norsk språk er ikke avgjørende for å nyte spillet. <BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 92 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Jagen en versla Dinosaurussen voor voedsel en DNA in de grote mooie omgevingen! <BR>Take down veel Dinosaur soorten, roofdieren en prooi. <BR>Verzamel DNA om aanpassingen zoals Heads, Colours, huisdieren en meubels voor de Hub (thuis) te ontgrendelen. <BR>Versier je Hub door op versieringen en eetbare voorwerpen, tafel, kampvuur, fruit, ananas en meer! <BR>Speciale eindbaas Mecha T-Rex, strijden op de Maan in lage zwaartekracht! <BR>Draag de hoofden van uw versloeg Carnivore rivalen, Spinosaurus en Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Kleuren, 9 Heads, 9 Dieren, 9 Hub decoraties, 9 soorten Dinosaurussen! <BR><BR>Touch screen compatible maar niet noodzakelijk. <BR>Engels taal niet van vitaal belang om het spel te genieten. <BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 92 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Dopaść i pokonać Dinozaury w odniesieniu do żywności i DNA w dużych pięknym otoczeniu! <BR>Burzenie wiele gatunków dinozaurów, drapieżnikami i drapieżne. <BR>Zebrać DNA do odblokowania, takie jak szefowie dostosowania kolorów, Zwierzęta, i meble dla piasty (dom). <BR>Udekoruj Hub z wciskając ozdoby i przedmioty jadalne, stół, ognisko, owoce, ananasy i więcej! <BR>Mecha specjalny boss T-Rex, walczą na Księżycu w niskiej grawitacji! <BR>Nosić głowy swoimi Carnivore, pokonanych rywali Spinosaurus i Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 kolorów, 9 Głowy, 9 Zwierzęta, 9 dekoracje Hub, 9 gatunków dinozaurów! <BR><BR>Ekran dotykowy kompatybilny, ale nie jest to konieczne. <BR>Język angielski nie ważne aby cieszyć się grą. <BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 92 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Jaga och besegra Dinosaurs för mat och DNA i de stora vackra miljöer! <BR>Ta ner massor av Dinosaur arter, rovdjur och bytesdjur. <BR>Samla DNA för att låsa anpassningar såsom Heads, Färger, husdjur och möbler för Hub (hem). <BR>Dekorera din Hub genom att trycka dekorationer och ätbara föremål, bord, lägereld, frukt, ananas och mer! <BR>Särskild end boss Mecha T-Rex, slåss på Månen i låg gravitation! <BR>Bär cheferna för dina besegrade Carnivore rivaler, Spinosaurus och Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR><BR>9 Färger, 9 Heads, 9 husdjur, 9 Hub dekorationer, 9 arter av dinosaurier! <BR><BR>Pekskärm förenlig men inte nödvändigt. <BR>Engelska språket inte är avgörande för att njuta av spelet. <BR>60fps + <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 92 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
