<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00245_00">

  <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>158591904</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Udforsk et fredeligt skovområde natten og se, hvad hemmeligheder det gemmer.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Indholdsaktualisering Patch<BR><BR>Opdateret:<BR><BR>- Tilføjet nye funktioner til menuer<BR>- Ny lancering ikon og splash billede for anvendelse<BR>- Tilføjet præstation systemet<BR>- Tilføjet kreditter til slutningen spillet skærmen<BR>- Tilføjet knapper på skærmen for overordnede niveau<BR>- Website knap tager dig direkte til apps spilsiden på stedet.<BR><BR>patched:<BR><BR>- Fast bygning skalering problemer for spilleren<BR>- Forbedret belysning til overordnet kort<BR>- Bedre optimering til systemet<BR>- Fixed problem, hvor, hvis spilleren krøb lommelygten ville bøje ude af form<BR>- Rettet klodset knap og GUI tekst layout<BR>- Faste problemer opløsning med GUI<BR>- Forbedret skærmformat til anvendelse med generelle ordning <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 152 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Finsk/Dansk<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Entdecken Sie einen ruhigen Waldgebiet in der Nacht und zu sehen, welche Geheimnisse es speichert.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Content Update-Patch<BR><BR>aktualisiert:<BR><BR>- Neue Funktionen, Menüs Hinzugefügt<BR>- Neue Startsymbol und Bild Spritzen für Anwendung<BR>- Hinzugefügt Erfolgssystem<BR>- Bis Ende Spielbildschirm Hinzugefügt Credits<BR>- Zusätzliche Tasten auf dem Bildschirm für die Hauptebene<BR>- Website-Taste gelangen Sie direkt zum Spiel apps Seite vor Ort.<BR><BR>gepatcht:<BR><BR>- Fest Gebäude Skalierung Probleme für den Spieler<BR>- Verbesserte Beleuchtung für Übersichtskarte<BR>- Bessere Optimierung für System<BR>- Problem behoben, bei dem, wenn der Spieler hockten die Taschenlampe würde verbiegen<BR>- Fest klobig Taste und GUI Text-Layout<BR>- Fest Auflösung Probleme mit GUI<BR>- Verbesserte Seitenverhältnis für die Anwendung mit allgemeinen <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 152 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Dänisch/Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Französisch/Italienisch/Niederländisch/Finnisch<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Explore a peaceful woodland area at night and see what secrets it stores.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Content Update Patch <BR><BR>Updated:<BR><BR>- Added new features to menus<BR>- New launch icon and splash image for application<BR>- Added achievement system<BR>- Added credits to the end game screen<BR>- Added on-screen buttons for main level<BR>- Website button takes you directly to apps game page on site. <BR><BR>Patched:<BR><BR>- Fixed building scaling problems for the player<BR>- Improved lighting for overall map<BR>- Better optimization for system<BR>- Fixed issue in which if the player crouched the flashlight would bend out of shape<BR>- Fixed clunky button and GUI text layout<BR>- Fixed resolution issues with GUI<BR>- Improved aspect ratio for application with general system <BR><BR>Package size: 152 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Dutch/Finnish<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Explore a peaceful woodland area at night and see what secrets it stores.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Content Update Patch <BR><BR>Updated:<BR><BR>- Added new features to menus<BR>- New launch icon and splash image for application<BR>- Added achievement system<BR>- Added credits to the end game screen<BR>- Added on-screen buttons for main level<BR>- Website button takes you directly to apps game page on site. <BR><BR>Patched:<BR><BR>- Fixed building scaling problems for the player<BR>- Improved lighting for overall map<BR>- Better optimization for system<BR>- Fixed issue in which if the player crouched the flashlight would bend out of shape<BR>- Fixed clunky button and GUI text layout<BR>- Fixed resolution issues with GUI<BR>- Improved aspect ratio for application with general system <BR><BR>Package size: 152 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Dutch/Finnish<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Explore a peaceful woodland area at night and see what secrets it stores.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Content Update Patch <BR><BR>Updated:<BR><BR>- Added new features to menus<BR>- New launch icon and splash image for application<BR>- Added achievement system<BR>- Added credits to the end game screen<BR>- Added on-screen buttons for main level<BR>- Website button takes you directly to apps game page on site. <BR><BR>Patched:<BR><BR>- Fixed building scaling problems for the player<BR>- Improved lighting for overall map<BR>- Better optimization for system<BR>- Fixed issue in which if the player crouched the flashlight would bend out of shape<BR>- Fixed clunky button and GUI text layout<BR>- Fixed resolution issues with GUI<BR>- Improved aspect ratio for application with general system <BR><BR>Package size: 152 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Dutch/Finnish<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Explore a peaceful woodland area at night and see what secrets it stores.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Content Update Patch <BR><BR>Updated:<BR><BR>- Added new features to menus<BR>- New launch icon and splash image for application<BR>- Added achievement system<BR>- Added credits to the end game screen<BR>- Added on-screen buttons for main level<BR>- Website button takes you directly to apps game page on site. <BR><BR>Patched:<BR><BR>- Fixed building scaling problems for the player<BR>- Improved lighting for overall map<BR>- Better optimization for system<BR>- Fixed issue in which if the player crouched the flashlight would bend out of shape<BR>- Fixed clunky button and GUI text layout<BR>- Fixed resolution issues with GUI<BR>- Improved aspect ratio for application with general system <BR><BR>Package size: 152 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Dutch/Finnish<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Explore una zona boscosa tranquila por la noche y ver qué secretos que guarda.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Contenido parche de actualización<BR><BR>Actualizado:<BR><BR>- Se ha añadido nuevas características a los menús<BR>- Imagen splash Nuevo icono de inicio y para la aplicación<BR>- Sistema de logros Añadido<BR>- Créditos Añadido a la pantalla final del juego<BR>- Añadido botones de la pantalla de nivel principal<BR>- Botón Web te lleva directamente a la página de aplicaciones de juegos en el sitio.<BR><BR>parcheado:<BR><BR>- Problemas de escala de construcción fijos para el jugador<BR>- Una mejor iluminación para el mapa global<BR>- Mejor optimización de sistema<BR>- Solucionado el problema en el que si el jugador se agachó la linterna se inclinaba fuera de forma<BR>- Corregido botón torpe y el diseño de texto GUI<BR>- Corregidos problemas resolución con in <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 152 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Danés/Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Francés/Italiano/Holandés/Finlandés<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Tutustu rauhallinen metsän alue yöllä ja mitä salaisuuksia se tallentaa.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Sisällön päivitys Patch<BR><BR>Päivitetty:<BR><BR>- Lisätty uusia ominaisuuksia valikoita<BR>- Uudet käynnistää kuvaketta ja tilkka kuvan sovelluksen<BR>- Lisätty saavutus järjestelmä<BR>- Lisätty luottoja loppuun pelin näytön<BR>- Lisätty näytön painikkeet päätason<BR>- Verkkosivujen painike vie suoraan apps peli sivu päällä.<BR><BR>paikattava:<BR><BR>- Kiinteät rakennus skaalaus ongelmia pelaaja<BR>- Parannettu valaistus yleinen kartta<BR>- Parempi optimointi järjestelmän<BR>- Korjattu ongelma, jossa jos pelaaja kyyristyi taskulamppu taipuu huonossa kunnossa<BR>- Kiinteät kömpelöitä -painiketta ja GUI tekstin asettelu<BR>- Kiinteät resoluutio ongelmia GUI<BR>- Parannettu kuvasuhteen sovelluksen yleisen järjestelmän <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 152 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti/Ranska/Saksa/Italia/Hollanti/Suomi/Tanska<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Explorez un quartier paisible forêt la nuit et voir quels secrets il stocke.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Mise à jour du contenu Patch<BR><BR>Mise à jour:<BR><BR>- Ajout de nouvelles fonctionnalités aux menus<BR>- Nouvelle image de démarrage icône de lancement et pour l'application<BR>- Système de réalisation Ajouté<BR>- Ajout de crédits à l'écran de fin de jeu<BR>- Ajout de boutons d'écran pour le niveau principal<BR>- Bouton de site Web, vous emmène directement à la page des applications de jeu sur place.<BR><BR>patché:<BR><BR>- Des problèmes de mise à l'échelle de construction fixes pour le joueur<BR>- Amélioration de l'éclairage pour une carte globale<BR>- Une meilleure optimisation pour le système<BR>- Correction d'un problème dans lequel si le joueur se accroupit la lampe de poche se penchait hors de forme<BR>- Bouton maladroit fixe et GUI disposition <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 152 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Danois/Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Français/Italien/Néerlandais/Finnois<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Explorez un quartier paisible forêt la nuit et voir quels secrets il stocke.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Mise à jour du contenu Patch<BR><BR>Mise à jour:<BR><BR>- Ajout de nouvelles fonctionnalités aux menus<BR>- Nouvelle image de démarrage icône de lancement et pour l'application<BR>- Système de réalisation Ajouté<BR>- Ajout de crédits à l'écran de fin de jeu<BR>- Ajout de boutons d'écran pour le niveau principal<BR>- Bouton de site Web, vous emmène directement à la page des applications de jeu sur place.<BR><BR>patché:<BR><BR>- Des problèmes de mise à l'échelle de construction fixes pour le joueur<BR>- Amélioration de l'éclairage pour une carte globale<BR>- Une meilleure optimisation pour le système<BR>- Correction d'un problème dans lequel si le joueur se accroupit la lampe de poche se penchait hors de forme<BR>- Bouton maladroit fixe et GUI disposition <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 152 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Danois/Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Français/Italien/Néerlandais/Finnois<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Esplora una tranquilla area boschiva di notte e vedere quali segreti esso memorizza.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Aggiornamento Contenuti Patch<BR><BR>aggiornato:<BR><BR>- Aggiunte nuove funzioni per i menu<BR>- Splash immagine Nuova icona di lancio e per l'applicazione<BR>- Sistema di realizzazione Aggiunto<BR>- Aggiunta crediti alla schermata di gioco end<BR>- Aggiunti pulsanti sullo schermo per il livello principale<BR>- Tasto Website porta direttamente alla pagina apps gioco sul sito.<BR><BR>patched:<BR><BR>- Problemi di scala edilizia fissi per il giocatore<BR>- Migliorata l'illuminazione per la mappa globale<BR>- Una migliore ottimizzazione per il sistema<BR>- Risolto il problema in cui se il giocatore si accucciò la torcia sarebbe piegato fuori forma<BR>- Tasto goffo fisso e il layout del testo GUI<BR>- Problemi di risoluzione fissa con GUI<BR>- Migliorata <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 152 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Danese/Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Francese/Italiano/Olandese/Finlandese<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>夜に平和な森林エリアを探索し、それが格納何の秘密を参照してください。<BR><BR>V。1.02<BR><BR>コンテンツ更新パッチ<BR><BR>更新日：<BR><BR>- メニューに新しい機能を追加しました<BR>- アプリケーションのための新しい起動アイコンとスプラッシュイメージ<BR>- を追加しました成果システム<BR>- エンドゲーム画面にクレジットを追加しました<BR>- 主なレベルを追加しました画面上のボタン<BR>- ウェブサイトのボタンがサイト上でアプリのゲームのページに直接アクセスできます。<BR><BR>パッチを適用：<BR><BR>- プレイヤーのための固定建物スケーリングの問題<BR>- 全体的な地図のための改良照明<BR>- システムのためのより良い最適化<BR>- プレイヤーが懐中電灯をうずくまっている場合において修正された問題は、形状の外に曲がるだろう<BR>- 固定無骨なボタンとGUIテキストレイアウト<BR>- GUIを修正解像度の問題<BR>- 一般的なシステムとアプリケーションのための改良アスペクト比 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 152 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>デンマーク語/ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/フランス語/イタリア語/オランダ語/フィンランド語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Utforske en fredelig skogområde om natten og se hvilke hemmeligheter den lagrer.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Innhold Oppdatering Patch<BR><BR>oppdatert:<BR><BR>- Lagt til nye funksjoner i menyer<BR>- Ny lansering ikonet og splash bilde for søknad<BR>- Lagt prestasjon system<BR>- Lagt kreditter til slutten spillet skjermen<BR>- Lagt på skjermen knapper for hovednivå<BR>- Nettstedet knappen tar deg direkte til apps spillsiden på stedet.<BR><BR>lappet:<BR><BR>- Faste byggeskalerings problemer for spilleren<BR>- Bedre belysning for generell kartet<BR>- Bedre optimalisering for system<BR>- Fikset problem med at hvis spilleren huket lommelykten ville bøye ute av form<BR>- Fikset clunky knapp og GUI tekst layout<BR>- Faste oppløsning problemer med GUI<BR>- Forbedret sideforholdet for søknad med generell system <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 152 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Finsk/Dansk<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Ontdek een rustige bosrijke omgeving in de nacht en zien welke geheimen het slaat.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Inhoud bijwerken Patch<BR><BR>bijgewerkt:<BR><BR>- Toegevoegde nieuwe functies om de menu's<BR>- Nieuwe afbeelding splash lancering pictogram en voor toepassing<BR>- Toegevoegd prestatie-systeem<BR>- Toegevoegde kredieten aan het einde spel scherm<BR>- Added on-screen knoppen voor de belangrijkste niveau<BR>- Website knop brengt u rechtstreeks naar apps spel pagina op de site.<BR><BR>gepatched:<BR><BR>- Fixed gebouw scaling problemen voor de speler<BR>- Betere verlichting voor algemene kaart<BR>- Betere optimalisatie voor systeem<BR>- Fixed probleem waarbij als de speler gehurkt de zaklamp zou uit vorm te buigen<BR>- Vaste onhandig knop en GUI tekstopmaak<BR>- Vaste resolutie problemen met GUI<BR>- Verbeterde aspect ratio voor applicatie met algemeen ste <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 152 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels/Frans/Duits/Italiaans/Nederlands/Fins/Deens<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Przeglądaj w spokojnej zalesionej okolicy w nocy i zobaczyć, jakie tajemnice przechowuje.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Content Update Patch<BR><BR>Aktualizacja:<BR><BR>- Dodano nowe funkcje do menu<BR>- Nowa ikona uruchomienie i tło dla aplikacji<BR>- Dodano system osiągnięć<BR>- Dodano kredytów do ekranu koniec gry<BR>- Dodano przyciski ekranowe do poziomu głównego<BR>- Przycisk strony prowadzi bezpośrednio do strony aplikacje gry na miejscu.<BR><BR>poprawione:<BR><BR>- Naprawiono problemy skalowania budynek dla gracza<BR>- Poprawa oświetlenia ogólnego mapie<BR>- Lepsza optymalizacja dla systemu<BR>- Naprawiono błąd, w którym, jeśli gracz przykucnął latarkę stawali na kształt<BR>- Naprawiono przylegający przycisk GUI i układ tekstu<BR>- Naprawiono problemy z GUI rozdzielczości<BR>- Lepsze proporcje do zastosowania z ogólnego systemu <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 152 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Duński/Niemiecki/Angielski/Angielski/Fiński/Francuski/Włoski/Holenderski<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Utforska ett lugnt skogsområde på natten och se vilka hemligheter den lagrar.<BR><BR>v. 1.02<BR><BR>Innehåll Update Patch<BR><BR>Uppdaterad:<BR><BR>- Lagt till nya funktioner till menyer<BR>- Ny lansering ikon och stänkbild för ansökan<BR>- Inkom prestation system<BR>- Inkom krediter till slutspelskärmen<BR>- Tillagd på skärmen knappar för huvudnivå<BR>- Webbplats knappen tar dig direkt till apps spel sida på webbplatsen.<BR><BR>patched:<BR><BR>- Fast bygga skal problem för spelaren<BR>- Förbättrad belysning för övergripande karta<BR>- Bättre optimering för systemet<BR>- Fast problem där om spelaren hukade ficklampan skulle böja ur form<BR>- Fast clunky knapp och GUI textlayout<BR>- Fast upplösning problem med GUI<BR>- Förbättrad bildförhållande för tillämpning med generella ordningen <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 152 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska/Franska/Tyska/Italienska/Holländska/Finska/Danska<BR><BR>BTKi Gaming<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Simulation"/><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
