<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00001_00">
 <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>80604848</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[土地を略奪滑らかなタッチのインターフェイスを使用して、新しい、ユニークなブロックマッチングパズルゲームです。それは、高速で、楽しさとプレイしやすいです。<br>土地全体の村や町を通じ、彼らが暴れ、金やマナを岸および収集し、それらを送信するために参加アップ野生のヴァイキング。<br>前に、各レベルは北欧の神を呼ぶか、魔法の呪文をプレイするためにあなたのマナを使用するあなたのバイキングrunestonesを装備することができます。<br>これは、すべて順風満帆ではありません！クモの攻撃、酔った軍隊、戦争の霧に気をつけろとのより多くのあなたの進歩を妨げ、あなたが気づいてキャッチすることができます。<br><br>コンテンツ容量:77 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>© 2012 Playerthree Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Loot the Land is a new, unique block-matching puzzle game using a slick touch interface. It’s fast, fun and easy to play.<br>Join-up the jolly Vikings to send them to shore and collect gold or mana as they rampage through villages and towns throughout the land.<br>Before each level your can equip Viking runestones that call upon the Norse gods or use your mana to cast magical spells.<br>It’s not all plain sailing! Watch out for spider attacks, drunken armies, the mist of war and more can hinder your progress and catch you unaware.<br><br>Package size: 77 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>© 2012 Playerthree Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Loot the Land est un jeu de block puzzle qui utilise une interface astucieuse.<br>C'est rapide, sympa et facile à jouer!<br>Rejoins les joyeux vikings et envoie les en mer pour collecter de l'or et des mana alors qu'ils pillent les villages et les villes alentours.<br>Avant chaque niveau, équipe tes Vikings de pierre de runique pour en appeler aux Dieux nordiques ou utilise tes mana pour jeter des sorts.<br>Ce n'est pas juste de la navigation! Prends garde à ne pas te laisser prendre au dépourvu par les attaques d'araignées, les armées de soldats ivres, le brouillard guerrier, et bien plus encore de dangers qui n'ont pour seul but que de t'empêcher de progresser.<br><br>Taille du paquet: 77 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>© 2012 Playerthree Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Loot The Land è un nuovo, unico block-matching puzzle game con una interfaccia touch innovativa. E 'veloce, divertente e facile da giocare.<br>Mettere in contatto le vichinghi jolly di mandarli a riva e raccogliere oro o mana come rampage attraverso villaggi e città in tutto il paese.<br>Prima di ogni livello puoi equipaggiare rune vichinghe per chiedere aiuto alle divinità nordiche o utilizzare il mana per lanciare incantesimi.<br>Non è tutto rose e fiori! Attenzione, attacchi dei ragni, eserciti ubriachi, la nebbia di guerra e altro possono ostacolare il tuo progresso e prenderti di sorpresa.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 77 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>© 2012 Playerthree Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Loot The Land es un nuevo y único bloque de coincidencia de juego de puzzle con un interfaz táctil pulido. Es rápido, divertido y fácil de jugar.<br>Join-el salvaje Vikings para enviarlos a la orilla y recoger el oro o maná, ya que alboroto a través de pueblos y ciudades por todo el país.<br>Antes de cada nivel pueden equipar sus piedras rúnicas vikingas que invocan a los dioses nórdicos o usar su maná para lanzar hechizos mágicos.<br>No todo es coser y cantar! Tenga cuidado con los ataques de araña, Ejércitos borrachos, la niebla de la guerra y más pueden obstaculizar su progreso y pillarte desprevenido.<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 77 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<br><br>© 2012 Playerthree Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Loot The Land ist eine neue, einzigartige Block-Matching-Puzzle-Spiel mit einem glatten Touch-Interface. Es ist schnell, einfach und macht Spaß zu spielen.<br>Join-up die wilden Wikinger zu senden an Land und sammeln Gold oder Mana wie sie Amoklauf durch Dörfer und Städte im ganzen Land.<br>Vor jeder Ebene kann rüsten Sie Ihre Viking Runensteine​​, die auf der nordischen Götter anrufen oder verwenden Ihre Mana magische Zaubersprüche.<br>Es ist nicht alles glatt! Watch out for spider Attacken, betrunkene Armeen, den Nebel des Krieges und Ihren Fortschritt behindern können und fangen Sie nicht wissen.<br><br>Paketgröße: 77 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<br><br>© 2012 Playerthree Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Loot the Land is a new, unique block-matching puzzle game using a slick touch interface. It’s fast, fun and easy to play.<br>Join-up the jolly Vikings to send them to shore and collect gold or mana as they rampage through villages and towns throughout the land.<br>Before each level your can equip Viking runestones that call upon the Norse gods or use your mana to cast magical spells.<br>It’s not all plain sailing! Watch out for spider attacks, drunken armies, the mist of war and more can hinder your progress and catch you unaware.<br><br>Package size: 77 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>© 2012 Playerthree Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Loot the Land est un jeu de block puzzle qui utilise une interface astucieuse.<br>C'est rapide, sympa et facile à jouer!<br>Rejoins les joyeux vikings et envoie les en mer pour collecter de l'or et des mana alors qu'ils pillent les villages et les villes alentours.<br>Avant chaque niveau, équipe tes Vikings de pierre de runique pour en appeler aux Dieux nordiques ou utilise tes mana pour jeter des sorts.<br>Ce n'est pas juste de la navigation! Prends garde à ne pas te laisser prendre au dépourvu par les attaques d'araignées, les armées de soldats ivres, le brouillard guerrier, et bien plus encore de dangers qui n'ont pour seul but que de t'empêcher de progresser.<br><br>Taille du programme: 77 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>© 2012 Playerthree Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Casual"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
