<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00148_00">

  <appVersion>2.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>26298416</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Respekter dine ældste! I denne finurlige handling rollespil, tage rollen som Grandsun, en helt opgave med restaurering af universet ... af sine bedsteforældre. Kæmper gennem horder af absurde uhyrligheder vil Grandsun indsamle plyndre, der kan bruges til forskellige formål såsom at øge hans stats, ekstra erfaringspoint, og bringe orden på en kaotisk eksistens.<BR><BR>Med en original soundtrack spænder fra klassisk til heavy metal, Grand Sun RYEZ er sikker på at underholde gennem flere playthroughs og indhold opdateringer. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 26 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Respektieren Sie Ihre Ältesten! In diesem skurrilen Action-Rollenspiel, nehmen Sie die Rolle des Grandsun, ein Held mit der Wiederherstellung des Universums beauftragt ... von seinen Großeltern. Der Kampf durch Horden von absurd Monstrositäten, werden Grandsun Beute, die für verschiedene Zwecke wie die Erhöhung der seine Statistiken, extra Erfahrungspunkte, und bringen Ordnung in eine chaotische Existenz eingesetzt werden können zu sammeln. <BR><BR>Mit einem Original-Soundtrack von Klassik bis Heavy Metal, ist Grand Sun RYEZ sicher, dass Sie durch mehrere Spielen hinweg und Content-Updates zu unterhalten. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 26 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Respect your elders! In this quirky action role-playing game, take the role of Grandsun, a hero tasked with the restoration of the universe... by his grandparents. Battling through hordes of absurd monstrosities, Grandsun will collect loot which can be used for various purposes such as increasing his stats, extra experience points, and bringing order to a chaotic existence.<BR><BR>Featuring an original soundtrack ranging from classical to heavy metal, Grand Sun RYEZ is sure to entertain through multiple playthroughs and content updates.<BR><BR>New in ver 2.01: Dramatically increased text quality, and adjusted item drop rates <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Respect your elders! In this quirky action role-playing game, take the role of Grandsun, a hero tasked with the restoration of the universe... by his grandparents. Battling through hordes of absurd monstrosities, Grandsun will collect loot which can be used for various purposes such as increasing his stats, extra experience points, and bringing order to a chaotic existence.<BR><BR>Featuring an original soundtrack ranging from classical to heavy metal, Grand Sun RYEZ is sure to entertain through multiple playthroughs and content updates.<BR><BR>New in ver 2.01: Dramatically increased text quality, and adjusted item drop rates <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Respect your elders! In this quirky action role-playing game, take the role of Grandsun, a hero tasked with the restoration of the universe... by his grandparents. Battling through hordes of absurd monstrosities, Grandsun will collect loot which can be used for various purposes such as increasing his stats, extra experience points, and bringing order to a chaotic existence.<BR><BR>Featuring an original soundtrack ranging from classical to heavy metal, Grand Sun RYEZ is sure to entertain through multiple playthroughs and content updates.<BR><BR>New in ver 2.01: Dramatically increased text quality, and adjusted item drop rates <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Respect your elders! In this quirky action role-playing game, take the role of Grandsun, a hero tasked with the restoration of the universe... by his grandparents. Battling through hordes of absurd monstrosities, Grandsun will collect loot which can be used for various purposes such as increasing his stats, extra experience points, and bringing order to a chaotic existence.<BR><BR>Featuring an original soundtrack ranging from classical to heavy metal, Grand Sun RYEZ is sure to entertain through multiple playthroughs and content updates.<BR><BR>New in ver 2.01: Dramatically increased text quality, and adjusted item drop rates <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[!Respeta a tus ancianos! En este juego raro y peculiar de accion y roleplay, toma el papel de Grandsun- un heroe asignado con la tarea de la restoracion del universo... por sus abuelos. Peleando contra hordas de monstruos absurdos, Grandsun obtrendra plata que puede estar utilizada para varias cosas como aumentar a sus estadisticas, puntos de experiencia extra y poner orden a una existencia caoitica.<BR>Caucion - hay juego de palabra al extremo! !Las tonterias no son lo que parecen!<BR>Con musica tradicional de un grupo escandenavo "Los Aaltos" (de la misma familia del creador del juego) y con una opcion de tener musica mas caotica( por los mismos creadores del juego), Grand Sun RYEZ es seguro para entretener a traves de multiples playthroughs y contendido nuevo.<BR>Ver 2.01: todo nuevo! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 26 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Kunnioita vanhuksia! Tässä omituisessa toiminta roolipelissä pelaaja ottaa päähenkilö Grandsunin roolin, sankari jonka tehtävänä on luoda järjestysta Universumiin, isovanhempiensa avulla. Taistele tiesi läpi kauheita hiriviöitä ja kerää ryöstää jonka avulla voit parantaa hahmosi, nostaa kokemuspisteitä ja tuoda järjestysta kaaokseen. Omaperäinen musiikki joka vaihtelee klassisesta musiikista heavy metalliin ja lukuisia pelitasoja ja sisältöpäivityksiä antaa pelaajalle paljon viihdettä. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 26 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Respectez vos ainés! Dans ce jeux de rôle, prenez le rôle de Grandsun - un héro chargé de restaurer l’univers... de ses grand-parents. Combattant à travers des hordes de monstruosités absurdes, Grandsun collectera du butin qui lui serviront a augmenter ses statistiques, points d’expérience et tenter de ramener l'ordre dans cette existence chaotique. Prudence - jeux de mots extrêmes! Absurdités et inepties n'en sont probablement pas! Accompagné de musiques Scandinave traditionnelle du groupe The Aaltos (membres de la famille du créateur), musiques audacieuses et underground, Grand Sun RYEZ est certain de vous divertir au travers de nombreuses parties ainsi que d'abondante mises à jour de contenu. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 26 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Respectez vos ainés! Dans ce jeux de rôle, prenez le rôle de Grandsun - un héro chargé de restaurer l’univers... de ses grand-parents. Combattant à travers des hordes de monstruosités absurdes, Grandsun collectera du butin qui lui serviront a augmenter ses statistiques, points d’expérience et tenter de ramener l'ordre dans cette existence chaotique. Prudence - jeux de mots extrêmes! Absurdités et inepties n'en sont probablement pas! Accompagné de musiques Scandinave traditionnelle du groupe The Aaltos (membres de la famille du créateur), musiques audacieuses et underground, Grand Sun RYEZ est certain de vous divertir au travers de nombreuses parties ainsi que d'abondante mises à jour de contenu. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 26 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Rispetta gli anziani! In questa azione stravagante gioco di ruolo, assumere il ruolo di Grandsun, un eroe incaricato con la restaurazione dell'universo ... dai nonni. Combattendo attraverso orde di mostruosità assurde, Grandsun raccoglierà bottino che può essere utilizzato per vari scopi, come l'aumento sue statistiche, punti esperienza extra, e portando per un'esistenza caotica. <BR><BR>Caratterizzato da una colonna sonora originale che va dalla musica classica al metal, Grand Sun RYEZ è sicuro per intrattenere attraverso molteplici partite e gli aggiornamenti dei contenuti. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 26 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[お年寄りを大切に！このとっぴなアクションRPGでは、<BR>祖父母から世界の復旧という使命を課せられた「グランドサン」という名のヒーローとして大活躍！<BR><BR>しゃれにならない怪物の群れに立ち向かい、ステータスの増強や経験値の増幅など、<BR>様々な目的に活用できる戦利品を集めながら、混沌とした世界に秩序を取り戻します。<BR><BR>注意 ！－ 言葉遊びの量がハンパない！一見無意味な言葉にも隠された意図が？！<BR><BR>スカンジナビのアーティストグループ「ザ・アルトーズ」（当ゲーム開発チームの家族により構成）よりお届けする伝統的な音楽をフィーチャーし、<BR>よりエッジの効いた音楽（当ゲーム開発チーム作）もオプションとして楽しめる「グランドサンライズ」は高いリプレイバリューとコンテンツアップデートで、毎回フレッシュな面白さをご提供します！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 26 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Respekter de som er eldre! I denne quirky handlingen rollespill, ta rollen som Grandsun, en helt oppgave med restaurering av universet ... av sine besteforeldre. Kjemper gjennom horder av absurde uhyrer, vil Grandsun samle tyvegods som kan brukes til ulike formål, for eksempel å øke sin statistikk, ekstra erfaringspoeng, og bringe orden i en kaotisk tilværelse.<BR><BR>Med et originalt soundtrack som spenner fra klassisk til heavy metal, er Grand Sun RYEZ sikker på å underholde gjennom flere playthroughs og innholdsoppdateringer. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 26 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Respecteer uw oudsten! In deze eigenzinnige actie role-playing game, neemt de rol van Grandsun, een held belast met de restauratie van het heelal ... door zijn grootouders. Vechten door hordes absurd monstruositeiten, zal Grandsun buit die kan worden gebruikt voor verschillende doeleinden, zoals het verhogen van zijn stats, extra experience points, en het op orde brengen van een chaotisch bestaan ​​te verzamelen. <BR>Met een originele soundtrack variërend van klassiek tot heavy metal, Grand Sun RYEZ is zeker te vermaken door middel van meerdere playthroughs en content updates. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 26 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Szanuj swoich rodziców! W tym dziwaczne działania cRPG, przyjąć rolę Grandsun, bohatera, którego zadaniem jest przywrócenie wszechświata ... przez dziadków. Walki przez hordy absurdalnych potworności, Grandsun będzie zbierać łupy, które mogą być wykorzystywane do różnych celów, takich jak zwiększenie jego statystyki, dodatkowe punkty doświadczenia i porządkowanie chaosu egzystencji. <BR><BR>Posiada oryginalną ścieżkę dźwiękową, począwszy od klasycznego heavy metalu, Grand Sun RYEZ z pewnością bawić przez wiele playthroughs i aktualizacji treści. <BR><BR>Nowy w ver 2.01: Znacznie wzrosła jakość tekstu i spadek skorygowanej pozycji stopy <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 26 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Respektera de äldre! I detta egendomliga action rollspel tar du på dig rollen som Grandsun, en hjälte med uppdrag att bringa ordning i Universum... med hjälp av sina morföräldrar. Genom att kämpa mot horder av hemska monster kan Grandsun samla på sig olika föremål som kan användas till att förbättra din spelarkaraktär, öka dina erfarenhetspoäng och bringa ordning i kaoset. Med ett originellt soundtrack som sträcker sig från klassisk musik till hårdrock och heavy metal kommer Grand Sun RYEZ att underhålla dig med mängder av spelnivåer och innehållsuppdateringar. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 26 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2015 Black Star Nursery. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:RPG"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Language.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Language.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_17.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_16.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_14.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_18.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
