<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00243_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>133964160</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Putte Deinen Ball auf dieser herausfordernden 18-Loch Minigolfbahn von "Mini Golf Mundo" ein. Spiele mit bis zu 3 Freunden über 4 verschiedene Bahnen. Neben super Grafiken bietet dieses Spiel viele anspruchsvolle Löcher, die viel Spaß machen. Mini Golf Mundo wurde mit einer modernen Physik-Engine entwickelt, die ein realistisches Spiel liefert; von Spezialisten verfeinert, ist dieses Spiel so reibungslos wie irgend möglich. Egal ob Regen oder Sonnenschein, bei uns ist alles grün! <BR> <BR>Jede unserer vier Bahnen bietet eine Reihe schwieriger werdende Herausforderungen. Dies gibt Dir die Möglichkeit, Deine Fähigkeiten immer weiter zu entwickeln!  Wir haben den Spielstand im Auge, Du brauchst nur zu golfen. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 128 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1-4 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>© 2013-2014 EnsenaSoft, S.A. de C.V.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Putt your ball around these challenging 18 hole mini golf courses in “Mini Golf Mundo”. Play along or with up to 3 friends across 4 different courses. In addition to great looking graphics, this game features many challenging yet fun holes. Mini Golf Mundo was built using an advanced physics engine which provides realistic game play and refined by the masters to be as smooth as possible. It doesn't matter if it is sunshine or rain outside, in here it is nothing but green!<BR><BR>Each of the four courses offer a set of increasingly complex challenges. This allows you grow your skill set as you go! You can play with multiple players across all 18 holes. We keep the score, you just do the golfing. <BR><BR>Package size: 128 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1-4 Players<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>© 2013-2014 EnsenaSoft, S.A. de C.V.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Golpea la bola a lo largo de estos 18 desafiantes campos de minigolf en “Mini Golf Mundo”. Juega solo o con hasta 3 amigos en 4 campos diferentes. Además de los fantásticos gráficos, este juego incluye muchos hoyos difíciles a la vez que divertidos. Mini Golf Mundo utiliza un avanzado motor físico que proporciona una juego realista y perfeccionado por los especialistas para lograr la mayor apariencia posible. No importa que llueva o haga sol, ¡aquí solo hay verde!<BR><BR>Cada uno de los cuatro campos ofrece un conjunto de retos cada vez más complejos. ¡Esto te permite incrementar tus habilidades conforme avanzas! Además de los fantásticos campos de golf, puede jugar los 18 hoyos con varios jugadores. Nosotros contamos los puntos mientras que tú juegas al golf. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 128 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1-4 jugadores<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>© 2013-2014 EnsenaSoft, S.A. de C.V.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Rentrez vos putts à travers des terrains de mini-golf à 18 trous dans “Mini Golf Mundo”. Jouez seul ou avec jusque 3 amis sur 4 terrains de golf différents. En plus d'être doté de superbes graphismes, ce jeu comprend plein de putt difficiles, mais divertissants, à rentrer. Mini Golf Mundo a été conçu en utilisant un moteur de physiques de pointe, ce qui fournit au jeu une jouabilité réaliste et affinée pour qu'il soit le plus fluide possible. <BR>Peu importe si il fait beau ou mauvais dehors, ici c'est toujours vert ! <BR> <BR>Chacun des quatre terrains offre un ensemble de défis de plus en plus complexes. Cela vous permet de développer votre ensemble de compétences au fur et à mesure que vous jouez ! Nous gardons le score, vous faites juste du golf. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 128 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1-4 joueurs<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>© 2013-2014 EnsenaSoft, S.A. de C.V.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Tira la palla in buca in questi impegnativi minicampi da golf da 18 buche in “Mini Golf Mundo”. Gioca da solo o insieme a un massimo di tre amici all'interno di quattro diversi campi. Oltre alla fantastica grafica, in questo gioco ci sono tante buche impegnative ma allo stesso tempo divertenti. Mini Golf Mundo è stato sviluppato utilizzando un motore fisico avanzato che fornisce una giocabilità realistica ed è stato perfezionato dai maestri per essere il più fluido possibile. Non importa se fuori piove o c'è il sole: qui dentro non c'è nulla se non il verde!<BR><BR>Ognuno dei quattro campi offre una serie di sfide di complessità crescente; questo ti permette di accrescere il tuo insieme di abilità man mano che avanzi.  Noi teniamo il punteggio, voi pensate a giocare a golf! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 128 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1-4 giocatori<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>© 2013-2014 EnsenaSoft, S.A. de C.V.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>「ミニゴルフムンド」の挑戦的な18のミニゴルフコースを回って、ボールをパットしましょう。<BR><BR>3人までの友人と協力して、あるいは一緒に、4つの異なるコースをプレイしましょう。素晴らしいグラフィックに加えて、このゲームは多くの挑戦的で、楽しいホールを特色としています。<BR><BR>ミニゴルフムンドは、現実的なゲームプレイをもたらす高度な物理エンジンを使用して作成され、また、マスターズによって、できる限りスムーズになるよう、改良が加えられています。<BR><BR>外で太陽が照っていていようが、雨が降っていいようが、何の問題もありません、こちらはただのグリーンにほかなりません！<BR><BR>各4つのコースは、ウッドランドフォールズ、ハイランドヒルズ、スプリングウオーターバレー、メドウランドプレインズで、各コースは一連のますます複雑な課題を提供しています。これをやることで、あなたの知識と技能は成長します！素晴らしいコースに加えて、全18ホールに渡って、複数のプレイヤーとプレイすることができます。家族や友人たちと少しの時間で一緒にゲームを楽しむのは、素晴らしい方法です。スコアをつけて、とにかくゴルフをやるしかありません。<BR><BR>「ミニゴルフムンド」を購入していただきありがとうございます！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 128 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1～4人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>© 2013-2014 EnsenaSoft, S.A. de C.V.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Sla uw bal rond deze uitdagende mini-golfbanen met 18 holes in "Mini Golf Mundo". Speel mee of speel met maximaal 3 vrienden op 4 verschillende banen. Naast de fantastische grafieken, is dit spel voorzien van vele uitdagende maar leuke holes. Mini Golf Mundo werd gebouwd met behulp van een gevorderde fysica-motor die een realistisch spel biedt en verfijnd is door de meesters om het zo makkelijk mogelijk te maken. Het maakt niet uit of buiten de zon schijnt of het regent, hier is het niets anders dan groen! <BR> <BR>Elk van de vier banen bieden elk een set van steeds complexere uitdagingen. Hierdoor kunt u uw vaardigheden verhogen vanaf de start!  Wij houden de score bij, u hoeft enkel te golfen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 128 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1-4 spelers<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>© 2013-2014 EnsenaSoft, S.A. de C.V.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Sports"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
