<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00106_00">

  <appVersion>2.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>9656992</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Efter en irriterende dag i skolen, du bare vil have lidt fred og ro. Men alt i hjemmet er så støjende! Mr. Peabody er overmenneskeligt græsslåning hans græsplæne, far er kanal surfing og mor er bjæffe på telefonen. Din irriterende lillebror, vil ikke gå i seng, og selv dine kæledyr killinger kører du sindssyg! Udforsk, interagere med miljøet og løse gåder.<BR><BR>- Classic eventyrspil sjov på din håndholdte enhed.<BR>- Udforsk en munter og humoristisk miljø.<BR>- Brug din forstand og de ​​emner, du finde på at løse gåder.<BR>- Tre killinger følger med hvert køb! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 9431 KB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Nach einem ärgerlichen Tag in der Schule, Sie wollen einfach nur etwas Ruhe und Frieden. Aber alles zu Hause ist so laut! Mr. Peabody ist zwanghaft seinen Rasen mäht, ist Dad Zappen und Mama auf dem Telefon Kläffen. Ihre lästigen kleinen Bruder nicht ins Bett zu gehen, und auch Ihr Haustier Kätzchen sind Sie verrückt! Entdecken Sie interagieren mit der Umgebung und Rätsel lösen.<BR><BR>- Classic Adventure Spaß auf Ihrem Handheld-Gerät.<BR>- Erkunden Sie eine heitere und humorvolle Umwelt.<BR>- Benutze deinen Verstand und die Artikel, die Sie finden, um Rätsel zu lösen.<BR>- Drei Kätzchen bei jedem Einkauf im Lieferumfang enthalten! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 9431 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[After an annoying day at school, you just want some peace and quiet. But everything at home is so noisy! Mr. Peabody is obsessively mowing his lawn, Dad is channel surfing and Mom is yapping on the phone. Your pesky kid brother won't go to bed, and even your pet kittens are driving you crazy! Explore, interact with your environment and solve puzzles.<BR><BR>- Classic adventure game fun on your hand-held device.<BR>- Explore a lighthearted and humorous environment.<BR>- Use your wits and the items you find to solve puzzles.<BR>- Three kittens included with every purchase! <BR><BR>Package size: 9431 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Después de un día irritante en la escuela, lo que desea es un poco de paz y tranquilidad. Pero todo en la casa es tan ruidoso! Sr. Peabody es obsesivamente segar el césped, papá está haciendo zapping y mamá está ladrando en el teléfono. Su hermano menor molestos no irá a la cama, e incluso a sus gatitos mascotas están volviendo loco! Explorar, interactuar con su entorno y resolver puzzles.<BR><BR>- Aventura clásica diversión juego en tu dispositivo portátil.<BR>- Explora un ambiente alegre y chistoso.<BR>- Utiliza tu ingenio y los elementos que encuentres para resolver puzzles.<BR>- Tres gatitos incluye con cada compra! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 9431 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Jälkeen harmittaa päivä koulussa, haluat vain rauhaa ja hiljaisuutta. Mutta kaikki kotona on niin meluisa! Mr. Peabody on pakkomielteisesti niitto hänen nurmikkoa, isä on kanava surffausta ja äiti on yapping puhelimessa. Your ärsyttävä pikkuveli ei mennä nukkumaan, ja jopa lemmikkisi pennut ajo olet hullu! Tutki, vuorovaikutuksessa ympäristön kanssa ja ratkaista arvoituksia.<BR><BR>- Classic seikkailupeli hauskaa teidän kädessä pidettävä laite.<BR>- Tutki hilpeä ja humoristinen ympäristössä.<BR>- Käytä järkeä ja kohteet löydät ratkaista arvoituksia.<BR>- Kolme pentua mukana jokaisessa ostaa! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 9431 Kt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Après une journée ennuyeuse à l'école, vous voulez juste un peu de paix et de tranquillité. Mais tout à la maison est si bruyant! M. Peabody est obsessionnelle tonte sa pelouse, papa surf canal et maman est jacasser sur le téléphone. Votre petit frère embêtants ne sera pas aller au lit, et même vos animaux de compagnie sont les chatons vous rend fou! Explorez, interagir avec votre environnement et résoudre des énigmes.<BR><BR>- Amusant jeu d'aventure classique sur votre appareil portatif.<BR>- Explorez un environnement gai et plein d'humour.<BR>- Utilisez votre intelligence et les articles que vous trouvez pour résoudre des énigmes.<BR>- Trois chatons inclus avec chaque achat! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 9431 Ko - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Dopo una giornata noiosa a scuola, si vuole solo un po 'di pace e tranquillità. Ma tutto a casa è così rumoroso! Mr. Peabody è ossessivamente tagliare il prato, papà è zapping e la mamma è abbaiare al telefono. Il tuo fratellino fastidioso non andare a letto, e anche i vostri animali domestici sono gattini facendo impazzire! Esplora, interagire con l'ambiente e risolvere i puzzle.<BR><BR>- Classic divertente gioco di avventura sul tuo dispositivo portatile.<BR>- Esplora un ambiente allegro e divertente.<BR>- Usa il tuo ingegno e gli oggetti che si trovano per risolvere i puzzle.<BR>- Tre gattini incluso con ogni acquisto! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 9431 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[学校で迷惑な一日を過ごした後は、あなただけのいくつかの平和と静かにしたい。しかし、自宅ですべてがとても騒々しいです！ピーボディ氏は、彼の執拗な芝刈りされて、お父さんはチャンネルサーフィンされているとママが電話で話している。あなたの厄介な弟はベッドに行くことはありません、さらにはあなたのペットの子猫はあなたが狂った運転している！お使いの環境と相互作用し、パズルを解く、探検。<BR><BR>- あなたのハンドヘルドデバイス上でクラシックアドベンチャーゲームの楽しみ。<BR>- 陽気でユーモラスな環境を探検。<BR>- あなたのウィットとあなたがパズルを解決するために見つける項目を使用します。<BR>- 三匹の子猫は、すべての購入に含まれて！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 9431 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Etter en irriterende dag på skolen, du bare ønsker litt fred og ro. Men alt hjemme er så bråkete! Mr. Peabody er besatt klippe plenen hans, er pappa kanal surfing og mamma er yapping på telefonen. Din pesky lillebror vil ikke gå til sengs, og til og med kjæledyret kattunger kjører du gal! Utforsk, samhandle med omgivelsene og løse gåter.<BR><BR>- Klassisk eventyrspill moro på din håndholdte enhet.<BR>- Utforsk en munter og humoristisk miljø.<BR>- Bruk vettet og varene du finner å løse gåter.<BR>- Tre kattunger som følger med hvert kjøp! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 9431 KB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Na een vervelende dag op school, wil je gewoon wat rust en stilte. Maar alles in huis is zo luidruchtig! Mr Peabody obsessief zijn gazon maaien, papa is zappen en Mama yapping op de telefoon. Je vervelende broertje zal niet naar bed, en zelfs uw huisdier kittens aan het rijden je gek! Verkennen, interactie met je omgeving en puzzels op te lossen.<BR><BR>- Classic adventure game plezier op uw hand-held apparaat.<BR>- Ontdek een luchthartige en humoristische omgeving.<BR>- Gebruik je verstand en de items die je vindt om puzzels op te lossen.<BR>- Drie kittens inbegrepen bij elke aankoop! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 9431 KB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Po irytujące dnia w szkole, po prostu chcesz trochę ciszy i spokoju. Ale wszystko w domu jest tak głośno! Pan Peabody jest obsesyjnie koszenia jego trawnik, tato jest kanał surfing i Mama yapping na telefon. Twój cholerny dzieciak brat nie pójdzie do łóżka, a nawet swoje kocięta domowe jazdy cię do szaleństwa! Eksploruj, interakcji z otoczeniem i rozwiązywać zagadki. <BR><BR>- Klasyczna gra przygodowa na urządzeniu ręcznym. <BR>- Poznaj się komfortowy i humorystyczny środowiska. <BR>- Użyj sprytu i elementy można znaleźć do rozwiązania zagadki. <BR>- Trzy kocięta uwzględnione przy każdym zakupie! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 9431 KB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Efter en irriterande dag i skolan, du bara vill ha lite lugn och ro. Men allt hemma är så högljudda! Mr Peabody är tvångsmässigt klipper sin gräsmatta, är pappa kanalväxling och mamma är yapping på telefonen. Din odrägliga lillebror kommer inte att gå till sängs, och även dina husdjur kattungar kör du galen! Upptäck, interagera med din omgivning och lösa pussel.<BR><BR>- Klassiskt äventyrsspel kul på din handhållna enhet.<BR>- Utforska en lättsam och humoristisk miljö.<BR>- Använd din intelligens och de objekt som du hittar för att lösa pussel.<BR>- Tre kattungar som följer med varje köp! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 9431 KB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright 2013 Nostatic Software<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Adventure"/><genre value="Games:Family"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
