<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00177_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>41313280</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Overview: <BR>Puzzle game based on Mitsuteru Yokoyama's masterpiece "Records of the Three Kingdoms". Battle it out against the enemy generals with Zhuge Liang and the " Mitsuteru Yokoyama’s Records of the Three Kingdoms Mahjong Puzzle "!  The " Mitsuteru Yokoyama’s Records of the Three Kingdoms Mahjong Puzzle " is a classic puzzle game based on Mahjong.<BR><BR>Features:  <BR>-A total of six generals, each with their own stages. Three difficulty levels per stage. <BR>-Authentic gong sounds that echo across the battlefield. <BR>-Loaded with cut-ins based on the original story.<BR>※（C）SUNSOFT <BR><BR>Package size: 40 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>ⒸHikari Production<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Vue d'ensemble:<BR>Jeu de puzzle basé sur le chef d'œuvre de Mitsuteru Yokoyama " dossiers des Trois Royaumes" . Battez-vous contre les généraux ennemis avec Zhuge Liang et les " Dossiers de Mitsuteru Yokoyama du Puzzle Trois Royaumes " Mahjong ! Les « Dossiers de Mitsuteru Yokoyama du Puzzle Trois Royaumes Mahjong" est un jeu classique de puzzle basé sur Mahjong. <BR><BR>Caractéristiques:<BR>- Un total de six généraux , chacun avec leurs propres étapes . Trois niveaux de difficulté par étape.<BR>Sons authentiques de gong qui font écho à travers le champ de bataille.<BR>- Chargé de coupe -ins sur la base de l'histoire originale.<BR>※（C）SUNSOFT <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 40 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>ⒸHikari Production<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[■概要 <BR>横山光輝の名作『三国志』のパズルゲーム！ <BR>諸葛孔明と「上海パズル」で敵将と戦おう！ <BR>「上海パズル」は、麻雀牌をベースにした定番パズルゲーム。 <BR>スマートフォンならではのタッチ操作、コミックスをイメージしたカットイン、銅鑼の「ジャーン！ジャーン！ジャーン！」音など横山光輝「三国志」の世界観をお楽しみいただけます。 <BR>「曹操」、「孫権」、「周瑜」、「司馬懿」など、三国志を代表する武将たちと上海パズルでバトル！<BR>同じ絵柄の牌を探して消して、クリアを目指そう！ <BR>牌の消す順番を間違えると、手詰まりになってしまうから要注意！ <BR>知略を尽くして全ての武将を倒すのじゃ！<BR> <BR>■特徴 <BR>・全6武将分のステージ <BR>・1ステージにつき3つの難易度  <BR>・「ジャーン！ジャーン！ジャーン！」戦場に響く銅鑼の音 <BR>・原作をベースにしたカットイン演出 <BR>※『上海 Puzzle Game Shanghai』及び『SUNSOFT』は、サン電子株式会社の登録商標です。 <BR>※『上海 Puzzle Game Shanghai』に関する日本国内における全ての権利は、サン電子株式会社が保有しております。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 40 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>ⒸHikari Production<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
