<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00204_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>110243440</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>En gammel skole type skydespil, du finde dig selv fast nede i dalen i en cyklus af at skyde mobs, indsamling grus, og jagter en højere score, der kan kun bringes til ophør ved at blive trukket ned af dem onde mobs. Vælg mellem to temaer at spille. Niveauer er proceduremæssigt genereret. Hvordan vil du klare nede i dalen? <BR><BR>1.01 opdatering <BR>- Tilføjet en riffel <BR>- Tilføjet nye fjende, Skull Bandit: De kommer efter dig, og intet kommer i vejen, bortset fra dine kugler <BR>- Andre mindre gameplay og programopdateringer <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 106 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Ein alter Schultyp Shooter, findet man sich stecken Down in the Valley in einem Zyklus von Mobs schießen, Sammeln Splitt, und jagt eine höhere Punktzahl, die nur von unten durch die bösen Mobs gebracht beendet werden kann. Wählen Sie aus zwei Themen zu spielen. Ebenen sind prozedural generiert. Wie werden Sie sich ergehen im Tal? <BR><BR>1.01 Update <BR>- Hat ein Gewehr <BR>- Neue Gegner, der Schädel Bandit: sie kommen für Sie und nichts in die Quere kommt, außer Ihre Kugeln <BR>- Andere kleinere Gameplay und Anwendungs-Updates <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 106 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>An old school type of shooter, you find yourself stuck Down in the Valley in a cycle of shooting mobs, collecting grit, and chasing a higher score that can only be ended by being brought down by those evil mobs. Choose from two themes to play. Levels are procedurally generated. How will you fare Down in the Valley?<BR><BR>1.01 update<BR>- added a rifle<BR>- added new enemy, the Skull Bandit: they're coming for you and nothing gets in their way except your bullets<BR>- other minor gameplay and application updates <BR><BR>Package size: 106 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>An old school type of shooter, you find yourself stuck Down in the Valley in a cycle of shooting mobs, collecting grit, and chasing a higher score that can only be ended by being brought down by those evil mobs. Choose from two themes to play. Levels are procedurally generated. How will you fare Down in the Valley?<BR><BR>1.01 update<BR>- added a rifle<BR>- added new enemy, the Skull Bandit: they're coming for you and nothing gets in their way except your bullets<BR>- other minor gameplay and application updates <BR><BR>Package size: 106 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Un viejo tipo de escuela del tirador, te encuentras atrapado Abajo en el valle en un ciclo de disparar turbas, la recolección de grano, y persiguiendo una puntuación más alta que sólo puede ser terminado por ser derribado por los mal turbas. Elija a partir de dos temas para jugar. Los niveles se generan de procedimiento. ¿Cómo se tarifa Abajo en el valle? <BR><BR>1.01 actualización <BR>- Añadido un rifle <BR>- Añadido nuevo enemigo, el cráneo Bandit: Vienen a por ti y nada se interpone en su camino, excepto sus balas <BR>- Otras actualizaciones de juego y de aplicaciones de menor importancia <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 106 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Old school tyyppi ampuja, löydät itsesi kiinni Alhaalla laaksossa sykli ammunta väkijoukot, kerätä soraa, ja jahtaa korkeammat pisteet, joka voidaan lopettaa vain olemalla kaatoi paha väkijoukot. Valittavana kaksi teemaa pelata. Tasot ovat menettelyllisesti syntyy. Miten pärjäävät Down in the Valley? <BR><BR>1.01 päivitys <BR>- Lisäsi kivääri <BR>- Lisätään uusi vihollinen, Skull Bandit: he tulevat sinulle eikä mitään saa omalla tavallaan paitsi luoteja <BR>- Muita pieniä pelattavuus ja sovelluspäivitykset <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 106 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Un vieux type de jeu de tir à l'école, vous vous retrouvez coincé vers le bas dans la vallée dans un cycle de prise de vue des foules, la collecte de grain, et la poursuite d'un score plus élevé que ne peut être finit par être abattu par les mal foules. Choisissez parmi deux thèmes à jouer. Les niveaux sont générés procédure. Comment allez-vous tirera vers le bas dans la vallée? <BR><BR>1.01 mise à jour <BR>- Ajout d'un fusil <BR>- Nouvel ennemi ajoutée, le crâne Bandit: ils viennent pour vous et rien ne passe à leur manière, sauf vos balles <BR>- D'autres mises à jour de jeu et d'application mineures <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 106 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Un vieux type de jeu de tir à l'école, vous vous retrouvez coincé vers le bas dans la vallée dans un cycle de prise de vue des foules, la collecte de grain, et la poursuite d'un score plus élevé que ne peut être finit par être abattu par les mal foules. Choisissez parmi deux thèmes à jouer. Les niveaux sont générés procédure. Comment allez-vous tirera vers le bas dans la vallée? <BR><BR>1.01 mise à jour <BR>- Ajout d'un fusil <BR>- Nouvel ennemi ajoutée, le crâne Bandit: ils viennent pour vous et rien ne passe à leur manière, sauf vos balles <BR>- D'autres mises à jour de jeu et d'application mineures <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 106 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Una vecchia scuola di tipo sparatutto, ti ritrovi bloccato Down in the Valley in un ciclo di tiro folle, raccogliendo grinta, e inseguendo un punteggio più alto che può essere concluso solo per essere abbattuto da chi il male mobs. Scegli tra due temi da svolgere. I livelli sono generate proceduralmente. Come si passeranno Down in the Valley? <BR><BR>1.01 aggiornamento <BR>- Ha aggiunto un fucile <BR>- Aggiunto un nuovo nemico, il Teschio Bandit: stanno arrivando per te e nulla viene a loro modo, tranne i proiettili <BR>- Altri aggiornamenti di gioco e delle applicazioni minori <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 106 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>シューターの古い学校のタイプは、あなた自身が、モブを撮影グリットを収集し、そしてのみ悪暴徒によって倒されることによって終了することができ、より高いスコアを追いかけての周期で谷にダウン立ち往生見つける。プレイする2つのテーマからお選びいただけます。レベルは手続き的に生成されます。どのようにバレーにダウン運賃のだろうか？ <BR><BR>1.01アップデート <BR>- ライフルを追加しました <BR>- 追加された新たな敵、スカル強盗：彼らはあなたのために来ていると、何もあなたの弾丸を除く彼らの邪魔になるん <BR>- 他のマイナーなゲームプレイやアプリケーションのアップデート <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 106 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>En gammel skole type skytespill, finner du deg selv sittende fast Down in the Valley i en syklus av skyting mobs, samle grus, og jage en høyere poengsum som bare kan avsluttes ved å bli brakt ned av de onde mobs. Velg mellom to temaer å spille. Nivåene er prosedyregenerert. Hvordan vil du fare Down in the Valley? <BR><BR>1.01 oppdatering <BR>- Lagt en rifle <BR>- Lagt til nye fiende, Skull Bandit: de kommer for deg og ingenting kommer i deres vei unntatt kulene dine <BR>- Andre mindre spilling og programoppdateringer <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 106 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Een oude school type shooter, vind je jezelf vast in het dal in een cyclus van schieten mobs, het verzamelen van gruis, en achter een hogere score die alleen kan worden beëindigd door te worden neergehaald door deze boze mobs. U kunt kiezen uit twee thema's te spelen. Levels zijn procedureel gegenereerd. Hoe gaat u omlaag vergaan in de vallei? <BR><BR>1.01-update <BR>- Voegde een geweer <BR>- Toegevoegd nieuwe vijand, de Skull Bandit: ze komen voor jou en niets krijgt in de weg, behalve je kogels <BR>- Andere kleine gameplay en applicatie-updates <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 106 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Stary typ szkoły shooter, utkniesz w dół doliny w cyklu strzelania mobów, zbieranie żwiru i goni wyższy wynik, który może być zakończony tylko poprzez wniesione przez tych złych potworów. Wybierz jedną z dwóch tematów do gry. Poziomy są generowane proceduralnie. Jak będzie wiodło w dół w dolinie? <BR><BR>1.01 aktualizacja <BR>- Dodaje karabin <BR>- Dodano nowy wróg, Czaszka Bandit: oni przychodzą do ciebie i nic nie staje na ich drodze poza swoimi kulami <BR>- Inne drobne rozgrywki i aktualizacje aplikacji <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 106 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>En gammal skola typ av skytten, du befinner dig fastnat Nere i dalen i en cykel av skytte mobs, samla grus, och jaga en högre poäng som bara kan avslutas genom att de förs ned av de onda mobs. Välj mellan två teman för att spela. Nivåerna är förfarandemässigt genereras. Hur kommer du att klara Ner i dalen? <BR><BR>1,01 uppdatering <BR>- Lagt ett gevär <BR>- Lagt ny fiende, den Skull Bandit: de kommer på dig och ingenting kommer i deras väg, utom dina kulor <BR>- Andra mindre gameplay och programuppdateringar <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 106 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Shooter"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
