<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00233_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>108881136</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Ferien er lige rundt om hjørnet, og du kunne bruge en festlig touch til sætte alle i ferien ånd.<BR><BR>Lysere din skiferie Yule Log app!<BR><BR>Bare starte Yule Log app og se som din skærm bliver til en pejs, der ser så ægte du bare kan være bange for at røre ved det!<BR><BR>Branden brøler med indånder hensyntagen gengivelse af Vi ønsker en glædelig jul spiller i baggrunden, at par perfekt med lyden af en brølende ild. (Hvis du ønsker, kan du slukke for musikken).<BR><BR>Du kan endda tilpasse din ild med masser af muligheder (fra branden størrelse og farve til mængden af belysning i lokalet, kan du tilpasse det hele)!<BR><BR>Glædelig jul og Happy Holidays fra dine venner på Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 104 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Die Ferien sind gleich um die Ecke und Sie nutzen könnten eine festliche Note an alle in den Urlaub Geist setzen.<BR><BR>Erhellen Sie Ihren Urlaub mit der Yule Log App!<BR><BR>Starten Sie einfach die Julblock App und zusehen, wie Ihr Bildschirm verwandelt sich in einen Kamin, der so real du könn Angst, es zu berühren aussieht!<BR><BR>Die Brand brüllt mit einem atmen unter Wiedergabe von We Wish You A Merry Christmas spielt im Hintergrund, dass passt perfekt mit dem Sound von einem prasselnden Feuer. (Wenn Sie möchten, können Sie deaktivieren die Musik).<BR><BR>Sie können sogar Ihr Feuer mit vielen Optionen (ab Größe des Feuers und Farbe, um die Menge der Beleuchtung im Raum können Sie alles anpassen)!<BR><BR>Frohe Weihnachten und Happy Holidays von Ihren Freunden an Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 104 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>The Holidays are just around the corner and you could use a festive touch to put everybody into the Holiday Spirit.<BR><BR>Brighten your holidays with the Yule Log app!<BR><BR>Just start the Yule Log app and watch as your screen turns into a fireplace that looks so real you just might be afraid to touch it!<BR><BR>The fire roars with a breathe taking rendition of We Wish You A Merry Christmas playing in the background that pairs perfectly with the sound of a roaring fire. (If you want you can turn off the music).<BR><BR>You can even customize your fire with lots of options (from the fire's size and color to the amount of lighting in the room you can customize it all)!<BR><BR>Merry Christmas and Happy Holidays from your friends at Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Package size: 104 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>The Holidays are just around the corner and you could use a festive touch to put everybody into the Holiday Spirit.<BR><BR>Brighten your holidays with the Yule Log app!<BR><BR>Just start the Yule Log app and watch as your screen turns into a fireplace that looks so real you just might be afraid to touch it!<BR><BR>The fire roars with a breathe taking rendition of We Wish You A Merry Christmas playing in the background that pairs perfectly with the sound of a roaring fire. (If you want you can turn off the music).<BR><BR>You can even customize your fire with lots of options (from the fire's size and color to the amount of lighting in the room you can customize it all)!<BR><BR>Merry Christmas and Happy Holidays from your friends at Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Package size: 104 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>The Holidays are just around the corner and you could use a festive touch to put everybody into the Holiday Spirit.<BR><BR>Brighten your holidays with the Yule Log app!<BR><BR>Just start the Yule Log app and watch as your screen turns into a fireplace that looks so real you just might be afraid to touch it!<BR><BR>The fire roars with a breathe taking rendition of We Wish You A Merry Christmas playing in the background that pairs perfectly with the sound of a roaring fire. (If you want you can turn off the music).<BR><BR>You can even customize your fire with lots of options (from the fire's size and color to the amount of lighting in the room you can customize it all)!<BR><BR>Merry Christmas and Happy Holidays from your friends at Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Package size: 104 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>The Holidays are just around the corner and you could use a festive touch to put everybody into the Holiday Spirit.<BR><BR>Brighten your holidays with the Yule Log app!<BR><BR>Just start the Yule Log app and watch as your screen turns into a fireplace that looks so real you just might be afraid to touch it!<BR><BR>The fire roars with a breathe taking rendition of We Wish You A Merry Christmas playing in the background that pairs perfectly with the sound of a roaring fire. (If you want you can turn off the music).<BR><BR>You can even customize your fire with lots of options (from the fire's size and color to the amount of lighting in the room you can customize it all)!<BR><BR>Merry Christmas and Happy Holidays from your friends at Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Package size: 104 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Las fiestas están a la vuelta de la esquina y usted podría usar un toque festivo a poner a todo el mundo en el espíritu navideño.<BR><BR>Aclare sus vacaciones con la aplicación del registro de Yule!<BR><BR>Simplemente comienza la aplicación del registro de Yule y ver como da vuelta a su pantalla en una chimenea que se ve tan real que sólo podría tener miedo de tocarlo!<BR><BR>Los rugidos de fuego con una alucinante interpretación de Le deseamos una Feliz Navidad jugando en el fondo que los pares a la perfección con el sonido de una fogata. (Si lo desea, puede desactivar la música).<BR><BR>Usted puede incluso personalizar el fuego con un montón de opciones (de tamaño de fuego y color a la cantidad de iluminación de la habitación se puede personalizar todos)! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 104 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Lomat ovat aivan nurkan takana, ja voit käyttää juhla touch laittaa kaikki otetaan Holiday Spirit.<BR><BR>Piristä lomapäiväsi Jouluhalko app!<BR><BR>Ala vain Jouluhalko app ja katsella näytön muuttuu takka, joka näyttää niin todellinen juuri ehkä uskalla koskettaa sitä!<BR><BR>Palo ulvoo kanssa henkeäsalpaavia luovuttamista Hyvän joulun toivotus soimaan taustalle, että paria täydellisesti ääni möly palo. (Jos haluat, voit sammuttaa musiikki).<BR><BR>Voit jopa muokata palo, jossa on paljon vaihtoehtoja (tulesta koon ja värin määrä valaistus huoneessa voit muokata sitä kaikki)!<BR><BR>Hyvää joulua ja onnellista joulunaikaa ystäväsi Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 104 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Les vacances sont juste autour du coin et vous pouvez utiliser une touche festive à mettre tout le monde dans l'esprit des Fêtes.<BR><BR>Illuminez vos vacances avec l'application bûche de Noël!<BR><BR>Il suffit de lancer l'application bûche de Noël et regardez votre écran se transforme en un foyer qui semble si réel que vous pourriez avoir peur d'y toucher!<BR><BR>Les rugissements de feu avec un rendu respirer prendre de Nous vous souhaitons un Joyeux Noël en musique de fond qui se marie parfaitement avec le son d'un feu de cheminée. (Si vous voulez, vous pouvez éteindre la musique).<BR><BR>Vous pouvez même personnaliser votre feu avec de nombreuses options (de la taille et la couleur de l'incendie à la quantité d'éclairage dans la salle, vous pouvez personnaliser tout)! <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 104 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Les vacances sont juste autour du coin et vous pouvez utiliser une touche festive à mettre tout le monde dans l'esprit des Fêtes.<BR><BR>Illuminez vos vacances avec l'application bûche de Noël!<BR><BR>Il suffit de lancer l'application bûche de Noël et regardez votre écran se transforme en un foyer qui semble si réel que vous pourriez avoir peur d'y toucher!<BR><BR>Les rugissements de feu avec un rendu respirer prendre de Nous vous souhaitons un Joyeux Noël en musique de fond qui se marie parfaitement avec le son d'un feu de cheminée. (Si vous voulez, vous pouvez éteindre la musique).<BR><BR>Vous pouvez même personnaliser votre feu avec de nombreuses options (de la taille et la couleur de l'incendie à la quantité d'éclairage dans la salle, vous pouvez personnaliser tout)! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 104 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Le vacanze sono dietro l'angolo e si potrebbe utilizzare un tocco di festa per mettere tutti nello spirito di festa.<BR><BR>Illumina le tue vacanze con l'app Yule Log!<BR><BR>Basta avviare l'applicazione Yule Log e vedere come lo schermo si trasforma in un camino che sembra così reale si potrebbe anche aver paura di toccarlo!<BR><BR>Ruggisce il fuoco con un respiro prendendo resa di We Wish You A Merry Christmas in sottofondo che si abbina perfettamente con il suono di un fuoco scoppiettante. (Se volete potete spegnere la musica).<BR><BR>È anche possibile personalizzare il fuoco con un sacco di opzioni (dalla dimensione del fuoco e colore alla quantità di luce nella stanza è possibile personalizzare tutto)!<BR><BR>Buon Natale e Buone Feste dai tuoi amici a Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 104 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>休日は角を曲がったところであり、あなたはホリデースピリットに皆を置くためにお祝いのタッチを使用することができます。<BR><BR>ユール·ログ·アプリであなたの休日を明るく！<BR><BR>ただユールログアプリを起動し、画面では、ちょうどそれに触れることを恐れてかもしれないので、本当の見える暖炉に変身として見てください！<BR><BR>私たちの息を取って演奏した火災のうなり声は、暖炉の音とそのペア完全にバックグラウンドで遊んであなたにメリークリスマスをお祈りしております。 （あなたがしたい場合は、音楽をオフにすることができます）。<BR><BR>あなたも、（あなたがそれをすべてカスタマイズすることができます部屋の照明の量に火の大きさや色から）多くのオプションを使用して火をカスタマイズすることができます！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 104 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Ferien er rett rundt hjørnet, og du kan bruke en festlig preg å sette alle i julestemning.<BR><BR>Brighten ferien med Yule Log app!<BR><BR>Bare start Yule Log app og se skjermen din blir til en peis som ser så ekte at du bare kan være redd for å ta på den!<BR><BR>Brann brøler med puste tar rendition of Vi ønsker deg en riktig god jul spilles i bakgrunnen at parene perfekt med lyden av en knitrende peis. (Hvis du vil kan du slå av musikken).<BR><BR>Du kan selv tilpasse din brann med mange alternativer (fra brannens størrelse og farge til mengden av lys i rom du kan tilpasse det hele tatt)!<BR><BR>God Jul og Godt nytt fra dine venner på Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 104 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>De feestdagen zijn net om de hoek en je kon gebruik maken van een feestelijk tintje aan iedereen in de Geest van de Vakantie zetten.<BR><BR>Fleur uw vakantie met het Logboek Yule app!<BR><BR>Gewoon beginnen met de Yule Log app en zie hoe je scherm verandert in een open haard, dat ziet er zo echt je gewoon bang om het aan te raken zou kunnen zijn!<BR><BR>De brand brult met een ademen vertolking van We Wish You A Merry Christmas op de achtergrond speelt dat paren perfect met het geluid van een knapperend haardvuur. (Als je wilt, kun je de muziek draaien).<BR><BR>U kunt zelfs uw brand te passen met veel opties (vanaf maat van het vuur en de kleur aan het bedrag van de verlichting in de kamer, je kunt het allemaal aanpassen)!<BR><BR>Vrolijk Kerstfeest en Gelukkig Vakantie van uw vrienden bij Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 104 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Wakacje to tuż za rogiem i można wykorzystać świąteczny akcent umieścić wszystkich w świąteczny nastrój.<BR><BR>Rozjaśnić się wakacje z app Yule Log!<BR><BR>Wystarczy uruchomić aplikację Yule Zaloguj i patrzeć, jak twój ekran zamienia się w kominek, który wygląda tak realne, po prostu może bać się go dotknąć!<BR><BR>Ogień ryczy z oddychać biorąc wydaniu Życzymy Wesołych Świąt gry w tle, które parami doskonale z dźwiękiem kominkiem. (Jeśli chcesz, możesz wyłączyć muzykę).<BR><BR>Możesz nawet dostosować swoje ognia z dużą ilością opcji (od wielkości ognia i koloru do ilości światła w pomieszczeniu można wszystko dostosować)!<BR><BR>Wesołych Świąt i Szczęśliwego święta od znajomych na Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 104 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>De Semester är precis runt hörnet och du kan använda ett festligt handlag för att sätta alla i julstämning.<BR><BR>Förgyll din semester med Yule Log app!<BR><BR>Bara starta Yule Log-appen och titta på skärmen förvandlas till en eldstad som ser så verkliga att du bara kan vara rädd att röra den!<BR><BR>Brand vrålar med andas med återgivande av Vi önskar dig en god jul spelar i bakgrunden att par perfekt med ljudet av en sprakande eld. (Om du vill kan du stänga av musiken).<BR><BR>Du kan även anpassa din eld med massor av alternativ (från eldens storlek och färg till mängden ljus i rummet som du kan skräddarsy allt)!<BR><BR>God Jul och Glad helg från dina vänner på Skunk Software. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 104 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Skunk Software<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Entertainment"/><genre value="Apps:Lifestyle"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
