<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00006_00">
 <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>22424624</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[「ワードブロック」はひねりを加えて遊ぶクロスワードパズルゲームです。このゲームでは縦横３文字のブロックをひねったり、回転させたりして単語を作っていきます。より長い単語を作って高得点を獲得したり、単語を正しくつなげ合わせて得点を倍にすることもできます。デバイスを振って文字がランダムにミックスされたら、キューブ上で並べ替えることができます！<br><br>時間制限モードでは、設定時間内にできるだけ多くの単語を見つけていきます。爆弾やミサイルを使えばキューブ上に求めていた文字が現れるかもしれません。<br><br>リラックスモードでは、最高得点を獲得してレベル１０にチャレンジしましょう。あなたは「ワード」に「ブロック」されずにどこまで進めるか！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:22 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>Quirkat(tm) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Word Blocked is a word game with a twist, quite literally. The game revolves around a 3x3 block of letters that can be twisted and turned to align into words. Form longer words for higher scores and earn multipliers when you form a series of correct words. Shake your device at any time to jumble up the letters and rearrange them on the cube!<br>In Time Limit mode you must find as many words as possible within the time limit. Use bombs and missiles to change the letters on the cube for greater word options. <br>In Relaxed mode, try to make it all the way to Level 10 by achieving the highest score possible, and play as long as you can until you are Word Blocked!<br><br>Package size: 22 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>Quirkat(tm) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Word Blocked est un jeu de mots différent. Le jeu tourne autour d'un bloc de 3 x 3 lettres qui peuvent être tordus et être retournés pour aligner les mots.  Le but est de former des mots plus longs pour faire des scores plus élevés et de gagner des multiplicateurs lorsque vous formez une série de mots corrects. Secouez votre appareil à tout moment pour mélanger les lettres et les réorganiser sur le cube!<br>En mode de temps limité  vous devez trouver autant de mots que possible dans le délai imparti. Utilisez des bombes et des missiles pour changer les lettres sur le cube pour une plus grande option de mots.<br>En mode relax essayez d'atteindre le niveau 10 pour obtenir le plus haut score possible et jouer aussi longtemps jusqu'à ce que vous devenez Word Blocked! <br><br>Taille du paquet: 22 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>Quirkat(tm) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Word Blocked è un gioco di parole con un “twist”, letteralmente! Il gioco consiste in un blocco di 3 x 3 lettere che possono essere aggiustate e riallineate per comporre parole. Più lunghe sono le parole più alti i punteggi e guadagnare ulteriori punti è possibile componendo una serie successiva di parole. Scuoti il dispositivo in qualsiasi momento per rimescolare le lettere e riorganizzarle nel cubo! È possibile giocare in due modalità: con o senza tempo limite. <br><br>In modalità tempo limite l’obiettivo è trovare quante più parole possibile entro il tempo a disposizione. Bombe e missili possono essere usati per modificare le lettere sul cubo e ottenere ulteriori opzioni di parole. <br><br>In modalità relax, l’obiettivo è raggiungere il livello 10 con il massimo punteggio, giocando fino a diventare “Word Blocked”! <br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 22 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>Quirkat(tm) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Word Blocked es un juego de palabras con un giro, literalmente. El juego gira en torno a un bloque de 3 x 3 de letras que pueden ser girado dedo vuelta para alinearse en palabras. Forme palabras más largas para puntuaciones más altas y gane multiplicadores cuando usted forma una serie de palabras correctas. Agitar el dispositivo en cualquier momento para reorganizar las letras en el cubo!<br>En el modo con tiempo límite debe encontrar tantas palabras como sea posible dentro de ese tiempo límite. Utilice bombas y misiles para cambiar las letras en el cubo para mayores opciones de palabras. <br>En el modo relajado, trate de completar hasta el nivel 10 para lograr la mayor puntuación posible y jugar tanto tiempo como usted pueda hasta que estés Word Blocked!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 22 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<br><br>Quirkat(tm) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Word Blocked ist ein Wortspiel mit einem Twist, ganz wörtlich. Das Spiel dreht sich um ein 3 x 3-Buchstabenblock, die verdreht werden kann, in Worte auszurichten. Bilden Sie längere Wörter für eine höhere Spielstand und verdienen Sie Multiplikatoren wenn Sie eine Serie von richtigen Wörtern bilden. Schütteln Sie Ihr Gerät jederzeit um die Buchstaben durcheinander zuvermischen und dann auf dem Cube anordnen! <br><br>Im Frist Mode müssen Sie so viele Wörter wie möglich innerhalb einer bestimmten Zeit finden. Verwenden Sie Bomben und Raketen um die Buchstaben auf der Cube zu verändern für größere Word Möglichkeiten. <br><br>Im Relaxed Mode, holen Sie sich das höchste Punktzahl möglich, um Level 10 zu erreichen. Weiter spielen, bis Sie Word Blocked sind!<br><br>Paketgröße: 22 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<br><br>Quirkat(tm) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Word Blocked is a word game with a twist, quite literally. The game revolves around a 3x3 block of letters that can be twisted and turned to align into words. Form longer words for higher scores and earn multipliers when you form a series of correct words. Shake your device at any time to jumble up the letters and rearrange them on the cube!<br>In Time Limit mode you must find as many words as possible within the time limit. Use bombs and missiles to change the letters on the cube for greater word options. <br>In Relaxed mode, try to make it all the way to Level 10 by achieving the highest score possible, and play as long as you can until you are Word Blocked!<br><br>Package size: 22 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>Quirkat(tm) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Word Blocked est un jeu de mots différent. Le jeu tourne autour d'un bloc de 3 x 3 lettres qui peuvent être tordus et être retournés pour aligner les mots.  Le but est de former des mots plus longs pour faire des scores plus élevés et de gagner des multiplicateurs lorsque vous formez une série de mots corrects. Secouez votre appareil à tout moment pour mélanger les lettres et les réorganiser sur le cube!<br>En mode de temps limité  vous devez trouver autant de mots que possible dans le délai imparti. Utilisez des bombes et des missiles pour changer les lettres sur le cube pour une plus grande option de mots.<br>En mode relax essayez d'atteindre le niveau 10 pour obtenir le plus haut score possible et jouer aussi longtemps jusqu'à ce que vous devenez Word Blocked! <br><br>Taille du programme: 22 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>Quirkat(tm) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:BrainTraining"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
