<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00150_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>54048256</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Colors er et vanedannende puslespil baseret strategi spil, der kræver en blanding af dygtighed og held til at udrette. <BR><BR>For at være en succes, du har brug for at ændre farven på firkanterne indtil hele skærmen er en enkelt fast farve. Startende med firkant i øverste venstre hjørne, kan du ændre farven på blokkene for at matche, at af de omkringliggende pladser. Dette sker, indtil hele skærmen er en enkelt farve. <BR><BR>Deres mål er at rydde skærmen i så få træk som muligt. Så snart blive en succes i flere niveauer, bliver spillet mere komplekse, og langt flere pladser vises på skærmen, og vanskeligheden vil stige og blive mere udfordrende. <BR><BR>Hav det sjovt og held og lykke! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 52 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Spansk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Farben ist ein süchtig machendes Puzzle-basierte Strategie-Spiel, das eine Mischung aus Können und Glück, um zu erreichen, erfordert. <BR><BR>Um erfolgreich zu sein, müssen Sie die Farbe der Quadrate ändern, bis der gesamte Bildschirm ist eine einzige feste Farbe. Beginnend mit dem Quadrat in der linken oberen Ecke können Sie die Farbe der Blöcke, um die der umgebenden Quadrate entsprechen ändern. Dies geschieht, bis der gesamte Bildschirm ist eine einzige Farbe.<BR><BR>Ihr Ziel ist es, den Bildschirm in so wenigen Zügen wie möglich zu löschen. Sobald in mehreren Ebenen erfolgreich zu werden, wird das Spiel immer komplexer, und noch viel mehr Plätze auf dem Bildschirm erscheinen und die Schwierigkeit wird zunehmen und immer anspruchsvoller. <BR><BR>Viel Spaß und viel Glück! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 52 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Colors is an addictive puzzle based strategy game that requires a mixture of skill and luck in order to accomplish.<BR><BR>To be successful you need to change the colour of the squares until the entire screen is a single solid colour. Starting with the square in the upper left corner, you can change the colour of the blocks in order to match that of the surrounding squares. This is done until the entire screen is a single colour.<BR><BR>Your objective is to clear the screen in as few moves as possible. As soon as become successful in more levels, the game becomes more complex, and much more squares appear on your screen and the difficulty will increase and becoming more challenging.<BR><BR>Have fun &amp; Good luck! <BR><BR>Package size: 52 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Colors is an addictive puzzle based strategy game that requires a mixture of skill and luck in order to accomplish.<BR><BR>To be successful you need to change the colour of the squares until the entire screen is a single solid colour. Starting with the square in the upper left corner, you can change the colour of the blocks in order to match that of the surrounding squares. This is done until the entire screen is a single colour.<BR><BR>Your objective is to clear the screen in as few moves as possible. As soon as become successful in more levels, the game becomes more complex, and much more squares appear on your screen and the difficulty will increase and becoming more challenging.<BR><BR>Have fun &amp; Good luck! <BR><BR>Package size: 52 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Colors is an addictive puzzle based strategy game that requires a mixture of skill and luck in order to accomplish.<BR><BR>To be successful you need to change the colour of the squares until the entire screen is a single solid colour. Starting with the square in the upper left corner, you can change the colour of the blocks in order to match that of the surrounding squares. This is done until the entire screen is a single colour.<BR><BR>Your objective is to clear the screen in as few moves as possible. As soon as become successful in more levels, the game becomes more complex, and much more squares appear on your screen and the difficulty will increase and becoming more challenging.<BR><BR>Have fun &amp; Good luck! <BR><BR>Package size: 52 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Colors is an addictive puzzle based strategy game that requires a mixture of skill and luck in order to accomplish.<BR><BR>To be successful you need to change the colour of the squares until the entire screen is a single solid colour. Starting with the square in the upper left corner, you can change the colour of the blocks in order to match that of the surrounding squares. This is done until the entire screen is a single colour.<BR><BR>Your objective is to clear the screen in as few moves as possible. As soon as become successful in more levels, the game becomes more complex, and much more squares appear on your screen and the difficulty will increase and becoming more challenging.<BR><BR>Have fun &amp; Good luck! <BR><BR>Package size: 52 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Colors es un juego adictivo que requiere de una mezcla entre habilidad estratégica y suerte.<BR><BR>Para tener éxito es necesario cambiar el color de los cuadrados hasta que la pantalla entera sea de un solo color sólido. A partir de los botones de la esquina superior izquierda, se puede cambiar el color de los bloques con el fin de que coincida con la de los cuadrados de los alrededores. Esto se hace hasta que la pantalla entera es un solo color.<BR><BR>Su objetivo es limpiar la pantalla en el menor número de movimientos posibles limitados. A medida que avanzas de niveles, el juego se vuelve más complejo, y aparecen mucho más cuadrados en la pantalla y la dificultad irá aumentando y cada vez es más desafiante.<BR><BR>Diviértete y buena suerte! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 52 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Colors on pulmapelissä strategiapeli, joka vaatii sekoitus taitoa ja onnea Saavuttaakseen. <BR><BR>On onnistunut sinun täytyy vaihtaa väriä neliöitä, kunnes koko näyttö on yksi yksivärinen. Alkaen neliön vasemmassa yläkulmassa, voit vaihtaa väriä lohkojen jotta ne vastaavat, että ympäröivän neliöt. Tämä tehdään, kunnes koko näyttö on yksivärinen. <BR><BR>Sinun tavoitteena on selkeä näytön niin vähän liikkuu kuin mahdollista. Heti menestyvät enemmän tasoja, peli muuttuu monimutkaisemmaksi, ja paljon muuta neliöitä näkyä ruudulla ja vaikeus kasvaa ja yhä haastava. <BR><BR>Pidä hauskaa ja onnea! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 52 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti/Espanja<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Pixels Couleurs est un puzzle basé jeu de stratégie addictif qui nécessite un mélange de compétence et de chance pour accomplir. <BR><BR>Pour réussir, vous devez changer la couleur des carrés jusqu'à ce que la totalité de l'écran est d'une seule couleur solide. A partir de la place dans le coin supérieur gauche, vous pouvez changer la couleur des blocs afin de correspondre à celui des places environnantes. Cela se fait jusqu'à ce que la totalité de l'écran est d'une seule couleur. <BR><BR>Votre objectif est de vider l'écran en le moins de coups possible. Dès que réussir dans plusieurs niveaux, le jeu devient plus complexe, et beaucoup plus carrés apparaissent sur votre écran et la difficulté augmente et de plus en plus difficile. <BR><BR>Amusez-vous et bonne chance! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 52 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Colori Pixel è un gioco di strategia di puzzle basato coinvolgente che richiede un mix di abilità e fortuna, al fine di realizzare. <BR><BR>Per avere successo è necessario modificare il colore dei quadrati fino a quando l'intero schermo è un singolo colore solido. Partendo con la piazza nell'angolo in alto a sinistra, è possibile cambiare il colore dei blocchi in modo che corrisponda a quello delle piazze circostanti. Ciò avviene fino a quando l'intero schermo è un colore unico. <BR><BR>Il vostro obiettivo è quello di cancellare lo schermo nel minor numero di mosse possibili. Appena avere successo in più livelli, il gioco diventa più complesso, e molto più quadrati appaiono sullo schermo e la difficoltà aumenta e diventa più impegnativo. <BR><BR>Buon divertimento e buona fortuna! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 52 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[ピクセルカラーは、達成するために、スキルと運の混合物を必要とする中毒性のパズルの戦略ゲームです。 <BR><BR>成功するためには、画面全体が単一の固体の色になるまでの正方形の色を変更する必要があります。左上隅の正方形以降では、周囲の正方形のものと一致させるために、ブロックの色を変更することができる。画面全体が単一色になるまで、これが行われます。 <BR><BR>あなたの目的は、可能な限りいくつかの動きで画面をオフにしています。とすぐにそれ以上のレベルで成功になるように、ゲームはより複雑になり、多くの正方形は、画面に表示され、難易度が増加し、より困難になってきます。 <BR><BR>娯楽と幸運を持っている！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 52 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Farger er et vanedannende puslespill basert strategi spill som krever en blanding av dyktighet og flaks for å oppnå. <BR><BR>For å lykkes må du endre fargen på rutene til hele skjermen er en enkelt farge. Starter med torget i øvre venstre hjørne, kan du endre fargen på blokkene for å tilpasse det til de omkringliggende rutene. Dette gjøres før hele skjermen er en enkelt farge. <BR><BR>Målet ditt er å tømme skjermen på så få trekk som mulig. Så snart bli vellykket i flere nivåer, blir spillet mer komplisert, og mye flere ruter vises på skjermen din, og vanskelighetsgraden øker og blir mer utfordrende. <BR><BR>Ha det gøy og lykke til! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 52 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Spansk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Kleuren is een verslavende puzzel-based strategie spel dat een mix van vaardigheid en geluk nodig om volledig te bereiken. <BR><BR>Om succesvol te zijn moet je de kleur van de vierkantjes veranderen totdat het gehele scherm is een effen kleur. Te beginnen met het plein in de linker bovenhoek, kunt u de kleur van de blokken om overeenkomen met die van de omliggende pleinen veranderen. Dit wordt gedaan totdat het gehele scherm is een enkele kleur. <BR><BR>Uw doel is om het scherm te wissen in zo weinig mogelijk zetten. Zodra succesvol in meer niveaus te worden, wordt het spel steeds complexer, en nog veel meer vierkantjes op het scherm en de moeilijkheidsgraad zal toenemen en steeds meer uitdagend. <BR><BR>Veel plezier &amp; Good luck! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 52 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels/Spaans<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Pixel Colors är ett beroendeframkallande pusselbaserade strategispel som kräver en blandning av skicklighet och tur för att åstadkomma. <BR><BR>För att bli framgångsrik måste du ändra färgen på rutorna tills hela skärmen är en enda färg. Från och med torget i det övre vänstra hörnet kan du ändra färgen på blocken så att de matchar de omgivande rutorna. Detta sker tills hela skärmen är en enda färg. <BR><BR>Ditt mål är att rensa skärmen på så få drag som möjligt. Så snart bli framgångsrika i flera nivåer, blir spelet mer komplext, och mycket fler rutor visas på skärmen och svårigheten ökar och blir mer utmanande. <BR><BR>Ha kul och lycka till! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 52 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska/Spanska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Strategy"/><genre value="Games:Unique"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
