<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00216_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>165455168</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>It's time to do some paperwork! Play as Harry, the most generic employee, as he is tasked with delivering reports to other departments. Soon he realizes something odd is going on with the company.<BR><BR>Paperwork is a platform action game, with very easy mechanics, but with very difficult obstacles along the way. Travel through 10 levels in 5 different departments, where you will have to jump, dodge and crouch with great timing, in order to make it to the goal. Each department has its own visual and gameplay style, accompanied with a varied, lively soundtrack. Between each level, you will have the chance to talk to your coworkers, who will make you laugh and give you clues about the mystery of the enterprise. <BR><BR>Package size: 158 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Spanish<BR><BR>© CerosWare 2014 All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>¡Es hora de hacer papeleo! Juega como Harry, el empleado más genérico, mientras se le encarga llevar reportes a otros departamentos. Pronto se da cuenta que algo raro está pasando con la empresa.<BR><BR>Paperwork es un juego de acción y plataformas, con mecánicas muy sencillas, pero con obstáculos muy difíciles en el camino. Viaja a través de 10 niveles en 5 distintos departamentos, donde tendrás que saltar, esquivar y agacharte con gran precisión, para así llegar a la meta. Cada departamento tiene su propio estilo visual y de jugabilidad, acompañado de un soundtrack variado y animado. Entre cada nivel, tendrás la oportunidad de hablar con tus compañeros de trabajo, quienes te harán reír y te darán pistas acerca del misterio de la compañía. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 158 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Español<BR><BR>© CerosWare 2014 All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>C'est temps du travail. Jouer comme Harry, un simple employé, pendant ce temps transporte des documents à d'autres départements. Il voit quelque chose est rare à l'enterprise.<BR><BR>Paperwork c'est un jeu du video d'action, avec des simple instructions, mais avec des obstacles difficiles en route. Voyages dans 10 niveaux avec 5 departements, tu dois sauter, échapper et se courber avec précision pour atteindre l'objectif. Chaque département a un style visuel et gameplay avec une bande sonore. Entre les niveaux vous pouvez parler avec des collègues, ils vous feront rire et donner des conseils sur mystère. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 158 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Espagnol<BR><BR>© CerosWare 2014 All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>E 'tempo di fare lavoro d'ufficio! Gioca come Harry, il più generico dipendente, mentre si prende cura i rapporti agli altri reparti. Presto si racconta che qualcosa rara sta accadendo con la compagnia.<BR><BR>Paperwork è un gioco di azione-platform con la meccanica molto semplice, ma molto difficili ostacoli lungo la strada. Viaggio attraverso 10 livelli in 5 diversi reparti, dove si deve saltare, schivare e piegarsi con grande precisione, al fine di raggiungere l'obiettivo. Ogni reparto ha il suo stile visivo e di gameplay, accompagnato da una colonna sonora varia e vivace. Tra ogni livello, avrete l'opportunità di parlare con i tuoi colleghi di lavoro, che vi farà ridere e vi darà indizi per il mistero della società. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 158 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Spagnolo<BR><BR>© CerosWare 2014 All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>ペーパーワークの　時間だ！。<BR><BR>いちばん　ふつうな　サラリーマンの　ハリーに　なうの！　じむしょには　たくさん　手続きが　あるよね。<BR>でも、　このかいしゃには　なんか　おかしい　ことが　あるそう。<BR><BR>Paperworkは　アクションと　プラットフォームの　ゲームです。　メカニックスは　かんたんですが、障害物が　むずかしい。<BR><BR>レベルが　10！ブランチが　５つ！　ジャンプして！　交わして！　竦めて！　成功！<BR><BR>各ブランチは　ちがう　グラフィックスと　ゲームプレーと　サウンドトラックが　あります。<BR><BR>レベルの　あとで　同僚と　話すことができます。　たのしいですよ。　そして　会社の秘密について　ヒントを　与えるでしょう。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 158 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/スペイン語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>© CerosWare 2014 All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
