<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00209_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>6948816</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Hexagonal-Puzzle-Spiel !!! <BR>Das Ziel ist einfach anzuschließen 6 kleine Sechsecke (Hexi) zusammen, um ein großes (Blume), den Vorstand bilden reinigen! <BR>Zwei Modi: <BR>+ Zeit-Modus: wenn die Karte voll ist, verlieren Sie! <BR>+ Praxis-Modus: Erweitern Sie Ihre Fähigkeiten Reinigungs 77 Stufen der Praxis <BR>* Durch das Löschen der Praxis Stufen einige neue Fähigkeiten kann entriegelt werden <BR>* Vorsicht vor schwarzen Hexi Stücke, haben sie einen Weg, um misterios gelöscht und sind schwer wieder loszuwerden! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 6786 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Spanisch/Japanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Hexagonal puzzle game!!!<BR>The goal is simple join 6 small hexagons(HEXi) together to form a big one(FLOWER) to clean the board!<BR>Two Modes:<BR>+ Time mode: if the board gets full you lose!<BR>+ Practice mode: Hone your skills cleaning 77 practice stages<BR>* By clearing practice stages some new abilities may be unlocked<BR>* Beware black HEXi pieces, they have a misterios way to be cleared and are hard to get rid of! <BR><BR>Package size: 6786 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Spanish/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Juego Puzzle Hexagonal!<BR>El objetivo es simple, junta 6 hexagonitos (HEXi) para formar uno grade(FLOR) para limpiar el tablero!<BR>Dos modos:<BR>+ Modo de Tiempo: Si el tablero se llena pierdes!<BR>+ Modo de practica: pule tus habilidades limpiando 77 niveles de practica<BR>* Al limpiar algunos niveles de practica podras desbloquear nuevas habilidades<BR>* Cuidado con los HEXi negros, su forma de desaparecer es un misterio! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 6786 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Español/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Kuusikulmainen pulmapeli !!! <BR>Tavoitteena on yksinkertainen liittyä 6 pieni laput (Hexi) yhteen muodostaen iso (kukka) puhdistaa hallituksen! <BR>Kaksi tilaa: <BR>+ Aika-tila: jos hallitus saa täyden häviät! <BR>+ Practice mode: hioa taitojasi puhdistus 77 käytännön vaiheet <BR>* Poistamalla käytännössä vaiheissa uusia kykyjä voi olla lukitsematon <BR>* Varo musta Hexi kappaletta, heillä Mistérios tapa tyhjentää ja on vaikea päästä eroon! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 6786 Kt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Espanja<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Hexagonale jeu de puzzle !!! <BR>Le but est simple rejoindre 6 petits hexagones (HEXI​​) ensemble pour former un gros (FLEUR) pour nettoyer le bord! <BR>Deux modes: <BR>Mode + Temps: si la carte est pleine, vous perdez! <BR>+ Mode de pratique: Aiguisez vos compétences de nettoyage 77 étapes pratiques<BR>* En désactivant les étapes de la pratique de nouvelles capacités peuvent être déverrouillé <BR>* Méfiez-vous des pièces de Hexi noirs, ils ont une façon de misterios être effacé et il est difficile de se débarrasser! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 6786 Ko - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Espagnol/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Gioco di puzzle esagonale !!! <BR>L'obiettivo è semplice unire 6 piccoli esagoni (Hexi) insieme per formare un grande (FIORE) per pulire il bordo! <BR>Due modalità: <BR>Modalità + Tempo: se la scheda si riempie si perde! <BR>+ Modalità Pratica: affinare le tue abilità di pulizia 77 fasi di pratica <BR>* Con la compensazione fasi di pratica alcune nuove abilità possono essere sbloccati <BR>* Attenzione pezzi Hexi neri, hanno un modo misterios per essere eliminato e sono difficili da sbarazzarsi di! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 6786 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Spagnolo/Giapponese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>六角パズルゲームだ！！！<BR>目的は簡単です、六つの小さいピース（ヘックシ）を大きい六角の形（フラワー）で集めてとボードをきれいに～<BR>モードが二つ：<BR>＋タイムモード：ボードがピース（ヘックシ）でいっぱいになったら負けです！<BR>＋練習（れんしゅう）モード：７７ステージをクリアとスキルを磨け！<BR>＊れんしゅうステージをクリアすると新技を得る！<BR>＊黒いヘックシは危険です！黒いヘックシのクリア方法は謎です難しいです！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 6786 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/スペイン語/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Zeshoekige puzzelspel !!! <BR>Het doel is eenvoudig mee 6 kleine zeshoeken (Hexi) samen om een grote (bloem) op het bord schoon te maken! <BR>Twee modi: <BR>+ Time mode: als het bord vol raakt je verliest! <BR>+ Practice-modus: Scherp je vaardigheden schoonmaken 77 praktijk stadia <BR>* Bij de goedkeuring van de praktijk stappen een aantal nieuwe mogelijkheden ontgrendeld kan worden <BR>* Pas op voor zwarte hexi stukken, hebben ze een misterios manier worden opgeruimd en zijn moeilijk om zich te ontdoen van! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 6786 KB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Spaans<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Sześciokątny gra logiczna !!! <BR>Cel jest prosty dołączyć 6 małych sześciokątów (Hexi) ze sobą, tworząc jeden wielki (kwiat), aby wyczyścić planszę! <BR>Dwóch trybach: <BR>Tryb + Czas: jeśli płyta staje się pełna tracisz! <BR>+ Tryb Practice: doskonalić swoje umiejętności praktyczne czyszczące 77 stopni <BR>* Poprzez wyczyszczenie etapy praktyki kilka nowych umiejętności może być odblokowany <BR>* Uważaj czarne kawałki Hexi, że mają sposób Misterios być wyczyszczone i trudno się pozbyć! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 6786 KB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Hiszpański/Japoński<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Hexagonal pusselspel !!! <BR>Målet är enkelt gå med 6 små hexagoner (Hexi) ihop till en stor en (BLOMMA) för att rengöra tavlan! <BR>Två lägen: <BR>+ Tidsläget: om styrelsen blir full du förlorar! <BR>+ Övningsläge: Finslipa dina färdigheter städning 77 övningssteg <BR>* Genom att avsluta övningssteg några nya förmågor kan vara upplåst <BR>* Se upp svarta Hexi stycken, de har en Misterios sätt rensas och är svåra att bli av med! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 6786 KB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Spanska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
