<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00133_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>29170208</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Før Mr. Nibbles, det agern-hamstrende egern, gennem forskellige baner i dette charmerende platformseventyr. Indsaml de agern, der ligger rundt omkring i hver zone, så du har nok at spise hele vinteren. Spillets styring er superenkel, det har et antal forskellige spillemekanikker og ser nuttet ud. Little Acorns er et eventyr, der helt og holdent hører hjemme på PlayStation®Mobile <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 28 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR>- Bevægelsessensor<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Führe das Eicheln sammelnde Eichhörnchen Mr. Nibbles bei diesem bezaubernden Plattform-Abenteuer durch abwechslungsreiche Levels. Sammle die überall in einer Zone verteilten Eicheln, um dich auf den Winter vorzubereiten. Little Acorns ist mit super einfacher Steuerung, abwechslungsreichen Spielmechanismen mit einem süßen und lieblichen Stil ein Abenteuer, das perfekt zu PlayStation®Mobile passt. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 28 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR>- Bewegungssensor<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Japanisch<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Guide Mr. Nibbles the acorn-hoarding squirrel through a variety of levels in this charming platforming adventure. Collect the acorns scattered around each zone to stock up for winter. Featuring super simple controls, a variety of game mechanics with a cute and loveable look, Little Acorns is an adventure that is completely at home on PlayStation®Mobile <BR><BR>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Guide Mr. Nibbles the acorn-hoarding squirrel through a variety of levels in this charming platforming adventure. Collect the acorns scattered around each zone to stock up for winter. Featuring super simple controls, a variety of game mechanics with a cute and loveable look, Little Acorns is an adventure that is completely at home on PlayStation®Mobile <BR><BR>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Guide Mr. Nibbles the acorn-hoarding squirrel through a variety of levels in this charming platforming adventure. Collect the acorns scattered around each zone to stock up for winter. Featuring super simple controls, a variety of game mechanics with a cute and loveable look, Little Acorns is an adventure that is completely at home on PlayStation®Mobile <BR><BR>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Guía al Sr. Nibbles, la ardilla recolectora de bellotas, en una gran variedad de niveles en esta cautivadora aventura de plataformas. Recoge las bellotas que hay dispersadas en cada zona para tener reservas suficientes para el invierno. Little Acorns es una aventura disponible para iOS que cuenta con unos controles superbásicos, diferentes mecánicas de juego y un estilo adorable. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 28 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR>- Sensor de movimiento<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Japonés<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Opasta terhoja keräävää Mr. Nibbles -oravaa erilaisissa kentissä tässä hurmaavassa tasohyppelyseikkailussa. Kerää kullekin alueelle varisseet terhot talven varalle. Yksinkertaisen ohjauksen, erilaisten pelimekanismien ja söpön ulkoasun ansiosta Little Acorns -seikkailu on kuin kotonaan PlayStation®Mobile-palvelussa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 28 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR>- Liikeohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Ranska/Espanja/Saksa/Italia<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Guidez Mr. Nibbles, grand amateur de glands, dans les différents niveaux de cette charmante aventure de plateforme. Trouvez les glands éparpillés sur chacune des zones et faites le plein pour l'hiver. Avec ses commandes ultra simples et des graphismes aussi mignons qu'adorables, Little Acorns trouve merveilleusement sa place sur PlayStation®Mobile. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 28 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR>- Détecteur de mouvements<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Japonais<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Guida Mr. Nibbles, lo scoiattolo accumulatore di ghiande attraverso una serie di livelli in questa splendida avventura in stile platform. Colleziona le ghiande sparse in ciascun ambiente e accumulale per l'inverno. I comandi ultra semplici, l'aspetto buffo e adorabile e la varietà delle meccaniche di gioco rendono Little Acorns un'avventura perfetta per PlayStation®Mobile <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 28 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR>- Sensore di movimento<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Giapponese<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Hjelp ekornet Nibbles, som elsker å samle nøtter, gjennom mange ulike brett i dette sjarmerende plattformeventyret. Samle nøttene som er spredt omkring i sonene, så du har nok til vinteren. Spillet har enkle kontroller, variert spillmekanikk og et søtt og koselig utseende. Little Acorns er et eventyr som hører hjemme på PlayStation®Mobile <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 28 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR>- Bevegelsessensor<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Leid Mr. Nibbles de eikelverzamelende eekhoorn door een reeks levels in dit charmante platformavontuur. Verzamel de eikels die over elke zone zijn verspreid om een wintervoorraad aan te leggen. Met supereenvoudige bediening, een reeks spelmechanieken met een schattig en lief uiterlijk is Little Acorns een avontuur dat helemaal thuis is op PlayStation®Mobile <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 28 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR>- Bewegingssensor<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Frans/Spaans/Duits/Italiaans<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Hjälp mr Nibbles, den ekollonsamlande ekorren, att ta sig fram genom en mängd nivåer i det här charmiga plattformsäventyret. Samla ihop ekollon som ligger utspridda i de olika områdena och spara dem till vintern. Det söta och charmiga spelet har superenkla kontroller och olika sorters spelmekanik. Little Acorns är ett äventyr som passar perfekt för PlayStation®Mobile. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 28 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR>- Rörelsesensor<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Franska/Spanska/Tyska/Italienska<BR><BR>© Team Pesky 2013<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
