<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00012_00">
 <appVersion>1.05</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>155554976</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[世界中の猫たちは牛乳の供給不足で大変困っています。<br>貴方は猫達のミルク採掘チームと水恐怖症を乗り越え、力合わせて海底より地球の自然乳を発見せよ！<br><br>故に海の機械生物から猫達の見守りも頼む！<br>水中に進み潜水艦の多彩なアクションをお楽しみに<br><br>コンテンツ容量:149 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Due to a sudden shortage of milk, cats around the world are forced to seek out new sources to get their fix.<br><br>You and your team of milk mining kittens have overcome a fear of water to drill down under the ocean seabed and begin extracting vast reserves of what seems to be naturally forming full-fat milk.<br><br>Get ready for fast paced submarine action, defending the kittens from disruptive mechanical sea creatures.<br>The milk must flow!<br><br>Package size: 149 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[En raison d'une soudaine pénurie de lait, les chats à travers le monde sont contraints de chercher de nouvelles sources pour obtenir leur dose.<br><br>Vous et votre équipe de chatons minières du lait ont surmonté une peur de l'eau pour descendre sous l'océan des fonds marins et de commencer à extraire de vastes réserves de ce qui semble être naturellement formation riche en matière grasse du lait.<br><br>Préparez-vous pour l'action sous-marine au rythme rapide, la défense des chatons de perturbateurs créatures marines mécaniques.<br>Le lait doit couler!<br><br>Taille du paquet: 149 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[A causa di un'improvvisa carenza di latte, i gatti di tutto il mondo sono costretti a cercare nuove fonti.<br><br>Tu e la tua squadra di gattini in cerca di latte avete superato la paura dell'acqua per scendere sul fondo dell'oceano e estrarre quello che sembra essere una riserva naturale di latte intero.<br><br>Tieniti pronto per una azione rapida sottomarina per difendere i gattini da pericolosissime creature meccaniche marine.<br>Che latte sia!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 149 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Debido a una repentina escasez de leche, los gatos de todo el mundo se ven obligados a buscar nuevas fuentes para obtener su dosis.<br><br>Usted y su equipo de los gatitos de minería de la leche han superado un miedo al agua para ver los detalles bajo el océano y comenzar a extraer las vastas reservas de lo que parece ser de origen natural que forma la leche entera.<br><br>¡Prepárate para la acción rápida submarino ritmo, la defensa de los gatitos de los perturbadores criaturas marinas mecánicos.<br>La leche debe fluir!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 149 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Durch eine plötzliche Verknappung von Milch, sind Katzen auf der ganzen Welt gezwungen, suchen nach neuen Quellen, um ihre Fix erhalten.<br><br>Sie und Ihr Team von Milch Bergbau Kätzchen haben Angst vor dem Wasser, um einen Drilldown unter dem Ozean und Meeresboden beginnen Extrahieren enormen Reserven des scheinbar natürlich bildenden Vollmilch sein, zu überwinden.<br><br>Machen Sie sich bereit für schnellen U-Boot-Aktion, die Verteidigung der Kätzchen aus störende mechanische Meeresbewohner.<br>Die Milch muss fließen!<br><br>Paketgröße: 149 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Due to a sudden shortage of milk, cats around the world are forced to seek out new sources to get their fix.<br><br>You and your team of milk mining kittens have overcome a fear of water to drill down under the ocean seabed and begin extracting vast reserves of what seems to be naturally forming full-fat milk.<br><br>Get ready for fast paced submarine action, defending the kittens from disruptive mechanical sea creatures.<br>The milk must flow!<br><br>Package size: 149 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[En raison d'une soudaine pénurie de lait, les chats à travers le monde sont contraints de chercher de nouvelles sources pour obtenir leur dose.<br><br>Vous et votre équipe de chatons minières du lait ont surmonté une peur de l'eau pour descendre sous l'océan des fonds marins et de commencer à extraire de vastes réserves de ce qui semble être naturellement formation riche en matière grasse du lait.<br><br>Préparez-vous pour l'action sous-marine au rythme rapide, la défense des chatons de perturbateurs créatures marines mécaniques.<br>Le lait doit couler!<br><br>Taille du programme: 149 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Arcade"/>
  <genre value="Games:Shooter"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
