<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00128_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>3097712</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Hyper Erinnerung kategorisiert werden können, ist es Notepad / ToDo App, einfach so zu verwalten.<BR><BR>[Features]<BR>- Verwalten Sie die Liste in Kategorien unterteilt. (Kategorie können registriert werden. Bis zu bis zu 60)<BR>- Kann für jede Titel eingestellt werden und alle Icons aus es ist in der Kategorie<BR>- Konfigurierbare sub Liste weiter in der Liste. Es ist leicht zu Eltern-Kind-Struktur der Kategorie&gt; Liste&gt; sub Liste zu verwalten.<BR>- Der Fortschritt ist leicht zu auf einen Blick bar wird durch die Fortschritte in der Liste aktualisiert verstehen.<BR><BR>Beide bekommen ein bequemes Leben und eine Notiz fühlen Sie sich frei, die Sie tun möchten, dass Sie tun wollten, was Sie sich merken wollen. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 3026 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Hyper reminder can be categorized, it is Notepad / ToDo app, easy to manage so.<BR><BR>[Features]<BR>- Manage the list is divided into categories. (Category can be registered. Up to up to 60)<BR>- Can be set for any title and any icons from it is available in category<BR>- Configurable sub list further in the list. It is easy to manage parent-child structure of the category&gt; List&gt; sub list.<BR>- Progress is easy to understand at a glance bar is updated by the progress of the list.<BR><BR>Both get a comfortable life and a note feel free that you want to do, that you wanted to do, what you want to remember. <BR><BR>Package size: 3026 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Recordatorio Hyper pueden clasificar, es el Bloc de notas / Tareas aplicación, fácil de manejar eso.<BR><BR>[Características]<BR>- Administrar la lista se divide en categorías. (Categoría Pueden registrarse. Hasta un máximo de 60)<BR>- Se puede configurar para cualquier título y los iconos de la misma se encuentra disponible en la categoría<BR>- Sub lista Configurable más en la lista. Es fácil de manejar la estructura de elementos primarios y secundarios de la categoría&gt; Lista&gt; Lista de sub.<BR>- El progreso es fácil de entender en un bar de vista se actualiza por el progreso de la lista.<BR><BR>Ambos reciben una vida cómoda y una nota no dude que usted quiere hacer, que lo que quería hacer, lo que quiere recordar. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 3026 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Hyper rappel peut être classé, il est Notepad / ToDo application, facile à gérer, donc.<BR><BR>[Features]<BR>- Gérer la liste est divisée en catégories. (Catégorie peuvent être enregistrés. Jusqu'à jusqu'à 60)<BR>- Peuvent être définis pour n'importe quel titre et les icônes d'elle est disponible dans la catégorie<BR>- Sous-liste configurable en outre dans la liste. Il est facile de gérer la structure parent-enfant de la catégorie&gt; Liste&gt; sous-liste.<BR>- Progrès est facile à comprendre dans un bar de vue est mis à jour par les progrès de la liste.<BR><BR>Tous deux obtiennent une vie confortable et une note n'hésitez que vous voulez faire, ce que vous vouliez faire, ce que vous voulez rappeler. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 3026 KB – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Promemoria Hyper può essere classificato, è Notepad / ToDo app, facile da gestire così.<BR><BR>[Caratteristiche]<BR>- Gestire l'elenco è diviso in categorie. (Categoria possibile registrare. Fino a un massimo di 60)<BR>- Può essere impostato per ogni titolo e le icone da esso è disponibile in categoria<BR>- Configurabile sub elenco ulteriormente nella lista. E 'facile da gestire la struttura padre-figlio della categoria&gt; Elenco&gt; Elenco sub.<BR>- Il progresso è facile da capire in un bar sguardo viene aggiornato dal progresso della lista.<BR><BR>Entrambi ottenere una vita agiata e una nota sentitevi liberi che si vuole fare, che si voleva fare, ciò che si vuole ricordare. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 3026 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[ハイパーリマインダーはカテゴリ分類ができ、とても管理のしやすいメモ帳・ToDoアプリです。<BR><BR>[特長]<BR>・カテゴリに分けてリストを管理。(カテゴリは最大60個まで登録可能。)<BR>・カテゴリには用意された中から任意のアイコンと任意のタイトルを設定可能<BR>・リストの中にはさらにサブリストを設定可能。カテゴリ＞リスト＞サブリストの親子構造で管理しやすい。<BR>・リストの進行具合によってバーが更新され進捗がひと目でわかりやすい。<BR><BR>やりたいこと、やりたかったこと、思い出したいことを気軽にメモして快適な生活のお共に。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 3026 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Lifestyle"/><genre value="Apps:Utilities"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
