<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00129_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>33664992</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[When hunger strikes, strike oil! Velkommen til et forunderligt sted, hvor landskabet i bogstaveligste forstand er levende – og det sulter! Det er dit arbejde, at hente olien fra det brudte rør til de underlige skabningers munde. Det bliver ikke nemt for du skal bruge alt muligt sjovt værktøj, og din hjerne, til at løse gåderne. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 33 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Wenn dich der Hunger packt, stoss auf Öl! Willkommen zu einem eigenartigen und wundervollen Ort, wo das Land wort wörtlich am leben ist - und es ist am verhungern! Deine Aufgabe ist es das Öl von dem kaputten Rohr, zu den Mäulern der eigenartigen Kreaturen zu bekommen. Es wird aber nicht leicht sein, da du alle mögliche Lustige Werkzeuge und auch dein Gehirn benutzen musst, um die Puzzles zu lösen. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 33 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[When hunger strikes, strike oil! Welcome to a weird and wonderful place where the land is literally alive — and it’s starving! Your job is to get the oil from the broken pipe to the mouths of the strange creatures. It won’t be easy though, as you’ll need to use all sorts of fun tools, as well as your brains, to solve the puzzles. <BR><BR>Package size: 33 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[When hunger strikes, strike oil! Welcome to a weird and wonderful place where the land is literally alive — and it’s starving! Your job is to get the oil from the broken pipe to the mouths of the strange creatures. It won’t be easy though, as you’ll need to use all sorts of fun tools, as well as your brains, to solve the puzzles. <BR><BR>Package size: 33 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[When hunger strikes, strike oil! Welcome to a weird and wonderful place where the land is literally alive — and it’s starving! Your job is to get the oil from the broken pipe to the mouths of the strange creatures. It won’t be easy though, as you’ll need to use all sorts of fun tools, as well as your brains, to solve the puzzles. <BR><BR>Package size: 33 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Cuando el hambre acecha, ¡usa el petróleo! Te damos la bienvenida a un lugar extraño, a la par que maravilloso, en la que la tierra cobra vida (literalmente), ¡y se muere de hambre! Tu tarea es conseguir introducir el aceite industrial de la tubería rota en las bocas de las extrañas criaturas. Sin embargo, no será fácil, ya que necesitarás usar todo tipo de herramientas divertidas, además de tu lógica, si quieres resolver los rompecabezas. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 33 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Kun nälkä iskee, etsi öljyä! Tervetuloa outoon paikkaan, jossa maa on kirjaimellisesti elossa – ja nääntymässä nälkään! Tehtäväsi on kuljettaa öljy murtuneesta putkesta outojen otusten suihin. Se ei ole helppoa, sillä joudut ratkomaan pulmia kaikenlaisilla hauskoilla työkaluilla ja omilla aivoillasi. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 33 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Mettez-leur le pétrole à la bouche ! Bienvenue dans un endroit tout aussi merveilleux qu'étrange où la terre est littéralement en vie... Et elle a faim ! Votre travail consiste à nourrir d'étranges créatures en amenant le pétrole du tuyau cassé jusqu'à leurs bouches. Mais ce ne sera pas facile et vous devrez utiliser des objets amusants tout autant que vos méninges pour résoudre les niveaux. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 33 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Quando la fame arriva, tu trova il petrolio! Ti diamo il benvenuto in un luogo strano e meraviglioso, dove la terra è viva, nel vero senso della parola, e sta morendo di fame! Il tuo compito consiste nel portare il petrolio dalla conduttura rotta alle bocche di quelle strane creature. Ma non sarà facile, dovrai usare un sacco di attrezzi strani e il tuo cervello, per risolvere i rompicapi. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 33 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Når sulten slår til, finn olje! Velkommen til et merkelig og fantastisk sted hvor landet bokstavelig talt lever – og det sulter! Jobben din er å få oljen fra det ødelagte røret opp til munnene til de merkelige skapningene. Det blir ikke lett, for du må bruke mange morsomme verktøy, i tillegg til hjernen, til å løse oppgavene. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 33 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Breek de olie aan als de honger toeslaat! Welkom bij een vreemde en prachtige plek waar het land letterlijk leeft — en het heeft honger! Jouw taak is de olie van de kapotte pijp in de monden van de vreemde wezens te krijgen. Het zal echter niet makkelijk zijn, omdat je allerlei leuke gereedschappen moet gebruiken en je hersens om de puzzels op te lossen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 33 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Släck hungern ... med olja! Välkommen till en knäpp och underbar plats där marken praktiskt taget är vid liv – och den är hungrig! Ditt jobb är att mata de underliga varelserna med olja från det trasiga röret. Men det blir inte lätt. Du måste använda alla möjliga sorters roliga verktyg och dessutom vara smart för att kunna lösa pusslen. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 33 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>@ 2011-2013 HolyWaterGames<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Family"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
