<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00016_00">
 <appVersion>1.04</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>29533408</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[マッチ3、麻雀、パズルの3種類のお馴染みゲーム<br>Treasure Hunt(宝探し)では、動物をマッチ3して動物園に入れ、宝物とコインをゲット。ゴールドエレファントの頭を見付ければ、さらに多くのゲームモードで遊べるようになるよ。<br>砂漠からジャングル、はたまた月までも、6つの場所を旅して30種類の動物とお宝満載の宝箱を見つけてね。<br>Animahjong(アニマル麻雀)では、手軽に麻雀を楽しめるよ。動物を集めてアニマル盗賊から助け出そう。<br>Puzzle Quest(パズルクエスト)では、新しいユニークなゲームモードで頭脳試しだ。<br><br>コンテンツ容量:29 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>(c)2012 Big Head Games Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[3 classic gameplay styles, match-3, mahjong and puzzle.<br>Match 3 animals in Treasure Hunt to add animals to your zoo and earn treasure and coins, find the gold elephant head to unlock more game modes.<br>Visit 6 locations from Desert to Jungle and even the Moon in search of over 30 animals and a chest full of treasure.<br>Animahjong plays a fast game of Mahjong, matching animals to free them from the animal bandits.<br>Puzzle Quest is a test of your brain skills in a new and unique game mode.<br><br>Package size: 29 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>(c)2012 Big Head Games Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[3 styles de jeux classiques : match-3, mahjong et puzzle.<br>Faites correspondre 3 animaux de la Chasse aux trésors pour ajouter des animaux à votre zoo et obtenir un trésor et des pièces, et trouvez la tête d’éléphant en or pour déverrouiller plus de modes de jeu.<br>Visitez 6 lieux, du désert à la jungle en passant par la lune, pour découvrir plus de 30 animaux et un coffre rempli de trésors.<br>Animahjong est un jeu de mahjong rapide où il vous faut faire correspondre des animaux pour les libérer des griffes de redoutables bandits.<br>Puzzle Quest fait appel à votre réflexion grâce à un mode de jeu nouveau et unique.<br><br>Taille du paquet: 29 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>(c)2012 Big Head Games Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Tre classiche modalità di gioco: match-3, mahjong e puzzle.<br>Abbina tre animali in Treasure Hunt per aggiungere animali al tuo zoo e accumulare tesori e monete. Scopri l'elefante d'oro per sbloccare ulteriori modalità di gioco!<br>Visita sei ambientazioni, dal deserto, alla giungla, alla luna, in cerca di oltre 30 animali e di un forziere traboccante di tesori.<br>Animahjong si gioca come una partita veloce di Mahjong, abbinando gli animali per liberarli dai bracconieri.<br>Puzzle Quest metterà alla prova le tue meningi con una nuova e originale modalità di gioco.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 29 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>(c)2012 Big Head Games Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Tres grandes clásicos: conecta 3, mahjong y puzzle.<br>Junta a tres animales en Treasure Hunt para añadir animales a tu zoo y ganar tesoros y monedas. Encuentra la cabeza del elefante de oro y desbloquea más modos de juego.<br>Visita seis lugares, desde el desierto hasta la jungla pasando incluso por la luna, en busca de más de 30 animales y de un cofre lleno de tesoros.<br>Animahjong es un acelerado juego de Mahjong, emparejando animales para liberarlos de los bandidos animales.<br>Puzzle Quest es una prueba de destreza para tu cerebro a través de un nuevo y exclusivo modo de juego.<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 29 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<br><br>(c)2012 Big Head Games Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[3 klassische Spielvarianten: 3-Gewinnt, Mahjong und Puzzle.<br>Kombiniere in Treasure Hunt Tiere, um neue Tiere für deinen Zoo, Schätze und Münzen zu erhalten und finde den goldenen Elefantenkopf, um neue Spielmodi freizuschalten.<br>Durchsuche sechs Schauplätze, von der Wüste über den Dschungel bis zum Mond nach über 30 verschiedenen Tieren und einer prall gefüllten Schatztruhe.<br>Animahjong ist eine schnelle Mahjong-Variante, in der du Tiere durch Kombination aus den Klauen von Tierfängern befreist.<br>Und im neuen und einzigartigen Spielmodus Puzzle Quest kannst du deine geistigen Fähigkeiten auf die Probe stellen.<br><br>Paketgröße: 29 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<br><br>(c)2012 Big Head Games Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[3 classic gameplay styles, match-3, mahjong and puzzle.<br>Match 3 animals in Treasure Hunt to add animals to your zoo and earn treasure and coins, find the gold elephant head to unlock more game modes.<br>Visit 6 locations from Desert to Jungle and even the Moon in search of over 30 animals and a chest full of treasure.<br>Animahjong plays a fast game of Mahjong, matching animals to free them from the animal bandits.<br>Puzzle Quest is a test of your brain skills in a new and unique game mode.<br><br>Package size: 29 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>(c)2012 Big Head Games Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[3 styles de jeux classiques : match-3, mahjong et puzzle.<br>Faites correspondre 3 animaux de la Chasse aux trésors pour ajouter des animaux à votre zoo et obtenir un trésor et des pièces, et trouvez la tête d’éléphant en or pour déverrouiller plus de modes de jeu.<br>Visitez 6 lieux, du désert à la jungle en passant par la lune, pour découvrir plus de 30 animaux et un coffre rempli de trésors.<br>Animahjong est un jeu de mahjong rapide où il vous faut faire correspondre des animaux pour les libérer des griffes de redoutables bandits.<br>Puzzle Quest fait appel à votre réflexion grâce à un mode de jeu nouveau et unique.<br><br>Taille du programme: 29 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>(c)2012 Big Head Games Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Strategy"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
