<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00018_00">
 <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>4584208</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[「まさに隠れた名作だ。プレイしてみる価値は十分にある。」<br>―『メダル・オブ・オナー』プロデューサー Tomo Moriwaki <br><br>『sixty second shooter Deluxe』は、1分間以内にできる限りの破壊を行うゲームです。敵の大群は容赦なく向かってくるので、勝利を収めるには鋭い機知と素早い反射神経が必要となります。真に危険な敵の待ち受ける深い階層に強気で乗り込んでいきますか？このデュアルスティック使用のペースの速いゲームでは、常に時間が経過していきます。<br><br>ありがたいことに、Happion Laboratories の果敢な科学者は、この60秒間の地獄をあなたが切り抜けることができるように最新の兵器を開発してくれました。ミサイルを使用して大きな連鎖ボーナスをゲットしたり、遠隔操作によって爆発する致命的な爆弾に対戦相手を誘い込んだりしましょう。これらの最新兵器の導入で、1分間を十分に生き抜きるようなあらゆる戦略を取ることができます。<br><br>高い評価を得た受賞作品『Spider-Man 2』と『Schizoid』のゲーム・デベロッパー Jamie Fristrom によって制作。<br><br>コンテンツ容量:4477 KB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語<br><br>著作権等:<br>Copyright (c) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[“This game is a hidden gem. It's worth getting into.”<br>- Tomo Moriwaki, producer of Medal of Honor<br><br>“*sixty second shooter* takes a simple concept and delivers it in small, intense bites. You can come back at any time and attempt to improve your performance, and you’ll want to.”<br>- VentureBeat | GamesBeat<br><br>In *sixty second shooter Deluxe* you'll be given one minute to deal as much destruction as possible. The enemy hordes are relentless, so only the sharpest wits and the fastest reflexes will prevail. Will you press your luck and fly to the deep levels where the truly treacherous foes await? The clock is always ticking in this fast-paced dual-stick shooter.<br><br>Thankfully, our intrepid scientists at Happion Laboratories have developed all-new weapons to help you in those sixty seconds of hell. Use missiles to build a large chain bonus or lure your opponents into deadly remote-detonating bombs. With these tools at your disposal, you can develop all kinds of strategies to make that minute last a lifetime!<br><br>Created by Jamie Fristrom, game developer behind the critically acclaimed and award-winning games Spider-Man 2 and Schizoid.<br><br>Package size: 4477 KB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Copyright (c) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[« Ce jeu est un véritable bijou vidéoludique qui vous fera passer des moments d'anthologie ! »<br>- Tomo Moriwaki, producteur de Medal of Honor<br><br>Dans sixty second shooter Deluxe, vous disposez d'une minute pour semer le chaos tous azimuts. Affrontez des hordes d'ennemis implacables auxquelles seuls les pilotes chevronnés les plus rusés et les plus véloces survivront ! Tenterez-vous le tout pour le tout en vous aventurant dans les profondeurs insondables de niveaux inexplorés où de redoutables entités sont tapies dans l'ombre ? Une fois le chrono lancé, rien ni personne ne peut l'arrêter dans ce shoot'em up à deux joysticks au rythme effréné.<br><br>Heureusement, les scientifiques des laboratoires Happion ont développé un arsenal dernier cri pour vous aider à surmonter ces soixante secondes infernales ! Faites appel à une technologie balistique dévastatrice pour générer des bonus d'enchaînement délirants ou pulvérisez vos adversaires en les attirant sournoisement à proximité de bombes surpuissantes que vous ferez exploser à distance !  Grâce à cet armement de pointe, libre à vous d'élaborer une multitude de stratégies qui transformeront cette minute frénétique en une éternité !<br><br>Créé par Jamie Fristrom, qui a également participé au développement de Spider-Man 2 et Schizoid, deux jeux primés et salués par la critique.<br><br>Taille du paquet: 4477 ko – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Copyright (c) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[“Questo gioco è una vera e propria chicca. Assolutamente da provare.”<br>- Tomo Moriwaki, producer di Medal of Honor<br><br>In sixty second shooter Deluxe avrai un minuto di tempo a tua disposizione per distruggere tutto quello che ti si presenterà di fronte. I nemici arrivano a getto continuo: per batterli, ti serviranno acutezza d'ingegno e riflessi pronti! E se sfiderai la sorte passando ai livelli superiori, ti attenderanno gli avversari più insidiosi. Doppia levetta e ritmo serrato: in questo sparatutto il tempo non si ferma fai! <br><br>Fortunatamente, gli intrepidi scienziati di Happion Laboratories hanno sviluppato armi nuove di zecca per aiutarti in quei sessanta secondi di inferno. Ad esempio, puoi usare i missili per ottenere enormi bonus oppure attirare i nemici verso le mortali bombe a detonazione remota. Grazie a questi strumenti potrai mettere in atto numerose strategie per far durare quel minuto un’eternità!<br><br>Creato da Jamie Fristrom, sviluppatore di Spider-Man 2 e Schizoid, pluripremiati e acclamati dalla critica.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 4477 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano<br><br>Copyright (c) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[“Este juego es una joya oculta. Merece la pena probarlo”.<br>- Tomo Moriwaki, productor de Medal of Honor<br><br>En sixty second shooter Deluxe tendrás un minuto para destruir todo lo que puedas. Las hordas enemigas son implacables, así que solo los jugadores más hábiles y con los reflejos más rápidos podrán sobrevivir. ¿Vas a tentar a la suerte jugando en los niveles más difíciles donde te aguardan los enemigos más traicioneros? El tiempo siempre apremia en este vertiginoso shooter de dos sticks.<br><br>Gracias a nuestros intrépidos científicos de Happion Laboratories hemos desarrollado nuevas armas para ayudarte durante esos 60 segundos infernales. Lanza misiles para conseguir bonificaciones en cadena o atrae a tus enemigos hacia bombas detonadas a distancia. Con estas herramientas a tu disposición, podrás desarrollar toda clase de estrategias para que ese minuto dure toda una vida.<br><br>Creado por Jamie Fristrom, el productor de videojuegos galardonados y aclamados por la crítica como Spider-Man 2 y Schizoid.<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 4477 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano<br><br>Copyright (c) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA["Ein echter Geheimtipp, den man sich keinesfalls entgehen lassen sollte!"<br>- Tomo Moriwaki, Producer bei Medal of Honor<br><br>In sixty second shooter Deluxe geht es darum, innerhalb von einer Minute möglichst viel Schaden anzurichten. Nur wer über einen scharfen Verstand und blitzschnelle Reflexe verfügt, wird sich gegen die zahllosen Feindwellen durchsetzen. Doch wagst du dich auch in die wirklich anspruchsvollen Levels, wo dich die hinterlistigsten Gegner erwarten? In diesem actiongeladenen Shooter tickt unbarmherzig die Uhr!<br><br>Zum Glück haben unsere couragierten Wissenschaftler von Happion Laboratories brandneue Waffen entwickelt, die dir dabei helfen, die 60 Höllen-Sekunden zu überstehen. Feuere Raketen ab und sichere dir riesige Kettentreffer-Boni oder locke deine Gegner in tödliche Bombenfallen. Entwickle individuellen Strategien und erlebe die längste Minute deines Lebens!<br><br>Entwickelt von Jamie Fristrom, Schöpfer der preisgekrönten Spiele Spider-Man 2 und Schizoid.<br><br>Paketgröße: 4477 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch<br><br>Copyright (c) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[“This game is a hidden gem. It's worth getting into.”<br>- Tomo Moriwaki, producer of Medal of Honor<br><br>“*sixty second shooter* takes a simple concept and delivers it in small, intense bites. You can come back at any time and attempt to improve your performance, and you’ll want to.”<br>- VentureBeat | GamesBeat<br><br>In *sixty second shooter Deluxe* you'll be given one minute to deal as much destruction as possible. The enemy hordes are relentless, so only the sharpest wits and the fastest reflexes will prevail. Will you press your luck and fly to the deep levels where the truly treacherous foes await? The clock is always ticking in this fast-paced dual-stick shooter.<br><br>Thankfully, our intrepid scientists at Happion Laboratories have developed all-new weapons to help you in those sixty seconds of hell. Use missiles to build a large chain bonus or lure your opponents into deadly remote-detonating bombs. With these tools at your disposal, you can develop all kinds of strategies to make that minute last a lifetime!<br><br>Created by Jamie Fristrom, game developer behind the critically acclaimed and award-winning games Spider-Man 2 and Schizoid.<br><br>Package size: 4477 KB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Copyright (c) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[« Ce jeu est un véritable bijou vidéoludique qui vous fera passer des moments d'anthologie ! »<br>- Tomo Moriwaki, producteur de Medal of Honor<br><br>Dans sixty second shooter Deluxe, vous disposez d'une minute pour semer le chaos tous azimuts. Affrontez des hordes d'ennemis implacables auxquelles seuls les pilotes chevronnés les plus rusés et les plus véloces survivront ! Tenterez-vous le tout pour le tout en vous aventurant dans les profondeurs insondables de niveaux inexplorés où de redoutables entités sont tapies dans l'ombre ? Une fois le chrono lancé, rien ni personne ne peut l'arrêter dans ce shoot'em up à deux joysticks au rythme effréné.<br><br>Heureusement, les scientifiques des laboratoires Happion ont développé un arsenal dernier cri pour vous aider à surmonter ces soixante secondes infernales ! Faites appel à une technologie balistique dévastatrice pour générer des bonus d'enchaînement délirants ou pulvérisez vos adversaires en les attirant sournoisement à proximité de bombes surpuissantes que vous ferez exploser à distance !  Grâce à cet armement de pointe, libre à vous d'élaborer une multitude de stratégies qui transformeront cette minute frénétique en une éternité !<br><br>Créé par Jamie Fristrom, qui a également participé au développement de Spider-Man 2 et Schizoid, deux jeux primés et salués par la critique.<br><br>Taille du programme: 4477 ko - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Copyright (c) 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Arcade"/>
  <genre value="Games:Action"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
