<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00135_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>58850336</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA["Når du først kommer i gang med at træde i pedalerne, vil du aldrig stoppe i dette sjove cykelspil!<BR>Den populære mobil-app ""Bike Rider"" – nu påPlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Mor dig med en forfriskende ny blanding af hop-og-køre-action på bumpede veje og i dybe dale og med hop over mure på din cykel. Kør på baner over hele verden i ""WORLD TOUR""-delen, eller se, hvor langt du kan komme i den uendelige ""GRAND PRIX""-del. Brug et udvalg af genstande, der giver dig ekstra fart eller gør brug af særlige effekter, såsom kæmpestore hvirvelvinde, på din vej gennem baner over hele verden! Derudover rummer PS Store-versionen en eksklusiv WORLD TOUR-ekstrabane, som du kan låse op for, hvis du samler nok mønter!<BR><BR>Når du træder i pedalerne, vil du aldrig stoppe igen! Prøv et helt nyt hop-og-kør-spil!" <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 57 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Tritt in die Pedale und die Action geht los! Japans beliebtes Plattform-Jump'n'run "Bike Rider DX" garantiert Fun ohne Ende.<BR><BR>Erlebe eine erfrischend neue Art von Jump 'n' run! Bretter los und bezwinge holprige Wege, tiefe Schluchten und jede Menge Hindernisse auf dem Fahrrad. Reise durch die ganze Welt in der "World Tour" oder sieh, wie weit du im endlosen "GRAND PRIX"-Modus kommst. Setze allerlei Items wie z.B. den "Air Ride" oder Propeller ein und nutze spezielle Gimmicks wie riesige Tornados auf dem Weg durch mehr als 60 Levels! Schaffst du es, alle goldenen Medaillien zu sammeln? Bretter los mit Bike Rider DX!!! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 57 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Start to pedal and you'll never want to stop this bracing jump 'n bike action!<BR>Everyone's favorite mobile app "Bike Rider" - now available on PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Enjoy a refreshing new kind of jump 'n run action, riding bumpy roads, crossing deep valleys and jumping over walls on your bike. Challenge stages all over the globe in the "WORLD TOUR" mode or see how far you can go in the endless "GRAND PRIX" mode. Use a variety of items that e.g. speed you up and make use of special gimmicks like giant whirlwinds on your way through the stages of the world! Furthermore, the PS　Store version holds an exclusive "WORLD TOUR" extra stage for you to unlock ? if you manage to collect enough coins!<BR><BR>Once you pedal, you'll never want to stop! Try out a new kind of jump 'n run action! <BR><BR>Package size: 57 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Start to pedal and you'll never want to stop this bracing jump 'n bike action!<BR>Everyone's favorite mobile app "Bike Rider" - now available on PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Enjoy a refreshing new kind of jump 'n run action, riding bumpy roads, crossing deep valleys and jumping over walls on your bike. Challenge stages all over the globe in the "WORLD TOUR" mode or see how far you can go in the endless "GRAND PRIX" mode. Use a variety of items that e.g. speed you up and make use of special gimmicks like giant whirlwinds on your way through the stages of the world! Furthermore, the PS　Store version holds an exclusive "WORLD TOUR" extra stage for you to unlock ? if you manage to collect enough coins!<BR><BR>Once you pedal, you'll never want to stop! Try out a new kind of jump 'n run action! <BR><BR>Package size: 57 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Start to pedal and you'll never want to stop this bracing jump 'n bike action!<BR>Everyone's favorite mobile app "Bike Rider" - now available on PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Enjoy a refreshing new kind of jump 'n run action, riding bumpy roads, crossing deep valleys and jumping over walls on your bike. Challenge stages all over the globe in the "WORLD TOUR" mode or see how far you can go in the endless "GRAND PRIX" mode. Use a variety of items that e.g. speed you up and make use of special gimmicks like giant whirlwinds on your way through the stages of the world! Furthermore, the PS　Store version holds an exclusive WORLD TOUR extra stage for you to unlock ? if you manage to collect enough coins!<BR><BR>Once you pedal, you'll never want to stop! Try out a new kind of jump 'n run action! <BR><BR>Package size: 57 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Start to pedal and you'll never want to stop this bracing jump 'n bike action!<BR>Everyone's favorite mobile app "Bike Rider" - now available on PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Enjoy a refreshing new kind of jump 'n run action, riding bumpy roads, crossing deep valleys and jumping over walls on your bike. Challenge stages all over the globe in the "WORLD TOUR" mode or see how far you can go in the endless "GRAND PRIX" mode. Use a variety of items that e.g. speed you up and make use of special gimmicks like giant whirlwinds on your way through the stages of the world! Furthermore, the PS　Store version holds an exclusive "WORLD TOUR" extra stage for you to unlock ? if you manage to collect enough coins!<BR><BR>Once you pedal, you'll never want to stop! Try out a new kind of jump 'n run action! <BR><BR>Package size: 57 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Comience a pedalear y nunca querra detener la accion bike n este salto refuerzos '!<BR>Favorito de aplicaciones moviles "Bike Rider" de todo el mundo - ya esta disponible en PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Disfrute de un nuevo tipo de restauracion de la accion n jump 'run, equitacion caminos llenos de baches, cruzando valles profundos y saltando por encima de las paredes de su bicicleta. Etapas reto de todo el mundo en el modo WORLD TOUR o ver que tan lejos puede ir en el modo sin fin GRAND PRIX. Usar una variedad de articulos que, por ejemplo, que acelerar y hacer uso de trucos especiales como torbellinos gigantes en su camino a traves de los escenarios del mundo! Por otra parte, la version de PS Store tiene un exclusivo WORLD TOUR etapa extra para desbloquear? <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 57 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA["Ryhdy polkemaan ja et koskaan halua lopettaa pelaamasta tätä hyppyjen ja pyöräilyn täyttämää peliä!<BR>Jokaisen suosikkimobiilisovellus, Bike Rider, on nyt saatavissa PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Nauti tuoreesta pyöräsi kanssa hyppytoiminnasta, kuoppaisesta maastosta, syvien laaksojen ylittämisestä ja muurien yli hyppimisestä. WORLD TOUR -tilasta löytyy haastavia kenttiä ympäri maailman, mutta voit myös kokeilla rajojasi loputtomassa GRAND PRIX -tilassa. Käytä erilaisia esineitä, jotka voivat mm. nopeuttaa sinua, ja erityistemppuja, kuten valtavia pyörteitä, kun ajat läpi maailman kenttien! Tämän lisäksi PS Storen versio sisältää rajoitetun WORLD TOUR -lisäkentän avattavaksesi, jos vain pystyt keräämään tarpeeksi monta kolikkoa!<BR><BR>Kun ryhdyt polkemaan, et halua lopettaa! Kokeile upouutta hyppytoim <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 57 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Découvrez un nouveau genre de jeu d'action de saut et de course, en enfourchant votre vélo sur des routes bosselées, en traversant des vallées profondes et en évitant tous les obstacles. Parcourez le monde pour être le champion du mode WORLD TOUR, ou améliorez le meilleur score dans le mode sans fin GRAND PRIX pour voir jusqu'où vous pouvez aller. Vous pouvez utiliser de nombreux objets d'amélioration comme le "Air Ride" et profiter d'astuces comme les tourbillons géants à travers les niveaux ! Saurez-vous collecter toutes les pièces d'or et débloquer les niveaux de bonus spéciaux ? <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 57 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Découvrez un nouveau genre de jeu d'action de saut et de course, en enfourchant votre vélo sur des routes bosselées, en traversant des vallées profondes et en évitant tous les obstacles. Parcourez le monde pour être le champion du mode WORLD TOUR, ou améliorez le meilleur score dans le mode sans fin GRAND PRIX pour voir jusqu'où vous pouvez aller. Vous pouvez utiliser de nombreux objets d'amélioration comme le "Air Ride" et profiter d'astuces comme les tourbillons géants à travers les niveaux ! Saurez-vous collecter toutes les pièces d'or et débloquer les niveaux de bonus spéciaux ? <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 57 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Iniziare a pedalare e non vorrete mai smettere n azione questo salto tonificante 'bici!<BR>Preferito app mobile "ciclista" di ognuno - ora disponibile su PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Godere di un nuovo tipo di rinfresco di n azione run jump ', cavalcando strade molto sconnesse, attraversando valli profonde e saltando muri sulla bicicletta. Fasi Sfide in tutto il mondo nella modalita "WORLD TOUR" o vedere quanto lontano si puo andare in modalita infinita "GRAND PRIX". Utilizzare una varieta di elementi che ad esempio accelerare in su e fare uso di espedienti speciali come vortici giganti sulla tua strada attraverso gli stadi di tutto il mondo! Inoltre, la versione PS Store detiene un esclusivo "WORLD TOUR" tappa in piu per voi per sbloccare? se si riesce a raccogliere le monete sufficienti! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 57 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA["Ta tråpedalene fatt og ikke gi slipp på dette actionfylte sykkelhopp-spillet.<BR>Alles favoritt-app ""Bike Rider"" er nå tilgjengelig på PlayStation®Mobile.<BR><BR>prøv deg på et litt annerledes løp og hopp-spill, kjør på humpete veier, kom deg gjennom dype daler og hopp over vegger med sykkelen din. Med utfordringsnivåer fra over hele verden i ""WORLD TOUR""-modus, eller se hvor langt du holder ut i ""GRAND PRIX""-modus. Bruk en rekke gjenstander som hjelder deg med å få fart på sakene, og bruk spesielle evner som f.eks. tornadoer for å komme deg gjennom nivåene. Du får også et ekstra skjult nivå som du kan låse opp i WORLD TOUR, i versjonen fra Ps Store. Om du klarer å samle nok mynter vel å merke.<BR><BR>Begynn å sykle og du vil ikke gi slipp. Prøv en ny type hopp og løp-spill." <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 57 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Begin te trappen en je zult nooit willen deze schoren jump 'n fiets actie te stoppen!<BR>Ieders favoriete mobiele app "Ruiter van de Fiets" - nu beschikbaar op PlayStation ® Mobile!<BR><BR>Geniet van een verfrissend nieuw soort jump 'n run actie, paardrijden hobbelige wegen, het oversteken van diepe dalen en springen over muren op je fiets. Challenge stadia over de hele wereld in de "World Tour"-modus of zie hoe ver je kunt gaan in de eindeloze "GRAND PRIX" modus. Gebruik een verscheidenheid aan items die bijv. versnelt u en gebruik maken van speciale gimmicks als reusachtige wervelwinden op uw weg door de fasen van de wereld! Bovendien is de PS Store-versie heeft een exclusieve "World Tour" extra podium voor u om te ontgrendelen? als het je lukt om genoeg munten te verzamelen!<BR><BR>Zodra je pedaal, zu <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 57 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA["När du börjat trampa vill du aldrig sluta i det här läckra cykelhopp-spelet!<BR>Allas favorit-mobilapp ""Bike Rider"" - finns nu på PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Njut av en fräsch hopp-och-spring-action, där du cyklar på guppiga vägar, korsar djupa dalar och hoppar över murar på din cykel. Ta dig an banor från hela världen i ""WORLD TOUR""-läget eller se hur långt du kan komma i det ändlösa""GRAND PRIX""-läget. Använd en massa olika föremål som t.ex. ger dig högre fart och använd speciella effekter som jättelika virvelvindar på väg genom världens banor! Dessutom har PS　Store-versionen en exklusiv extrabana att låsa upp till WORLD TOUR, om du lyckas samla ihop tillräckligt med mynt!<BR><BR>När du börjat trampa vill du aldrig sluta! Pröva en ny sorts hopp-o-spring-action!" <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 57 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska<BR><BR>(C)LIRENEOSOFT x (C)Spicysoft Corporation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
