<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00149_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>46057872</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Brain spil for hele familien. Spillet handler om at svare rigtigt på regneoperationer så hurtigt som muligt. Spillet starter let, med simple operationer, og det bliver mere udfordrende med tiden. <BR><BR>Er du god til matematik? Virkelig? Nu kan du vise det til verden! I dette helt vanedannende spil du nødt til at gøre beløb, subtraktioner, multiplikationer og divisioner så hurtigt som du kan. Træne din hjerne samtidig have det sjovt! <BR><BR>Spillet har to tilstande: <BR>- Arcade mode: Vanskeligheden stiger progressivt, først med nemme summer, derefter subtractions, derefter multiplikationer og endelig divisioner. <BR>- Master-mode: Enhver af de tidligere operationer med tilfældig vanskeligheder. Gælder for kun menneskelige regnemaskiner! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 44 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Spansk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Gehirn-Spiel für die ganze Familie. Das Spiel wird über die korrekte Beantwortung Rechenoperationen so schnell wie möglich. Das Spiel beginnt einfach, mit einfachen Operationen, und es wird mit der Zeit immer anspruchsvoller. <BR><BR>Sind Sie gut in Mathe? Wirklich? Jetzt können Sie es der Welt zeigen! In diesem völlig süchtig Spiel müssen Sie Summen, Subtraktionen, Multiplikationen und Divisionen, so schnell wie möglich zu tun. Trainieren Sie Ihren Verstand und dabei Spaß haben! <BR><BR>Das Spiel hat zwei Modi: <BR>- Arcade-Modus: Die Schwierigkeit erhöht sich schrittweise, zunächst mit einfachen Summen, dann Subtraktionen, Multiplikationen und schließlich dann Divisionen. <BR>- Master-Modus: Jede der vorherigen Operationen mit zufälligen Schwierigkeiten. Gültig für nur ein Mensch Rechner! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 44 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Brain game for all the family. The game is about correctly answering arithmetic operations as fast as possible. The game starts easy, with simple operations, and it becomes more challenging over time.<BR><BR>Are you good at maths? Really? Now you can demonstrate it to the world! In this completely addicting game you have to do sums, subtractions, multiplications and divisions as fast as you can. Train your mind while having fun!<BR><BR>The game has two modes: <BR>- Arcade mode: The difficulty increases progressively, first with easy sums, then subtractions, then multiplications and finally divisions.<BR>- Master mode: Any of the previous operations with random difficulty. Valid for human calculators only! <BR><BR>Package size: 44 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Brain game for all the family. The game is about correctly answering arithmetic operations as fast as possible. The game starts easy, with simple operations, and it becomes more challenging over time.<BR><BR>Are you good at maths? Really? Now you can demonstrate it to the world! In this completely addicting game you have to do sums, subtractions, multiplications and divisions as fast as you can. Train your mind while having fun!<BR><BR>The game has two modes: <BR>- Arcade mode: The difficulty increases progressively, first with easy sums, then subtractions, then multiplications and finally divisions.<BR>- Master mode: Any of the previous operations with random difficulty. Valid for human calculators only! <BR><BR>Package size: 44 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Brain game for all the family. The game is about correctly answering arithmetic operations as fast as possible. The game starts easy, with simple operations, and it becomes more challenging over time.<BR><BR>Are you good at maths? Really? Now you can demonstrate it to the world! In this completely addicting game you have to do sums, subtractions, multiplications and divisions as fast as you can. Train your mind while having fun!<BR><BR>The game has two modes: <BR>- Arcade mode: The difficulty increases progressively, first with easy sums, then subtractions, then multiplications and finally divisions.<BR>- Master mode: Any of the previous operations with random difficulty. Valid for human calculators only! <BR><BR>Package size: 44 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Brain game for all the family. The game is about correctly answering arithmetic operations as fast as possible. The game starts easy, with simple operations, and it becomes more challenging over time.<BR><BR>Are you good at maths? Really? Now you can demonstrate it to the world! In this completely addicting game you have to do sums, subtractions, multiplications and divisions as fast as you can. Train your mind while having fun!<BR><BR>The game has two modes: <BR>- Arcade mode: The difficulty increases progressively, first with easy sums, then subtractions, then multiplications and finally divisions.<BR>- Master mode: Any of the previous operations with random difficulty. Valid for human calculators only! <BR><BR>Package size: 44 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Juego de Inteligencia para toda la familia. El juego es responder correctamente acerca de las operaciones aritméticas tan rápido como sea posible. El juego empieza fácil, con operaciones sencillas, y se hace más difícil con el tiempo.<BR><BR>¿Eres bueno en matemáticas? ¿En serio? Ahora usted puede mostrarlo al mundo! En este juego totalmente adictivo que tiene que hacer sumas, restas, multiplicaciones y divisiones tan rápido como puedas. Entrena tu mente mientras te diviertes!<BR><BR>El juego tiene dos modos:<BR>- Modo Arcade: La dificultad aumenta progresivamente, primero con sumas sencillas, luego restas, multiplicaciones y luego finalmente divisiones.<BR>- Modo Maestro: cualquiera de las operaciones anteriores con dificultad al azar. Válido sólo para las calculadoras humanas! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 44 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Aivot peli koko perheelle.Peli on noin oikein vastaamalla laskutoimituksia niin nopeasti kuin mahdollista.Peli alkaa helppoa, yksinkertaisilla toimenpiteillä, ja se muuttuu haastavammaksi ajan. <BR><BR>Oletko hyvä matematiikassa? Oikeasti? Nyt voit osoittaa sen maailmalle! Tässä täysin addicting peli sinun täytyy tehdä summia, subtractions kertolaskua ja toimialojen niin nopeasti kuin pystyt. Kouluttaa mielesi samalla hauskaa! <BR><BR>Pelissä on kaksi tilaa: <BR>- Arcade-tila: vaikeus kasvaa progressiivisesti, ensin helppo summia, niin subtractions sitten kertolaskua ja lopulta divisioonaan. <BR>- Master-tila: Mikään edellisen toiminnan satunnaisella vaikeuksia. Voimassa ihmisen laskimet vain! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 44 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti/Espanja<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Jeu de cerveau pour toute la famille. Le jeu est sur ​​répondre correctement à des opérations arithmétiques aussi vite que possible. Le jeu commence facile, avec des opérations simples, et il devient plus difficile au fil du temps. <BR><BR>Etes-vous bon en maths? Vraiment? Maintenant, vous pouvez démontrer au monde! Dans ce jeu complètement addictif vous avez à faire des montants, des soustractions, des multiplications et des divisions aussi vite que vous le pouvez. Entraînez votre esprit tout en s'amusant! <BR><BR>Le jeu a deux modes: <BR>- Mode Arcade: La difficulté augmente progressivement, d'abord avec des sommes faciles, puis soustractions, multiplications et puis enfin divisions. <BR>- Mode Master: Toute les opérations précédentes avec difficulté aléatoire. Valable pour seulement calculatrices humains <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 44 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Brain gioco per tutta la famiglia. Il gioco è di circa rispondendo correttamente le operazioni aritmetiche più velocemente possibile. Il gioco inizia facile, con semplici operazioni, e diventa più difficile nel tempo. <BR><BR>Sei bravo in matematica? Davvero? Ora puoi dimostrare al mondo! In questo gioco completamente coinvolgente che dovete fare somme, sottrazioni, moltiplicazioni e divisioni più velocemente possibile. Allena la tua mente divertendosi! <BR><BR>Il gioco ha due modalità: <BR>- Modalità Arcade: La difficoltà aumenta progressivamente, in primo luogo con le somme facile, allora sottrazioni, moltiplicazioni e poi infine le divisioni. <BR>- Modalità Master: Una delle operazioni precedenti con difficoltà casuale. Valido solo per calcolatrici umane! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 44 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[すべての家族のための頭脳ゲーム。ゲームは約正しくできるだけ速く算術演算に答えている。ゲームは簡単な操作で、簡単に開始し、それが時間の経過とともにより困難になる。 <BR><BR>あなたは数学が得意ですか？本当に？今、あなたは世界にそれを証明することができます！この完全に中毒ゲームでは、早くすることができますように合計、減算、乗算と除算を行う必要があります。楽しみながらあなたの心を訓練する！ <BR><BR>ゲームは2つのモードがあります。 <BR>- アーケードモード：難易度は最初に簡単にして、次に合計、減算、乗算、最終的には部門と、徐々に増加します。 <BR>- マスタモード：ランダムな難しさと、前の操作のいずれか。人間だけ電卓の有効！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 44 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Brain spill for hele familien. Spillet handler om å svare riktig på aritmetiske operasjoner så fort som mulig. Spillet starter enkelt, med enkle operasjoner, og det blir mer utfordrende over tid. <BR><BR>Er du god i matte? Virkelig? Nå kan du vise det til verden! I dette helt addicting spillet må du gjøre summer, subtractions, multiplikasjon og divisjon så fort du kan. Tren hjernen din mens du har det gøy! <BR><BR>Spillet har to moduser: <BR>- Arcade mode: Vanskeligheten øker gradvis, først med enkle summer, deretter subtractions, så multiplikasjon og til slutt divisjoner. <BR>- Master-modus: Noen av de tidligere operasjoner med tilfeldig vanskelighetsgrad. Gyldig for menneskelige kalkulatorer bare! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 44 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Spansk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Brain spel voor het hele gezin. Het spel is over de juiste beantwoording van rekenkundige bewerkingen zo snel mogelijk. Het spel begint eenvoudig, met eenvoudige handelingen, en het wordt meer uitdagende tijd. <BR><BR>Ben je goed in wiskunde? Echt waar? Nu kunt u het laten zien aan de wereld! In deze volledig verslavend spel moet je sommen, aftrekken, vermenigvuldigen en delen doen zo snel als je kunt. Train je geest terwijl je plezier! <BR><BR>Het spel heeft twee modi: <BR>- Arcade mode: De moeilijkheid stijgt geleidelijk, eerst met makkelijke sommen, dan aftrekken, dan vermenigvuldigingen en tenslotte divisies. <BR>- Master mode: Elk van de voorgaande handelingen met willekeurige moeilijkheidsgraad. Alleen geldig voor de menselijke rekenmachines! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 44 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels/Spaans<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Brain spel för hela familjen. Spelet handlar om att korrekt besvara aritmetiska operationer så fort som möjligt. Spelet börjar enkelt, med enkla åtgärder, och det blir svårare med tiden. <BR><BR>Är du bra på matte? Verkligen? Nu kan du visa det för världen! I det här helt beroendeframkallande spel du måste göra belopp, subtraktioner, multiplikationer och divisioner så fort du kan. Träna din hjärna och samtidigt ha roligt! <BR><BR>Spelet har två lägen: <BR>- Arcade mode: Svårigheten ökar successivt, först med enkla summor, sedan subtraktioner, sedan multiplikationer och slutligen divisioner. <BR>- Master-läget: Någon av tidigare verksamhet med slumpvis svårigheter. Gäller endast mänskliga räknare! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 44 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska/Spanska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 PlungeInteractive SL. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Educational"/><genre value="Games:Unique"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
