<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00278_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>139437840</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="ja"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Ny genre turbaseret robot kamp<BR>For sagen ødelæggelse retfærdighed finder fjenden!<BR><BR>ADVARSEL: Dette spil vil blive dræbt på stedet i en smule af fejlvurdering (for Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ Spil Oversigt ◇<BR>Wingman og udslettelse, opsamling, vil jeg gennemføre missionen af basen ødelæggelse<BR>System funktioner, der vises eneste fjende, der har indgået synsfeltet<BR>Der er en spænding for at beskytte mod fjenden fra ser og ikke steder.<BR>Vær mastering så forskellige fly, bevæbnet leveres<BR>Vejen forude bagfra finder fjenden til at angribe sejr <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 133 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>New Genre rundenbasiertes Kampfroboter<BR>Für die Zerstörung Fall Gerechtigkeit findet den Feind!<BR><BR>WARNUNG: Dieses Spiel wird sofort in einem kleinen Fehleinschätzung der getötet werden (für Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ ◇ Spielüberblick<BR>Wingman und Vernichtung, Erfassung, werde ich den Auftrag des Grund Zerstörung zu erreichen<BR>System-Funktionen, die nur angezeigt werden, Feind, der in den Sichtbereich eingetreten ist<BR>Es gibt eine Spannung gegen feindliche von den Blicken und nicht die Orte zu bewachen.<BR>Bitte Mastering so vielfältig, Flugzeuge, bewaffnete werden zur Verfügung gestellt<BR>Straße voran von hinten findet den Feind anzugreifen Sieg <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 133 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>New genre turn-based robot battle<BR>For the destruction case justice finds the enemy!<BR><BR>WARNING: This game will be killed instantly in a little of misjudgment (for Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ Game Overview ◇<BR>Wingman and annihilation, capture, I will achieve the mission of the base destruction<BR>System features that are displayed only enemy that has entered into the field of vision<BR>There is a tension to guard against enemy from the looks and not places.<BR>Please be mastering so diverse aircraft, armed are provided<BR>Road ahead from behind finds the enemy to assault victory <BR><BR>Package size: 133 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Nueva género batalla robot basado en turnos<BR>Para la justicia caso de destrucción se encuentra el enemigo!<BR><BR>ADVERTENCIA: Este juego se murió instantáneamente en un poco de error de juicio (por Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ ◇ Resumen del juego<BR>Wingman y aniquilación, capturar, voy a lograr la misión de la destrucción de base<BR>Las características del sistema que se muestran único enemigo que ha entrado en el campo de visión<BR>Hay una tensión para proteger contra enemigo de las miradas y no lugares.<BR>Por favor, ser el dominio de la aeronave de manera diversa, están dentro de armada<BR>Camino por delante por detrás se encuentra el enemigo a la victoria asalto <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 133 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Uusi genre vuoropohjainen robotti taistelu<BR>Hävittämisestä tapauksessa tuomioistuin toteaa vihollinen!<BR><BR>VAROITUS: Tämä peli on kuollut hetkessä hieman virhearvioinnilla (for Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ Game yleiskatsaus ◇<BR>Wingman ja tuhoaminen, kaapata, aion saavuttaa tehtävän pohja tuhoa<BR>Järjestelmän ominaisuuksia, jotka näkyvät vain vihollinen, joka on tehnyt näkökentän<BR>On jännitystä suojautua vihollisen näyttää eikä paikkoja.<BR>Ole masterointi niin erilaisia lentokoneita, aseellinen tarjotaan<BR>Tiestä takaa löytää vihollinen hyökkäys voittoon <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 133 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Genre nouveau robot de combat au tour par tour<BR>Pour le cas de la destruction de la justice trouve l'ennemi!<BR><BR>ATTENTION: Ce jeu sera tué sur le coup dans une petite erreur de jugement (pour Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ ◇ Présentation du jeu<BR>Wingman et l'anéantissement, la capture, je vais réaliser la mission de la destruction de base<BR>Les caractéristiques du système qui sont affichés seul ennemi qui a conclu le champ de vision<BR>Il ya une tension pour se prémunir contre l'ennemi de l'apparence et non les lieux.<BR>Se il vous plaît être maîtriser aéronef de façon diverse, armés sont prévus<BR>Route de derrière trouve l'ennemi à la victoire d'assaut <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 133 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Nuovo genere di battaglia robot a turni<BR>Per la giustizia caso distruzione trova il nemico!<BR><BR>ATTENZIONE: Questo gioco sarà ucciso all'istante in un po 'di errore di valutazione (per Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ Gioco Panoramica ◇<BR>Wingman e annientamento, la cattura, io realizzare la missione della distruzione di base<BR>Caratteristiche del sistema che vengono visualizzate solo nemico che è entrata nel campo visivo<BR>C'è una tensione in guardia contro nemici dagli sguardi e non luoghi.<BR>Si prega di essere mastering aerei così diversi, armati sono forniti<BR>Strada avanti da dietro trova il nemico alla vittoria assalto <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 133 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>新ジャンル　ターン制ロボットバトル<BR>敵を見つけ出し破壊せよ　正義のために！<BR><BR>警告：このゲームはちょっとの判断ミスで即死します（ヘビーゲーマ向け）<BR><BR>　◇　ゲーム概要　◇<BR>　僚機と殲滅、捕獲、基地破壊の任務を達成します<BR>　特徴は視界内に入った敵のみ表示されるシステム<BR>　見えていない個所からの敵を警戒する緊張感があります。<BR>　多様な機体、武装が用意されているので使いこなしてください<BR>　先に敵を見つけ出し背後から強襲が勝利への道 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 133 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Ny sjanger turbasert robot kamp<BR>For ødeleggelse saken rettferdighet finner fienden!<BR><BR>ADVARSEL: Dette spillet vil bli drept umiddelbart i litt av feilvurdering (for Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ Spill Oversikt ◇<BR>Wingman og utslettelse, fange, vil jeg klare oppdraget basen ødeleggelse<BR>Systemfunksjoner som vises eneste fiende som har inngått synsfeltet<BR>Det er en spenning for å beskytte mot fienden fra utseende og ikke steder.<BR>Vær mestre så mangfoldig fly, væpnet er gitt<BR>Veien videre fra bak finner fienden til overgrep seier <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 133 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Nieuw genre turn-based robot strijd<BR>Voor de vernietiging geval rechtvaardigheid vindt de vijand!<BR><BR>WAARSCHUWING: Dit spel zal direct worden gedood in een beetje van miskenning (voor Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ Game Overzicht ◇<BR>Wingman en vernietiging, vastleggen, zal ik de missie van de basis vernietiging te bereiken<BR>Systeemfuncties die worden weergegeven enige vijand die in het gezichtsveld is aangegaan<BR>Er is een spanningsveld te beschermen tegen de vijand van de looks en niet plaatsen.<BR>Wees mastering zo divers vliegtuig, bewapend zijn aanwezig<BR>Weg te gaan van achter vindt de vijand aan te vallen overwinning <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 133 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Nowy gatunek turowa walka robota<BR>Dla przypadku zniszczenia sprawiedliwości znajdzie wroga!<BR><BR>UWAGA: Ta gra będzie zabity tam w trochę błędnej oceny sytuacji (na Hebigema)<BR><BR>Przegląd gier ◇ ◇<BR>Skrzydłowym i unicestwienie, chwytania, będę osiągnąć misji podstawowej zniszczenia<BR>Funkcje systemowe, które są wyświetlane tylko wrogiem, który wszedł w polu widzenia<BR>Istnieje napięcie, aby ustrzec się przed wrogiem od spojrzeń i nie miejsc.<BR>Prosimy o opanowanie tak różnorodny samolot, uzbrojony są<BR>Droga od tyłu znajdzie wroga szturmowym zwycięstwa <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 133 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Japoński<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Ny genre tur-baserade robot striden<BR>För förstörelsen fallet rättvisan finner fienden!<BR><BR>VARNING: Det här spelet kommer att dödas omedelbart i lite av felbedömning (för Hebigema)<BR><BR>◇ Spelöversikt ◇<BR>Wingman och förintelse, fånga, kommer jag få uppdraget av basen förstörelse<BR>Systemfunktioner som visas endast fiende som har ingått i synfältet<BR>Det finns en spänning för att skydda mot fienden från ser och inte platser.<BR>Var bemästra så olika flygplan, är beväpnade tillhandahålls<BR>Väg framåt bakifrån finner fienden till misshandel seger <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 133 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>teasoft<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Strategy"/><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
