<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00276_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>7673744</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Here comes the AWESOME arcade shooter WING WARRIORS. This is an incredible story about three great Wing Warriors (Kai, Gaia and Raiden) who are in fight with the Black Emperor. Enjoy this game with successful air combats. Top quality graphics and sound. Hordes of enemies and different weapons. 3 long levels, 3 deadly bosses. Three characters following epic storylines. Touch your screen, select your character and begin the wonderful combats of WING WARRIORS. Prepare for battle! <BR><BR>Package size: 7494 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright © 2015 Kitmaker Entertainment S.A. All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Aquí llega el impresionante arcade de disparos WING WARRIORS. Esta es la increíble historia sobre tres guerreros alados Kai, Gaia y Raiden) que luchan contra el malvado Emperador Negro. Disfruta de este juego con sucesivas batallas aéreas. Gráficos y sonido de alta calidad. Hordas de enemigos y diferentes armas. Tres largas fases con sus tres mortales jefes. Tres personajes a elegir con su propia historia épica. Usa la pantalla táctil o controles físicos, selecciona tu personaje y  comienza el combate con WING WARRIORS. ¡Prepárate para la batalla! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 7494 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright © 2015 Kitmaker Entertainment S.A. All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>素晴らしい弾幕ゲームのウィング・ウォリアーズが完成した！暗黒の皇帝に挑む、翼をもった三人（カイ・ガイア・ライデン）の勇敢な戦士の伝説。空中戦を楽めるクォリティーの高いグラフィックとサウンド。目まぐるしく現れる敵に対戦しろ。三つの長いステージに三つの恐ろしいボス。三人の戦士にはそれぞれのストーリーがある。スクリーンをタッチして好きな戦士を選んで、ウィング・ウォリアーズの壮大な戦いを始めよう。準備せよ！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 7494 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright © 2015 Kitmaker Entertainment S.A. All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Shooter"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Language.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Language.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
