<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00327_00">

  <appVersion>1.20</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>1067249408</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>I en verden hvor mennesker og Youkai lever i sameksistens, kommer Kaede Yamabuki, den indbildske andetårs tempelnonne-aspirant, i klemme ved starten af vinterferien. Et par underlige briller, fundet i skoven, fører hende til sin hidtil hårdeste udfordring: at blive forelsket.<BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode, er komplet 3D RPG/Adventurespil, med alle stemmer på japansk, og med muligheden for japanske eller engelske undertekster.<BR><BR>* Engelsk support er tilgængelig via e-mail og twitter. Besøg vores webside for at få mere at vide. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 1018 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>In einer Welt in der Menschen und Youkai friedlich zusammen leben findet sich die dreiste Kaede Yamabuki, die im zweiten Jahr des Noviziats bei den Schrein-Mägden ist, zu Beginn der Winterferien in der Klemme. Eine seltsame Brille, die im Wald gefunden wurde, führt sie zu ihrer härtesten Herausforderung: Sich zu verlieben.<BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode ist ein RPG/Adventure Game komplett in 3D mit vollständig japanischer Sprachausgabe und sowohl englischen als auch japanischen Untertiteln.<BR><BR>* Englischer Support steht über E-Mail und Twitter zur Verfügung. Besuche unsere Webseite für mehr Information. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 1018 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>In a world where humans and youkai coexist, uppity second year shrine maiden student Kaede Yamabuki finds herself in a pinch as the winter recess starts. A pair of strange glasses found in the woods leads her to her toughest challenge yet: falling in love. <BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode is a full 3D RPG/Adventure game, fully voiced in Japanese, with subtitles available in Japanese and English.<BR><BR>* English support is available via e-mail and twitter. Visit our webpage for more information. <BR><BR>Package size: 1018 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>En un mundo donde coexisten humanos y espíritus, las energética sacerdotisa Kaede se encuentra en aprietos tras comenzar las vacaciones de invierno. Un par de gafas que encuentra en el bosque la llevan a encontrar su mayor desafío: enamorarse.<BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode es un juego RPG/Aventura en 3D, completamente doblado al Japonés, con subtítulos disponibles en Japonés e Inglés.<BR><BR>* Hay soporte en inglés disponible para este juego, via correo electrónico y twitter. Visite nuestra página web para mayor información. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 1018 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Maailmassa, jossa ihmiset ja henget elävät yhdessä, koppava toisen vuoden nunnaoppilas Kaede Yamabuki löytää itsensä pinteestä talviloman alkaessa. Metsästä löytyneet oudot silmälasit johtavat hänet vaikean haasteen äärelle: hän rakastuu.<BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode on japaniksi puhuttu 3D RPG/seikkailupeli, joka on saatavilla ainoastaan japanin- ja englanninkielisillä tekstityksillä.<BR><BR>* Englanninkielinen tuki on saatavilla sähköpostin ja twitterin kautta. Viraille verkkosivuilla saadaksesi lisää tietoa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 1018 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Dans un monde où les humains et les Youkai cohabitent, Kaede Yamabuki, apprentie Miko de deuxième année débordante d'énergie, se retrouve dans le pétrain alors que les vacances d'hiver commencent. Une étrange paire de lunettes qu'elle a trouvée dans les bois la mène au défi le plus dûr qu'elle n'ait jamais affronté: tomber amoureuse.<BR><BR>"Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode" est un jeu d'aventure/RPG entièrement en 3D, doublé intégralement en japonais et disposant de sous-titres anglais ou japonais.<BR><BR>* Support en anglais disponible via e-mail et twitter. Visitez notre site web pour plus d'informations. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 1018 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>In un mondo in cui umani e youkai coesistono, all'inizio della pausa invernale, un'arrogante apprendista monaca del secondo anno, Kaede Yamabuki, finisce nei guai. Uno strano paio di occhiali trovati nel bosco la conduce ad affrontare la sfida più difficile: innamorarsi.<BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode è un RPG/Gioco d'avventura completamente in 3D, pieno di voci in giapponese, e con sottotitoli disponibili in giapponese ed inglese.<BR><BR>* Il supporto è disponibile in inglese per questo gioco, via email e Twitter. Visita il nostro sito per ulteriori informazioni. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 1018 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>ここは人間と動物、そして多種多彩な妖怪たちが共生する世界。<BR><BR>冬休みが始まった。妖ノ山巫女学校2年生である元気いっぱいの山吹楓は相変わらず学校でトラブルに巻き込まれている。<BR><BR>森に見つけられた不思議なメガネから、楓の最大の試練が始まる。<BR><BR>これは、楓が恋を知りそして失恋するまでの物語。<BR><BR>「巫女学校物語～楓編」は完全３Dフルボイス巫女みこADV・RPGゲームです。字幕は日本語と英語に設定することができます。<BR><BR>※　当作品のサポートはメールやtwitterにで行っております。詳細にはホームページを御覧ください。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 1018 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>I en verden hvor mennesker og youkai lever hånd i hånd - sitter den sprudlende alterpikestudenten Kaede Yamabuki i en knipe da vinterferien begynner. Et par rare briller som ble funnet i skogen, fører henne til det som blir hennes tøffeste utfordring: å bli forelsket.<BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode er et RPG/Eventyr-spill i 3D, med alle stemmer på japansk og undertekster tilgjengelig på japansk og engelsk.<BR><BR>* Engelsk støtte er tilgjengelig via e-post og twitter. Besøk nettstedet vårt for mer informasjon. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 1018 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>In een wereld waar mensen en youkai samenleven, komt de hooghartige tweedejaars leerling-tempelnon Kaede Yamabuki in de problemen als het winterreces begint. Een vreemde bril, die in het bos wordt gevonden, zorgt voor haar grootste uitdaging tot nu toe: verliefd worden. <BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode is een volledig 3D RPG-/Avonturen-game dat geheel in het Japans is gesproken. Er is ondertiteling beschikbaar in het Japans en het Engels.<BR><BR>* Engelse ondersteuning is via e-mail en Twitter beschikbaar. Bezoek onze website voor meer informatie. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 1018 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>W świecie, w którym współistnieją ludzie i youkai, zarozumiała studentka drugiego roku i kapłanka świątyni – Kaede Yamabuki – znajdzie się w opałach wraz z początkiem przerwy zimowej. Para dziwnych okularów znalezionych w lesie sprawi, że będzie musiała sprostać największemu jak dotąd wyzwaniu – zakochaniu.<BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode to pełna gra RPG/przygodowa 3D w japońskiej wersji językowej, z japońskimi i angielskimi napisami.<BR><BR>* Wsparcie po angielsku dostępne jest poprzez e-mail i twittera. Więcej informacji znajdziesz odwiedzając naszą stronę internetową. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 1018 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Japoński<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>I en värld där människor och youkai samexisterar befinner sig den stöddiga Kaede Yamabuki, andraårsstudent på tempelskolan, i en knipa när vinterterminen startar. Ett par mystiska glasögon hittades i skogen och leder henne till hennes tuffaste utmaning hittills: att bli kär. <BR><BR>Miko Gakkou Monogatari: Kaede Episode är ett fullt 3D RPG/äventyrsspel, med japanska röster överallt, med undertexter tillgängliga på japanska och engelska.<BR><BR>* Engelsk support finns tillgänglig via e-post och twitter. Besök vår webbsida för mer information. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 1018 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2015. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:RPG"/><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Language.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Language.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
