<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00269_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>232012688</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>År 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs), berømt højteknologisk virksomhed, en ny robot bliver testet, sit navn: IVE eller Intelligence Vainglory Explorer.<BR>De installationer af BEL bliver piratkopieret af dig, en freelance hacker hyret af regeringen til at undersøge dette selskab.<BR>Med ordene fra virksomheden blev IVE designet til at udforske planeter langt ud over de kendte grænser for universet, hvor mennesker ikke kan nå. Men de vigtigste Intelligence agenturer verden mistanke om, at er en løgn, og den virkelige skæbne denne næste generations bot er at angribe menneskeheden og erobre verden for ejeren af den onde firma: J.Phil, som ikke må være undervurdering, han vil forsøge at komme tilbage sin dyrebare ny skabelse til at opfylde hans dagsorden.<BR>Du er nødt til at stjæle bot og bringe d <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 222 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Jahr 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Unternehmen Labs), berühmte High-Tech-Unternehmen, ein neuer Roboter getestet wird, seinen Namen: IVE oder Intelligenz Vainglory Explorer.<BR>Die Installationen von BEL werden von Ihnen Raubkopien, ein freischaffender Hacker von der Regierung angeheuert, um diese Firma zu untersuchen.<BR>In Worten des Unternehmens, IVE wurde entwickelt, um Planeten weit über die bekannten Grenzen des Universums, wo die Menschen nicht erreichen können, zu erkunden. Aber die wichtigsten Nachrichtenagenturen der Welt vermuten, dass eine Lüge und das reale Schicksal dieses Next-Gen-Bot ist es, die Menschheit angreifen und erobern die Welt für den Besitzer des bösen Unternehmen: J.Phil, der nicht unterschätzt werden darf, er wird versuchen, wieder seine wertvolle neue Schöpfung auf seine Age <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 222 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Year 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs),famous high technology company,a new robot is being tested, its name: I.V.E., or Intelligence Vainglory Explorer.<BR>The installations of BEL are being pirated by you, a freelance hacker hired by the government to investigate this company.<BR>In words of the company, IVE was designed to explore planets far beyond the known limits of the universe, where humans can't reach. But the most important Intelligence Agencies of the world suspect that is a lie and the real destiny of this next-gen bot is to attack humanity and conquer the world for the owner of the evil company: J.Phil, who must not be underestimate, he will try getting back its precious new creation to fulfill his agenda.<BR>You have to steal the bot and bring it to the space station <BR><BR>Package size: 222 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Year 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs),famous high technology company,a new robot is being tested, its name: I.V.E., or Intelligence Vainglory Explorer.<BR>The installations of BEL are being pirated by you, a freelance hacker hired by the government to investigate this company.<BR>In words of the company, IVE was designed to explore planets far beyond the known limits of the universe, where humans can't reach. But the most important Intelligence Agencies of the world suspect that is a lie and the real destiny of this next-gen bot is to attack humanity and conquer the world for the owner of the evil company: J.Phil, who must not be underestimate, he will try getting back its precious new creation to fulfill his agenda.<BR>You have to steal the bot and bring it to the space station <BR><BR>Package size: 222 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Year 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs),famous high technology company,a new robot is being tested, its name: I.V.E., or Intelligence Vainglory Explorer.<BR>The installations of BEL are being pirated by you, a freelance hacker hired by the government to investigate this company.<BR>In words of the company, IVE was designed to explore planets far beyond the known limits of the universe, where humans can't reach. But the most important Intelligence Agencies of the world suspect that is a lie and the real destiny of this next-gen bot is to attack humanity and conquer the world for the owner of the evil company: J.Phil, who must not be underestimate, he will try getting back its precious new creation to fulfill his agenda.<BR>You have to steal the bot and bring it to the space station <BR><BR>Package size: 222 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Year 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs),famous high technology company,a new robot is being tested, its name: I.V.E., or Intelligence Vainglory Explorer.<BR>The installations of BEL are being pirated by you, a freelance hacker hired by the government to investigate this company.<BR>In words of the company, IVE was designed to explore planets far beyond the known limits of the universe, where humans can't reach. But the most important Intelligence Agencies of the world suspect that is a lie and the real destiny of this next-gen bot is to attack humanity and conquer the world for the owner of the evil company: J.Phil, who must not be underestimate, he will try getting back its precious new creation to fulfill his agenda.<BR>You have to steal the bot and bring it to the space station <BR><BR>Package size: 222 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Año 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs), famosa compañía de alta tecnología.Un nuevo robot está siendo probado, su nombre: IVE, o Inteligencia Vanagloria Exploradora.<BR>Las instalaciones de BEL están siendo pirateadas por tñi, un hacker independiente contratado por el gobierno para investigar esta empresa.<BR>En palabras de la compañía, IVE fue diseñado para explorar los planetas más allá de los límites conocidos del universo, donde los seres humanos no pueden alcanzar. Pero las agencias de inteligencia más importantes del mundo sospechan que es una mentira y el destino real de esta próxima generación-bot es para atacar a la humanidad y conquistar el mundo para el maligno dueño de BEL: J.Phil, que no debe ser subestimado,pues no intentará recuperar a su preciosa nueva creación <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 222 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Vuosi 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs), kuuluisa korkean teknologian yritys, uusi robotti testataan, sen nimi: IVE tai Intelligence turhan kunnian pyynnöstä Explorer.<BR>Asennukset BEL ovat laittomasti jonka te, freelance hakkeri palkkaama hallitusta tutkimaan tämän yrityksen.<BR>Vuonna sanoin yrityksen, IVE suunniteltiin tutkimaan planeettoja kauas tiedossa rajojen maailmankaikkeuden, jossa ihmiset eivät pääse. Mutta tärkein tiedusteluelinten maailman epäilty, joka on valhe, ja todellisen kohtalon tämän seuraavan sukupolven bot on hyökätä ihmiskuntaa ja valloittaa maailman omistajan pahan yrityksen: J.Phil, joka ei saa olla aliarvioida, hän yrittää saada takaisin sen arvokas uusi luomus täyttämään hänen asialistalla.<BR>Sinun täytyy varastaa bot ja tuo se avaruusaseman <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 222 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Année 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs), célèbre société de haute technologie, un nouveau robot est testé, son nom: IVE, ou Intelligence Vainglory Explorer.<BR>Les installations de BEL sont piratés par vous, un hacker indépendant embauché par le gouvernement pour enquêter sur cette société.<BR>Dans les mots de l'entreprise, IVE a été conçu pour explorer des planètes au-delà des limites connues de l'univers, où les humains ne peuvent pas atteindre. Mais les plus importantes agences de renseignement du suspect de monde qui est un mensonge et la véritable destinée de cette next-gen bot est d'attaquer l'humanité et conquérir le monde pour le propriétaire de l'entreprise mal: J.Phil, qui ne doit pas être sous-estimé, il va essayer de se remettre de sa nouvelle création précieuse pour remplir son <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 222 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Année 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs), célèbre société de haute technologie, un nouveau robot est testé, son nom: IVE, ou Intelligence Vainglory Explorer.<BR>Les installations de BEL sont piratés par vous, un hacker indépendant embauché par le gouvernement pour enquêter sur cette société.<BR>Dans les mots de l'entreprise, IVE a été conçu pour explorer des planètes au-delà des limites connues de l'univers, où les humains ne peuvent pas atteindre. Mais les plus importantes agences de renseignement du suspect de monde qui est un mensonge et la véritable destinée de cette next-gen bot est d'attaquer l'humanité et conquérir le monde pour le propriétaire de l'entreprise mal: J.Phil, qui ne doit pas être sous-estimé, il va essayer de se remettre de sa nouvelle création précieuse pour remplir son <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 222 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Anno 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs), famosa società ad alta tecnologia, un nuovo robot è stato testato, il suo nome: IVE, o Intelligenza Vainglory Explorer.<BR>Le installazioni di BEL vengono piratati da voi, un hacker indipendenti assunti dal governo per indagare su questa azienda.<BR>Nelle parole della società, IVE è stato progettato per esplorare pianeti ben oltre i limiti conosciuti dell'universo, dove gli esseri umani non possono raggiungere. Ma le agenzie di intelligence più importanti del sospetto mondo che è una bugia e il vero destino di questo next-gen è bot per attaccare l'umanità e conquistare il mondo per il proprietario della società malvagia: J.Phil, che non deve essere sottostimato, egli cercherà di tornare il suo prezioso nuova creazione per realizzare il suo ordine del g <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 222 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>年2043.Inside BEL新しいロボットがテストされている（ボットエンタープライズ研究所）、有名なハイテク企業、その名：IVE、または知能虚飾エクスプローラ。<BR>BELのインストールは、あなたによってこの会社を調査するために、政府に雇わフリーランスのハッカーを海賊版されています。<BR>同社の言葉では、IVEは、これまで人間が到達できない宇宙の既知の限界を超えて惑星を探索するように設計されました。しかし、嘘と、この次世代ロボットの実運命である世界の容疑者の中で最も重要な諜報機関は、人間を攻撃し、悪の会社の所有者のために世界を征服することです：J.Phil、過小評価であってはなりません、彼は彼の議題を満たすために、その貴重な新しい創造を取り戻す試みます。<BR>あなたはボットを盗み、宇宙ステーションにそれを持参する必要があり <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 222 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>År 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs), berømt høyteknologisk selskap, en ny robot blir testet, sitt navn: IVE, eller Intelligence forfengelighet Explorer.<BR>Installasjonene av BEL blir piratkopiert av deg, en freelance hacker ansatt av regjeringen å undersøke dette selskapet.<BR>I ord i selskapet, ble IVE designet for å utforske planeter langt utover de kjente grensene i universet, der mennesker ikke kan nå. Men de viktigste etterretningsorganisasjoner i verden mistenkte som er en løgn, og den virkelige skjebnen til dette neste generasjons bot er å angripe menneskeheten og erobre verden for eieren av den onde selskapet: J.Phil, som ikke må være undervurdere, han vil prøve å få tilbake sin dyre ny skapning å oppfylle sin agenda.<BR>Du må stjele bot og bringe den til romstasjonen <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 222 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Jaar 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs), beroemde high-tech bedrijf, een nieuwe robot wordt getest, zijn naam: IVE of Intelligence Vainglory Explorer.<BR>De installaties van de BEL worden piraterij door u, een freelance hacker ingehuurd door de overheid om dit bedrijf te onderzoeken.<BR>In de woorden van het bedrijf, werd IVE ontworpen om planeten te verkennen ver buiten de bekende grenzen van het universum, waar mensen niet kunnen bereiken. Maar het belangrijkste Intelligence Agencies van de wereld vermoeden dat is een leugen en de echte bestemming van deze next-gen bot is om de mensheid te vallen en de wereld te veroveren voor de eigenaar van het kwaad bedrijf: J.Phil, die niet onderschat mag worden, hij zal proberen terug te krijgen zijn kostbare nieuwe creatie op zijn agenda te vervullen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 222 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Rok 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Przedsiębiorstwo Labs), słynnej firmy wysokich technologii, nowa robota jest testowany, jego nazwa: IVE lub Intelligence próżność Explorer.<BR>Instalacje bel są pirackie przez Ciebie, freelance haker wynajęty przez rząd do zbadania tej firmy.<BR>W słowach firmy, IVE został zaprojektowany do odkrywania planet daleko poza znane granice wszechświata, gdzie ludzie nie mogą dotrzeć. Ale najważniejsze agencje wywiadowcze podejrzanego światowej, która jest kłamstwem i prawdziwe przeznaczenie tego Next-Gen bot jest zaatakować ludzkość i podbić świat dla właściciela firmy: J.Phil zła, które nie musi być zaniżona, będzie starał się z powrotem swój cenny nowe stworzenie spełnić jego agendy.<BR>Musisz ukraść bota i dostosowania go do stacji kosmicznej <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 222 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>År 2043.Inside BEL (Bot Enterprise Labs), berömd högteknologiskt företag, en ny robot testas, dess namn: IVE, eller intelligens högfärd Explorer.<BR>Installationerna av BEL håller piratkopierad av dig, en frilans hacker anlitats av regeringen att utreda detta företag.<BR>I ord av företaget, var IVE utformad för att utforska planeter långt bortom de kända gränserna för universum, där människor inte kan nå. Men de viktigaste underrättelseorgan i världen misstänker att är en lögn och den verkliga öde detta nästa generations bot är att angripa mänskligheten och erövra världen för ägaren av det onda företaget: J.Phil, som inte får vara underskattning, han kommer att försöka få tillbaka sin dyrbara nya skapelse att uppfylla sin agenda.<BR>Du måste stjäla bot och föra den till rymdstationen <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 222 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>xixgames<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Shooter"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_14.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_16.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
