<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00143_00">

  <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>66608928</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Buba er et hovedbrudsspil, hvor det handler om at samle alle frø i de forskellige baner. Banerne består af flisestier med indlagte forhindringer, som du skal få Buba til at gå hen over. Fliserne skifter farve, når Buba træder på dem, og Buba kan kun træde på fliser, der passer til hans aktive farve. Det handler om at tænke strategisk og bruge de magiske fliser, der giver dig mulighed for at ændre Bubas farve, så du kan komme rundt på stierne med så få træk som muligt. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 64 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Buba ist ein Puzzlespiel, bei dem es darauf ankommt, in jedem Level alle Samen einzusammeln. Steuere Buba über verschiedene Felder und bahne dir einen Weg um die Hindernisse! Die Felder ändern die Farbe, wenn Buba über sie läuft. Er kann nur über Felder seiner aktuellen Farbe laufen. Strategisches Denken ist gefragt! Dein Ziel besteht darin, das Level mit möglichst wenigen Zügen abzuschließen. Dafür stehen dir Zauberfelder zur Verfügung, mit denen du Bubas Farbe ändern kannst. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 64 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Buba is a puzzle game with the objective of collecting all the seeds available in each level. The levels consist of different paths of tiles that you, as Buba, walk over with certain constraints of course. Tiles change colour when Buba passes over them, and Buba can only walk on tiles that match his current colour. Strategically planning your moves and with the aid of magic tiles that let you change Buba’s colour, your aim is to chart your path with the least number of moves to progress in the game. <BR><BR>Package size: 64 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Buba is a puzzle game with the objective of collecting all the seeds available in each level. The levels consist of different paths of tiles that you, as Buba, walk over with certain constraints of course. Tiles change colour when Buba passes over them, and Buba can only walk on tiles that match his current colour. Strategically planning your moves and with the aid of magic tiles that let you change Buba’s colour, your aim is to chart your path with the least number of moves to progress in the game. <BR><BR>Package size: 64 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Buba is a puzzle game with the objective of collecting all the seeds available in each level. The levels consist of different paths of tiles that you, as Buba, walk over with certain constraints of course. Tiles change colour when Buba passes over them, and Buba can only walk on tiles that match his current colour. Strategically planning your moves and with the aid of magic tiles that let you change Buba’s colour, your aim is to chart your path with the least number of moves to progress in the game. <BR><BR>Package size: 64 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Buba is a puzzle game with the objective of collecting all the seeds available in each level. The levels consist of different paths of tiles that you, as Buba, walk over with certain constraints of course. Tiles change colour when Buba passes over them, and Buba can only walk on tiles that match his current colour. Strategically planning your moves and with the aid of magic tiles that let you change Buba’s colour, your aim is to chart your path with the least number of moves to progress in the game. <BR><BR>Package size: 64 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Buba es un juego de puzles ¬en el que controlas a un pequeño escarabajo que tiene que recorrer diferentes caminos para recoger todas las semillas del nivel. Aunque parezca fácil, no lo es tanto, ya que Buba solo puede pasar por las casillas que son de su mismo color. Además, estas cambian de color cuando pasa por ellas. Planea cuidadosamente tus movimientos con la ayuda de casillas mágicas que te permiten jugar con el color de Buba. El objetivo es abrirte paso en el menor número de movimientos para así poder avanzar en el juego. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 64 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Buba on pulmapeli, jossa on tavoitteena kerätä kaikki siemenet jokaisella tasolla. Tasot koostuvat erilaisista laattapoluista, joita pitkin Buba kulkee tietyin rajoituksin. Laattojen väri vaihtuu, kun Buba kulkee niiden yli, ja Buba voi kulkea vain laatoilla, joiden väri vastaa hänen senhetkistä väriään. Suunnittele siirtosi harkitusti ja käytä apunasi taikalaattoja, joiden avulla voit vaihtaa Buban väriä. Tavoitteenasi on löytää polku tason halki mahdollisimman vähillä siirroilla. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 64 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Buba est un jeu de puzzle dont le but est de récupérer toutes les graines de chaque niveau. Les niveaux sont formés de différents chemins de carreaux que vous, en tant que Buba, devez traverser en respectant, bien sûr, quelques contraintes. Les carreaux changent de couleur quand Buba passe dessus, et celui-ci peut uniquement avancer sur les carreaux qui correspondent à sa couleur actuelle. Prévoyez stratégiquement vos déplacements et, à l'aide des carreaux magiques qui changent la couleur de Buba, tracez votre chemin en faisant le moins de déplacements possible pour progresser dans le jeu. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 64 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Buba est un jeu de puzzle dont le but est de récupérer toutes les graines de chaque niveau. Les niveaux sont formés de différents chemins de carreaux que vous, en tant que Buba, devez traverser en respectant, bien sûr, quelques contraintes. Les carreaux changent de couleur quand Buba passe dessus, et celui-ci peut uniquement avancer sur les carreaux qui correspondent à sa couleur actuelle. Prévoyez stratégiquement vos déplacements et, à l'aide des carreaux magiques qui changent la couleur de Buba, tracez votre chemin en faisant le moins de déplacements possible pour progresser dans le jeu. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 64 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Buba è un rompicapo in cui devi raccogliere tutti i semi di un livello. Ciascun livello contiene delle caselle su cui Buba dovrà spostarsi facendo cambiar loro colore. Buba può spostarsi solo su quelle che hanno il suo stesso colore. Decidi con astuzia la tua mossa e sfrutta le caselle magiche per cambiare il colore di Buba. Riuscirai a completare il percorso con il minor numero di mosse? <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 64 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[Buba は、ステージ毎に落ちている種を全て集めてクリアしていくパズルゲームです。プレイヤーは主人公である小さな虫（Buba）を操って、一定のルールに従いつつ、各ステージに並べられたタイルの上を移動させることができます。Bubaが通過したタイルの色は変化し、Bubaはその時点での自分の羽と同じ色のタイルの上だけを歩くことが出来ます。プレイヤーの目的は、戦略的な移動で、時にはBubaの色を変化させるマジックタイルを使いながら、最短のルートを選ぶことです。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 64 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Buba er et puzzle-spill der du skal samle alle frøene på de ulike brettene. Brettene består av fliser som danner ulike veier som du, Buba, beveger deg på – men det er selvfølelig ikke alt. Flisene endrer farge når Buba går over dem, og han kan bare gå på fliser med samme farge som seg selv. Du må planlegge godt, tenke strategisk og bruke magiske fliser som lar deg endre Bubas farge. Målet er å finne veien som tar deg gjennom brettet på færrest mulig trekk. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 64 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Buba is een puzzelspel waarin je alle zaadjes in een level moet zien te verzamelen. Elk level bestaat uit verschillende tegelpaden waar jij als Buba overheen loopt. Er zijn natuurlijk beperkingen. De tegels veranderen van kleur terwijl Buba eroverheen loopt en Buba mag alleen op tegels gaan staan die dezelfde kleur hebben als hijzelf. Plan je zetten strategisch en gebruik magische tegels om Buba van kleur te laten veranderen. Je vordert in het spel door een pad uit te stippelen met zo min mogelijk zetten. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 64 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Buba är ett pusselspel där målet är att samla in alla frön på de olika nivåerna. Nivåerna består av utplacerade plattor som du – det vill säga Buba – kan gå på, dock med vissa begränsningar. Plattorna ändrar nämligen färg när Buba går över dem, och han kan bara gå över plattor som matchar hans nuvarande färg. Planera dina drag strategiskt, ta hjälp av magiska plattor som gör att du kan byta färg på Buba, och klara nivåerna på så få drag som möjligt. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 64 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>All Rights Reserved. Quirkat<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
