<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00154_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.20</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>38382064</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Dette spil er en aflytning typen skydespil. <BR>Flyt drift af en spiller kan ikke udføres. <BR>Lad os kæmpe med fire våben! <BR>Vælg våben godt efter fjendens art og afstand. <BR>Med et våben, kan en fjendes angreb blive skudt ned eller en fjendes angreb kan blokeres. <BR>Antallet af patroner har begrænsning på hvert våben. <BR>Mens udkig efter capture-metoden Alle 6-området venligst nyde dig selv. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 37 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Dieses Spiel ist ein Ballerspiel des Abfangens Typ.<BR>Es ist nicht möglich, der Bedienung des Spielers zu bewegen.<BR>Sie kämpfen durch Umschalten der Waffe von vier, um den Feind oder Situation entsprechen.<BR><BR>Und verschiedene Arten von Feinden, abhängig von der Entfernung, wählen Sie bitte die Waffe gut.<BR>Mit Waffe, können Sie entweder feindliche Angriffe erschossen, mit dem Angriff des Feindes stören.<BR><BR>Die Arme jeweils gibt eine Reihe von Kugeln, die verwendet werden können, bestimmt.<BR>Bitte genießen Sie alle 6 Bereich, während der Suche nach einem Capture-Methode. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 37 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[This game is an interception type shooting game. <BR>Move operation of a player cannot be performed. <BR>Let's fight with four weapons! <BR>Please choose a weapon well according to enemy's kind and distance. <BR>With a weapon, an enemy's attack can be shot down or an enemy's attack can be blocked. <BR>The number of cartridges has restriction at each weapon. <BR>While looking for the capture method   All the 6 area   Please enjoy yourself. <BR><BR>Package size: 37 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Este juego es un tipo de interceptación juego de disparos.<BR>Mueva la operación de un jugador no se puede realizar.<BR>Luchemos con cuatro armas!<BR>Por favor, elija un arma bien según su naturaleza y la distancia del enemigo.<BR>Con un arma, el ataque de un enemigo puede ser derribado o el ataque de un enemigo puede ser bloqueada.<BR>El número de cartuchos tiene restricción en cada arma.<BR>Mientras busca el método de captura Toda la zona 6 Por favor, disfrutar. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 37 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Tämä peli on ammunta peli torjuntahävittäjä tyyppiä. <BR>Se ei ole mahdollista siirtää soittimen toimintaa. <BR>Katsotaanpa kohdata aseita neljä lähestyy vihollinen! <BR><BR>Ja erilaisia ​​vihollisia, etäisyydestä riippuen, valitse aseen hyvin. <BR>Ase ja voit ammuttiin alas vihollisen hyökkäyksiä, häiritä hyökkäys vihollisen. <BR><BR>Kussakin ase, määrä luoteja, joita voidaan käyttää on päätetty. <BR>Ole hyvä ja nauti kaikkien kuuden alueen etsiessään kaappaustapaa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 37 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Ce jeu est un type d'interception jeu qui s'élance. <BR>Bougez l'opération d'un joueur ne peut pas être exécutée. <BR>Combattons avec quatre armes! <BR>S'il vous plaît choisissez bien une arme d'après le genre d'ennemi et distance. <BR>Avec une arme, l'attaque d'un ennemi peut être abattue ou l'attaque d'un ennemi peut être bloquée. <BR>Le nombre de cartouches a la restriction à chaque arme. <BR>En cherchant la méthode de la capture Toute la 6 région Veut amusez-vous. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 37 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Questo gioco è un tipo di intercettazione gioco di tiro.<BR>Spostare il funzionamento di un giocatore non può essere eseguita.<BR>Combattiamo con quattro armi!<BR>Si prega di scegliere un'arma bene secondo tipo e la distanza del nemico.<BR>Con un arma, l'attacco di un nemico può essere abbattuto o l'attacco di un nemico può essere bloccata.<BR>Il numero di cartucce ha restrizione ad ogni arma.<BR>Mentre cerca il metodo di catturare tutta l'area 6 Si prega di divertirsi. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 37 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このゲームは、迎撃タイプのシューティングゲームです。<BR>プレイヤの移動操作はできません。<BR>迫りくる敵を ４つの武器で 立ち向かいましょう！<BR><BR>敵の種類や、距離に応じて、上手く武器を選択してください。<BR>武器によって、敵の攻撃を撃ち落したり、敵の攻撃を妨害することができます。<BR><BR>それぞれの武器には、使える弾数がきまっています。<BR>攻略方法を探しながら 全6エリアを お楽しみください。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 37 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Dette spillet er en avskjæring typen skytespill. <BR>Flytt drift av en spiller kan ikke utføres. <BR>La oss kjempe med fire våpen! <BR>Vennligst velg et våpen godt i henhold til fiendens slag og distanse. <BR>Med et våpen, kan fiendens angrep bli skutt ned eller fiendens angrep kan bli blokkert. <BR>Antallet av kassetter har begrensning på hvert våpen. <BR>Mens jakt etter fangst metode Alle seks området Vennligst nyte deg selv. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 37 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Dit spel is een soort onderschepping schietspel. <BR>Move exploitatie van een speler kan niet worden uitgevoerd. <BR>Laten we vechten met vier wapens! <BR>Kies een wapen goed volgens type en afstand vijand. <BR>Met een wapen, kan de aanval van een vijand te worden neergeschoten of aanvallen van een vijand kan worden geblokkeerd. <BR>Het aantal cartridges heeft beperkingen bij elk wapen. <BR>Op zoek naar de capture methode Alle 6 gebied Gelieve genieten. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 37 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Ta gra to strzelanka typu rywali. <BR>Ruch działanie odtwarzacza nie można wykonać. <BR>Walczmy z czterech broni! <BR>Proszę wybrać broń oraz w zależności od rodzaju i odległości wroga. <BR>Z bronią, atak wroga może być zestrzelony lub atak wroga może zostać zablokowane.<BR>Liczba wkładów ma ograniczeń w każdej broni. <BR>Szukając sposobu przechwytywania Wszystkie strefy 6 Proszę cieszyć się. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 37 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski/Japoński<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Detta spel är en interception typ skjutspel. <BR>Move drift av en spelare kan inte utföras. <BR>Låt oss kämpa med fyra vapen! <BR>Välj ett vapen och enligt fiendens slag och distans. <BR>Med ett vapen, kan en fiendes attack skjutas ner eller fiendens attack kan blockeras. <BR>Antalet patroner har begränsning på varje vapen. <BR>Samtidigt söker den fångstmetod All 6 område Vänligen njuta. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 37 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>(C) studio iris 2012<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Shooter"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
