<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00151_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>3420304</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Guide Trolly Bird igennem en labyrint af rør for at score point i denne meget addicting sjovt tempofyldt uendelige spil.<BR>Hvor mange rør kan du gå igennem? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Spil det på, mens man venter på læger kontor, i Bilka, skole, arbejde pause, hvor som helst!<BR>Trolly Bird er let at samle op, svært at mestre!<BR>Med enkle touch screen kontrol, det aldrig bliver alt for kompliceret, bare Tryk på skærmen og se Trolly Flyv op med hver hanen!<BR><BR>Konkurrer med dine venner for at se, hvem der kan score flest point,<BR>eller konkurrere med din egen bedste.<BR><BR>understøtter:<BR>- Leader boards er nu understøttet<BR>- Simple touch screen kontrol (bare tryk!)<BR>- Bedste score automatisk gemme funktion.<BR>- Baggrundsmusik play (mp3-afspiller eller Music Unlimited [afhængig af tilgængelighed]). <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 3341 KB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Leitfaden Trolly Vogel Trog ein Labyrinth aus Rohren, um Punkte in diesem hoch süchtig Spaß schnelllebigen Endlosspiel punkten.<BR>Wie viele Rohre können Sie durch gehen? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Spielen Sie es während der Wartezeit an der Ärzte Büro, im Supermarkt, in der Schule, Arbeitspause, überall!<BR>Trolly Bird ist leicht zu erlernen, schwer zu meistern!<BR>Mit einfachen Touchscreen-Steuerung, es wird nie übermäßig kompliziert, tippen Sie einfach auf den Bildschirm und beobachten Trolly Fliegen mit jedem Wasserhahn!<BR><BR>Fordere deine Freunde zu sehen, wer die meisten Punkte können,<BR>oder im Wettbewerb mit Ihrem eigenen Besten.<BR><BR>unterstützt:<BR>- Leader-Boards werden nun unterstützt<BR>- Einfache Touchscreen-Steuerung (tippen Sie einfach auf!)<BR>- Best-Score Automatik zu speichern.<BR>- Hintergrundmusikwiedergabe <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 3341 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Guide Trolly Bird trough a maze of pipes to score points in this highly addicting fun fast paced endless game.<BR>How many pipes can you go through? 1? 8? 50? 300? <BR>Play it at while waiting at the Doctors office, in the grocery store, school, work break, anywhere! <BR>Trolly Bird is easy to pick up, hard to master!<BR>With simple touch screen controls, it never gets overly complicated, just Tap the screen and watch Trolly Fly up with every tap!<BR><BR>Compete with your friends to see who can score the most points,<BR>or compete with your own best.<BR><BR>Supports:<BR>- Leader boards are now supported<BR>- Simple touch screen controls (just tap!)<BR>- Best score auto save feature.<BR>- Background music play (mp3 player or Music Unlimited [subject to availability]). <BR><BR>Package size: 3341 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Guide Trolly Bird trough a maze of pipes to score points in this highly addicting fun fast paced endless game.<BR>How many pipes can you go through? 1? 8? 50? 300? <BR>Play it at while waiting at the Doctors office, in the grocery store, school, work break, anywhere! <BR>Trolly Bird is easy to pick up, hard to master!<BR>With simple touch screen controls, it never gets overly complicated, just Tap the screen and watch Trolly Fly up with every tap!<BR><BR>Compete with your friends to see who can score the most points,<BR>or compete with your own best.<BR><BR>Supports:<BR>- Leader boards are now supported<BR>- Simple touch screen controls (just tap!)<BR>- Best score auto save feature.<BR>- Background music play (mp3 player or Music Unlimited [subject to availability]). <BR><BR>Package size: 3341 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Guide Trolly Bird trough a maze of pipes to score points in this highly addicting fun fast paced endless game.<BR>How many pipes can you go through? 1? 8? 50? 300? <BR>Play it at while waiting at the Doctors office, in the grocery store, school, work break, anywhere! <BR>Trolly Bird is easy to pick up, hard to master!<BR>With simple touch screen controls, it never gets overly complicated, just Tap the screen and watch Trolly Fly up with every tap!<BR><BR>Compete with your friends to see who can score the most points,<BR>or compete with your own best.<BR><BR>Supports:<BR>- Leader boards are now supported<BR>- Simple touch screen controls (just tap!)<BR>- Best score auto save feature.<BR>- Background music play (mp3 player or Music Unlimited [subject to availability]). <BR><BR>Package size: 3341 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Guide Trolly Bird trough a maze of pipes to score points in this highly addicting fun fast paced endless game.<BR>How many pipes can you go through? 1? 8? 50? 300? <BR>Play it at while waiting at the Doctors office, in the grocery store, school, work break, anywhere! <BR>Trolly Bird is easy to pick up, hard to master!<BR>With simple touch screen controls, it never gets overly complicated, just Tap the screen and watch Trolly Fly up with every tap!<BR><BR>Compete with your friends to see who can score the most points,<BR>or compete with your own best.<BR><BR>Supports:<BR>- Leader boards are now supported<BR>- Simple touch screen controls (just tap!)<BR>- Best score auto save feature.<BR>- Background music play (mp3 player or Music Unlimited [subject to availability]). <BR><BR>Package size: 3341 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Guía Trolly Bird través de un laberinto de tubos para sumar puntos en este divertido altamente adictivo de ritmo rápido de juego sin fin.<BR>¿Cuántos canales se puede ir a través de? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Tenga un tiempo de espera en el consultorio del médico, en el supermercado, la escuela, la rotura de trabajo, en cualquier lugar!<BR>Trolly Bird es fácil de aprender, difícil de dominar!<BR>Con los controles de pantalla táctil simples, que nunca se pone demasiado complicado, sólo Toque la pantalla y ver Trolly Volar con cada toque!<BR><BR>Compite con tus amigos para ver quién puede anotar la mayor cantidad de puntos,<BR>o competir con su propio mejor.<BR><BR>Ayudas:<BR>- El panel de clasificación son ahora soportados<BR>- Controles de pantalla táctil simple (sólo toque!)<BR>- Mejor puntuación de la función de ahorro automático. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 3341 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Opas Trolly Bird aallonpohjasta sokkelo putkien pisteitä tässä erittäin addicting hauska nopeatempoinen loputon peli.<BR>Kuinka monta putket voi mennä läpi? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Pelata sitä odotellessa Lääkärit toimistossa, ruokakauppaan, koulu, työ tauko, missä tahansa!<BR>Trolly Bird on helppo poimia, vaikea hallita!<BR>Yksinkertaisia ​​kosketusnäyttöohjaustavan, se ei koskaan saa liian monimutkainen, vain koskettamalla näyttöä ja katsella Trolly Lennä jokaisella kosketuksella!<BR><BR>Kilpaile ystäviesi kanssa siitä, kuka pystyy pisteet eniten pisteitä,<BR>tai kilpailla oma paras.<BR><BR>tukee:<BR>- Leader levyt tuetaan nyt<BR>- Yksinkertainen kosketusnäyttöohjaustavan (vain koskettamalla!)<BR>- Parhaat pisteet automaattinen tallentaa ominaisuus.<BR>- Taustamusiikki toisto (mp3-soitin tai Music Unlimited [saatavuus]). <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 3341 Kt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Guide des oiseaux Chariot creux un labyrinthe de tuyaux de marquer des points dans ce jeu hautement addictif de jeu sans fin rapide.<BR>Combien de tuyaux pouvez-vous passer? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Jouer à ce jeu tout en attendant au bureau de médecins, dans l'épicerie, l'école, la rupture de travail, n'importe où!<BR>Chariot Bird est facile à ramasser, difficile à maîtriser!<BR>Avec de simples commandes de l'écran tactile, il ne fait jamais trop compliqué, il suffit Touchez l'écran et de regarder Trolly mouche avec chaque robinet!<BR><BR>Rivaliser avec vos amis pour voir qui peut marquer le plus de points,<BR>ou en concurrence avec votre meilleur.<BR><BR>Prise en charge:<BR>- Les tableaux des leaders sont désormais pris en charge<BR>- Simples contrôles de l'écran tactile (Il suffit de taper!)<BR>- Meilleur auto score fonction d'é <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 3341 Ko - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Guidage des oiseaux Chariot creux un labyrinthe de tuyaux de marquer des points dans ce jeu hautement addictif de jeu sans fin rapide.<BR>Combien de tuyaux pouvez-vous passer? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Jouer à ce jeu tout en attendant au bureau de médecins, dans l'épicerie, l'école, la rupture de travail, n'importe où!<BR>Chariot Bird est facile à ramasser, difficile à maîtriser!<BR>Avec de simples commandes de l'écran tactile, il ne fait jamais trop compliqué, il suffit Touchez l'écran et de regarder Trolly mouche avec chaque robinet!<BR><BR>Rivaliser avec vos amis pour voir qui peut marquer le plus de points,<BR>ou en concurrence avec votre meilleur.<BR><BR>Prise en charge:<BR>- Simples contrôles de l'écran tactile (Il suffit de taper!)<BR>- Meilleur auto score fonction d'économie.<BR>- Le jeu de fond de musique <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 3341 Ko - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Guida Trolly Uccello attraverso un labirinto di tubi per segnare punti in questo altamente coinvolgente divertimento frenetico gioco senza fine.<BR>Quante pipe si può passare? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Gioca in attesa all'ufficio dei medici, nel negozio di alimentari, scuola, pausa di lavoro, ovunque!<BR>Trolly Bird è facile da imparare, difficile da padroneggiare!<BR>Con semplici comandi touch screen, non diventa mai troppo complicato, basta toccare lo schermo e guardare Trolly Vola con ogni tocco!<BR><BR>Competi con i tuoi amici per vedere chi può segnare più punti,<BR>o competere con il tuo migliore.<BR><BR>Supporta:<BR>- Classifiche sono ora supportati<BR>- Comandi touch screen semplici (basta toccare!)<BR>- Miglior punteggio salvataggio automatico funzione.<BR>- Riproduzione musica di sottofondo <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 3341 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[ガイドトロリーバードは、この非常に中毒楽しい速いペースで無限のゲームでポイントを獲得するパイプの迷路の谷。<BR>あなたはどのように多くのパイプを介して行くことができますか？ 1？ 8？ 50？ 300？<BR>どこでも、食料品店、学校、仕事の休憩中に、医師のオフィスで待っている間に、それをプレイ！<BR>トロリーバードマスターする、取り出しやすいにくい！<BR>シンプルなタッチスクリーンコントロールを使用すると、それだけで、画面をタップして、トロリーは、すべてのタップで飛ぶ見て、過度に複雑になることはありません！<BR><BR>誰が最もポイントを獲得することができます参照してお友達と競争し、<BR>またはあなた自身のベストと競合している。<BR><BR>サポートされています。<BR>- リーダーボードがサポートされるようになりました<BR>- シンプルなタッチスクリーンコントロール（タップするだけ！）<BR>- ベストスコアの自動保存機能。<BR>- バックグラウンド音楽再生（MP3プレーヤーやMusic Unlimitedの[利用状況による]）。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 3341 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Guide Trolly Bird gjennom en labyrint av rør for å score poeng i dette svært addicting moro hektisk løse spillet.<BR>Hvor mange rør kan du gå gjennom? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Spill det på mens du venter på leger kontor, i dagligvarebutikk, skole, arbeid pause, hvor som helst!<BR>Trolly Bird er lett å plukke opp, vanskelig å mestre!<BR>Med enkle berøringsskjermkontroller, det blir aldri altfor komplisert, bare Trykk på skjermen og se Trolly Fly opp med hvert trykk!<BR><BR>Konkurrer med dine venner for å se hvem som kan score flest poeng,<BR>eller konkurrere med din egen beste.<BR><BR>støtter:<BR>- Leader styrene støttes nå<BR>- Enkle berøringsskjermkontroller (bare trykk!)<BR>- Beste poengsum auto save-funksjonen.<BR>- Bakgrunnsmusikk play (mp3-spiller eller Music Unlimited [avhengig av tilgjengelighet]). <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 3341 KB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Gids Trolly Bird via een doolhof van buizen om punten te scoren in deze zeer verslavend leuke snelle eindeloos spel.<BR>Hoeveel pijpen kan je door? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Speel het op tijdens het wachten bij de dokter, in de supermarkt, school, werk pauze, overal!<BR>Trolly Bird is makkelijk op te pakken, moeilijk te beheersen!<BR>Met eenvoudige touch screen bediening, het wordt nooit te ingewikkeld, gewoon Tik op het scherm en kijk Trolly Vlieg bij elke tik!<BR><BR>Speel met je vrienden om te zien wie de meeste punten scoren,<BR>of concurreren met je eigen beste.<BR><BR>ondersteunt:<BR>- Leader boards worden nu ondersteund<BR>- Eenvoudige bediening via het touchscreen (tikt u gewoon op!)<BR>- Beste score automatische save functie.<BR>- Achtergrondmuziek afspelen (mp3-speler of Music Unlimited [afhankelijk van beschikbaarheid]). <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 3341 KB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Guide Trolly Bird igenom en labyrint av rör för att få poäng i denna mycket beroendeframkallande roligt fartfyllda oändliga spel.<BR>Hur många rör kan du gå igenom? 1? 8? 50? 300?<BR>Spela det på i väntan på läkare kontor, i mataffären, skola, arbete paus, var som helst!<BR>Trolly Bird är lätt att plocka upp, svårt att bemästra!<BR>Med enkla kontroller pekskärm, aldrig blir det alltför komplicerat, bara peka på skärmen och titta Trolly Fly upp med varje kran!<BR><BR>Tävla med dina vänner för att se vem som kan göra flest poäng,<BR>eller tävla med din egen bästa.<BR><BR>stödjer:<BR>- Leader brädor stöds nu<BR>- Enkla kontroller pekskärm (bara knacka!)<BR>- Bästa poäng autosparfunktionen.<BR>- Bakgrundsmusik play (mp3-spelare eller Music Unlimited [mån av tillgång]). <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 3341 KB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Martinez.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
