<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00017_00">
 <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>25583008</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[究極のクイズゲーム<br><br>QuizQuizQuizにようこそ。新たなBuzzerモード（先に解答するために対戦相手より前に飛び入り！）を含め、5種類のモードに渡る中毒的なシングルおよびマルチプレイヤーゲームを搭載したハイペースクイズゲームです。 <br><br>英語、フランス語、イタリア語、ドイツ語、スペイン語話者向けに何百ものカテゴリからの5000以上の質問は、全てプロのトリビア専門家に書かれています。 <br>BeginnerからMastermind難易度まで、誰にでもお楽しみ頂けます！<br><br>ハイスコアや成績が実装され、PlayStation Mobile上で最も中毒的なクイズゲームで誰がキング・オブ・クイズなのかわかるようになりました。<br><br>帰宅中の電車での5分間のトリビアパーティだろうと、賞品や実績を賭けて家族との対戦だろうと、QuizQuizQuizはクイズゲームのニーズを全て満たします。<br><br>コンテンツ容量:25 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1-5人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語<br><br>著作権等:<br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[The Ultimate Quiz game<br><br>Welcome to QuizQuizQuiz, the fast paced quiz game featuring addictive single and multiplayer gaming across five modes including the new Buzzer mode (buzz in before your opponents to win the chance to answer first!). <br><br>Featuring over 5000 questions for English, French, Italian, German and Spanish speakers in hundreds of categories, all written by professional trivia experts. <br>From Beginner to Mastermind difficulty, there is something for everyone!<br><br>Complete with high scores and statistics you can finally discover who is King of the Quiz in the most addictive quiz game on PlayStation Mobile.<br><br>Whether it’s a five minute trivia blast on your train journey home or an evening competing against your family to win awards and achievements, QuizQuizQuiz will appeal to all your quiz gaming needs.<br><br>Package size: 25 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1-5Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Le Quiz ultime<br><br>Bienvenue dans QuizQuizQuiz, le quiz ultra rapide en solo ou en multijoueur. Cinq modes, dont le nouveau mode Buzzer (buzzez avant l'adversaire pour répondre le premier !).<br><br>Avec plus de 5 000 questions en anglais, français, italien, allemand et espagnol, dans une centaine de catégories, toutes rédigées par des experts du genre.<br>Que vous soyez Novice ou Génie, vous y trouverez votre compte !<br><br>Grâce au système de meilleurs scores et de statistiques, découvrez qui sera le Roi du quiz, dans le quiz le plus captivant sur PlayStation Mobile.<br><br>Que vous cherchiez un quiz éclair de cinq minutes dans le métro ou une compétition du soir contre votre famille pour remporter récompenses et succès, QuizQuizQuiz est là pour vous.<br><br>Taille du paquet: 25 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1-5joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Il quiz definitivo<br><br>Benvenuto su QuizQuizQuiz, il velocissimo gioco a quiz pieno di giochi avvincenti per giocatore singolo o multigiocatore con cinque modalità tra cui la nuova modalità Buzzer (prenotati con il buzzer prima che i tuoi avversari abbiano la possibilità di rispondere per primi!).<br><br>Più di 5000 domande in inglese, francese, italiano, tedesco e spagnolo in centinaia di categorie, tutte realizzate da esperti di quiz.<br>Dalla difficoltà principiante a quella genio, ce n'è per tutti!<br><br>Grazie ai record e alle statistiche potrai scoprire chi è il Re del quiz nel gioco a quiz più avvincente su PlayStation Mobile.<br><br>Non importa se la tua partita dura cinque minuti mentre sei in treno e torni a casa o se passi una serata a giocare con la tua famiglia per vincere premi e obiettivi, QuizQuizQuiz soddisferà qualunque voglia di quiz!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 25 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1-5giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[El juego de preguntas definitivo<br><br>Bienvenido a QuizQuizQuiz, un juego de preguntas con un ritmo de vértigo que cuenta con los adictivos modos para un jugador y multijugador en cinco diferentes modos de juego, incluyendo el nuevo modo Pulsador (¡accione el pulsador antes que sus adversarios para tener la oportunidad de responder primero!).<br><br>El juego cuenta con más de 5.000 preguntas para jugadores de lengua inglesa, francesa, italiana, alemana y española, todas ellas escritas por expertos en el sector.<br>Con niveles de dificultad que van de principiante a maestro, ¡hay preguntas para todos los gustos!<br><br>Gracias a los récords y a las estadísticas podrá saber quién es el rey de las preguntas en el juego de preguntas más adictivo para PlayStation Mobile.<br><br>Tanto en una partida relámpago de 5 minutos de vuelta a casa en tren, como en una tarde de relax con su familia para conseguir premios y logros, ¡QuizQuizQuiz es todo lo que necesita para pasar un buen rato!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 25 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1-5jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Das ultimative Quizspiel<br><br>Willkommen zu QuizQuizQuiz, dem temporeichen Quizspiel mit süchtig machenden Einzel- und Mehrspieleroptionen über 5 verschiedene Modi, einschließlich des neuen Buzzer-Modus. (Drücken Sie den Buzzer vor Ihren Gegner, um zuerst antworten zu können!)<br><br>Sie erwarten über 5000 Fragen auf Englisch, Französisch, Italienisch, Deutsch und Spanisch in hunderten von Kategorien. Alle Fragen wurden von professionellen Quizexperten erstellt. <br>Von Leicht bis Superhirn gibt es für jeden einen Schwierigkeitsgrad!<br><br>Mit Hilfe von Höchstpunktzahlen und Statistiken können Sie endlich herausfinden, wer im faszinierendsten Quizspiel auf PlayStation Mobile der Quizkönig ist.<br><br>Ob es sich um ein schnelles Spiel auf einer Zugfahrt nach Hause handelt oder um einen Abend, an dem Sie gegen Ihre Familie um Preise und Erfolge antreten – QuizQuizQuiz stellt sich all Ihren Quizspiel-Anforderungen.<br><br>Paketgröße: 25 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1-5Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[The Ultimate Quiz game<br><br>Welcome to QuizQuizQuiz, the fast paced quiz game featuring addictive single and multiplayer gaming across five modes including the new Buzzer mode (buzz in before your opponents to win the chance to answer first!). <br><br>Featuring over 5000 questions for English, French, Italian, German and Spanish speakers in hundreds of categories, all written by professional trivia experts. <br>From Beginner to Mastermind difficulty, there is something for everyone!<br><br>Complete with high scores and statistics you can finally discover who is King of the Quiz in the most addictive quiz game on PlayStation Mobile.<br><br>Whether it’s a five minute trivia blast on your train journey home or an evening competing against your family to win awards and achievements, QuizQuizQuiz will appeal to all your quiz gaming needs.<br><br>Package size: 25 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1-5Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Le Quiz ultime<br><br>Bienvenue dans QuizQuizQuiz, le quiz ultra rapide en solo ou en multijoueur. Cinq modes, dont le nouveau mode Buzzer (buzzez avant l'adversaire pour répondre le premier !).<br><br>Avec plus de 5 000 questions en anglais, français, italien, allemand et espagnol, dans une centaine de catégories, toutes rédigées par des experts du genre.<br>Que vous soyez Novice ou Génie, vous y trouverez votre compte !<br><br>Grâce au système de meilleurs scores et de statistiques, découvrez qui sera le Roi du quiz, dans le quiz le plus captivant sur PlayStation Mobile.<br><br>Que vous cherchiez un quiz éclair de cinq minutes dans le métro ou une compétition du soir contre votre famille pour remporter récompenses et succès, QuizQuizQuiz est là pour vous.<br><br>Taille du programme: 25 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1-5joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Family"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
