<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00250_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>57178544</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Balloner vil flyve, og du er nødt til pop balloner af samme farve så meget som du kan.Prøv at pop 10 eller flere balloner af samme farve for at generere Awesome combos!Du kan trække dem fra pinden til at organisere dem og gemme dem til en fantastisk Crushing!<BR>* Nyd at trække og popping fantastiske balloner!<BR>* Med mere end 40 + udfordrende niveauer!<BR>* Særlige balloner, som vil hjælpe dig på dette eventyr!<BR>* Funny ansigter og lyde til at have en lykkelig tid!<BR>* Mere end 130 + stjerner for at låse! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 55 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Luftballons fliegen und Sie Ballons der gleichen Farbe, wie viel Sie können Pop haben.Versuchen Sie, 10 oder mehr Ballons der gleichen Farbe zu Super Combos erzeugen Pop!Sie können sie von dem Stock ziehen, um sie zu organisieren und speichern Sie sie für eine erstaunliche Crushing!<BR>* Genießen Sie Ziehen und knallen erstaunliche Luftballons!<BR>Mit mehr als 40 + herausfordernde Levels!<BR>* Sonder Ballons, die Sie auf diesem Abenteuer helfen!<BR>* Lustige Gesichter und Klänge, eine glückliche Zeit haben!<BR>* Mehr als 130 + Sterne zu entsperren! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 55 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Balloons will fly and you have to pop balloons of the same color as much as you can.<BR>Try to pop 10 or more balloons with the same color to generate Awesome combos!<BR>You can drag them from the stick to organize them and save them for an amazing Crushing!<BR>* Enjoy dragging and popping amazing balloons!<BR>* With more than 40+ challenging levels!<BR>* Special balloons that will help you on this adventure!<BR>* Funny faces and sounds to have a happy time!<BR>* More than 130+ stars to unlock! <BR><BR>Package size: 55 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Globos volarán y usted tiene que estallar los globos del mismo color lo más que pueda.Trata de abrir 10 o más globos del mismo color para generar combos impresionantes!Usted puede arrastrarlos desde el palo para organizar y guardar para una trituración increíble!<BR>* Disfruta de arrastrar y quitar los globos increíbles!<BR>* Con más de 40 desafiantes niveles!<BR>* Globos especiales que te ayudarán en esta aventura!<BR>* Caras divertidas y sonidos para tener un rato feliz!<BR>* Más de 130 + estrellas para desbloquear! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 55 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Ilmapallot lentää ja on pop ilmapallot samaa väriä niin paljon kuin voit.<BR>Yritä pop 10 tai enemmän palloja on sama väri tuottaa Awesome komboja!<BR>Voit vetää ne kiinni järjestää ne ja tallentaa ne hämmästyttävä Murskaus!<BR>* Nauti vetämällä ja popping hämmästyttävä ilmapalloja!<BR>* Yli 40 + haastavaa tasoa!<BR>* Special ilmapalloja, jotka auttavat sinua tässä seikkailu!<BR>* Funny kasvot ja äänet ovat onnellista aikaa!<BR>* Yli 130 + tähdet avata! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 55 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Ballons voleront et vous devez éclater des ballons de la même couleur autant que vous le pouvez.Essayez de pop 10 ou plusieurs ballons de la même couleur pour générer des combos impressionnants!Vous pouvez les faire glisser de la baguette de les organiser et de les enregistrer pour une Concassage incroyable!<BR>* Profitez de glisser-popping ballons incroyables!<BR>* Avec plus de plus de 40 niveaux difficiles!<BR>* Ballons spéciaux qui vous aideront dans cette aventure!<BR>* Funny faces et les sons d'avoir un temps heureux!<BR>* Plus de plus de 130 étoiles à débloquer! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 55 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Palloncini volerà e si deve scoppiare i palloncini dello stesso colore il più possibile.<BR>Cercate di pop 10 o più palloncini dello stesso colore per generare combo impressionanti!È possibile trascinare dal bastone per organizzarli e salvarli per un Frantumazione incredibile!<BR>* Godetevi trascinando e popping palloncini incredibili!<BR>* Con più di 40 + livelli di sfida!<BR>* Palloncini speciali che ti aiuteranno in questa avventura!<BR>* Divertente facce e suoni per avere un tempo felice!<BR>* Più di 130 + le stelle per sbloccare! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 55 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>風船が飛ぶし、あなたができる限り同じ色の風船をポップする。連続で同じ色の風船で10個以上をポップしてみて、素晴らしいコンボが手に入れる。風船の線をドラッグによって同じ色の風船を整理して、その後一気にポップして凄いコンボを取得しましょう。<BR><BR>*40以上のレベルを挑戦しましょう！<BR>*特別な風船がこの冒険であなたを助ける！<BR>*130以上の星ロックを解除するのを待っている！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 55 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Ballonger vil fly og du må pop bobler av samme farge så mye du kan.<BR>Prøv å pop 10 eller flere ballonger med samme farge for å generere Awesome komboer!Du kan dra dem fra pinnen til å organisere dem og lagre dem for en fantastisk Crushing!<BR>* Nyt dra og dukker fantastiske ballonger!<BR>* Med mer enn 40 + utfordrende nivåer!<BR>* Spesial ballonger som vil hjelpe deg på dette eventyret!<BR>* Funny ansikter og lyder for å ha en lykkelig tid!<BR>* Mer enn 130 + stjerner for å låse opp! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 55 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Ballonnen zal vliegen en je moet ballonnen van dezelfde kleur pop zo veel als je kunt.Probeer om 10 of meer ballonnen pop met dezelfde kleur om Awesome combo's te genereren!U kunt ze slepen van de stick om ze te ordenen en op te slaan voor een geweldige Crushing!<BR>* Geniet van slepen en popping geweldige ballonnen!<BR>* Met meer dan 40+ uitdagende levels!<BR>* Speciale ballonnen die je zal helpen op dit avontuur!<BR>* Grappige gezichten en geluiden om een gelukkige tijd te hebben!<BR>* Meer dan 130 + sterren te ontgrendelen! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 55 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Balony będą latać i trzeba balony tego samego koloru, jak to tylko możliwe.<BR>Spróbuj pop 10 lub więcej balonów tego samego koloru, aby wygenerować Firma Awesome combo!Możesz przeciągnąć je z kijem zorganizować je i zapisywać je na niesamowite kruszenia!<BR>* Ciesz się przeciągając i popping niesamowite balony!<BR>* Ponad 40 + trudnych poziomów!<BR>* Specjalne balony, które pomogą Ci w tej przygodzie!<BR>* Funny twarze i dźwięki do szczęśliwego czasu!<BR>* Ponad 130 + gwiazdki, aby odblokować! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 55 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Ballonger flyger och du måste pop ballonger av samma färg så mycket du kan.<BR>Försök att pop 10 eller fler ballonger med samma färg för att generera enorma combos!Du kan dra dem från pinnen för att organisera dem och spara dem för en fantastisk Krossning!<BR>* Njut dra och poppar fantastiska ballonger!<BR>* Med mer än 40 + utmanande nivåer!<BR>* Särskilda ballonger som hjälper dig på detta äventyr!<BR>* Roliga ansikten och ljud för att ha en lycklig tid!<BR>* Mer än 130 + stjärnor för att låsa upp! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 55 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2014 SS Inc<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Casual"/><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
