<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00143_00">

  <appVersion>1.60</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>5710816</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Det er juleaften, og du blot ønsker at gå i seng og vågne op julemorgen. Men træet er brudt, huset er det for koldt, Mr. Peabody er tacky Xmas skærm er irriterende og som altid din bror vil ikke gå i seng. Udforsk, interagere med miljøet og løse gåder i denne old-school eventyrspil.<BR><BR>- Classic eventyrspil sjov på din håndholdte enhed.<BR>- Farverig retro-stil grafik.<BR>- Udforsk en munter og humoristisk miljø.<BR>- Brug din forstand og de ​​emner, du finde på at få huset klar til jul. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 5577 KB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Es ist Heiligabend und Sie wollen einfach nur ins Bett gehen und aufwachen am Weihnachtsmorgen. Aber der Baum ist gebrochen, es ist zu kalt, das Haus ist Mr. Peabody klebrig Weihnachten Anzeige ärgerlich und wie immer dein Bruder nicht zu Bett gehen. Entdecken, die Interaktion mit der Umgebung und Rätsel zu lösen, in diesem Old-School-Adventure-Spiel.<BR><BR>- Klassisches Adventure-Spiel Spaß auf Ihrem Handheld-Gerät.<BR>- Bunte Retro-Stil-Grafik.<BR>- Erkunden Sie eine heitere und humorvolle Umgebung.<BR>- Benutze deinen Verstand und die Artikel, die Sie finden das Haus bereit für Weihnachten zu bekommen. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 5577 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[It is Christmas Eve and you just want to go to bed and wake up on Christmas morning. But the tree is broken, the house it too cold, Mr. Peabody's tacky Xmas display is annoying and as always your brother won't go to bed. Explore, interact with your environment and solve puzzles in this old-school adventure game.<BR><BR>- Classic adventure game fun on your hand-held device.<BR>- Colorful retro-styled graphics.<BR>- Explore a lighthearted and humorous environment.<BR>- Use your wits and the items you find to get the house ready for Christmas. <BR><BR>Package size: 5577 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Es víspera de Navidad y lo que desea es ir a la cama y despertar en la mañana de Navidad. Pero el árbol se rompe, la casa es demasiado frío, la pantalla pegajoso de la Navidad del Sr. Peabody es molesto y como siempre tu hermano no va a ir a la cama. Explorar, interactuar con su entorno y resolver puzzles en este juego de aventura de la vieja escuela.<BR><BR>- Aventura clásico juego de la diversión en su dispositivo de mano.<BR>- Coloridos gráficos de estilo retro.<BR>- Explora un ambiente alegre y chistoso.<BR>- Utiliza tu ingenio y los objetos que encuentres para preparar la casa para la Navidad. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 5577 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Se on jouluaatto ja haluat vain mennä nukkumaan ja herätä jouluaamuna. Mutta puu on rikki, talo on liian kylmä, herra Peabody n tahmea Xmas näyttö on ärsyttävää ja kuten aina veljesi ei mene nukkumaan. Tutki, vuorovaikutuksessa ympäristön kanssa ja ratkaise pulmia tässä vanhan koulukunnan seikkailupeli.<BR><BR>- Classic seikkailupeli hauskaa teidän kädessä pidettävä laite.<BR>- Värikäs retro-tyylistä grafiikkaa.<BR>- Tutki hilpeä ja humoristinen ympäristössä.<BR>- Käytä järkeä ja kohteet löydät saada talon valmiiksi jouluksi. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 5577 Kt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[C'est la veille de Noël et vous voulez juste aller au lit et se réveiller le matin de Noël. Mais l'arbre est brisé, la maison qu'il faisait trop froid, affichage mauvais goût de Noël de M. Peabody est ennuyeux et comme toujours votre frère ne sera pas aller au lit. Découvrir, interagir avec votre environnement et résoudre des énigmes dans ce jeu d'aventure old-school.<BR><BR>- Aventure classique jeu amusant sur ​​votre appareil portatif.<BR>- Colorful graphiques de style rétro.<BR>- Explorez un environnement gai et plein d'humour.<BR>- Utilisez votre intelligence et les objets que vous trouverez pour obtenir la maison prête pour Noël. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 5577 Ko - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[E 'la vigilia di Natale e si vuole solo andare a letto e svegliarsi la mattina di Natale. Ma l'albero è rotto, la casa è troppo freddo, Natale visualizzazione di cattivo gusto del signor Peabody è fastidioso e come sempre tuo fratello non andrà a letto. Esplorare, interagire con l'ambiente e risolvere enigmi in questo gioco di avventura old-school.<BR><BR>- Avventura classico divertente gioco sul vostro dispositivo portatile.<BR>- Grafica colorata in stile retrò.<BR>- Esplorare un ambiente allegro e divertente.<BR>- Usa il tuo ingegno e gli elementi che si trovano di ottenere la casa pronta per Natale. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 5577 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[それはクリスマスイブで、あなただけのベッドに行きたい、クリスマスの朝に目を覚ます。しかし、ツリーが壊れている、家は寒すぎる、氏ピーボディの粘着性のクリスマスディスプレイは迷惑ですし、いつものようにあなたの兄弟は、ベッドに行くことはありません。 、お使いの環境と相互作用し、この古い学校のアドベンチャーゲームでパズルを解く探る。<BR><BR>- あなたのハンドヘルドデバイス上の古典的なアドベンチャーゲームの楽しみ。<BR>- カラフルなレトロなスタイルのグラフィック。<BR>- 気軽かつユーモラスな環境を探る。<BR>- クリスマスのために家を準備するためにあなたのウィットとあなたが見つけるアイテムを使用してください。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 5577 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Det er julaften, og du bare ønsker å gå til sengs og våkne opp på julaften morgen. Men treet er ødelagt, huset det for kaldt, er Mr. Peabody klebrig Xmas skjerm irriterende og som alltid din bror vil ikke gå til sengs. Utforsk, samhandle med omgivelsene og løse gåter i denne old-school eventyrspill.<BR><BR>- Klassisk eventyrspill moro på din håndholdte enhet.<BR>- Fargerike retro-stylet grafikk.<BR>- Utforsk en munter og humoristisk miljø.<BR>- Bruk vettet og varene du finner å få huset klart til jul. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 5577 KB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Het is kerstavond en je wil gewoon naar bed gaan en wakker op kerstochtend. Maar de boom is gebroken, het huis het te koud, plakkerig Xmas scherm Mr Peabody's is vervelend en zoals altijd je broer zal niet naar bed. Verkennen, interactie met je omgeving en puzzels op te lossen in deze old-school adventure game.<BR><BR>- Classic adventure game plezier op uw hand-held apparaat.<BR>- Kleurrijke retro-stijl graphics.<BR>- Ontdek een luchthartige en humoristische omgeving.<BR>- Gebruik je verstand en de items die u naar het huis klaar voor Kerstmis krijgen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 5577 KB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Jest Wigilia i chcesz po prostu iść spać i obudzić się na Boże Narodzenie rano. Ale drzewo jest uszkodzony, dom jest zbyt zimno, tandetny wyświetlacz Xmas pana Peabody jest denerwujące i jak zawsze twój brat nie pójdzie do łóżka. Eksploruj, interakcji z otoczeniem i rozwiązywać zagadki w tej grze przygodowej starej szkoły. <BR><BR>- Klasyczna gra przygodowa na urządzeniu ręcznym. <BR>- Kolorowe stylu retro grafiki. <BR>- Poznaj się komfortowy i humorystyczny środowiska. <BR>- Użyj sprytu i elementy można znaleźć dostać dom gotowy na Boże Narodzenie. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 5577 KB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Det är julafton och du bara vill gå till sängs och vakna upp på juldagens morgon. Men trädet är trasig, det är för kallt, är huset Mr Peabodys klibbig Xmas display irriterande och som alltid din bror inte kommer att gå till sängs. Upptäck, interagera med din omgivning och lösa pussel i denna gamla skolan äventyrsspel.<BR><BR>- Klassiskt äventyrsspel kul på din handhållna enhet.<BR>- Färgglada retro-stil grafik.<BR>- Utforska en lättsam och humoristisk miljö.<BR>- Använd din intelligens och de objekt som du hittar för att få huset klart till jul. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 5577 KB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>2012-2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Family"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
