<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00161_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>17820976</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[En meget interessant tempofyldt parkour spil, spillet er meget enkel betjening, i det spil, du vil spille et lille egern, du behøver at gøre er at køre fremad og fortsætte med at undgå forskellige forhindringer og indsamle så mange små flaske. <BR>Knappen i nederste venstre hjørne af springet kan styre egern hoppe, skal du dobbeltklikke på den sekundære kan hoppe, hoppe til at krydse dygtige brug af to på hinanden følgende forhindringer Oh, fald i nederste højre hjørne er der en knap, tryk og hold for at styre egern glide fremad, at undgå højtliggende forhindringer. Egern indsamle flere flasker hver, vil øge et liv. <BR>PS: Dette spil er tilpasset fra spillet "iRunner" <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 17 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Kinesisk - forenklet/Kinesisk - traditionelt<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Das ist eines fantastisches taktisches Parkour Spiel und deren Ansteürung ist sehr einfach. Im diese Spiel würden Sie als eines minies Eichhörnchen spielen und ihre Aufgabe ist immer vorwärts rennen und jedem Hindernis ausweichen und die kleine Medikantflasche so viel wie moeglich einsammeln.<BR><BR>Mit dem Klicken des auf der untenlinks Seiten stehenden Sprungdruckknopf wird das Eichhörnchen hervorspringen. Mit dem zweimaligen Klicken kann das Eichhörnchen noch einmal springen. Die tüchtige Anwendung des zweimaligen Klickens ist der Schlüsser, der anschliessende Hindernisse zu überqüren. Auf der untenrechts Seite ist der Rutschdruckknopf. Duch dem Drucken kann das Eichhörnchen vorwärts rutschen, um die aus dem Himmel fallenden Hindernisse zu vermeiden. Nach der Sammelung der ein paar Medikantfl <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 17 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Vereinfachtes Chinesisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[It is a very interesting fast-paced running game and very simple to operate. You will play the role of a small squirrel in the game. All you need to do is to run forward and keep avoiding various obstacles and collect small medicine bottles as many as you can. <BR>　　　The button at the lower left corner is designed for controlling the squirrel’s jump. Double-click stands for a double jump and you can only go through consecutive obstacles if you can skillfully use double jump; the button at the lower right corner is the decline button. You can let the squirrel slide forward by pressing it, which is designed for avoiding obstacles in the air. Every time the squirrel collects several bottles, it will get another life. <BR>　　　PS: This game is adapted from the game "iRunner". <BR><BR>Package size: 17 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[It is a very interesting fast-paced running game and very simple to operate. You will play the role of a small squirrel in the game. All you need to do is to run forward and keep avoiding various obstacles and collect small medicine bottles as many as you can. <BR>　　　The button at the lower left corner is designed for controlling the squirrel’s jump. Double-click stands for a double jump and you can only go through consecutive obstacles if you can skillfully use double jump; the button at the lower right corner is the decline button. You can let the squirrel slide forward by pressing it, which is designed for avoiding obstacles in the air. Every time the squirrel collects several bottles, it will get another life. <BR>　　　PS: This game is adapted from the game "iRunner". <BR><BR>Package size: 17 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[It is a very interesting fast-paced running game and very simple to operate. You will play the role of a small squirrel in the game. All you need to do is to run forward and keep avoiding various obstacles and collect small medicine bottles as many as you can. <BR>　　　The button at the lower left corner is designed for controlling the squirrel’s jump. Double-click stands for a double jump and you can only go through consecutive obstacles if you can skillfully use double jump; the button at the lower right corner is the decline button. You can let the squirrel slide forward by pressing it, which is designed for avoiding obstacles in the air. Every time the squirrel collects several bottles, it will get another life. <BR>　　　PS: This game is adapted from the game "iRunner". <BR><BR>Package size: 17 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[It is a very interesting fast-paced running game and very simple to operate. You will play the role of a small squirrel in the game. All you need to do is to run forward and keep avoiding various obstacles and collect small medicine bottles as many as you can. <BR>　　　The button at the lower left corner is designed for controlling the squirrel’s jump. Double-click stands for a double jump and you can only go through consecutive obstacles if you can skillfully use double jump; the button at the lower right corner is the decline button. You can let the squirrel slide forward by pressing it, which is designed for avoiding obstacles in the air. Every time the squirrel collects several bottles, it will get another life. <BR>　　　PS: This game is adapted from the game "iRunner". <BR><BR>Package size: 17 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Es un muy interesante juego de parkour de ritmo rápido,la operación del juego es muy simple.En el juego, va a jugar un papel de pequeña ardilla, lo que tiene que hacer es correr hacia adelante y evitar diversos obstáculos constantemente,así como hacer todo lo posible para recoger los frascos.Botón del salto que está en la esquina inferior izquierda puede controlar el solto de la ardilla.haga doble clic puede haber dos saltos,sólo usar los dos salto hábilmente puede cruzar obstáculos consecutivos;Botón en la esquina inferior derecha es el botón de la disminución,puede controlar las ardillas se deslizan hacia adelante Manteniendo la presionada,para evitar los obstáculos de altitud. Cuando las ardillas recogen varias botellas, se incrementará una vida<BR>   PS: Este juego es una adaptación de <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 17 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Chino simplificado/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Erittäin mielenkiintoinen nopeatempoisessa parkour peli, peli on hyvin yksinkertainen toimenpide, peli voit pelata pieni orava, sinun tarvitsee vain ajaa eteenpäin ja edelleen välttämään erilaisia ​​esteitä ja kerätä mahdollisimman monta pientä pullo. <BR>Painiketta vasemmassa alakulmassa hyppy voi ohjata oravia hypätä kaksoisnapsauttamalla toissijainen voi hypätä, hypätä ylittää ammattitaitoisen käytön kahden peräkkäisen esteitä Oh, lasku oikeassa alakulmassa on painike, pidä ohjata oravia liukua eteenpäin, välttää korkeilla esteitä. Oravat keräävät useita pulloja jokainen, kasvaa elämän. <BR>PS: Tämä peli on mukautettu peli "iRunner" <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 17 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Kiina - yksinkertaistettu/Kiina - perinteinen<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[C’est un jeu intéressant de parkour très rapide, l’opération de ce jeu esttrès simple. Dans le jeu, vous jouerez un petit écureuil, ce que vous devez faire est de courir en avant et de continuer à éviter divers obstacles, et de recueillir autant flacon le plus assez possible.<BR>　　Bouton du saut dans le coin inférieur gauche peut contrôler les écureuils sauter, Double-clic peut exciter deux sauts, l'utilisation habile de deux sauts permet de franchir des obstacles consécutifs. Bouton dans le coin inférieur droit est le déclin, vous pouvez contrôler les écureuils coulisser vers l'avant en maintenant la touche, pour éviter les obstacles en haut. Chaque fors quand  l’ écureuil recueille plusieurs bouteilles, il gagne une vie.<BR>　　PS : Ce jeu est une adaptation du jeu "iRunner". <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 17 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[C’est un jeu intéressant de parkour très rapide, l’opération de ce jeu esttrès simple. Dans le jeu, vous jouerez un petit écureuil, ce que vous devez faire est de courir en avant et de continuer à éviter divers obstacles, et de recueillir autant flacon le plus assez possible.<BR>　　Bouton du saut dans le coin inférieur gauche peut contrôler les écureuils sauter, Double-clic peut exciter deux sauts, l'utilisation habile de deux sauts permet de franchir des obstacles consécutifs. Bouton dans le coin inférieur droit est le déclin, vous pouvez contrôler les écureuils coulisser vers l'avant en maintenant la touche, pour éviter les obstacles en haut. Chaque fors quand  l’ écureuil recueille plusieurs bouteilles, il gagne une vie.<BR>　　PS : Ce jeu est une adaptation du jeu "iRunner". <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 17 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Si tratta di un gioco Parkour a ritmo veloce, semplice da operare,. Nel gioco fai il ruolo di uno scoiattolo che deve sempre correre avanti evitando vari ostacoli nella strada e raccogliendo piu’ possibile le boccette di medicina.<BR>Il bottone di salto in basso a sinistra e’ quello per regolare come salta lo scoiattolo, qui facendosi due click per fare il salto progressive che e’ neccessario per scavalcare gli ostacoli in continuo; Il bottone di andamento scivoloso in basso a destra serve a evitare gli ostacoli in alto. A seguito di aver raccolto un certo numero di boccette, lo scoiattolo ha in piu’ una vita.<BR>NB: Tale gioco e’ stato estratto dal gioco “iRunner”. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 17 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Cinese semplificato/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[非常に面白くてリズムも速いパルクールのゲームです。このゲームはとても簡単な操作で、あなたが小さなリスの役を演じる、必要なのは前に走ってそれに様々な障害物を回避し続けて、しかも、できるだけ多くの小さなボトルを収集することです。 <BR>　　左下隅にあるジャンプのボタンはリスのジャンプを制御することができます。ダブルクリックをしてから二等ジャンプすることができ、二等ジャンプを熟練した後連続の障害物を回避し続けますよ。右下隅はスライドボタンで、それを押すと、リスが前方にスライドを制御する、高空の障害物を避けるためです。リスは幾つかのボトルを収集する毎に寿命を長くします。<BR>PS：このゲームは「iRunner」から採用されました。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 17 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>中国語(簡体字)/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[En veldig interessant hektisk parkour spill, er spillet svært enkel operasjon, i spillet vil du spille en liten ekorn, du trenger å gjøre er å løpe frem og fortsette å unngå ulike hindringer og samle så mange små flaske. <BR>-Knappen i nedre venstre hjørne av hoppet kan styre ekorn hoppe, dobbeltklikker du på videregående kan hoppe, hoppe å krysse dyktige bruk av to påfølgende hindringer Oh, nedgang i nedre høyre hjørne er en knapp, trykk og hold for å kontrollere ekorn skyves forover, å unngå høytliggende hindringer. Ekorn samle flere flasker hver, vil øke et liv. <BR>PS: Dette spillet er tilpasset fra spillet "iRunner" <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 17 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Kinesisk - Forenklet/Kinesisk - Tradisjonell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Dit zeer interessante parkour spel is heel eenvoudig te bedienen, in het spel zul je het rol van een kleine eekhoorntje spelen, wat je moet doen is steeds vooruit te lopen en de verschillende obstakels in de weg staan te passeren en zorgt ervoor om zoveel mogelijk kleine flestjes te verzamelen.<BR>Door op het knopje aan het linksonder te drukken, het eekhoorntje gaat dan springen, dubbel-klik erop, dan gaat ze twee keer achterelkaar springen, kunt U het knop goed beheersen dan kan het eekhoorntje steeds de hindernissen passeren; het knop aan het rechtsonder is voor daling,  na het indrukken gaat het eekhoorntje naar voren glijden, daardoor kan het eekhoortje de grote obstakels in de lucht passeren. Na het verzamelen van een aantal flesjes, wordt het "leven" van het eekhoorntje een keer verlen <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 17 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Chinees - Vereenvoudigd/Chinees - Traditioneel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[En mycket intressant snabbt tempo parkour spel, spelet är mycket enkel operation, i spelet du kommer att spela en liten ekorre, du behöver göra är att köra framåt och fortsätta att undvika olika hinder och samla så många små flaska. <BR>Knappen i det nedre vänstra hörnet av hoppet kan styra ekorrar hoppa, dubbelklicka på den sekundära kan hoppa, hoppa för att korsa den skickliga användning av två på varandra följande hinder Oh, nedgång i det nedre högra hörnet finns en knapp, tryck och håll för att styra ekorrar glida framåt, för att undvika hög höjd hinder. Ekorrar samlar flera flaskor vardera, kommer att öka ett liv. <BR>PS: Det här spelet är anpassad från spelet "iRunner" <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 17 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Kinesiska - förenklad/Kinesiska - traditionell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2014 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
