<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00171_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>120332240</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA["Kingdom Tre Musketerer" er et eventyr kortspil kamp. <BR>Jeg kan nyde den oprindelige historie, som hovedpersonen en kvinde fire personer. <BR><BR>Player mål er at genvinde al slottet blev røvet. Du kan vælge en favorit karakter, at angribe fjenden. <BR>Du kan vinde eller tab bestemmes af den type kort ud af hinanden for at vinde for at være 0 antallet af fjendens soldater. <BR>Ved at øge flere kort, evnen af den karakter, er det muligt at fortsætte med fordel slag. <BR>Den vandt hele 25 af slottet, så man i fred til at lede riget. <BR><BR>Det er til visning af kun japanske spil. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 115 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA["Kingdom drei Musketiere" ist ein Abenteuer-Kartenspiel Schlacht. <BR>Ich kann die Originalgeschichte zu genießen, dass die Hauptfigur eine Frau von vier Personen. <BR><BR>Spieler Ziel ist es, wieder die ganze Burg wurde ausgeraubt. Sie können einen Lieblings-Charakter aus, um den Feind anzugreifen. <BR>Sie können gewinnen oder Verlust wird durch die Art der Karte aus einem anderen bestimmt, um zu gewinnen, um 0 die Anzahl der feindlichen Soldaten sein. <BR>Durch die Erhöhung mehr Karten, die Fähigkeit des Charakters, ist es möglich, in vorteilhafter Weise vorgehen Schlacht. <BR>Es gewann alle 25 von der Burg, so dass Sie in Ruhe, um das Reich zu führen. <BR><BR>Es ist auf die Anzeige nur der japanischen Spiel. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 115 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Japanisch<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Kingdom Three Musketeers is an adventure card game battle. <BR>I can enjoy the original story that the main character a woman of four people. <BR><BR>Player objective is to regain all the castle was robbed. You can select a favorite character, to attack the enemy. <BR>You can win or loss is determined by the type of card out of one another to win to be 0 the number of enemy soldiers. <BR>By increasing more cards, the ability of the character, it is possible to proceed advantageously battle. <BR>It won all 25 of the castle, so you in peace to lead the kingdom. <BR><BR>It is to the display of only the Japanese game. <BR><BR>Package size: 115 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Japanese<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA["Unido tres mosqueteros" es una batalla tarjeta de juego de aventura. <BR>Puedo disfrutar de la historia original que el personaje principal a una mujer de cada cuatro personas. <BR><BR>Objetivo del jugador es recuperar todo el castillo fue robado. Se puede seleccionar un personaje favorito, para atacar al enemigo. <BR>Puedes ganar o pérdida se determina por el tipo de tarjeta de uno al otro que ganar para ser 0 el número de soldados enemigos. <BR>Al aumentar más tarjetas, la capacidad del carácter, es posible proceder ventajosamente batalla. <BR>Ganó los 25 del castillo, por lo que en paz para dirigir el reino. <BR><BR>Es a la pantalla de sólo el juego japonés. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 115 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Japonés<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA["Kingdom Kolme muskettisoturia" on seikkailu korttipeli taistelu. <BR>Voin nauttia alkuperäinen tarina, joka päähenkilö nainen neljä ihmistä. <BR><BR>Pelaajan tavoitteena on saada takaisin kaikki linnan ryöstettiin. Voit valita suosikki merkki, hyökätä vihollisen. <BR>Voit voittaa tai tappio määräytyy kortin tyypistä erilleen toisistaan ​​voittaa olla 0 määrä vihollisen sotilaita. <BR>Lisäämällä enemmän kortteja, kyky hahmo, on mahdollista edetä edullisesti taisteluun. <BR>Se voitti kaikki 25 linnan, joten voit rauhassa johtamaan valtakuntaan. <BR><BR>Se on näyttö vain japanilainen peli. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 115 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA["Uni Trois Mousquetaires" est une carte bataille jeu d'aventure.<BR>Je peux profiter de l'histoire originale que le personnage principal d'une femme de quatre personnes. <BR><BR>Objectif du joueur est de retrouver tous le château a été volé. Vous pouvez sélectionner un personnage préféré, pour attaquer l'ennemi. <BR>Vous pouvez gagner ou la perte est déterminé par le type de carte sur l'autre pour gagner à 0 le nombre de soldats ennemis. <BR>En augmentant d'autres catégories, la capacité du personnage, il est possible de procéder avantageusement bataille. <BR>Il a remporté tous les 25 du château, de sorte que vous en paix à la tête du royaume. <BR><BR>Il est à l'affichage de seulement le jeu japonais. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 115 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Japonais<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA["Unito Tre Moschettieri" è una battaglia gioco di carte avventura. <BR>Posso godere la storia originale che il personaggio principale una donna di quattro persone. <BR><BR>Obiettivo del giocatore è quello di recuperare tutto il castello fu derubato. È possibile selezionare un personaggio preferito, per attaccare il nemico. <BR>Si può vincere o perdita è determinato dal tipo di scheda di un altro per vincere a 0 il numero di soldati nemici. <BR>Aumentando più carte, la capacità del personaggio, è possibile procedere vantaggiosamente battaglia. <BR>Ha vinto tutti i 25 del castello, così in pace a guidare il regno. <BR><BR>È alla visualizzazione del solo gioco giapponese. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 115 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Giapponese<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[フェリス=ランカスターは１４歳で王国の頂き「皇女」となる。<BR>平穏に時が流れるかと思われていた矢先、王国で次々に反旗を翻す城が現れる。<BR>幼き皇女を守るため伝説の四人の女騎士は再び戦地へと赴く。<BR>彼女たちは再び、国を一つにする事ができるのか……<BR><BR>４人の女騎士の戦いを描く、それが、<BR>戦記アドベンチャーカードバトルゲーム「Kingdom 三銃士」です。<BR><BR>ゲームはキャラクター達のストーリーを楽しみながら、奪われた城をカードバトルによって取り返します。<BR><BR>カードバトルとは、戦力となる「兵種カード」と呼ばれるカードを選択し、互いのカードを出し合いカードの優劣で勝敗が決する、誰もが簡単に楽しむことができます。相手の思考を読み、的確な兵種カードを出し、敵の兵力を０にする事で勝利をつかむことができます。<BR><BR>時に兵種カードを購入して軍事を増強したり、キャラクターの能力を上げたり、ランカスター王国を強くしながら反旗を翻した敵に立ち向かいます。<BR><BR>キャラクターの特性を活かし、全ての城を取り戻し、<BR>混乱するランカスター王国を再び一つの国にまとめ上げよう！！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 115 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA["Kingdom tre musketerer" er et eventyr kortspill kamp. <BR>Jeg kan nyte den opprinnelige historien at hovedpersonen en kvinne på fire personer. <BR><BR>Spiller Målet er å gjenvinne all slottet ble ranet. Du kan velge en favoritt karakter, for å angripe fienden. <BR>Du kan vinne eller tap bestemmes av hvilken type kort ut av hverandre for å vinne for å være 0 antall fiendtlige soldater. <BR>Ved å øke flere kort, muligheten av karakter, er det mulig å gå videre med fordel slaget. <BR>Den vant hele 25 av slottet, slik at du i ro for å lede riket. <BR><BR>Det er til visning av bare den japanske spillet. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 115 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA["Koninkrijk Drie Musketiers" is een avontuur kaartspel strijd. <BR>Ik kan genieten van het originele verhaal dat de hoofdpersoon een vrouw van vier mensen. <BR><BR>Speler doel is om terug te krijgen alle het kasteel werd beroofd. U kunt een favoriete personage kiezen, om de vijand aan te vallen. <BR>Je kunt winnen of verliezen wordt bepaald door het type kaart uit elkaar om te winnen 0 het aantal vijandelijke soldaten. <BR>Door het verhogen meer kaarten, het vermogen van het karakter, is het mogelijk om met voordeel gaan strijd. <BR>Het won alle 25 van het kasteel, zodat je in alle rust naar het koninkrijk te leiden. <BR><BR>Het is de weergave van alleen het Japanse spel. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 115 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA["Kingdom tre musketörerna" är ett äventyr kortspel strid. <BR>Jag kan njuta av den ursprungliga berättelsen som huvudpersonen en kvinna av fyra personer. <BR><BR>Spelare mål är att återfå hela slottet var rånad. Du kan välja en favorit karaktär, för att attackera fienden. <BR>Du kan vinna eller förlust bestäms av vilken typ av kort av varandra för att vinna för att vara 0 antalet fiendesoldater. <BR>Genom att öka fler kort, är det förmågan hos det tecken möjligt att gå vidare med fördel slaget. <BR>Den vann hela 25 av slottet, så att du i lugn och ro för att leda riket. <BR><BR>Det är att visningen av endast den japanska spelet. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 115 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska<BR><BR>(c)2014 AQUADIA Co., Ltd.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Adventure"/><genre value="Games:Simulation"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Language.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
