<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00176_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>37995760</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Undgå terninger, og forsøge at få en høj score! En test af reaktion hastighed og fingerfærdighed. <BR><BR>Saml power op s komme forbi blokkene. Red PowerUp os gøre dig uovervindelig, Blå PowerUp ild en energi stråle på din efterspørgsel til at ødelægge blokke foran dig! <BR><BR>3 vanskeligheder at vælge imellem: <BR>Easy holder tid på en langsom hastighed. <BR>Normale starter langsom, så tiden går hurtigere, jo højere din score (stopper få hurtigere ved 100). <BR>Hard gør tid gå med dobbelt hastighed lige fra starten. <BR><BR>Dette er en hurtig simpelt spil at spille, når du har et par minutter til overs, med fokus på hurtige load-tider og instant play! <BR><BR>Vær på udkig efter nye funktioner i kommende opdateringer til dette spil. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 37 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Vermeiden Sie die Würfel und versuchen, eine hohe Punktzahl zu bekommen! Ein Test der Reaktionsgeschwindigkeit und Geschicklichkeit. <BR><BR>Sammeln PowerUp die in der Vergangenheit die Blöcke zu bekommen. Red PowerUp machen Sie unbesiegbar, Blau PowerUp Feuer ein Energiestrahl auf Ihrer Nachfrage, um die Blöcke vor euch zerstören! <BR><BR>3 Schwierigkeiten zur Auswahl: <BR>Einfach hält die Zeit mit einer geringen Geschwindigkeit. <BR>Normale beginnt langsam, dann schneller geht Zeit desto höher die Punktzahl (Haltestellen immer schneller bei 100). <BR>Fest macht Zeit zu gehen mit doppelter Geschwindigkeit von Anfang an. <BR><BR>Dies ist eine schnelle einfaches Spiel zu spielen, wenn Sie ein paar Minuten Zeit haben, konzentrierte sich auf schnelle Ladezeiten und Instant-Play! <BR><BR>Seien Sie auf der Suche nach neuen Fea <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 37 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Avoid the cubes, and try to get a high score!  A test of reaction speed and dexterity.<BR><BR>Collect PowerUp's to get past the blocks. Red PowerUp's make you invincible, Blue PowerUp's fire a energy beam on your demand to destroy the blocks in front of you!<BR><BR>3 difficulties to choose from: <BR>Easy keeps time at a slow speed.<BR>Normal starts slow, then time goes faster the higher your score (stops getting faster at 100).<BR>Hard makes time go at double speed right from the start.<BR><BR>This is a quick simple game to play when you have a few minutes to spare, focused on quick load times and instant play!<BR><BR>Be on the look out for new features in upcoming updates to this game. <BR><BR>Package size: 37 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Avoid the cubes, and try to get a high score!  A test of reaction speed and dexterity.<BR><BR>Collect PowerUp's to get past the blocks. Red PowerUp's make you invincible, Blue PowerUp's fire a energy beam on your demand to destroy the blocks in front of you!<BR><BR>3 difficulties to choose from: <BR>Easy keeps time at a slow speed.<BR>Normal starts slow, then time goes faster the higher your score (stops getting faster at 100).<BR>Hard makes time go at double speed right from the start.<BR><BR>This is a quick simple game to play when you have a few minutes to spare, focused on quick load times and instant play!<BR><BR>Be on the look out for new features in upcoming updates to this game. <BR><BR>Package size: 37 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Avoid the cubes, and try to get a high score!  A test of reaction speed and dexterity.<BR><BR>Collect PowerUp's to get past the blocks. Red PowerUp's make you invincible, Blue PowerUp's fire a energy beam on your demand to destroy the blocks in front of you!<BR><BR>3 difficulties to choose from: <BR>Easy keeps time at a slow speed.<BR>Normal starts slow, then time goes faster the higher your score (stops getting faster at 100).<BR>Hard makes time go at double speed right from the start.<BR><BR>This is a quick simple game to play when you have a few minutes to spare, focused on quick load times and instant play!<BR><BR>Be on the look out for new features in upcoming updates to this game. <BR><BR>Package size: 37 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Avoid the cubes, and try to get a high score!  A test of reaction speed and dexterity.<BR><BR>Collect PowerUp's to get past the blocks. Red PowerUp's make you invincible, Blue PowerUp's fire a energy beam on your demand to destroy the blocks in front of you!<BR><BR>3 difficulties to choose from: <BR>Easy keeps time at a slow speed.<BR>Normal starts slow, then time goes faster the higher your score (stops getting faster at 100).<BR>Hard makes time go at double speed right from the start.<BR><BR>This is a quick simple game to play when you have a few minutes to spare, focused on quick load times and instant play!<BR><BR>Be on the look out for new features in upcoming updates to this game. <BR><BR>Package size: 37 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Evite los cubos, y tratar de obtener una alta puntuación! Una prueba de la velocidad de reacción y la destreza. <BR><BR>Recoger PowerUp de deshacerse de los bloques. De PowerUp rojas te hacen invencible, el fuego del azul PowerUp un haz de energía en su demanda para destruir los bloques de delante de ti! <BR><BR>3 dificultades para elegir: <BR>Fácil mantiene la hora a una velocidad lenta. <BR>Arranques lentos normales, entonces el tiempo pasa más rápido cuanto mayor sea su puntuación (se detiene cada vez más rápido a 100). <BR>Duro hace tiempo ir al doble de velocidad desde el principio. <BR><BR>Se trata de un simple juego rápido de jugar cuando tienes un par de minutos de sobra, se centró en los tiempos de carga rápidos y juego instantáneo! <BR><BR>Esté en la mirada hacia fuera para las nuevas características en los próx <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 37 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Vältä kuutiot, ja yrittää saada korkeat pisteet!Testi reaktion nopeutta ja näppäryyttä. <BR><BR>Kerää PowerUp n ohittamaan lohkot. Red PowerUp n tehdä sinusta voittamaton, Blue PowerUp tulta energia säteen toiveenne tuhota lohkojen edessäsi! <BR><BR>3 vaikeuksia valita: <BR>Helppo pitää ajan hitaalla nopeudella. <BR>Normaalikäynnistyksille hidas, niin aika kuluu nopeammin korkeammat pisteet (pysähtyy yhä nopeampia 100). <BR>Kova tekee aika mennä kaksinkertaisella nopeudella alusta alkaen. <BR><BR>Tämä on nopea yksinkertainen peli pelata, kun sinulla on muutama minuutti ylimääräistä, keskittyi nopeasti latausajat ja instant pelata! <BR><BR>Ole varoa uusia ominaisuuksia tulevista päivityksistä tähän peliin. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 37 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Éviter les cubes, et essayer d'obtenir un score élevé! Un test de la vitesse de réaction et la dextérité. <BR><BR>Recueillir PowerUp de aller au-delà des blocs. PowerUp rouges de vous faire invincible, le feu de bleu PowerUp un faisceau d'énergie sur votre demande de détruire les blocs en face de vous! <BR><BR>3 difficultés à choisir: <BR>Facile garde le temps à une vitesse lente. <BR>Démarrage normal lents, puis le temps passe plus vite plus votre score (arrêts de plus en plus rapide à 100). <BR>Dur fait passer le temps à double vitesse dès le début. <BR><BR>C'est un jeu simple et rapide à jouer quand vous avez quelques minutes à perdre, a porté sur les temps de chargement rapides et un instant! <BR><BR>Soyez à l'affût de nouvelles fonctionnalités dans les mises à jour à venir à ce match. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 37 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Éviter les cubes, et essayer d'obtenir un score élevé! Un test de la vitesse de réaction et la dextérité. <BR><BR>Recueillir PowerUp de aller au-delà des blocs. PowerUp rouges de vous faire invincible, le feu de bleu PowerUp un faisceau d'énergie sur votre demande de détruire les blocs en face de vous! <BR><BR>3 difficultés à choisir: <BR>Facile garde le temps à une vitesse lente. <BR>Démarrage normal lents, puis le temps passe plus vite plus votre score (arrêts de plus en plus rapide à 100). <BR>Dur fait passer le temps à double vitesse dès le début. <BR><BR>C'est un jeu simple et rapide à jouer quand vous avez quelques minutes à perdre, a porté sur les temps de chargement rapides et un instant! <BR><BR>Soyez à l'affût de nouvelles fonctionnalités dans les mises à jour à venir à ce match. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 37 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Evitare i cubi, e cercare di ottenere un punteggio alto! Un test di velocità di reazione e destrezza. <BR><BR>Raccogliere PowerUp di per superare i blocchi. PowerUp rosse ti fanno invincibile, il fuoco Blue PowerUp un fascio di energia su vostra richiesta per distruggere i blocchi davanti a voi! <BR><BR>3 difficoltà tra cui scegliere: <BR>Facile tiene il tempo a bassa velocità. <BR>Partenze normali lenti, poi il tempo passa più velocemente più punti (si ferma sempre più veloce a 100). <BR>Difficile rende il tempo va a doppia velocità fin dall'inizio. <BR><BR>Questo è un breve gioco semplice da giocare quando si hanno pochi minuti per risparmiare, focalizzata su tempi di caricamento rapidi e instant play! <BR><BR>Essere alla ricerca di nuove funzionalità nei prossimi aggiornamenti su questo gioco. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 37 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>キューブを避け、高得点を取得してみてください！反応速度と器用のテスト。 <BR><BR>ブロックを乗り越えるためにパワーアップのを収集します。レッドパワーアップの目の前でブロックを破壊するためにブルーパワーアップの火のエネルギービームあなたの要求に応じて、あなたは無敵にする！ <BR><BR>から選択する3難しさ： <BR>簡単には低速での時間を保持します。 <BR>遅い通常の開始は、その時間がより速く、より高いスコアになる（100で速くなって停止します）。 <BR>ハードは時間が最初から倍の速度で移動します。 <BR><BR>これはあなたが余裕に数分を持っているときに再生するための簡単な単純なゲームですが、迅速なロード時間とインスタントプレイに焦点を当てた！ <BR><BR>このゲームへの今後のアップデートで新機能を見て外になる。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 37 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Unngå kuber, og prøve å få en høy score! En test av reaksjonshastighet og fingerferdighet. <BR><BR>Samle PowerUp er å komme forbi blokkene. Røde PowerUp oss gjøre deg uovervinnelig, Blå PowerUp ild en energistråle på ditt krav om å ødelegge blokkene foran deg! <BR><BR>3 vanskeligheter å velge mellom: <BR>Easy holder tid ved lav hastighet. <BR>Normale starter sakte, så tiden går fortere jo høyere poengsum (stopper stadig raskere på 100). <BR>Hard gjør tid gå med dobbel hastighet helt fra starten. <BR><BR>Dette er en rask enkelt spill å spille når du har noen minutter til overs, med fokus på raske lastetider og instant play! <BR><BR>Vær på utkikk etter nye funksjoner i kommende oppdateringer til dette spillet. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 37 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Vermijd de blokjes, en proberen om een hoge score te halen! Een test van de reactie snelheid en behendigheid. <BR><BR>Verzamel PowerUp's verleden de blokken te krijgen. Red PowerUp maken je onoverwinnelijk, Blue PowerUp's brand een energiestraal op uw vraag om de blokken te vernietigen voor u! <BR><BR>3 moeilijkheden om uit te kiezen: <BR>Gemakkelijk houdt de tijd bij een lage snelheid. <BR>Normaal begint langzaam, dan is de tijd gaat sneller hoe hoger je score (stopt steeds sneller op 100). <BR>Moeilijk maakt tijd gaan op dubbele snelheid vanaf het begin. <BR><BR>Dit is een snelle eenvoudig spel om te spelen als je een paar minuten te sparen, gericht op snelle laadtijden en direct spelen! <BR><BR>Ben op zoek naar nieuwe mogelijkheden in de komende updates voor dit spel. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 37 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Unikaj kostek i spróbować uzyskać wysoki wynik!Test szybkości reakcji i zręczności. <BR><BR>Zdobywaj PowerUp jest ominąć bloki. Czerwone PowerUp Marka jesteś niezwyciężony, ogień Niebieski PowerUp w wiązki energii na żądanie zniszczyć bloki przed tobą! <BR><BR>3 trudności do wyboru: <BR>Łatwo ustawia czas w zwolnionym tempie. <BR>Normalny zaczyna powoli, wtedy czas idzie szybciej wyższy wynik (zatrzymuje się coraz szybciej na 100). <BR>Czas iść ciężko robi podwójną prędkością od samego początku. <BR><BR>Jest to szybkie proste gry do gry, gdy masz kilka wolnych minut, skupia się na szybkich czas ładowania i instant play! <BR><BR>Być na zwrócić uwagę na nowe funkcje w kolejnych aktualizacjach tego meczu. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 37 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Undvik kuber, och försöka få en hög poäng! Ett test av reaktionshastigheten och fingerfärdighet. <BR><BR>Samla PowerUp s att komma förbi blocken. Röda PowerUp oss göra dig oövervinnerlig, blå PowerUp eld en energistråle på din begäran att förstöra blocken framför dig! <BR><BR>3 svårigheter att välja mellan: <BR>Lätt håller tiden i långsam hastighet. <BR>Normala starter långsamma, då tiden går fortare desto högre poäng (slutar blir snabbare vid 100). <BR>Hård gör tid gå med dubbel hastighet redan från början. <BR><BR>Detta är en sammanfattning av enkelt spel att spela när du har några minuter över, med fokus på snabba laddningstider och instant play! <BR><BR>Var på utkik efter nya funktioner i kommande uppdateringar av detta spel. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 37 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 David Omari<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
