<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00005_00">
 <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>20564688</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[Beats Trellisで音楽を作る　どこでもいつでも<br>Beats Trellisのシステムでさまざまな楽器やドラムやバックビートなどを使える<br>あたなのミュージックを創作できる　「生プレイ」できる<br><br>特徴<br>１６楽器トラック<br>８ドラムトラック<br>８バックビートトラック<br>１５楽器ボイス<br>６ドラムボイス－6種類のパーカッション音付き<br>６バックビートボイスー　プロな効果でき<br><br>エフェクトユニット：エコーエフェクトを楽器やドラムトラックに入れ！<br>オートエフェクトユニット：簡単に曲線を描くと楽器のボイスを変更させ！<br>「生プレイ」：ミュージックトラックを自由に再生や終止できる、Trellisはトラックの同時性を確保する<br><br>コンテンツ容量:20 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Create music any time, any place with Beats Trellis.<br>Using a simple grid based interface, Beats Trellis gives you a palette of instruments, drum kits and breakbeats, allowing you to create music patterns and play them back "live".<br><br>Features:<br>16 instrument tracks<br>8 drum kit tracks<br>8 breakbeat tracks.<br>15 instrument voices<br>6 drum kits - Each containing 6 different percussion sounds<br>6 breakbeats - Great for adding a professional touch to your mix!<br><br>Effects unit - Add echo (delay) effects to your instrument and drum tracks!<br>Automation effects unit - Simply draw a curve and hear your instrument voices come to life!<br>"Live Play" - Trigger your music tracks to play or stop. Trellis ensures that tracks are kept in sync.<br><br>Package size: 20 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Créer de la musique n'importe quand, n'importe où avec Beats Treillis<br>Grâce à une interface simple, Beats Trellis vous donne accès à une palette d'instruments, de batteries et de breakbeats, ce qui vous permet de créer des motifs musicaux et de les jouer en "live"<br><br>Caractéristiques:<br>16 pistes d'instruments<br>8 pistes de batterie<br>8 pistes breakbeat<br>15 voix instruments<br>6 batteries - Chacune contenant 6 différents sons de percussion<br>6 breakbeats - Idéal pour ajouter une touche professionnelle à votre mix<br><br>Effets - Ajouter des effets d'écho à vos piste d'instrument et de batterie<br>Automatisation des effets - Il suffit de dessiner une courbe et pour entendre vos instruments prendre vie<br>"Live Play" - Déclenchez la lecture ou l’arrêt de votre musique. Trellis veille à ce que les pistes sont bien synchronisés<br><br>Taille du paquet: 20 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Crea musica ovunque e quando vuoi con Beats Trellis.<br>Grazie a una semplice interfaccia basata su griglie, Beats Trellis è in grado di fornire una quantità diversa di strumenti, batterie e ritmi per aiutarti a creare vere e proprie tracce musicali da suonare dal “vivo”!<br><br>Caratteristiche:<br>16 Tracce strumentali<br>8 Tracce per batteria<br>8 Tracce breakbeat<br>15 Diversi strumenti<br>6 Tracce contenenti ognuna 6 diversi strumenti di percussione<br>6 Breakbeat – Un ottimo modo per aggiungere un tocco di professionalità al tuo mix!<br><br>Effetti audio – Aggiungi diversi effetti a strumenti e batteria!<br>Effetti automatici – Disegna una curva e ascolta la musica!<br>“Live Play” – Scegli quando attivare le tue tracce e Trellis si occuperà di tenerle sincronizzate.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 20 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Crea tu propia música en cualquier momento y estés donde estés con Beats Trellis.<br>Con un interfaz muy fácil de usar,  Beats Trellis te proporciona una paleta de instrumentos, baterías y ritmos predefinidos para que crees las secuencias de sonidos que más te gustan.<br><br>Características:<br>16 pistas para instrumentos<br>8 pistas para baterías<br>8 pistas para mezclar ritmos<br>15 instrumentos disponibles<br>6 baterías, cada una con 6 sonidos de percusión<br>6 ritmos predefinidos, perfectos para darle un toque profesional a tus mezclas.<br><br>Unidad de efectos: ¡Añade eco a tus pistas! ¡Y configura a tu gusto los efectos automáticos disponibles!<br>Mezcla y escucha tu música sin preocuparte de sincronizar tus pistas, ¡Trellis lo hace por ti!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 20 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Kreiere Musik zu jeder Zeit, an jedem Ort, wo auch immer mit Beats Trellis.<br>Mit einem einfachen Grid-basierte Eingabesystem und einer Palette von Instrumenten, Schlafzeugen und Breakbeats,<br>kann mit Beats Trellis Musik erstellt und "live" wiedergegeben werden.<br><br>Funktionen:<br>16 Instrumentalspuren.<br>8  Schlagzeugspuren.<br>8  Breakbeat-Spuren.<br>15 Instrumente<br>6  Schlagzeuge - jeweils 6 verschiedene Percussionsklänge<br>6 Breakbeats - Für den professionellen Touch zu Ihrem Mix!<br><br>Echo Effektgerät - Echo(Delay)-Effekte für alle Instrumente und Schalgzeuge!<br>Automations Effektgerät - Einfach eine Kurve zeichnen und schon wird das Instrument zum Leben erweckt!<br>"Live Play" - Die Musikspuren abspielen oder stoppen. Trellis sorgt dafür, dass die Spuren synchron gehalten werden.<br><br>Paketgröße: 20 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Create music any time, any place with Beats Trellis.<br>Using a simple grid based interface, Beats Trellis gives you a palette of instruments, drum kits and breakbeats, allowing you to create music patterns and play them back "live".<br><br>Features:<br>16 instrument tracks<br>8 drum kit tracks<br>8 breakbeat tracks.<br>15 instrument voices<br>6 drum kits - Each containing 6 different percussion sounds<br>6 breakbeats - Great for adding a professional touch to your mix!<br><br>Effects unit - Add echo (delay) effects to your instrument and drum tracks!<br>Automation effects unit - Simply draw a curve and hear your instrument voices come to life!<br>"Live Play" - Trigger your music tracks to play or stop. Trellis ensures that tracks are kept in sync.<br><br>Package size: 20 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Créer de la musique n'importe quand, n'importe où avec Beats Treillis<br>Grâce à une interface simple, Beats Trellis vous donne accès à une palette d'instruments, de batteries et de breakbeats, ce qui vous permet de créer des motifs musicaux et de les jouer en "live"<br><br>Caractéristiques:<br>16 pistes d'instruments<br>8 pistes de batterie<br>8 pistes breakbeat<br>15 voix instruments<br>6 batteries - Chacune contenant 6 différents sons de percussion<br>6 breakbeats - Idéal pour ajouter une touche professionnelle à votre mix<br><br>Effets - Ajouter des effets d'écho à vos piste d'instrument et de batterie<br>Automatisation des effets - Il suffit de dessiner une courbe et pour entendre vos instruments prendre vie<br>"Live Play" - Déclenchez la lecture ou l’arrêt de votre musique. Trellis veille à ce que les pistes sont bien synchronisés<br><br>Taille du programme: 20 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Apps:Audio"/>
  <genre value="Apps:Music"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
