<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00020_00">
 <appVersion>1.05</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>24733408</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[レッグサイドとミッドオフの違いがわかる？クリケット専門家だと思う？審判より良い仕事ができると思う？<br><br>あなたに必要なクリケットトリビアアプリはYou Are The Umpireだけです。<br><br>伝説のポール・トレヴィリオンによって描かれたたくさんのオフィシャルアートワークと、元国際審判ジョン・ホルダーの監修の下、You Are The Umpireは究極のクリケットトリビアゲームです。<br><br>特徴：<br><br>• スキルを試される2種類のゲームモード： 一切の間違いが許されないSudden Death と、あなたがホワイトコートに値するか根性を試されるAssessmentです！<br>• 美しい手書きのイラスト <br>• ありふれたものから全く馬鹿げたようなものまで何百もの質問と、クリケット史上で最も偉大な審判の一人による解答<br><br>コンテンツ容量:24 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Know your legside from your silly mid-off? Consider yourself a cricket expert? Think you could do a better job than the umpire?<br><br>You Are The Umpire is the only cricket trivia app you’ll ever need.<br><br>Incorporating a plethora of official artwork drawn by the legend that is Paul Trevillion and official guidance on the laws of the game from former International umpire John Holder, You Are The Umpire is the ultimate cricket trivia game.<br><br>Features:<br><br>• 2 game modes to test your skills: Sudden Death which makes no allowances for bad decisions and Assessment which will test your mettle and see if you are worthy of your white coat!<br>• Beautifully hand drawn illustrations <br>• Hundreds of questions ranging from the everyday to the flat-out ridiculous with answers from one of the greatest umpiring names in cricket<br><br>Package size: 24 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Vous maîtrisez à la perfection la balle et la batte ?<br>Vous pensez être incollable sur le cricket ?<br>Vous pensez pouvoir faire mieux que l'arbitre ?<br><br>You Are The Umpire est l'application de cricket qu'il vous faut.<br><br>Intégrant de nombreuses reproductions artistiques officielles du célèbre dessinateur Paul Trevillion et utilisant les conseils officiels de John Holder, ancien arbitre international de cricket, You Are The Umpire est le jeu de culture par excellence dans le domaine du cricket.<br><br>Caractéristiques :<br><br>• 2 modes de jeu pour mettre vos compétences à rude épreuve : Sudden Death qui sera sans pitié avec les mauvaises réponses, et Assessment qui testera votre courage sur le terrain<br>• De superbes illustrations <br>• Des centaines de questions très variées avec les réponses de l'un des meilleurs arbitres de l'histoire du cricket<br><br>Taille du paquet: 24 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Sai distinguere tra leg side e mid-off? Ti consideri un esperto di cricket? Pensi che potresti fare meglio dell’arbitro?<br><br>You Are The Umpire è l’unica App di curiosità di cricket di cui tu abbia bisogno.<br><br>Con una vasta gamma di disegni originali creati da Paul Trevillon e con la consulenza sulle regole del gioco dell’ex arbitro internazionale John Holder, You Are The Umpire è il gioco definitivo di curiosità sul cricket.<br><br>Caratteristiche:<br><br>• 2 modalità di gioco per mettere alla prova le tue abilità: Sudden Death, che non lascia spazio a decisioni sbagliate e Assessment che metterà alla prova il tuo coraggio per scoprire se sei degno di indossare la tua divisa!<br>• Bellissime illustrazioni disegnate a mano <br>• Centinaia di domande, dal quotidiano alle curiosità più strane, con le risposte di uno dei più grandi arbitri della storia del cricket.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 24 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¿Te sabes el reglamento del críquet de pe a pa? ¿Te consideras un experto en este anglosajón deporte? ¿Crees que lo harías mejor que el árbitro?<br><br>You Are The Umpire es la única aplicación de preguntas sobre críquet que necesitas.<br><br>Con montones de ilustraciones oficiales dibujadas por el legendario Paul Trevillion, y orientación oficial sobre el reglamento del ex árbitro John Holder, You Are The Umpire es el juego definitivo de preguntas sobre críquet.<br><br>Características:<br><br>• 2 modos de juego para poner a prueba tu destreza: Sudden Death, que no hace concesiones cuando te equivocas, y Assessment, que pondrá a prueba tus nervios de acero para ver si mereces ostentar tan alto cargo!<br>• Preciosas ilustraciones dibujadas a mano<br>• Cientos de preguntas que pasan de lo básico a lo ridículamente concreto, con respuestas de uno de los nombres más destacados en el arbitraje del críquet<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 24 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Du kannst deine Beinseite von der Mitte unterscheiden?<br>Du siehst dich selbst als Kricketexperten? <br>Du denkst, du bist besser als der Schiedsrichter?<br><br>Dann ist You are the Umpire das einzige Kricketspiel, das du je brauchen wirst.<br><br>Mit einer Fülle offizieller Grafiken von Legende Paul Trevillion und offizieller Anleitung zu den Spielregeln vom ehemaligen internationalen Schiedsrichters John Holder, ist You Are The Umpire das ultimative Kricketspiel für dich.<br><br>Funktionen:<br><br>• 2 Spielmodi, um deine Fähigkeiten zu testen: Sudden Death gewährt die keine falschen Entscheidungen und bei Assessment wird dein Eifer getestet, um zu sehen, ob du der weißen Uniform würdig bist!<br>• Schöne, handgezeichnete Illustrationen <br>• Hunderte Fragen vom Alltäglichen bis hin zum geradezu Lächerlichen, zusätzlich dazu die Antworten von einem der größten Schiedsrichternamen im Kricket<br><br>Paketgröße: 24 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Know your legside from your silly mid-off? Consider yourself a cricket expert? Think you could do a better job than the umpire?<br><br>You Are The Umpire is the only cricket trivia app you’ll ever need.<br><br>Incorporating a plethora of official artwork drawn by the legend that is Paul Trevillion and official guidance on the laws of the game from former International umpire John Holder, You Are The Umpire is the ultimate cricket trivia game.<br><br>Features:<br><br>• 2 game modes to test your skills: Sudden Death which makes no allowances for bad decisions and Assessment which will test your mettle and see if you are worthy of your white coat!<br>• Beautifully hand drawn illustrations <br>• Hundreds of questions ranging from the everyday to the flat-out ridiculous with answers from one of the greatest umpiring names in cricket<br><br>Package size: 24 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Vous maîtrisez à la perfection la balle et la batte ?<br>Vous pensez être incollable sur le cricket ?<br>Vous pensez pouvoir faire mieux que l'arbitre ?<br><br>You Are The Umpire est l'application de cricket qu'il vous faut.<br><br>Intégrant de nombreuses reproductions artistiques officielles du célèbre dessinateur Paul Trevillion et utilisant les conseils officiels de John Holder, ancien arbitre international de cricket, You Are The Umpire est le jeu de culture par excellence dans le domaine du cricket.<br><br>Caractéristiques :<br><br>• 2 modes de jeu pour mettre vos compétences à rude épreuve : Sudden Death qui sera sans pitié avec les mauvaises réponses, et Assessment qui testera votre courage sur le terrain<br>• De superbes illustrations <br>• Des centaines de questions très variées avec les réponses de l'un des meilleurs arbitres de l'histoire du cricket<br><br>Taille du programme: 24 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Family"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
