<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00185_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>184273008</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="ja"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Faktiske spiloplevelse er bedre end screenshots! <BR><BR>En indie musik-spil vil lancere hele verden denne sommer. <BR>-Genre af musik kan nævnes: rock, tromme og bas, 8 bit stil, fantasy elektronik og etc.some klassiske og virtuelle idoler Musik er også involveret.<BR>-Iørefaldende musik af talentfulde musikere. <BR>-Graceful illustrationer med Moe tegn.<BR>-High-tech stil interface.<BR>-Dramatiske visuelle effekter.<BR>-Klassisk game mode.<BR>-PlayStation®Vita fysiske bottons kontrol, komfortabel betjening følelse.<BR>-Mere ekstra musik kommer snart herunder gratis opdatering. <BR>-MUSYNC verden ikke lade dig ned for evigt! <BR>(Tips: MUSYNC er designet til PlayStation®Vita øjeblikket.) <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 176 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Portugisisk/Portugisisk/Russisk/Polsk/Finsk/Dansk/Norsk/Svensk/Koreansk/Kinesisk - forenklet/Kinesisk - traditionelt<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Die tatsächlichen Spielerlebnis ist besser als Screenshots! <BR><BR>Ein Indie-Musik-Spiel wird weltweit starten in diesem Sommer. <BR>-Genre der Musik sind: Rock, Drum &amp; Bass, 8-Bit-Stil, Fantasie Elektronik und etc.Some klassischen und virtuellen Idole Musik sind ebenfalls beteiligt.<BR>-Eingängige Musik von talentierten Musikern. <BR>-Graceful-Illustrationen mit moe Zeichen.<BR>-High-Tech-Stil-Schnittstelle.<BR>-Dramatic-visuelle Effekte.<BR>-Klassik-Spielmodus.<BR>-PlayStation®Vita-physikalischen bottons Kontrolle, komfortable Bedienung Gefühl. <BR>-Weitere zusätzliche Musik kommt bald wie kostenloses Update. <BR>Die MUSYNC-Welt nicht für immer im Stich lassen! <BR>(Tipps: MUSYNC für PlayStation®Vita derzeit konzipiert.) <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 176 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Dänisch/Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Niederländisch/Norwegisch/Polnisch/Portugiesisch(Portugal)/Portugiesisch(Brasilien)/Russisch/Finnisch/Schwedisch/Japanisch/Koreanisch/Vereinfachtes Chinesisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Actual gaming experience is BETTER than screen shots!!<BR><BR>An indie music game will be launched worldwide this summer.<BR><BR>-Genre of music includes: rock, drum and bass, 8 bit style,fantasy electronics etc. Some classical and virtual idols’ music are also included. <BR><BR>-Catchy music by talented musicians. <BR><BR>-Graceful illustrations with moe characters.<BR><BR>-High-tech style interface.<BR><BR>-Dramatic visual effects.<BR><BR>-Classical game mode.<BR><BR>-PlayStation®Vita physical bottons control, comfortable operation feeling.<BR><BR>-More additional music coming soon, including free updates.<BR><BR>-MUSYNC’s world forever will never let you down !<BR><BR>(Tips: MUSYNC is designed for PlayStation®Vita currently.) <BR><BR>Package size: 176 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Polish/Portuguese(Portugal)/Portuguese(Brazil)/Russian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese/Korean/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Experiencia de juego real es mejor que las capturas de pantalla! <BR><BR>Un juego de música indie lanzará en todo el mundo este verano. <BR>-Género de música incluyen: rock, drum and bass, el estilo de 8 bits, de la fantasía de la electrónica y la música de etc.Some ídolos clásicos y virtuales también están involucrados.<BR>-Pegadiza música de talentosos músicos. <BR>-Agraciado ilustraciones con personajes moe.<BR>Interfaz de estilo de alta tecnología.<BR>-Dramáticos efectos visuales.<BR>-Clásico modo de juego.<BR>-PlayStation®Vita de control bottons físicos, sensación cómoda de la operación.<BR>-Más música adicional próximamente incluyendo actualización gratuita. <BR>Mundo-MUSYNC no le fallará siempre! <BR>(Tips: MUSYNC está diseñado para PlayStation®Vita actualmente.) <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 176 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Danés/Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Holandés/Noruego/Polaco/Portugués(Portugal)/Portugués(Brasil)/Ruso/Finlandés/Sueco/Japonés/Coreano/Chino simplificado/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Varsinainen pelaaminen kokemus on parempi kuin kuvakaappauksia! <BR><BR>Indie-musiikin peli käynnistää maailmanlaajuisesti tänä kesänä. <BR>-Genren musiikkia kuuluu: Rock, rumpu ja basso, 8 bittinen tyyli, fantasia elektroniikka ja etc.some klassinen ja Virtual idolit musiikki ovat myös mukana <BR>tarttuva musiikkia lahjakkaita muusikoita. <BR>-Graceful piirroksia Moe merkkiä <BR>-High-tech-tyylinen käyttöliittymä <BR>-Dramatic visuaalisia tehosteita <BR>-Klassinen pelitila <BR>-PlayStation®Vita fyysinen bottons ohjaus, mukava käyttötuntuman <BR>-Enemmän lisää musiikkia tulossa myös ilmainen päivitys. <BR>-MUSYNC maailmassa ei petä ikuisesti! <BR>(Vinkkejä: MUSYNC on suunniteltu PlayStation®Vita tällä hetkellä.) <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 176 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Ranska/Espanja/Saksa/Italia/Hollanti/Portugali/Portugali/Venäjä/Puola/Suomi/Tanska/Norja/Ruotsi/Korea/Kiina - yksinkertaistettu/Kiina - perinteinen<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Expérience de jeu réel est mieux que des captures d'écran! <BR><BR>Un jeu de musique indie va lancer cet été dans le monde entier. <BR>-Genre de musique comprend: rock, drum and bass, le style 8 bits, de l'électronique de la fantaisie et de la musique de etc.Some idoles classiques et virtuels sont également impliqués.<BR>-Accrocheur musique par des musiciens talentueux. <BR>-Gracieuses illustrations avec des personnages moe <BR>-Interface style high-tech <BR>-Dramatiques effets visuels <BR>-Classique mode de jeu <BR>-PlayStation®Vita-contrôle des bottons physiques, sentiment de fonctionnement confortable <BR>-Plus musique additionnelle à venir, y compris mise à jour gratuite. <BR>Le monde-MUSYNC ne vous laisse pas tomber pour toujours! <BR>(Conseils: MUSYNC est conçu pour PlayStation®Vita pour le moment.) <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 176 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Danois/Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Néerlandais/Norvégien/Polonais/Portugais(Portugal)/Portugais(Brésil)/Russe/Finnois/Suédois/Japonais/Coréen/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Esperienza di gioco reale è migliore di colpi dello schermo! <BR><BR>Un gioco di musica indie lancerà in tutto il mondo questa estate. <BR>-Genere di musica includono: rock, drum and bass, stile 8 bit, fantasia elettronica e la musica etc.Some da idoli classici e virtuali sono coinvolti anche. <BR>-Orecchiabile musica di musicisti di talento. <BR>-Graceful illustrazioni con personaggi moe <BR>-Interfaccia in stile High-tech.<BR>-Drammatici effetti visivi.<BR>-Classica modalità di gioco.<BR>-PlayStation®Vita controllo bottoni fisici, sensazione funzionamento comodo.<BR>-Più musica addizionale presto compreso aggiornamento gratuito. <BR>Il mondo di-MUSYNC non vi deluderà per sempre! <BR>(Suggerimenti: MUSYNC è progettato per PlayStation®Vita attualmente.) <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 176 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Danese/Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Olandese/Norvegese/Polacco/Portoghese(Portogallo)/Portoghese(Brasile)/Russo/Finlandese/Svedese/Giapponese/Coreano/Cinese semplificato/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[（ゲームの感触はスクリーンショットにより優れる!）<BR><BR>∮インディーズ音楽ゲーム MUSYNC 正式発売∮<BR><BR>-ゲームノートは様々な楽器の音が含まれている:<BR> ギター、ドラム、8ビットゲーム、様々なエレクトロニック•ミュージック等<BR> 日本と中国のクラシック楽器またバーチャルアイドル音声もあり。<BR><BR>-有名作曲家による、魅力的なオリジナル曲の収録。<BR><BR>-手書きによる美しいイラスト,萌えなキャラクターデザイン。<BR><BR>-クラシックなゲームモード。<BR><BR>-PlayStation®Vitaボタンを押す際の感覚、派手なエフェクト效果による演出で最高の臨場感。<BR><BR>-爽快な操作と音楽の一体感で最強音楽ゲームに挑戦！ <BR><BR>-今後各分野の新規曲を発売予定、一部無料曲名があり！ <BR> <BR>MUSYNCの世界はあなたを失望させません！<BR><BR>（注：MUSYNCのみ現在PlayStation®Vita用に設計されています) <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 176 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>デンマーク語/ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語/オランダ語/ノルウェー語/ポーランド語/ポルトガル語(ポルトガル)/ポルトガル語(ブラジル)/ロシア語/フィンランド語/スウェーデン語/日本語/韓国語/中国語(簡体字)/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Selve spillopplevelsen er BEDRE enn skjermbilder! <BR><BR>En indie musikk spillet vil lansere hele verden denne sommeren. <BR>-Sjanger av musikk er: rock, drum and bass, 8 bit-stil, fantasy elektronikk og etc.some klassiske og virtuelle idoler sin musikk er også involvert.<BR>-Fengende musikk med dyktige musikere. <BR>-Graceful illustrasjoner med moe tegn.<BR>-High-tech-stil grensesnitt.<BR>-Dramatiske visuelle effekter.<BR>-Klassisk spill modus.<BR>-PlayStation®Vita fysiske bottons kontroll, komfortabel betjening følelse.<BR>-Mer mer musikk kommer snart inkludert gratis oppdatering. <BR>-MUSYNC verden ikke lar deg ned for alltid! <BR>(Tips: MUSYNC er designet for PlayStation®Vita i dag.) <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 176 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Portugisisk/Portugisisk/Russisk/Polsk/Finsk/Dansk/Norsk/Svensk/Koreansk/Kinesisk - Forenklet/Kinesisk - Tradisjonell<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Werkelijke game-ervaring is beter dan screenshots! <BR><BR>Een indie muziek game zal wereldwijd lanceren deze zomer. <BR>-Genre van muziek horen: rots, drum and bass, 8 bit stijl, fantasie elektronica en etc.Some klassieke en Virtual afgoden's muziek zijn ook betrokken.<BR>-Catchy muziek van getalenteerde muzikanten. <BR>-Graceful illustraties met moe personages.<BR>-High-tech achtige interface.<BR>-Dramatische visuele effecten.<BR>-Klassieke game mode.<BR>-PlayStation®Vita fysieke bottons controle, comfortabele bediening gevoel.<BR>-Meer extra muziek binnenkort inclusief gratis update. <BR>-MUSYNC de wereld je niet in de steek laten voor altijd! <BR>(Tips: MUSYNC is ontworpen voor PlayStation®Vita op dit moment.) <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 176 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Frans/Spaans/Duits/Italiaans/Nederlands/Portugees/Portugees/Russisch/Pools/Fins/Deens/Noors/Zweeds/Koreaans/Chinees - Vereenvoudigd/Chinees - Traditioneel<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Rzeczywiste doznania jest lepszy niż zrzuty ekranu! <BR><BR>Indie gra muzyka rozpocznie na całym świecie latem tego roku. <BR>-Gatunek muzyki to: rock, drum and bass, 8 bit styl, fantasy, elektroniki i muzyki klasycznej, jak i wirtualnych etc.some idole są również zaangażowane.<BR>-Chwytliwe muzyka przez utalentowanych muzyków. <BR>-Wdzięku ilustracje z postaciami Moe.<BR>-Interfejs-stylu high-tech.<BR>-Dramatyczne efekty wizualne.<BR>-Klasyczny tryb gry.<BR>-PlayStation®Vita bottons fizycznych kontroli, komfortowe uczucie operacja.<BR>-Więcej dodatkowa muzyka wkrótce w tym bezpłatnej aktualizacji. <BR>Światowej MUSYNC za nie zawiedzie Cię na zawsze! <BR>(Porady: MUSYNC jest przeznaczony dla PlayStation®Vita obecnie.) <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 176 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Duński/Niemiecki/Angielski/Angielski/Hiszpański/Fiński/Francuski/Włoski/Japoński/Koreański/Norweski/Holenderski/Polski/Portugalski/Portugalski/Rosyjski/Szwedzki/Chiński - uproszczony/Chiński - tradycyjny<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Faktisk spelupplevelse är BÄTTRE än skärmdumpar! <BR><BR>En indie musik spel kommer att lanseras över hela världen i sommar. <BR>-Genre av musik är: rock, drum and bass, 8 bit stil, fantasi elektronik och etc.some klassiska och virtuella idoler musik är också involverade.<BR>-Catchy musik av duktiga musiker. <BR>-Graceful illustrationer med moe tecken.<BR>-High-tech stil gränssnitt.<BR>-Dramatiska visuella effekter.<BR>-Klassiska spelläge.<BR>-PlayStation®Vita fysiska bottons kontroll, bekväm drift känsla.<BR>-Mer ytterligare musik kommer snart inklusive gratis uppdatering. <BR>-MUSYNC värld inte svika dig för evigt! <BR>(Tips: MUSYNC är avsedd för PlayStation®Vita idag.) <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 176 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Franska/Spanska/Tyska/Italienska/Holländska/Portugisiska/Portugisiska/Ryska/Polska/Finska/Danska/Norska/Svenska/Koreanska/Kinesiska - förenklad/Kinesiska - traditionell<BR><BR>I-Inferno<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:MusicRhythm"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
