<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00005_00">

  <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>21544480</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Lav musik når som helst og hvor som helst med Beats Trellis.<BR>Interfacet i Beats Trellis er bygget op omkring en enkelt netstruktur, og du har en vifte af instrumenter, trommesæt og breakbeats til rådighed, som du kan skabe musikalske mønstre med, der kan afspilles ”live”.<BR><BR>Funktioner:<BR>16 spor til instrumenter<BR>8 spor til trommesæt<BR>8 spor til breakbeats<BR>15 instrumentstemmer<BR>6 trommesæt – der hver indeholder seks forskellige slagtøjslyde <BR>6 breakbeats – giver dit mix en professionel lyd!<BR><BR>Effektenhed – tilføj ekko/delay-effekter til dine instrument- og trommespor!<BR>Automatisering af effektenhed – du kan bare tegne en kurve og høre instrumenterne komme til live!<BR>“Live Play” – sæt dine spor til at spille eller stoppe. Trellis sørger for at synkronisere sporene. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 21 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Kreiere Musik zu jeder Zeit, an jedem Ort, wo auch immer mit Trellis.<BR>Mit einem einfachen Grid-basierte Eingabesystem und einer Palette von Instrumenten, Schlafzeugen und Breakbeats,<BR>kann mit Trellis Musik erstellt und "live" wiedergegeben werden.<BR><BR>Funktionen:<BR>16 Instrumentalspuren.<BR>8  Schlagzeugspuren.<BR>8  Breakbeat-Spuren.<BR>15 Instrumente<BR>6  Schlagzeuge - jeweils 6 verschiedene Percussionsklänge<BR>6 Breakbeats - Für den professionellen Touch zu Ihrem Mix!<BR><BR>Echo Effektgerät - Echo(Delay)-Effekte für alle Instrumente und Schalgzeuge!<BR>Automations Effektgerät - Einfach eine Kurve zeichnen und schon wird das Instrument zum Leben erweckt!<BR>"Live Play" - Die Musikspuren abspielen oder stoppen. Trellis sorgt dafür, dass die Spuren synchron gehalten werden. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 21 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Create music any time, any place, anywhere with Trellis.<BR>Using a simple grid based interface, Trellis gives you a palette of instruments, drum kits and breakbeats, allowing you to create music patterns and play them back "live".<BR><BR>Features:<BR>16 instrument tracks<BR>8 drum kit tracks<BR>8 breakbeat tracks.<BR>15 instrument voices<BR>6 drum kits - Each containing 6 different percussion sounds<BR>6 breakbeats - Great for adding a professional touch to your mix!<BR><BR>Effects unit - Add echo (delay) effects to your instrument and drum tracks!<BR>Automation effects unit - Simply draw a curve and hear your instrument voices come to life!<BR>"Live Play" - Trigger your music tracks to play or stop. Trellis ensures that tracks are kept in sync. <BR><BR>Package size: 21 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Create music any time, any place, anywhere with Trellis.<BR>Using a simple grid based interface, Trellis gives you a palette of instruments, drum kits and breakbeats, allowing you to create music patterns and play them back "live".<BR><BR>Features:<BR>16 instrument tracks<BR>8 drum kit tracks<BR>8 breakbeat tracks.<BR>15 instrument voices<BR>6 drum kits - Each containing 6 different percussion sounds<BR>6 breakbeats - Great for adding a professional touch to your mix!<BR><BR>Effects unit - Add echo (delay) effects to your instrument and drum tracks!<BR>Automation effects unit - Simply draw a curve and hear your instrument voices come to life!<BR>"Live Play" - Trigger your music tracks to play or stop. Trellis ensures that tracks are kept in sync. <BR><BR>Package size: 21 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Create music any time, any place, anywhere with Trellis.<BR>Using a simple grid based interface, Trellis gives you a palette of instruments, drum kits and breakbeats, allowing you to create music patterns and play them back "live".<BR><BR>Features:<BR>16 instrument tracks<BR>8 drum kit tracks<BR>8 breakbeat tracks.<BR>15 instrument voices<BR>6 drum kits - Each containing 6 different percussion sounds<BR>6 breakbeats - Great for adding a professional touch to your mix!<BR><BR>Effects unit - Add echo (delay) effects to your instrument and drum tracks!<BR>Automation effects unit - Simply draw a curve and hear your instrument voices come to life!<BR>"Live Play" - Trigger your music tracks to play or stop. Trellis ensures that tracks are kept in sync. <BR><BR>Package size: 21 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Create music any time, any place, anywhere with Trellis.<BR>Using a simple grid based interface, Trellis gives you a palette of instruments, drum kits and breakbeats, allowing you to create music patterns and play them back "live".<BR><BR>Features:<BR>16 instrument tracks<BR>8 drum kit tracks<BR>8 breakbeat tracks.<BR>15 instrument voices<BR>6 drum kits - Each containing 6 different percussion sounds<BR>6 breakbeats - Great for adding a professional touch to your mix!<BR><BR>Effects unit - Add echo (delay) effects to your instrument and drum tracks!<BR>Automation effects unit - Simply draw a curve and hear your instrument voices come to life!<BR>"Live Play" - Trigger your music tracks to play or stop. Trellis ensures that tracks are kept in sync. <BR><BR>Package size: 21 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Crea tu propia música en cualquier momento y estés donde estés con Trellis.<BR>Con un interfaz muy fácil de usar,  Trellis te proporciona una paleta de instrumentos, baterías y ritmos predefinidos para que crees las secuencias de sonidos que más te gustan.<BR><BR>Características:<BR>16 pistas para instrumentos<BR>8 pistas para baterías<BR>8 pistas para breakbeats<BR>15 instrumentos disponibles<BR>6 baterías, cada una con 6 sonidos de percusión<BR>6 breakbeats predefinidos, perfectos para darle un toque profesional a tus mezclas.<BR><BR>Unidad de efectos: ¡Añade eco a tus pistas! ¡Y configura a tu gusto los efectos automáticos disponibles!<BR>Mezcla y escucha tu música sin preocuparte de sincronizar tus pistas, ¡Trellis lo hace por ti! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 21 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Beats Trellis -sovelluksella luot musiikkia missä ja milloin haluat.<BR>Helppoa ruudukkopohjaista käyttöliittymää hyödyntävä Beats Trellis antaa käyttöösi valikoiman soittimia, rumpusettejä ja breakbeatejä, joista voit luoda musiikkikuvioita soitettavaksi "livenä".<BR><BR>Ominaisuudet:<BR>16 instrumenttiraitaa<BR>8 rumpusettiraitaa<BR>8 breakbeat-raitaa<BR>15 instrumenttiääntä<BR>6 rumpusettiä – jokainen sisältää 6 erilaista perkussiosoundia<BR>6 breakbeatiä – lisää miksaukseen ammattimaista otetta!<BR><BR>Efektimoduuli – lisää kaikua instrumentti- ja rumpuraitoihin!<BR>Automaattinen efektimoduuli – piirrä käyrä, niin instrumenttiäänesi heräävät henkiin!<BR>Live Play – aloita tai lopeta musiikkiraitojesi toisto. Trellis varmistaa, että raidat pysyvät synkronoituina. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 21 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Créer de la musique n'importe quand, n'importe où avec Trellis<BR>Grâce à une interface simple, Trellis vous donne accès à une palette d'instruments, de batteries et de breakbeats, ce qui vous permet de créer des motifs musicaux et de les jouer en "live"<BR><BR>Caractéristiques:<BR>16 pistes d'instruments<BR>8 pistes de batterie<BR>8 pistes breakbeat<BR>15 voix instruments<BR>6 batteries - Chacune contenant 6 différents sons de percussion<BR>6 breakbeats - Idéal pour ajouter une touche professionnelle à votre mix<BR><BR>Effets - Ajouter des effets d'écho à vos piste d'instrument et de batterie<BR>Automatisation des effets - Il suffit de dessiner une courbe et pour entendre vos instruments prendre vie<BR>"Live Play" - Déclenchez la lecture ou l’arrêt de votre musique. Trellis veille à ce que les pistes sont bien synchronisés <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 21 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Créer de la musique n'importe quand, n'importe où avec Trellis<BR>Grâce à une interface simple, Trellis vous donne accès à une palette d'instruments, de batteries et de breakbeats, ce qui vous permet de créer des motifs musicaux et de les jouer en "live"<BR><BR>Caractéristiques:<BR>16 pistes d'instruments<BR>8 pistes de batterie<BR>8 pistes breakbeat<BR>15 voix instruments<BR>6 batteries - Chacune contenant 6 différents sons de percussion<BR>6 breakbeats - Idéal pour ajouter une touche professionnelle à votre mix<BR><BR>Effets - Ajouter des effets d'écho à vos piste d'instrument et de batterie<BR>Automatisation des effets - Il suffit de dessiner une courbe et pour entendre vos instruments prendre vie<BR>"Live Play" - Déclenchez la lecture ou l’arrêt de votre musique. Trellis veille à ce que les pistes sont bien synchronisés <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 21 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Crea musica ovunque e quando vuoi con Trellis.<BR>Grazie a una semplice interfaccia basata su griglie, Trellis e’ in grado di fornire una quantita’ diversa di strumenti, batterie e ritmi per aiutarti a creare vere e proprie tracce musicali da suonare dal “vivo”!<BR><BR>Caratteristiche:<BR>16 Tracce strumentali<BR>8 Tracce per batteria<BR>8 Tracce breakbeat<BR>15 Diversi strumenti<BR>6 Tracce contenenti ognuna 6 diversi strumenti di percussione<BR>6 Breakbeati – Un otttimo modo per aggiungere un tocco di professionalita’ al tuo mix!<BR><BR>Effetti audio – Aggiungi diversi effetti ai tuoi strumenti e batteria!<BR><BR>Effetti automatici – Disegna una curva e ascolta la musica!<BR> “Live Play” – Scegli quando attivare le tue tracce. Trellis si occupera’ di tenerle sincronizzate. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 21 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[Trellisで音楽を作る　どこでもいつでも<BR>Trellisのシステムでさまざまな楽器やドラムやバックビートなどを使える<BR>あたなのミュージックを創作できる　「生プレイ」できる<BR><BR>特徴<BR>１６楽器トラック<BR>８ドラムトラック<BR>８バックビートトラック<BR>１５楽器ボイス<BR>６ドラムボイス－6種類のパーカッション音付き<BR>６バックビートボイスー　プロな効果でき<BR><BR>エフェクトユニット：エコーエフェクトを楽器やドラムトラックに入れ！<BR>オートエフェクトユニット：簡単に曲線を描くと楽器のボイスを変更させ！<BR>「生プレイ」：ミュージックトラックを自由に再生や終止できる、Trellisはトラックの同時性を確保する <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 21 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Skap musikk når som helst, hvor som helst med Beats Trellis<BR>Ved å bruke et enkelt rutenett i brukergrensesnittet, gir Beats Trellis deg en samling av instrumenter, trommesett og rytmer, som lar deg skape ulike musikkmønstre og spille de av «live».<BR><BR>Funksjoner<BR>16 instrumentspor<BR>8 trommesettspor<BR>8 rytmespor<BR>15 stemmespor<BR>6 trommesett – hver av de inneholder 6 forskjellige perkusjonslyder<BR>6 rytmer – fantastisk for å legge til profesjonell lyd i miksen din!<BR><BR>Effekter – legg til ekko-effekter (forsinkelse) til instrumentene og trommesporene!<BR>Enhet for automatisering av effekter – tegn enkelt og greit en kurve, og hør instrumentstemmene komme til live! <BR>«Live Play» – Starter eller stopper musikksporene. Trellis forsikrer at sporene er synkronisert. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 21 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Maak muziek waar en wanneer je wilt met Beats Trellis.<BR>Met behulp van een eenvoudige rasterinterface geeft Beats Trellis je de beschikking over een groot aantal instrumenten, drumstellen en breakbeats, waarmee je muziekpatronen kunt creëren en die "live" kunt afspelen.<BR><BR>Features:<BR>16 instrumentsporen<BR>8 drumsporen<BR>8 breakbeatsporen<BR>15 instrumentstemmen<BR>6 drumstellen – met elk 6 verschillende slagwerkgeluiden<BR>6 breakbeats – geweldig om je mix professioneel te laten klinken!<BR><BR>Effecten – voeg echo-effecten (vertraging) toe aan je instrument- en drumsporen!<BR>Geautomatiseerde effecten – teken gewoon een curve en hoor je instrumentstemmen tot leven komen!<BR>"Live spelen" – laat je muzieksporen starten en stoppen. Trellis zorgt ervoor dat de sporen gelijk blijven lopen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 21 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Skapa musik var som helst och när som helst med Beats Trellis.<BR>Med hjälp av ett enkelt rutnätsgränssnitt ger Beats Trellis en uppsättning instrument, trumset och breakbeat spelar tillbaka dem ”live”.<BR><BR>Det här får du:<BR>16 instrumentspår<BR>8 trumsetsspår<BR>8 breakbeatspår<BR>15 instrumentröster<BR>6 olika trumset – alla med varierande perkussionsljud<BR>6 olika breakbeat – perfekt när du vill få en professionell känsla på din mix!<BR><BR>Effektenhet – lägg till ekoeffekter (fördröjningsljud) till dina instrument- och trumspår!<BR>Automatiserande effektenhet – dra helt enkelt en kurva och hör de olika instrumentrösterna väckas till liv!<BR>“Live Play” – starta eller stoppa dina musikspår. Trellis ser till att spåren är synkade. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 21 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Audio"/><genre value="Apps:Music"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
