<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00017_00">
 <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>39852240</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[80年代へ戻る旅の準備をしよう！<br>それは、1880年代です。<br><br>ビクトリア朝の探検家が、富と冒険を求めて火星に向かって進みます。<br>いったい何がおこるんだるだろ...？<br><br>Rock Boshers DXは、1980年代のZX Spectrumのような画像やフィーリングや音響を<br>作った、トップダウンと8方向シューティングゲームです。<br><br>火星への旅で、15色のパレットから描きだされたすごくきれいな風景を楽しんで<br>ください。<br><br>岩を砕け！ 休まず頑張ろう。<br><br>コンテンツ容量:39 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Get ready to take a trip back to the 80s, the 1880s!<br>Victorian explorers are heading to Mars, seeking fortune and adventure, what could possibly go wrong...?<br><br>Created to look, feel and sound like a ZX Spectrum styled videogame from the 1980s - Rock Boshers DX mixes top down and side on 8-way directional shooting action.<br><br>See amazing sights as you journey across Mars - drawn from an eye popping palette of 15 colours.<br>Prepare to bosh rocks! - with only the occasional break for tea and scones.<br><br>Package size: 39 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Préparez-vous à faire un voyage vers les années 80, les années 1880!<br>Des explorateurs victoriens se dirigent vers Mars, cherchant fortune et aventure. Qu’est-ce qui pourrait mal tourner ...?<br><br>Créé pour ressembler en tout point à  un jeu vidéo style ZX Spectrum des années 1980, Rock Boshers DX mélange les actions de tir sur 8 directions - de haut en bas et de côté.<br><br>Durant votre voyage sur Mars, vous serez enchantés par les étonnants paysages (rendus dans une éclatante palette de 15 couleurs).<br>Soyez prêts à pulvériser des rochers!  - sans oublier l'essentielle pause pour le thé.<br><br>Taille du paquet: 39 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Preparatevi per un viaggio negli anni 80, quelli del 1800!<br>Esploratori vittoriani diretti su Marte, alla ricerca di fortuna e avventure: cosa puo' andar storto...?<br><br>Sviluppato sul modello audio e video dei videogiochi per lo ZX Spectrum degli anni 80, Rock Boshers DX è uno sparatutto su 8 direzioni che mescola top down e laterale.<br><br>Tieniti pronto a far rompere le rocce, con solo qualche pausa per tè e biscotti.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 39 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¡Prepárate para ir de viaje de vuelta a los 80, a  1880!<br>Exploradores victorianos van a Marte en busca de riquezas y aventura. ¿Qué puede salir mal?<br><br>Creado para imitar el sonido, la imagen y la experiencia de un juego del Spectrum ZX de los 80, Rock Boshers DX mezcla comandos de cursor con habilidad de disparo multidireccional.<br><br>Descubre increíbles paisajes en tu viaje a través de Marte, creado con una paleta de 15 brillantes colores .<br>Prepárate a machacar rocas, parando de vez en cuando a tomar té con pastas.<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 39 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Machen Sie sich bereit auf eine Reise zurück in die 80er Jahre, die 1880er!<br>Victorianische Forscher machen sich auf den Weg zum Mars. Ein jeder sucht sein Glück und Abenteuer, was könnte da schon schief gehen ...?<br><br>Rock Boshers DX ist so entwickelt worden, dass es wie ein ZX Spectrum Videospiel aus den 80er Jahren  aussieht, sich so anhört und anfuehlt.<br>Rock Boshers DX bietet Schieß-Aktion aus 8 Richtungen - Kombinationen von oben nach unten und seitlich.<br><br>Die Reise über den Mars bietet erstaunliche Sehenswuerdigkeiten,  mit einer brillianten Bildqualität mit einer Farbpalette von 15 Farben. <br>Bereiten Sie sich vor zum "bosh  rocken"!  Mit nur einer gelegentlichen Pause für Kaffee und Kuchen. <br><br>Paketgröße: 39 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Get ready to take a trip back to the 80s, the 1880s!<br>Victorian explorers are heading to Mars, seeking fortune and adventure, what could possibly go wrong...?<br><br>Created to look, feel and sound like a ZX Spectrum styled videogame from the 1980s - Rock Boshers DX mixes top down and side on 8-way directional shooting action.<br><br>See amazing sights as you journey across Mars - drawn from an eye popping palette of 15 colours.<br>Prepare to bosh rocks! - with only the occasional break for tea and scones.<br><br>Package size: 39 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Préparez-vous à faire un voyage vers les années 80, les années 1880!<br>Des explorateurs victoriens se dirigent vers Mars, cherchant fortune et aventure. Qu’est-ce qui pourrait mal tourner ...?<br><br>Créé pour ressembler en tout point à  un jeu vidéo style ZX Spectrum des années 1980, Rock Boshers DX mélange les actions de tir sur 8 directions - de haut en bas et de côté.<br><br>Durant votre voyage sur Mars, vous serez enchantés par les étonnants paysages (rendus dans une éclatante palette de 15 couleurs).<br>Soyez prêts à pulvériser des rochers!  - sans oublier l'essentielle pause pour le thé.<br><br>Taille du programme: 39 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Arcade"/>
  <genre value="Games:Shooter"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
