<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00267_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>43747744</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Monsters dukkede pludselig i den idylliske landsby.<BR>Anmodning om straf kommer i Witch Emil.<BR>Hvem er med dem, der truer freden?<BR><BR>Lad besejrede den lilla sten til at indkalde et monster ved at udnytte et stort antal våben og sten og magi!<BR>Dette er en traditionel action RPG-stil actionspil.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 Opdateringen indhold.<BR>  * Den svarede til PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" indikation blev tilsat til den nye gain element.<BR>  * Magic og en parameter for et monster blev justeret.<BR>  * Dataene spare forarbejdning blev justeret.<BR>  * Flere fejl blev rettet.<BR>  * Den vis billede blev ændret til en justeret billede. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 42 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Monster plötzlich im idyllischen Dorf.<BR>Anfragen von Straf kommt Emil Hexe.<BR>Wer ist mit denen, die den Frieden bedrohen?<BR><BR>Lassen Sie besiegte die lila Stein, um ein Monster durch die Verwendung einer Vielzahl von Waffen und Stein und Magie beschwören!<BR>Dies ist eine herkömmliche Action-RPG-Stil Action-Spiel.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 der Aktualisierungsinhalt.<BR>  * Es entsprach PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" Anzeige wurde dem neuen Verstärkungs Artikel hinzugefügt.<BR>  * Magie und ein Parameter von einem Monster wurden angepasst.<BR>  * Datensicherungsverarbeitung wurde angepasst.<BR>  * Mehrere Defekte wurden behoben.<BR>  * Die bestimmte Bild wurde auf einer bereinigten Bild verändert. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 42 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Suddenly appeared monsters in the idyllic village.<BR>Request of punitive comes to witch Emil.<BR>Who is with those who threaten the peace?<BR><BR>Let's overthrow purple stone which makes full use of large number of weapons and devil stones and magic, and summons a monster!<BR>This is a conventional action RPG-style action game.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 The update contents.<BR>  * It corresponded to PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" indication was added to the new gain item.<BR>  * Magic and a parameter of a monster were adjusted.<BR>  * Data save processing was adjusted.<BR>  * Several defects were corrected.<BR>  * The certain picture was changed to an adjusted picture. <BR><BR>Package size: 42 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Monsters aparecieron de repente en el pueblo idílico.<BR>Solicitud de punitiva trata de bruja Emil.<BR>¿Quién está con los que amenazan la paz?<BR><BR>Let derrotó la piedra púrpura para convocar a un monstruo por la utilización de un gran número de armas y piedra y la magia!<BR>Esta es una acción convencional al estilo de juego de acción RPG.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 El contenido de actualización.<BR>  * Correspondió a PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" indicación de esta en el nuevo elemento de ganancia.<BR>  * La magia y un parámetro de un monstruo se ajustaron.<BR>  * Datos ahorra recursos se ajustó.<BR>  * Varios defectos fueron corregidos.<BR>  * La imagen determinada se cambió a una imagen ajustada. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 42 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Monsters ilmestyi yhtäkkiä idyllisessä kylässä.<BR>Pyyntö on rankaiseva tulee noita Emil.<BR>Kuka on niiden kanssa, jotka uhkaavat rauhaa?<BR><BR>Olkoon kukisti violetti kivi kutsua hirviö käyttämällä useita aseita ja kivi ja taikaa!<BR>Tämä on tavanomainen toiminta RPG-tyylinen toimintapeli.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 päivitys sisältöä.<BR>  * Se vastasi PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" maininta lisättiin uusi voitto kohde.<BR>  * Taikuutta ja parametri hirviö oikaistiin.<BR>  * Tiedot säästää jalostus oikaistiin.<BR>  * Useita puutteet korjattiin.<BR>  * Tietty kuva muutettiin mukautettua kuvaa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 42 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Monstres soudainement apparu dans le village idyllique.<BR>Demande d'punitive se agit de sorcière Emil.<BR>Qui est avec ceux qui menacent la paix?<BR><BR>Soit défait la pierre violette de convoquer un monstre en utilisant un grand nombre d'armes et de la pierre et de la magie!<BR>Ce est un jeu d'action classique d'action RPG de style.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 Le contenu de mise à jour.<BR>  * Il correspondait à PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" indication a été ajouté au nouvel élément de gain.<BR>  * Magie et un paramètre d'un monstre ont été ajustés.<BR>  * Données économiser du traitement a été ajusté.<BR>  * Plusieurs défauts ont été corrigés.<BR>  * Le certaine image a été changé à une image ajustée. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 42 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Monsters apparso improvvisamente nel villaggio idilliaco.<BR>Richiesta di punitiva viene a strega Emil.<BR>Chi è con coloro che minacciano la pace?<BR><BR>Let sconfitto la pietra viola di evocare un mostro utilizzando un gran numero di armi e pietre e magia!<BR>Questo è un gioco d'azione RPG in stile azione convenzionale.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 I contenuti di aggiornamento.<BR>  * E 'corrisponde alla PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" indicazione è stata aggiunta al nuovo elemento guadagno.<BR>  * Magia e un parametro di un mostro sono stati adeguati.<BR>  * Dati salvare l'elaborazione è stato rettificato.<BR>  * Diversi difetti sono stati corretti.<BR>  * La foto è stata certo cambiato in un quadro regolato. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 42 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[のどかな村に突如現れたモンスター達…<BR>見習い魔法使いエミルに討伐の依頼が舞い込む。<BR>平和を脅かす者とは一体…？<BR><BR>数々の武器/魔石/魔法を駆使して<BR>次々とモンスターを召喚する「紫岩」を撃破せよ！<BR>オーソドックスなアクションRPG風のアクション。<BR><BR>Ver 1.01　アップデート内容<BR>　・PlayStation®Vita TV（PlayStation®TV）に対応しました。<BR>　・新規入手アイテムに「New!」を表示するようにしました。<BR>　・一部の魔法とモンスターのパラメータを調整しました。<BR>　・データセーブ処理を調整しました。<BR>　・いくつかの不具合を修正しました。<BR>　・一部の画像を調整したものに変更しました。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 42 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Monstre dukket plutselig i den idylliske landsbyen.<BR>Anmodning fra straff kommer til heks Emil.<BR>Hvem er med dem som truer freden?<BR><BR>Let beseiret den lilla stein for å innkalle et monster ved å benytte et stort antall våpen og stein og magi!<BR>Dette er en vanlig handling RPG-stil actionspill.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 Oppdaterings innholdet.<BR>  * Det samsvarer PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" indikasjon ble tilsatt til den nye forsterkningselement.<BR>  * Magic og en parameter av et monster ble justert.<BR>  * Data spare behandlingen ble justert.<BR>  * Flere feil ble rettet.<BR>  * Den viss bildet ble endret til en justert bilde. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 42 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Monsters verscheen plotseling in het idyllische dorpje.<BR>Verzoek van bestraffende gaat om heks Emil.<BR>Wie is met degenen die de vrede bedreigen?<BR><BR>Laat versloeg de paarse steen aan een monster op te roepen door gebruik te maken van een groot aantal wapens en steen en magie!<BR>Dit is een conventionele actie RPG-stijl actie spel.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 De inhoud updaten.<BR>  * Het kwam overeen met PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" indicatie werd toegevoegd aan de nieuwe versterking punt.<BR>  * Magic en een parameter van een monster werden aangepast.<BR>  * Gegevens opslaan verwerking werd aangepast.<BR>  * Diverse gebreken werden gecorrigeerd.<BR>  * Het bepaalde foto werd veranderd in een aangepaste afbeelding. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 42 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Potwory pojawiła się nagle w idyllicznym miasteczku.<BR>Zapytaj o MORALNE przychodzi czarownica Emila.<BR>Kto jest z tymi, którzy zagrażają pokojowi?<BR><BR>Niech pokonał fioletowy kamień przywołać potwora, wykorzystując dużą ilość broni i kamienia i magii!<BR>To jest konwencjonalnym stylu RPG gra akcji.<BR><BR>Ver1.01 zawartość aktualizacji.<BR>  * To odzwierciedla PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" oznaczenie zostało dodane do nowej pozycji wzmocnienia.<BR>  * Magia i parametrów potwora zostały skorygowane.<BR>  * Dane zapisać przetwórstwa została skorygowana.<BR>  * Poprawiono kilka usterek.<BR>  * Pewien obraz został zmieniony na skorygowanego obrazu. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 42 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Japoński<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Monsters dök plötsligt i den idylliska byn.<BR>Begäran om straff kommer till häxa Emil.<BR>Vem är med dem som hotar freden?<BR><BR>Låt besegrade den lila stenen att kalla ett monster genom att utnyttja ett stort antal vapen och sten och magi!<BR>Detta är en konventionell åtgärd RPG-stil actionspel. <BR><BR>Ver1.01 innehållet uppdateringen.<BR>  * Det motsvarade PlayStation®Vita TV (PlayStation®TV).<BR>  * "New!" indikation sattes till den nya förstärkningen objektet.<BR>  * Magi och en parameter av ett monster justerades.<BR>  * Data spara bearbetning justerades.<BR>  * Flera defekter korrigerades.<BR>  * Den viss bild ändrades till ett justerat bilden. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 42 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:RPG"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
