<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00141_00">

  <appVersion>1.30</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>64821952</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice er et vanedannende handling puzzle spil med en kølig frisk ny tage på den velkendte matching spil formel. I Marathon mode, skal Crystal Ice afspillere klare så mange Crystal Klynger, som de kan, før spillet gitteret fyldes op med de hurtige droppe isblokke. Yderligere game modes inkluderer Challenge og Puzzle niveauer, hvor spillere kan bevise deres Crystal clearing færdigheder. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 62 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice ist ein fesselndes Action-Puzzle-Spiel mit einer kalten frischen neuen Sicht auf die vertrauten passenden Spiel-Formel. Im Marathon-Modus muss Crystal Ice Spieler so viele Kristallcluster zu löschen, da sie vor dem Spiel Grid füllt sich mit den schnellen Abwurf Eisblöcke. Weitere Spielmodi beinhalten Puzzle-Herausforderung und Ebenen, wo Spieler können ihre Kristall Clearing Fähigkeiten beweisen. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 62 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice is an addicting action puzzle game with a chilly fresh new take on the familiar matching game formula. In Marathon mode, Crystal Ice Players must clear as many Crystal Clusters as they can before the game grid fills up with the fast dropping Ice Blocks. Additional game modes include Challenge and Puzzle levels where Players can prove their Crystal clearing skills. <BR><BR>Package size: 62 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice is an addicting action puzzle game with a chilly fresh new take on the familiar matching game formula. In Marathon mode, Crystal Ice Players must clear as many Crystal Clusters as they can before the game grid fills up with the fast dropping Ice Blocks. Additional game modes include Challenge and Puzzle levels where Players can prove their Crystal clearing skills. <BR><BR>Package size: 62 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice is an addicting action puzzle game with a chilly fresh new take on the familiar matching game formula. In Marathon mode, Crystal Ice Players must clear as many Crystal Clusters as they can before the game grid fills up with the fast dropping Ice Blocks. Additional game modes include Challenge and Puzzle levels where Players can prove their Crystal clearing skills. <BR><BR>Package size: 62 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice is an addicting action puzzle game with a chilly fresh new take on the familiar matching game formula. In Marathon mode, Crystal Ice Players must clear as many Crystal Clusters as they can before the game grid fills up with the fast dropping Ice Blocks. Additional game modes include Challenge and Puzzle levels where Players can prove their Crystal clearing skills. <BR><BR>Package size: 62 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Cristal de hielo es un juego de puzzle de acción adictiva con una fría nueva consideración diferente de la fórmula de juego de correspondencias familiar. En el modo de maratón, Crystal Ice jugadores deben pasar la mayor cantidad de racimos de cristal, ya que pueden antes de que la rejilla de juego se llena de los que abandonan rápidamente bloques de hielo. Modos de juego adicionales incluyen Challenge y los niveles de rompecabezas donde los jugadores pueden probar sus habilidades de compensación de cristal. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 62 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice on himo toiminnantäyteinen pulmapeli, jossa kolea tuoreita uusi ottaa tuttu vastaava peli kaava. Marathon-tilassa, Crystal Ice Pelaajien on selkeä niin monta Crystal Clusters koska ne voivat ennen pelin ruudukko täyttyy nopeasti pudottamalla Ice Blocks. Muihin pelitiloja kuuluvat Challenge ja Puzzle tasoilla, joilla pelaajat voivat todistaa Crystal selvitys taitoja. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 62 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Cristal de glace est un jeu d'action puzzle addictif avec une nouvelle prise frais froid sur la formule bien connue de jeu de correspondance. En mode Marathon, Crystal lecteurs glace doivent dégager autant de grappes de cristal, car ils peuvent avant la grille de jeu se remplit de la chute rapide blocs de glace. Modes de jeu supplémentaires incluent des niveaux de réflexion où les joueurs peuvent prouver leurs compétences de compensation cristal défi et. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 62 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice è un gioco di puzzle di azione coinvolgente con un freddo nuovo introito fresco sulla formula di gioco di corrispondenza familiare. In modalità Maratona, Crystal ghiaccio giocatori devono eliminare il maggior numero di cluster di cristallo come si può prima che la griglia di gioco si riempie con i veloci cadere blocchi di ghiaccio. Modalità di gioco aggiuntive includono Challenge e livelli di puzzle dove i giocatori possono dimostrare le loro capacità di compensazione di cristallo. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 62 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[クリスタルアイスは、おなじみのゲームをマッチング式に肌寒い新鮮な新しいテイクと中毒アクションパズルゲームです。彼らはゲームのグリッドが速く落下氷塊をいっぱいにする前のようにマラソンモードでは、クリスタルアイスプレーヤーは、多くの結晶クラスターをクリアする必要があります。追加のゲームモードは、挑戦と選手たちのクリスタルクリアのスキルを証明することができますパズルのレベルがあります。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 62 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice er en addicting action puzzle-spill med en kjølig frisk ny vri på den kjente matchende spillet formel. I maratonmodus, må Crystal Ice Spillere fjerne så mange Crystal Clusters som de kan før spillet rutenettet fylles opp med de raske slippe isblokker. Andre spillmoduser inkluderer Challenge og Puzzle nivåer hvor spillere kan bevise sine Crystal clearing ferdigheter. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 62 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice is een verslavende actie puzzelspel met een koele frisse nieuwe kijk op de vertrouwde matching game formule. In Marathon modus moet Crystal Ice Spelers zoveel Crystal Clusters wissen als ze kunnen voordat het spel rooster vult met de snelle dropping Ice Blocks. Extra spelmodi bevatten Challenge en puzzel levels waar spelers hun Crystal clearing vaardigheden kunnen bewijzen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 62 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Crystal Ice är en beroendeframkallande åtgärd pusselspel med en kylig frisk ny ta på det välkända matchande spelet formel. I Marathon läge måste Crystal Ice spelare klara så många Crystal Kluster som de kan innan spelet rutnätet fylls med de snabbt släppa Ice Block. Ytterligare spellägen inkluderar Challenge och Pussel nivåer där spelare kan bevisa sina Crystal clearing färdigheter. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 62 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>CrazyMation<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
