<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00145_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>684125136</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS udnytter alle enhedens muligheder fuldt ud. <BR>Med et klassisk spilsystem, som alle rollespilsfans vil holde af, <BR>præsenterer det en storslået fortælling med fire forskellige scenarier,<BR>alle med fantastisk lyd og ufatteligt flot 3D-grafik. <BR><BR>Historien handler om en turnering, hvori deltagerne kæmper for deres liv: Ark Arena. <BR>Når du har valgt et par figurer, en mand og en kvinde, skal du kæmpe mod de andre par.<BR>Hvert par har deres egen historie, og sandheden bag Ark Arena vil ikke blive afsløret, før alle historierne er gennemført. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 653 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Finsk/Dansk/Norsk/Svensk/Koreansk/Kinesisk - forenklet/Kinesisk - traditionelt<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS nutzt das gesamte Potenzial, das Gerät bereitstellt. <BR>Das klassische Gameplay wird jeden RPG-Fan begeistern; die vier mit fantastischem Soundtrack und unglaublich flüssigen Grafiken untermalten Szenarien schaffen eine epische Legende. <BR><BR>Die Geschichte dreht sich um ein Turnier, bei dem es um das Leben der Teilnehmer geht: die Ark Arena. <BR>Der Spieler wählt einen männlichen und weiblichen Charakter aus und muss dann gegen andere Paare kämpfen.<BR>Jedes Paar hat seine eigene Geschichte, doch die Wahrheit hinter der Ark Arena wird nicht enthüllt bis jede Geschichte abgeschlossen ist. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 653 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Dänisch/Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Niederländisch/Norwegisch/Finnisch/Schwedisch/Japanisch/Koreanisch/Vereinfachtes Chinesisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS takes full advantage of the Device’s capabilities. <BR>Using a classic game system that any RPG fan will enjoy, <BR>it presents an epic tale consisting of four different scenarios,<BR>all brought to you with gorgeous sound and unbelievably smooth 3D graphics. <BR><BR>The story revolves around a tournament where combatants fight for their lives: the Ark Arena. <BR>Upon choosing a pair of characters, one male and one female, you will then have to fight against the other pairs.<BR>Each pair has their own story, and the truth behind the Ark Arena will not be revealed until each story is completed. <BR><BR>Package size: 653 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese/Korean/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS takes full advantage of your device’s capabilities, using classic and novel game mechanics that any RPG fan will enjoy to present an epic tale encompassing four unique and engaging storylines—all delivered with gorgeous sound and unbelievably smooth 3-D graphics!<BR><BR>The plot revolves around the Ark Arena—the stage of a brutal tournament that pits combatants against one another in a fight for survival. Choose a pair of characters, one male and one female, to send into battle against the others, each with their own story to tell. The ultimate truth behind the Ark Arena will not be revealed until each story is complete! <BR><BR>Package size: 653 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese/Korean/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS aprovecha al máximo toda la capacidad de dispositivo. <BR>Esta aventura épica dividida en cuatro escenarios combina un estilo de juego clásico, <BR>que hará las delicias de cualquier aficionado a los RPG, junto con lo mejor en sonido y gráficos 3D. <BR><BR>El eje central de la historia es un torneo en el que los contendientes deben luchar para sobrevivir: el Ark Arena. <BR>Tras elegir una pareja de personajes, uno masculino y otro femenino, deberás enfrentarte a otras parejas. <BR>Cada pareja tiene su propia historia, y deberás descubrirlas todas para desvelar el secreto del Ark Arena. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 653 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Danés/Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Holandés/Noruego/Finlandés/Sueco/Japonés/Coreano/Chino simplificado/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RING ottaa laitteen suorituskyvystä kaiken irti. <BR>Kaikkien roolipelifanien nauttima klassinen pelijärjestelmä <BR>tarjoaa eeppisen, neljästä skenaariosta koostuvan tarinan,<BR>joka tarjotaan upeiden äänten ja uskomattoman sulavien 3D-grafiikoiden kera. <BR><BR>Tarina kertoo turnauksesta, jossa kilpailijat taistelevat elämiensä puolesta: Ark Arena. <BR>Hahmoparin valittuasi, yksi mies ja yksi nainen, sinun on taisteltava muita pareja vastaan.<BR>Jokaisella parilla on oma tarinansa, ja Ark Arenan salaisuutta ei paljasteta, ennen kuin jokainen tarina on läpäisty. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 653 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Ranska/Espanja/Saksa/Italia/Hollanti/Suomi/Tanska/Norja/Ruotsi/Korea/Kiina - yksinkertaistettu/Kiina - perinteinen<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS exploite au maximum les capacités d'appareil. <BR>Basé sur un système de jeu classique apprécié de tout fan de RPG, <BR>ce jeu épique se compose de quatre scénarios différents, <BR>tous dotés de somptueux effets sonores et de graphismes en 3D d'une fluidité exceptionnelle. <BR><BR>L'histoire est celle d'un tournoi où les participants combattent pour leur vie : l'Ark Arena.<BR>Choisissez un duo de personnages, un homme et une femme, qui affronteront les autres duos.<BR>Chaque duo a sa propre histoire et la vérité derrière l'Ark Arena n'éclatera qu'une fois chaque histoire terminée. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 653 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Danois/Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Néerlandais/Norvégien/Finnois/Suédois/Japonais/Coréen/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS sfrutta al massimo le potenzialità di dispositivo: <BR>basato su un sistema di gioco classico che tutti i fan del genere apprezzeranno, <BR>questo gioco è composto da quattro differenti scenari, dotati di straordinari effetti sonori e di una grafica 3D dalla fluidità eccezionale. <BR><BR>La storia ruota intorno a un torneo dove si lotta per la vita: l'Ark Arena. <BR>Scegli i due personaggi, uno femminile e uno maschile, che dovranno affrontare le altre coppie. <BR>Ogni coppia ha la sua storia. <BR>La verità celata nell'Ark Arena non sarà rivelata fino a che tutte le storie non saranno completate. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 653 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Danese/Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Olandese/Norvegese/Finlandese/Svedese/Giapponese/Coreano/Cinese semplificato/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[世界中から絶賛を受けた大作RPGがついにPlayStation®Mobileに登場！<BR><BR>-------------------------------------------------------------<BR>・容量の大きいアプリのため、ダウンロードに時間がかかります。<BR>・Wifi環境でのダウンロードを推奨しております。<BR>・本アプリの容量は700MB程度ございますので、ダウンロードの際は空き容量に<BR>　余裕を持ってお試しいただけますようよろしくお願いいたします。<BR>-------------------------------------------------------------<BR><BR>『ケイオスリングス』は、デバイスの性能をフルに活かした王道RPGです。<BR>RPGファンが慣れ親しんだオーソドックスなゲームシステムを踏襲しつつ、<BR>4本のシナリオが織りなす壮大な物語、それに引けを取らない豪華なサウンド、<BR>そして、驚くほど滑らかに動く3Dグラフィックをお楽しみいただけます。<BR><BR>物語の基軸は、生死を賭けたトーナメント「アルカ・アレーナ」。<BR>プレイヤーは最初に1組の男女を選択し、選ばなかったペアは対戦相手として登場します。<BR>それぞれのペアには異なるストーリーが用意されており、全ての物語をクリアすることで、<BR>アルカ・アレーナの真実、そして、その先に待つ人知を超えた存在が姿を現します。<BR><BR>＜ゲームの特徴＞<BR>・豪華声優陣によるキャラクターボイスを実装<BR><BR>・滑らかに動く3Dグラフィック<BR><BR>・コントローラーとタッチパネルどちらでもプレイ可能<BR><BR>・それぞれのペアで違う展開を見せる重厚なストーリー&amp;マルチエンディング<BR><BR>・洗練された王道のゲームシステム・戦闘<BR><BR>・隠しボス・隠し武器などのやり込み要素で、どこまででも遊べるゲームボリューム <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 653 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>デンマーク語/ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語/オランダ語/ノルウェー語/フィンランド語/スウェーデン語/日本語/韓国語/中国語(簡体字)/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS utnytter seg fullt av enhetens evner.<BR>Ved hjelp av et klassisk spillsystem som alle RPG-fans kan kose seg med,<BR>presenterer vi en episk fortelling som består av fire ulike scenarier,<BR>alle brakt til deg med nydelig lyd og utrolig 3D-grafikk.<BR><BR>Historien tar utgangspunkt i en turnering hvor deltakerne kjemper for sine liv: Ark Arena.<BR>Du velger karakterene dine i et par, en mann og en kvinne, og du må kjempe mot de andre parene i arenaen.<BR>Hvert par har sin egen historie, og sannheten bak Ark Arena vil ikke bli avslørt før hver historie er fullført. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 653 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Finsk/Dansk/Norsk/Svensk/Koreansk/Kinesisk - Forenklet/Kinesisk - Tradisjonell<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS maakt optimaal gebruik van de mogelijkheden van je apparaat met klassieke en nieuwe speltechnieken waardoor elke RPG-fan kan genieten van een episch verhaal met vier unieke en spannende verhaallijnen - en dat alles met een prachtig geluid en ongelooflijk vloeiende 3D-graphics!<BR><BR>Het verhaal draait om de Ark Arena, waar in een wreed toernooi tegenstanders het tegen elkaar opnemen in een gevecht op leven en dood. <BR>Kies twee personages, een man en een vrouw, en stuur deze samen de strijd in om te vechten tegen de anderen. En elk heeft zijn eigen verhaal te vertellen. <BR>De uiteindelijke waarheid achter de Ark Arena wordt pas onthuld als elk verhaal compleet is! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 653 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Frans/Spaans/Duits/Italiaans/Nederlands/Fins/Deens/Noors/Zweeds/Koreaans/Chinees - Vereenvoudigd/Chinees - Traditioneel<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[CHAOS RINGS utnyttjar enhetens möjligheter till fullo.<BR>Med ett klassiskt spelsystem som alla RPG-fans kommer gilla, <BR>presenteras en episk berättelse med fyra olika scenarion –<BR>alla med fantastiskt ljud och otroliga smidig 3D-grafik. <BR><BR>Berättelsen kretsar kring en turnering där kombattanterna slåss för sina liv: Ark Arena. <BR>Efter att ha valt ett par figurer, en man och en kvinna, ska du strida mot de andra paren.<BR>Varje par har sin egen berättelse – och sanningen bakom Ark Arena kommer inte att avslöjas innan varje berättelse har slutförts. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 653 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Franska/Spanska/Tyska/Italienska/Holländska/Finska/Danska/Norska/Svenska/Koreanska/Kinesiska - förenklad/Kinesiska - traditionell<BR><BR>© 2013 SQUARE ENIX CO., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:RPG"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
