<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00134_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>107945792</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Vi er stolte af at præsentere den engelske version af dette visual novel-spil med stemmer, udviklet i samarbejde med Akihabaras stemmecafé og -bar "Seiyuu no Tamago".<BR><BR>Bemærk:<BR><BR>* Dette er et visual novel-spil med stemmer. Al stemme er japansk, og alle tekster er omhyggeligt oversat til engelsk.<BR><BR>* Der findes kun en rute gennem dette spil. Brugerinteraktion har ikke nogen effekt på spillets slutning.<BR><BR>* Engelsk support er tilgængelig via e-mail og twitter. Besøg vores webside for at få mere at vide. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 103 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Wir sind stolz ihnen die Englischsprachige Version dieser komplett vertonten graphischen Spielgeschichte zu präsentieren. Das Spiel wurde in Zusammenarbeit mit Akihabaras Voice Café und Bar "Seiyuu no Tamago" erstellt.<BR><BR>Hinweis:<BR><BR>* Dies ist eine komplett vertonte graphische Spielgeschichte. Alle Stimmen sind japanisch und alle Texte wurden behutsam ins Englische übersetzt.<BR><BR>* Es gibt eine Einzige Route in diesem Spiel. Interaktionen des Spielers haben keinen Effekt auf des Ergebnis des Spiels.<BR><BR>* Englischen Support ist via E-mail und Twitter möglich. Für weitere Informationen besuchen sie unsere Webseite. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 103 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[We are proud to present the English version of this fully voiced visual novel game, created in collaboration with Akihabara's voice cafe and bar "Seiyuu no Tamago".<BR><BR>Notice:<BR><BR>* This is a fully voiced visual novel game. All voices are in Japanese, and all texts have been carefully translated into English.<BR><BR>* There is a single route in this game. User interaction does not have an effect on the outcome of the game.<BR><BR>* English support is available via e-mail and twitter. Visit our webpage for more information. <BR><BR>Package size: 103 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Estamos orgullosos de presentar la versión en Inglés de nuestra novela visual, que ha sido creada en colaboración con el voice café y bar de Akihabara "Seiyuu no Tamago".<BR><BR>Aviso:<BR><BR>* Este juego es una novela visual completamente doblada. Aunque todas las voces se encuentran en Japonés, todos los textos han sido cuidadosamente traducidos a inglés.<BR><BR>* Este juego es completamente lineal. Las interacciones del usuario no afectan el resultado del juego.<BR><BR>* Hay soporte en inglés disponible para este juego, via correo electrónico y twitter. Visite nuestra página web para mayor información. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 103 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Olemme ylpeitä voidessamme esitellä englanninkielisen version tästä täysin puhutusta visuaalisesta tarinapelistä, joka on kehitetty yhteistyössä Akihabaran voice cafen ja baarin "Seiyuu no Tamago" kanssa.<BR><BR>Huom:<BR><BR>* Tämä on täysin puhuttu visuaalinen tarinapeli. Kaikki puhe on japaniksi ja kaikki teksti on käännetty tarkasti englanniksi.<BR><BR>* Pelissä on yksi reitti. Käyttäjän toiminnoilla ei ole vaikutusta pelin lopputulokseen.<BR><BR>* Englanninkielinen tuki on saatavilla sähköpostin ja twitterin kautta. Viraille verkkosivuilla saadaksesi lisää tietoa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 103 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Nous sommes heureux de vous présenter ce Visual Novel crée en collaboration avec le voice cafe et bar "Seiyuu no Tamago" de Akihabara.<BR><BR>Notice:<BR><BR>* Ce jeu est un visual novel entièrement double. Toutes les voix sont en Japonais et tous les textes ont été traduits avec minution en anglais.<BR><BR>* Ce jeu est linéaire: il ne presente qu'un seul scenario et les interctions du joueur n'ont aucune consequence sur le deroulement de l'histoire.<BR><BR>* Nous restons à votre disposition (en anglais) via e-mail ou twitter. Merci de visiter notre site internet pour plus d'informations. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 103 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Siamo fieri di annunciare la versione inglese di questo gioco visual novel completamente doppiato, creato in collaborazione con il voice cafè e bar di Akihabara "Seiyuu no Tamago".<BR><BR>Nota bene:<BR><BR>* Questo gioco è interamente doppiato. Tutte le voci sono in giapponese, e tutti i testi sono stati accuratamente tradotti in inglese.<BR><BR>* Esiste una sola trama all'interno del gioco. L'interazione o le scelte dell'utente non hanno un effetto a livello di trama.<BR><BR>* Il supporto in inglese è disponibile sia via e-mail sia via twitter. Si prega di visitare il nostro sito per maggiori informazioni. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 103 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Vi er stolte over å presentere deg den engelske versjonen av dette stemmebaserte visuelle romanspillet, laget i samarbeid med Akihabaras stemmebaserte kafe og bar, "Seiyuu no Tamago".<BR><BR>Obs:<BR><BR>* Dette er et stemmebasert visuelt romanspill. Alle stemmene er på japansk og alle tekstene har blitt oversatt til engelsk.<BR><BR>* Det er en enkel vei i dette spillet. Spillestil påvirker ikke hvordan spillet ender.<BR><BR>* Engelsk støtte er tilgjengelig via e-post og twitter. Besøk nettstedet vårt for mer informasjon. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 103 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Wij zijn trots de Engelse versie van dit volledig ingesproken visuele romanspel te kunnen presenteren, dat gemaakt is in samenwerking met Akihabara's stemcafé en bar "Seiyuu no Tamago".<BR><BR>Let op:<BR><BR>* Dit is een volledig ingesproken visueel romanspel. Alle stemmen zijn in het Japans en alle teksten zijn zorgvuldig in het Engels vertaald.<BR><BR>* Er is één route in dit spel. Gebruikersinteractie heeft geen effect op de uitkomst van het spel.<BR><BR>* Engelse ondersteuning is via e-mail en Twitter beschikbaar. Bezoek onze website voor meer informatie. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 103 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Z dumą prezentujemy wersję angielską tej w pełni odegranej przez aktorów gry gatunku powieści wizualnej (visual novel), stworzoną we współpracy z muzyczną kawiarnią Akihabara i barem "Seiyuu no Tamago".<BR><BR>Uwaga:<BR><BR>* Jest to w pełni odegrana przez aktorów gra gatunku powieści wizualnej (visual novel). Wszystkie wypowiedzi są po japońsku, a wszystkie teksty zostały starannie przetłumaczone na angielski.<BR><BR>* W tej grze jest jeden przebieg. Interakcja użytkownika nie ma wpływu na wynik gry.<BR><BR>* Wsparcie po angielsku dostępne jest poprzez e-mail i twittera. Więcej informacji znajdziesz odwiedzając naszą stronę internetową. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 103 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Vi presenterar stolt den engelska versionen av det här röstbaserade spelet i Visual Novel-genren, skapat i samarbete med Akihabaras talföra kafé och bar "Seiyuu no Tamago".<BR><BR>Observera:<BR><BR>* Detta är ett röstbaserat spel i Visual Novel-genren. Alla röster är på japanska och texterna är noggrant översatta till engelska.<BR><BR>* Det finns en enda väg i det här spelet. Samspel mellan användare påverkar inte spelresultatet.<BR><BR>* Engelsk support finns tillgänglig via e-post och twitter. Besök vår webbsida för mer information. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 103 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
