<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00031_00">
 <appVersion>1.07</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>49934128</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[...あの音は何ですか？誰かいますか？<br><br>真夜中に町を通ってあなたの方法を悩ませ放棄された時計塔のほこりっぽいホールを残す！ 、博物館から病院、劇場、クルーズ船の人々を追い払うために、あなたの幽霊のような魂を持つオブジェクトを所有している。あなたは夜が終わる前に、皆を追い払うと、失われたものを取り戻すことができるのだろうか？<br><br>横スクロールアクションパズルゲームは幽霊を主演！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:48 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)<br><br>著作権等:<br>©SFB Games Ltd 2012. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[...What was that sound? Is somebody there?<br><br>Leave the dusty halls of an abandoned clock tower to haunt your way through a town in the dead of night! Possess objects with your ghostly soul, to scare people away from a museum, a hospital, a theatre and a cruise ship.  Will you be able to scare everyone out and reclaim what has been lost, before the night is over?<br><br>A side-scrolling action puzzle game starring ghosts!<br><br>Package size: 48 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>©SFB Games Ltd 2012. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[C'était quoi, ce bruit? Y'a quelqu'un?<br> <br>Quittez le hall poussiéreux d'un clocher abondonné et allez hanter la ville en pleine nuit. Prenez possession d'objects avec votre âme fantomatique, de façon à chasser les gens d'un musée, d'un hôpital, d'un théatre et d'un bateau de croisière. Vas-tu être capable de balayer tout le monde et récupérer ce qui avait été perdu avant que la nuit soit passée?<br> <br>Un jeu side-scrolling Action-Puzzle, avec des fantômes en premier rôle!<br><br>Taille du paquet: 48 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>©SFB Games Ltd 2012. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Che cos'era quel rumore? C'è qualcuno qui? <br><br>Lascia le sale polverose della torre dell'orologio abbandonato per continuare la tua caccia nelle strade di una città immersa nel buio profondo della notte! Possiedi oggetti con la tua anima fantasma, e spaventa gente via dal museo, dall'ospedale, dal teatro e da una nave da crociera. Sarai in grado di spaventare tutti e ritrovare ciò che è andato perduto, prima che la notte sia finita? <br><br>Un frenetico rompicapo pieno di fantasmi!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 48 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<br><br>©SFB Games Ltd 2012. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[“¿Qué es ese ruido? ¿Hay alguien ahí?”<br><br>¡Sal de las salas polvorientas de una abandonada torre del reloj para rondar por las calles en el silecio sepulcral de la noche! Aprópriate de los objectos con tu espíritu fantasmal para echar la gente de un museo, un hospital, un teatro y un barco de crucero. ¿Serás capaz de darles un susto de muerte y reclamar las cosas perdidas antes de que termine la noche?<br><br>¡Un juego scroll con puzzles y fantasmas!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 48 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<br><br>©SFB Games Ltd 2012. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[...was war das für ein Geräusch? Ist da jemand?<br><br>Lasse die verstaubten Hallen eines stillgelegten Glockenturms hinter dir um in der schwärzesten Nacht durch die Gassen eines Dorfes zu spuken! Mit deiner geisterhaften Gestalt ergreifst du Besitz über Gegenstände um Angst und Schrecken in einem Museum, einem Spital, einem Theater und einem Kreuzfahrtschiff zu verbreiten.  Schaffst du es, alle unerwünschten Gäste zu vertreiben und noch vor Anbruch des Tages wiederzufinden was lange verloren war?<br><br>Ein gespenstisches Side-Scrolling Action Puzzle Spiel!<br><br>Paketgröße: 48 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)<br><br>©SFB Games Ltd 2012. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[...What was that sound? Is somebody there?<br><br>Leave the dusty halls of an abandoned clock tower to haunt your way through a town in the dead of night! Possess objects with your ghostly soul, to scare people away from a museum, a hospital, a theatre and a cruise ship.  Will you be able to scare everyone out and reclaim what has been lost, before the night is over?<br><br>A side-scrolling action puzzle game starring ghosts!<br><br>Package size: 48 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>©SFB Games Ltd 2012. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[C'était quoi, ce bruit? Y'a quelqu'un?<br> <br>Quittez le hall poussiéreux d'un clocher abondonné et allez hanter la ville en pleine nuit. Prenez possession d'objects avec votre âme fantomatique, de façon à chasser les gens d'un musée, d'un hôpital, d'un théatre et d'un bateau de croisière. Vas-tu être capable de balayer tout le monde et récupérer ce qui avait été perdu avant que la nuit soit passée?<br> <br>Un jeu side-scrolling Action-Puzzle, avec des fantômes en premier rôle!<br><br>Taille du programme: 48 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>©SFB Games Ltd 2012. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Action"/>
  <genre value="Games:Unique"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
