<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00265_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>79237312</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="de"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Du er Alessia en "hacker-pige" fanget i virtuelle cyberspace! Flygte fra nettet.<BR>Hjælpe Abby finde bekvemmeligheder, at deaktivere laser, og undslippe de grimme robotter!<BR>Se dine modstandere og tænke over din strategi til ikke at blive fanget.<BR>På minimap, har du fået alt i syne (nøglen, modstander, switch)<BR>Deaktivere laser at gå ubemærket hen i nye sektioner.<BR>Krybe for at komme til målet, fordi modstanderen kan du ikke kun se men også høre! En virkelig udfordring!<BR>Forsøge at samle alle elementer for at mestre spillet 100%. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 76 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Du bist Alessia ein „Hacker-Girl“ gefangen im Virtuellen Cyberspace! Entkomme aus dem Netz.<BR>Hilf Alessia die Keycards zu finden, Laser zu deaktivieren, und den fiesen Robotern zu entkommen!<BR>Beobachte deine Gegner und überlege deine Strategie um nicht erwischt zu werden.<BR>Über die Minimap hast du alles im Blick (Schlüssel, Gegner, Schalter)<BR>Deaktiviere die Laser um unbemerkt in neue Abschnitte vorzudringen.<BR>Schleiche um zum Ziel zu kommen, denn die Gegner können dich nicht nur sehen sondern auch hören! Eine echte Herausforderung!<BR>Versuche alle Items einzusammeln um das Spiel zu 100% zu meistern. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 76 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>You are Alessia a "hacker-girl" trapped in virtual cyberspace! Escape from the net.<BR>Help Alessia find the comforts, to disable laser, and escape the nasty robots!<BR>Watch your opponents and think about your strategy to not getting caught.<BR>On the minimap, you've got everything in sight (key, opponent, switch)<BR>Disable the laser to move unnoticed into new sections.<BR>Creep to get to the target, because the opponent can you not only see but also hear! A real challenge!<BR>Try to collect all items in order to master the game 100%. <BR><BR>Package size: 76 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Eres Alessia una "hacker-chica" atrapada en el ciberespacio virtual! Escapar de la red.<BR>Ayuda a Abby encontrar las comodidades, para desactivar el láser y escapar de los robots desagradables!<BR>Cuidado con tus oponentes y pensar en su estrategia para no ser atrapado.<BR>En el minimapa, tienes todo a la vista (opositor, interruptor de llave)<BR>Deshabilitar el láser para pasar desapercibido a nuevas secciones.<BR>Fluencia para llegar a la meta, porque el rival puede no sólo ver pero también escuchar. Un verdadero reto!<BR>Trata de recoger todos los elementos con el fin de dominar el juego 100%. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 76 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Alessia "hakkeri-tyttö" loukussa on virtuaalinen kyberavaruudessa! Paeta verkossa.<BR>Apua Abby löytää mukavuudet käytöstä laser, ja paeta ilkeä robotit!<BR>Tarkkaile vastustajiasi ja miettiä strategiaa ei saada kiinni.<BR>Minimap olet saanut kaiken näköpiirissä (avain, vastustaja, kytkin)<BR>Poista laser siirtyä huomaamatta uusia osia.<BR>Hiipiä saada tavoite, koska vastustaja voi ei vain nähdä, mutta myös kuulla! Todellinen haaste!<BR>Yritä kerätä kaikki kohteet jotta hallita peliä 100 %. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 76 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Vous êtes Alessia une « pirate-fille » pris au piège dans le cyberespace virtuel ! S'échapper du filet.<BR>Aider Abby trouver le confort, afin de désactiver le laser et échapper les robots méchants !<BR>Regardez vos adversaires et pensez à votre stratégie pour ne pas se faire attraper.<BR>Sur la minicarte, vous avez tout en vue (interrupteur à clé, adversaire)<BR>Désactiver le laser de passer inaperçu dans les nouvelles sections.<BR>Fluage pour arriver à la cible, car l'adversaire peut vous voir non seulement mais aussi entendez ! Un vrai défi !<BR>Essayez de recueillir tous les éléments pour maîtriser le jeu 100 %. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 76 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Sei una "hacker-ragazza" intrappolata di Alessia nel cyberspazio virtuale! Fuggire dalla rete.<BR>Aiutare Abby trovare il comfort, per disattivare i laser e fuggire i robot cattivi!<BR>Guarda i tuoi avversari e pensare la tua strategia per non essere scoperti.<BR>Sulla minimappa, che hai tutto in vista (interruttore avversario, chiave)<BR>Disattivare il laser per passare inosservato in nuove sezioni.<BR>Strisciare per raggiungere la destinazione, perché l'avversario può non solo vedere ma anche sentire! Una vera sfida!<BR>Cercare di raccogliere tutti gli elementi al fine di padroneggiare il gioco 100%. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 76 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>「ハッカー少女」閉じ込めアレシア仮想サイバー スペースでは ！ネットからの脱出します。<BR>アビー レーザーを無効にする快適さを見つけるし、厄介なロボットの脱出を助けて ！<BR>あなたの対戦相手を見るし、あなたの戦略に巻き込まれないについて考えます。<BR>ミニマップ、全てを網羅した視力 (キー、相手、スイッチ)<BR>新しいセクションに見過ごされて移動するレーザーを無効にします。<BR>クリープ相手することができますだけでなくがも聞くので、ターゲットを取得する ！本当の挑戦 ！<BR>100% ゲームをマスターするためにすべての項目を収集してください。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 76 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Du er Alessia en "hacker-jente" fanget i virtuelle cyberspace! Flykte fra nettet.<BR>Hjelp Abby finne komfort, deaktivere laser, og flykte ekkel roboter!<BR>Se dine motstandere og tenke strategi å ikke bli fanget.<BR>På minimap, har du alt i sikte (nøkkel, motstanderen, bryter)<BR>Deaktivere laser flytte ubemerket til nye seksjoner.<BR>Krype for å komme til målet, fordi motstanderen kan du ikke bare se, men også høre! En skikkelig utfordring!<BR>Prøv å samle alle elementer for å mestre spillet 100%. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 76 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>U bent Alessia een "hacker-girl" gevangen in virtuele cyberspace! Ontsnappen aan het net.<BR>Help Abby vinden de gemakken, om te schakelen laser, en ontsnappen aan de vervelende robots!<BR>Bekijk uw tegenstanders en denk na over uw strategie om niet gepakt.<BR>Op de minimap heb je alles in zicht (sleutel, tegenstander, schakelaar)<BR>De laser onopgemerkt verplaatsen naar nieuwe secties uit te schakelen.<BR>Kruipen om aan de doelgroep, omdat de tegenstander kan u niet alleen zien, maar ook horen! Een echte uitdaging!<BR>Proberen te verzamelen alle items om te beheersen het spel 100%. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 76 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Jesteś Alessia "haker dziewczyna" uwięziony w wirtualnych cyberprzestrzeni! Ucieczka z sieci.<BR>Pomoc Abby znaleźć udogodnienia, aby wyłączyć laser i uniknąć nieprzyjemnych roboty!<BR>Oglądać przeciwników i myśleć o swojej strategii, aby nie dać się złapać.<BR>Na minimapie masz wszystko w zasięgu wzroku (klucz, przeciwnik, przełącznik)<BR>Wyłączyć laser do przejść niezauważona w nowej sekcji.<BR>Pełzanie, aby dotrzeć do celu, ponieważ przeciwnik może nie tylko zobaczyć, ale także usłyszeć! Prawdziwe wyzwanie!<BR>Postaraj się zebrać wszystkie przedmioty w celu opanowania gry 100%. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 76 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Du är en "hacker-girl" fångade Alessia virtuella cyberrymden! Fly från nätet.<BR>Hjälp Abby hitta bekvämligheter, inaktivera laser, och fly de elaka robotarna!<BR>Titta på dina motståndare och tänka på din strategi för att inte åka fast.<BR>På minimap, har du allt i sikte (nyckel, motståndare, switch)<BR>Avaktivera lasern att flytta obemärkt in i nya avsnitt.<BR>Krypa för att komma till målet, eftersom den motståndaren kan du inte bara se men också höra! En riktig utmaning!<BR>Försök att samla alla poster för att bemästra spelet 100%. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 76 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Strategy"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
