<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00143_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>30612336</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[「Adventure Bar Labyrinth」 er en RPG, der sætter dig i skoene af en eventyrer, med det ultimative mål at inddrive legendariske hemmelige skat fra en enorm, uhyggelig underjordisk labyrint.<BR><BR>Gør din vej til dybder af dank, nådesløse dungeons ved at udnytte varer fundet undervejs, kæmpe monstre, og nivellering op.<BR><BR>Når du har vovet sig ind i et fangehul, er der ingen vej ud, andet end at få den vare, du er ude efter, eller ved hjælp af en flugt element. Når besejret i en fangekælder, vil du miste alle de emner, du har fundet, og dit niveau vil vende tilbage til 1.. Og oven det, når du vender tilbage til fangehullet, vil dens layout være helt anderledes. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 30 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[「Adventure Bar Labyrinth」 ist ein Rollenspiel, das Sie legt in den Schuhen eines Abenteurers, mit dem Ziel der Wiederherstellung legendären geheimen Schatz von einem enormen, unheimlich unterirdische Labyrinth.<BR><BR>Machen Sie Ihren Weg in die Tiefen der nasskalten, unversöhnlich Dungeons durch die Nutzung Gegenstände auf dem Weg gefunden, kämpfen Monster, und Nivellierung.<BR><BR>Sobald Sie in einem Verlies gewagt haben, gibt es keinen Ausweg, außer den Erhalt der Artikel, den Sie nach sind oder mit einem Fluchtpunkt. Wenn in einem Dungeon besiegt, werden Sie alle Artikel, die Sie gefunden haben, zu verlieren, und Ihr Niveau wird auf 1 zurück. Und um das Ganze abzurunden, wenn man einmal in den Kerker zurückkehren, wird das Layout ganz anders sein. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 30 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA["Adventure Bar Labyrinth" is an RPG that puts you in the shoes of an adventurer, with the ultimate goal of recovering legendary secret treasure from an enormous, eerie underground labyrinth.<BR><BR>Make your way to the depths of dank, unforgiving dungeons by utilizing items found along the way, fighting monsters, and leveling up.<BR><BR>Once you have ventured into a dungeon, there is no way out, other than obtaining the item you're after or using an escape item. When defeated in a dungeon, you will lose all the items you've found, and your level will return to 1. And to top it off, once you return to the dungeon, its layout will be completely different.<BR><BR>Yet, although your character is back to square one, you yourself will have gained valuable experience which cannot be taken away. <BR><BR>Package size: 30 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA["Adventure Bar Labyrinth" is an RPG that puts you in the shoes of an adventurer, with the ultimate goal of recovering legendary secret treasure from an enormous, eerie underground labyrinth.<BR><BR>Make your way to the depths of dank, unforgiving dungeons by utilizing items found along the way, fighting monsters, and leveling up.<BR><BR>Once you have ventured into a dungeon, there is no way out, other than obtaining the item you're after or using an escape item. When defeated in a dungeon, you will lose all the items you've found, and your level will return to 1. And to top it off, once you return to the dungeon, its layout will be completely different.<BR><BR>Yet, although your character is back to square one, you yourself will have gained valuable experience which cannot be taken away. <BR><BR>Package size: 30 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[「Adventure Bar Labyrinth」 es un juego de rol que te pone en la piel de un aventurero, con el objetivo final de recuperar el legendario tesoro secreto de un enorme laberinto subterráneo, misterioso.<BR><BR>Haga su camino a las profundidades de las mazmorras, implacables húmedas utilizando los objetos que encuentres en el camino, luchando contra monstruos y subir de nivel.<BR><BR>Una vez que se han aventurado en un calabozo, no hay manera de salir, que no sea la obtención del elemento que está buscando o utilizando un elemento de escape. Cuando derrotado en una mazmorra, perderá todos los puntos que has encontrado, y su nivel volverá a 1. Y por si fuera poco, una vez que regrese a la cárcel, su diseño será completamente diferente. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 30 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[「Adventure Bar Labyrinth」 on RPG, joka vie sinut kengät seikkailija, jonka lopullisena tavoitteena periä legendaarinen salainen aarre valtava, aavemainen maanalainen labyrintti.<BR><BR>Tee tapa syvyyksiin dank, anteeksiantamaton luolastoja hyödyntämällä osumaa löytyi matkan varrella, taistelevat hirviöitä, ja tasoitus ylöspäin.<BR><BR>Kun olet uskaltautuneet Dungeon, ei ole ulospääsyä, muuta kuin saada kohde olet jälkeen tai käyttämällä paeta kohde. Kun hävisi Dungeon, menetät kaikki kohteet olet löytänyt, ja taso palaa 1. Ja alkuun se pois, kun palaat Dungeon, sen ulkoasu on täysin erilainen. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 30 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[「Adventure Bar Labyrinth」 est un RPG qui vous met dans la peau d'un aventurier, avec l'objectif ultime de récupération légendaire trésor secret d'un énorme labyrinthe souterrain mystérieux.<BR><BR>Faites votre chemin dans les profondeurs de donjons humides, impitoyables en utilisant objets trouvés le long du chemin, combattre des monstres et nivellement par le haut.<BR><BR>Une fois que vous avez osé dans un cachot, il n'y a pas moyen de sortir, autre que l'obtention de l'article que vous recherchez ou en utilisant un élément d'échappement. Lorsque vaincu dans un donjon, vous perdrez tous les articles que vous avez trouvé, et votre niveau revenez à 1. Et pour couronner le tout, une fois que vous revenez dans le donjon, sa mise en page sera complètement différent. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 30 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[「Adventure Bar Labyrinth」 è un RPG che ti mette nei panni di un avventuriero, con l'obiettivo finale di recuperare il leggendario tesoro segreto da un enorme labirinto sotterraneo inquietante.<BR><BR>Fai la tua strada nelle profondità umide, dungeon perdona utilizzando oggetti trovati lungo la strada, combattendo mostri e salire di livello.<BR><BR>Una volta che si sono avventurati in una prigione, non c'è via d'uscita, diverso ottenendo l'articolo che stai cercando o utilizzando un elemento di fuga. Quando viene sconfitto in un dungeon, si perderanno tutti gli oggetti che hai trovato, e il tuo livello tornerà a 1. E per finire, una volta si torna alla prigione, la sua struttura sarà completamente diverso. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 30 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[「Adventure Bar Labyrinth」 er et rollespill som setter deg i skoene til en eventyrer, med det endelige målet om å utvinne legendariske hemmelige skatten fra en enorm, uhyggelig underjordiske labyrint.<BR><BR>Lag din vei til dypet av klam, uforsonlige fangehull ved å utnytte elementer funnet underveis, kjemper mot monstre, og utjevning opp.<BR><BR>Når du har våget seg inn i et fangehull, er det ingen vei ut, annet enn å skaffe den varen du er ute etter, eller ved hjelp av en flukt element. Når beseiret i et fangehull, vil du miste alle elementene du har funnet, og ditt nivå vil komme tilbake til en. Og på toppen av det, når du kommer tilbake til fangehullet, vil oppsettet være helt annerledes. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 30 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[「Adventure Bar Labyrinth」 is een RPG dat je in de schoenen van een avonturier, met het uiteindelijke doel van het herstellen van de legendarische geheime schat van een enorme, angstaanjagende ondergronds labyrint.<BR><BR>Maak uw weg naar de diepten van bedompt, meedogenloos kerkers door gebruik te maken van items gevonden langs de weg, vechten tegen monsters, en nivellering naar boven toe.<BR><BR>Als je eenmaal hebt gewaagd in een kerker, is er geen uitweg, anders dan het verkrijgen van het item dat u na of het gebruik van een ontsnapping punt. Toen versloeg in een kerker, verliest u alle items die je hebt gevonden, en je niveau zal terugkeren naar 1. En om het af te maken, als je eenmaal terug te keren naar de dungeon, zal de lay-out volledig anders zijn. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 30 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[「Adventure Bar Labyrinth」 är ett rollspel som sätter dig i rollen som en äventyrare, med det yttersta målet att återvinna legendariska hemliga skatt från en enorm, kuslig jordisk labyrint.<BR><BR>Gör din väg till djupet av saftig, oförsonliga fängelsehålor genom att använda objekt hittades på vägen, bekämpa monster och utjämning upp.<BR><BR>När du har vågat sig in i en fängelsehåla, det finns ingen väg ut, annat än att få det objekt du är ute efter eller använda en flykt objekt. När besegrades i en fängelsehåla, förlorar du alla objekt som du har hittat, och din nivå kommer att återgå till 1. Och till råga på, när du återvänder till fängelsehålan, kommer dess layout vara helt annorlunda. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 30 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>(C)RideonJapan,Inc.  (C)Rideon,Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:RPG"/><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
