<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00022_00">
 <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>58153728</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[あの「Alien Breed」が２１周年を記念してカムバック！ <br><br>Team17によって開発されたトップダウンシューター「Alien Breed」。１９９１年に発売されたこののクラシックSFゲームがPlayStation®Mobile用にリメイクされて再登場。明かりを暗くしてボリュームをアップして、エイリアン達と再び遭遇しよう！ <br><br>特徴：<br>★ Classic Mode（クラシックモード） – オリジナル版のグラフィックス、BGM、操作方法を使用したモード <br>★ Enhanced Mode（改良モード） – 改良版のグラフィックス、音声、操作方法を使用したモード <br>★ ８つの新しいレベル – オリジナルストーリーと交差する新登場のレベル <br>★ オリジナル版の６つのレベル <br>★ １２の「Alien Breed」特別版レベル <br><br>コンテンツ容量:56 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語<br><br>著作権等:<br>Team17 Digital Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[The original Alien Breed is back in action, celebrating its 21st Anniversary! <br><br>Alien Breed is the classic sci-fi, top-down shooter developed by Team17. Launching originally in 1991, Alien Breed has now been remade for PlayStation®Mobile, which can only mean one thing… it’s time to turn down the lights, turn up the sounds and encounter Alien Breed again! <br><br>Features: <br>★ Classic Mode – Play using the original graphics, music and controls. <br>★ Enhanced Mode – Featuring enhanced graphics, audio and controls. <br>★ 8 New Levels – entirely new levels that intersect with the original Alien Breed story <br>★ 6 original Alien Breed levels <br>★ 12 Alien Breed Special Edition levels <br><br>Package size: 56 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Team17 Digital Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Le jeu d’origine revient pour fêter son 21ème anniversaire ! <br><br>Grand classique de science-fiction, Alien breed est le jeu de tir en vue de dessus développé par Team17. Sorti à l’origine en 1991, Alien Breed a été remis au goût du jour sur PlayStation®Mobile, ce qui veut dire… qu’il est l’heure d’éteindre la lumière, de monter le son et de repartir à l’assaut d’Alien Breed ! <br><br>Descriptif : <br>★ Mode classique – Jouez avec les graphismes, la musique et les commandes d’origine. <br>★ Mode amélioré – Ce mode dispose de graphismes, de sons et de commandes améliorés. <br>★ 4 niveaux inédits – Des niveaux entièrement nouveaux qui se mêlent à l’histoire initiale d’Alien Breed <br>★ 6 niveaux de la version d’origine d’Alien Breed <br>★ 12 niveaux de l’édition spéciale d’Alien Breed<br><br>Taille du paquet: 56 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Team17 Digital Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Il gioco originale è tornato in azione per celebrare il suo 21° Anniversario! <br><br>Alien Breed è un classico sparatutto con visuale dall'alto e ad ambientazione fantascientifica sviluppato da Team17. Rilasciato per la prima volta nel 1991, Alien Breed viene ora riproposto per dispositivi con PlayStation®Mobile, cosa che può voler dire soltanto che… è tempo di spegnere le luci, alzare il volume e prepararsi a un nuovo incontro ravvicinato con Alien Breed! <br><br>Caratteristiche: <br>★ Modalità Classica: gioca con la grafica, la musica e i comandi originali. <br>★ Modalità Potenziata: presenta grafica, suoni e comandi migliorati. <br>★ 4 livelli completamente nuovi che s'intrecciano con la trama originale di Alien Breed <br>★ 6 livelli originali di Alien Breed <br>★ 12 livelli di Alien Breed Special Edition<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 56 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano<br><br>Team17 Digital Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¡El juego original regresa a la acción y celebra su 21 aniversario! <br><br>Alien Breed es el juego de disparos de arriba abajo de ciencia ficción clásico desarrollado por Team17. Su lanzamiento original se produjo en 1991; desde entonces, Alien Breed ha sido adaptado para PlayStation®Mobile, lo que significa que… ¡es hora de bajar las luces, subir el volumen y volver a encontrarse con los alienígenas! <br><br>Características: <br>★ Modo Clásico – juega con los gráficos, música y controles originales. <br>★ Modo Mejorado – con gráficos, sonido y controles mejorados. <br>★ 8 nuevos niveles – completamente nuevos que se cruzan con la historia original de Alien Breed. <br>★ 6 niveles originales Alien Breed <br>★ 12 niveles de la Edición Especial de Alien Breed<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 56 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano<br><br>Team17 Digital Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Das Originalspiel ist zurück und feiert seinen 21. Geburtstag! <br><br>Alien Breed ist der klassische Sci-Fi-Shooter in Draufsicht von Team17. Alien Breed erschien erstmals 1991 und ist jetzt neu für PlayStation®Mobile erhältlich, was nur eins bedeuten kann ... Es ist wieder Zeit, die Lampen auszuschalten, die Lautstärke hochzudrehen und sich auf eine neue Begegnung mit Alien Breed einzustellen! <br><br>Features: <br>★ Klassischer Modus – Spiele mit den Grafiken, der Musik und der Steuerung des Originals. <br>★ Erweiterter Modus – Bietet verbesserte Grafiken, Audio und Steuerung. <br>★ 8 neue Level – brandneue Level, die mit der Geschichte des Originalspiels in Verbindung stehen <br>★ 6 originale Alien Breed-Level <br>★ 12 Alien Breed Special Edition-Level<br><br>Paketgröße: 56 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch<br><br>Team17 Digital Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[The original Alien Breed is back in action, celebrating its 21st Anniversary! <br><br>Alien Breed is the classic sci-fi, top-down shooter developed by Team17. Launching originally in 1991, Alien Breed has now been remade for PlayStation®Mobile, which can only mean one thing… it’s time to turn down the lights, turn up the sounds and encounter Alien Breed again! <br><br>Features: <br>★ Classic Mode – Play using the original graphics, music and controls. <br>★ Enhanced Mode – Featuring enhanced graphics, audio and controls. <br>★ 8 New Levels – entirely new levels that intersect with the original Alien Breed story <br>★ 6 original Alien Breed levels <br>★ 12 Alien Breed Special Edition levels <br>★ Gametel and iCade support<br><br>Package size: 56 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Team17 Digital Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Le jeu d’origine revient pour fêter son 21ème anniversaire ! <br><br>Grand classique de science-fiction, Alien breed est le jeu de tir en vue de dessus développé par Team17. Sorti à l’origine en 1991, Alien Breed a été remis au goût du jour sur PlayStation®Mobile, ce qui veut dire… qu’il est l’heure d’éteindre la lumière, de monter le son et de repartir à l’assaut d’Alien Breed ! <br><br>Descriptif : <br>★ Mode classique – Jouez avec les graphismes, la musique et les commandes d’origine. <br>★ Mode amélioré – Ce mode dispose de graphismes, de sons et de commandes améliorés. <br>★ 4 niveaux inédits – Des niveaux entièrement nouveaux qui se mêlent à l’histoire initiale d’Alien Breed <br>★ 6 niveaux de la version d’origine d’Alien Breed <br>★ 12 niveaux de l’édition spéciale d’Alien Breed<br><br>Taille du programme: 56 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Team17 Digital Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Action"/>
  <genre value="Games:Horror"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
