<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00217_00">

  <appVersion>3.50</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>201403440</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Gør dig klar til action med Delta Strike, et luftkampspil i 3D. Verden er i krig, og som ung pilot har du nu chancen for at vise, at du er en fantastisk militærofficer og blive et flyver-es. Hop om bord til nervepirrende action med dine foretrukne luftfartøjer, såsom klassiske fly, jetfly, helikoptere og endda en drone. <BR>Bring luftstøtte til de kæmpende landtropper eller kast dig ud i heftige kampzoner. Skyd dig igennem bygninger, missiler, kugler, tanks, helikoptere, jetfly og meget mere! Hvis du er til hæsblæsende action, så bliv medlem af vores eskadrille med det samme og oplev spændingen ved de intensive luftkampe.<BR><BR>Funktioner:<BR>- Tag kontrol af luftrummet med over 30 missioner.<BR>- Vælg mellem mere end 9 fantastiske luftfartøjer.<BR>- Lås op for særlige færdigheder til avancerede manøvrerer <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 193 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Bereiten Sie sich vor auf die Action mit Delta Strike, einem 3D-Luftkampfspiel. Die Welt befindet sich im Krieg und Sie als junger Pilot haben jetzt die Chance, sich selbst als ausgezeichneter Militärsoffizier zu beweisen und ein Fliegerass zu werden. Nehmen Sie teil an der intensiven Action mit Ihren Favoriten unter den Flugfahrzeugen, wie klassische Flugzeuge, Jets, Hubschrauber und sogar Drohnen. <BR>Unterstützen Sie die Bodentruppen per Luft beim Kampf oder engagieren Sie sich in bitter umkämpften Kampfzonen. Bomben Sie sich durch Gebäude, Raketen, Kugeln, Panzer, Hubschrauber, Jets und vieles mehr! Wenn Sie extreme Action lieben, sollten Sie jetzt sofort ein Mitglied unserer Staffel werden und die Spannung eines intensiven Kampfes erleben. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 193 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Prepare for action with Delta Strike, an air combat 3D game. The world is at war and as a young pilot now is your chance to prove yourself as a fine military officer and become a Flying Ace. Jump into intense action with your favorite aircrafts like classic airplanes, jets, helicopters and even a drone. Bring air support for grounded troops in combat or engage in fierce combat zones. Blast your way through buildings, missiles, bullets, tanks, helicopters, jets and much more! If you like extreme action, become a member of our squadron right now and feel the excitement of intense combat.<BR><BR>Features:<BR>-Take control of the skies in over 30 missions.<BR>-More than 9 amazing aircraft to choose from.<BR>-Unlock special skills for advanced maneuvers.<BR>-Upgrade and customize your planes. <BR><BR>Package size: 193 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Prepare for action with Delta Strike, an air combat 3D game. The world is at war and as a young pilot now is your chance to prove yourself as a fine military officer and become a Flying Ace. Jump into intense action with your favorite aircrafts like classic airplanes, jets, helicopters and even a drone. Bring air support for grounded troops in combat or engage in fierce combat zones. Blast your way through buildings, missiles, bullets, tanks, helicopters, jets and much more! If you like extreme action, become a member of our squadron right now and feel the excitement of intense combat.<BR><BR>Features:<BR>-Take control of the skies in over 30 missions.<BR>-More than 9 amazing aircraft to choose from.<BR>-Unlock special skills for advanced maneuvers.<BR>-Upgrade and customize your planes. <BR><BR>Package size: 193 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Prepárate a la guerra con Delta Strike un juego de aviones de combate en 3D.Sigue la accion de un joven piloto del aire y domina el espacio aéreo para vencer a tus enemigos. Como oficial militar podrás elegir aviones clásicos, de combate, helicopteros y hasta un drone. Vive la accion como nunca en zonas de combates intensas. Fuerza tu camino a través de los edificios, misiles, balas, tanques, helicopteros, aviones de guerra y mucho más. Busca y destruye a tus enemigos, completa las misiones y gana la experiencia necesaria para desbloquear habilidades avanzadas. Si te gusta el combate aéreo y destruir todo lo que haya en tu camino únete a nuestro escuadrón ahorra. En medio de la accion muestra al resto del mundo cómo restaurar la supremacía aérea. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 193 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Valmistaudu toimintaan Delta Strike 3D-ilmataistelu pelissä. Maailma on sodassa, nuorena lentäjänä sinulla on mahdollisuus todistaa kykysi sotilaana ja tulla Lentäjä-ässäksi. Lennä kiihkeään toimintaan suosikki koneillasi, klassisilla lentokoneilla, suihkukoneilla, helikoptereilla tai jopa maalilennokeilla.<BR>Tuo taisteluissa ilmatukea maajoukoille tai lennä hurjille taistelualueille. Räjäytä tiesi rakennusten läpi käyttäen ohjuksia, luoteja, tankkeja, helikoptereita, suihkukoneita ja paljon muuta! Jos pidät extreme toiminnasta, tule heti laivueemme jäseneksi ja koe kiihkeän taistelun jännitys. <BR><BR>Ominaisuudet:<BR>- Kontrolloi taivasta yli 30 tehtävässä.<BR>- Valittavanasi on yli 9 upeaa lentokonetta. <BR>- Avaa erityistaitoja edistyneisiin sotaharjoituksiin.<BR>- Päivitä ja muokkaa koneitasi. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 193 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Préparez-vous à la guerre avec Delta Strike un jeu d’avion de combat en 3D palpitant. Suivez l’action d’un jeune pilote de l’air qui veut faire ses preuves. En tant qu’officier militaire vous pourrez choisir parmi des avions classiques, des avions de chasses, des hélicoptères et même un drone. Vivez l’action comme jamais auparavant dans des zones de combat intenses. Frayez-vous un chemin à travers des bâtiments, des missiles, des balles, des tanks, des hélicoptères, des avions à réactions et bien plus. Recherchez et détruisez votre cible, complétez vos missions et gagnez l’expérience nécessaire pour effectuer des manœuvres avancées. Si vous aimez tous faire sauter sur votre passage devenez membre de notre escadron dès aujourd’hui. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 193 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Préparez-vous à la guerre avec Delta Strike un jeu d’avion de combat en 3D palpitant. Suivez l’action d’un jeune pilote de l’air qui veut faire ses preuves. En tant qu’officier militaire vous pourrez choisir parmi des avions classiques, des avions de chasses, des hélicoptères et même un drone. Vivez l’action comme jamais auparavant dans des zones de combat intenses. Frayez-vous un chemin à travers des bâtiments, des missiles, des balles, des tanks, des hélicoptères, des avions à réactions et bien plus. Recherchez et détruisez votre cible, complétez vos missions et gagnez l’expérience nécessaire pour effectuer des manœuvres avancées. Si vous aimez tous faire sauter sur votre passage devenez membre de notre escadron dès aujourd’hui. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 193 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Preparati all’azione con Delta Strike, un gioco di combattimento aereo in 3D. ll mondo è in guerra ed è arrivato il momento per te, giovane pilota, di mettere alla prova le tue doti di ufficiale militare e di diventare un asso del volo. Per entrare in azione potrai scegliere tra aeroplani classici, jet, elicotteri o drone e dare supporto aereo alle truppe terrestri in combattimento o addentrarti in zone di combattimento feroce.Prova a cavartela contro edifici, missili, pallottole, carri armati, elicotteri, jet e molto altro ancora! Se ti piace l’aventura estrema, arruolati subito e non perderti l’emozione del combattimento intenso!<BR><BR>Caratteristiche:<BR>- Prenderai il controllo del cielo in oltre 30 missioni.<BR>- Potrai scegliere tra più di 9 velivoli diversi. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 193 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>離陸する準備はできていますか？デルタストライクは空中戦の3Dゲームです。世界は戦争状態にあり、若きパイロットであるあなたは、優秀な空軍戦士であることを証明できるチャンスにあります。そしてフライングエースになれるのです。昔ながらの飛行機や、ジェット機、ヘリコプター、そしてドローンなど、お好みの飛行機に乗って激しい戦いに臨んでみませんか？ <BR>陸軍のために空を守るか、熾烈な戦闘ゾーンに入り込んでみてください。建物、ミサイル、銃弾、戦車、ヘリコプター、ジェット機などを破壊していきましょう！もし究極のアクションがお好きであれば、今すぐに戦隊に参加して、炸裂する戦いに挑んでみてください。<BR><BR>特性:<BR>-30ミッション以上で空域をコントロールできる。<BR>-9機を超える飛行機の中から選択可能。<BR>-上級者操作で特別な技能を放つことができる。<BR>-自分の機体をアップグレードおよびカスタマイズ可能。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 193 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Gjør deg klar for action med Delta Strike, et flykrigsspill i 3D. Verden er i krig og som ung pilot har du muligheten til å vise at du er en dyktig offiser og bli et Flying Ace. Opplev intens action med foretrukne flymaskiner som klassiske fly, jetfly, helikoptre og til og med en drone. <BR>Gi luftstøtte til bakkestyrker i kamp og delta i intense kampområder. Skyt gjennom bygninger, tanks, helikoptre og jetfly med raketter, kuler og mye mer! Bli medlem av vår skvadron nå hvis du liker ekstrem action og følelsen kriging gir deg.<BR><BR>Innhold:<BR>-Ta kontroll over luftrommet i over 30 oppdrag.<BR>-Velg blant 9 fantastiske flymaskiner.<BR>-Lås opp spesialferdigheter for avanserte manøvrer.<BR>-Oppgrader og brukertilpass flyene. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 193 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Maak je klaar voor actie met Delta Strike, een 3D luchtgevechtsspel. De wereld voert oorlog en als jonge piloot is dit jouw kans om jezelf als vooraanstaande militaire officier te bewijzen en topvliegenier te worden. Kom in actie met je favoriete vliegtuigen zoals echte klassiekers, straaljagers, helikopters en zelfs een drone.Geef luchtondersteuning voor de grondtroepen tijdens gevechten of doe mee aan hevige gevechtszones. Blaas je weg door gebouwen, raketten, kogels, tanks, helikopters, straaljagers en nog veel meer! Als je van extreme actie houdt, word dan meteen lid van ons squadron en voel de spanning van intense gevechten.<BR><BR>Kenmerken:<BR>- Neem de leiding over de lucht in 30 missies.<BR>- Meer dan 9 prachtige vliegtuigen om uit te kiezen.<BR>- Upgrade en personaliseer je vliegtuigen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 193 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Przygotuj się do bitwy w Delta Strike, strzelance powietrz. 3D. Na świecie toczy się wojna i jako młody pilot masz szansę sprawdzić się w roli świetnego wojskowego i zostać Asem Przestworzy. Dołącz do ostrych potyczek na pokładzie ulub. statku powietrz., np. klas. samolotu, odrzutowca, helikoptera, a nawet drona. <BR>Zapewnij wsparcie powietrz. wojskom ląd., bądź dołącz do zażartych walk. Utoruj sobie drogę przez budynki, grad rakiet i pocisków, czołgi, helikoptery, odrzutowce i wiele innych! Jeżeli lubisz ekstremalną walkę, zostań członkiem dywizjonu i poczuj emocje intensywnych walk.<BR><BR>Cechy:<BR>-Zawładnij niebem w ponad 30 misjach.<BR>-Do wyboru ponad 9 niesamowitych samolotów.<BR>-Odblokuj specjalne umiejętności, aby wykonywać zaaw. manewry.<BR>-Rozbuduj i dostosuj własne samoloty <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 193 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Förbered dig för action med Delta Strike, ett flygstridsspel i 3D. Det är krig i världen och du har nu din chans att som ung pilot bevisa att du är en duglig officer och bli ett flygaress. Kasta dig in i action med dina favoritflygmaskiner som klassiska flygplan, jetplan, helikoptrar och t.o.m. drönare. <BR>Var flygunderstöd åt marktrupper i strid eller inställ dig i våldsamma stridszoner. Spräng dig fram genom byggnader, missiler, kulor, stridsvagnar, helikoptrar, jetplan med mera! Om du gillar extrem action ska du bli medlem i vår skvadron nu och få känna på spänningen med heta strider.<BR><BR>Innehåller:<BR>-Ta kontroll över luftrummet i över 30 uppdrag.<BR>-Fler än 9 flygmaskiner att välja mellan.<BR>-Lås upp särskilda skills för avancerade manövrar.<BR>-Uppgradera och anpassa dina plan. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 193 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 by Cerberus. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
