<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00019_00">
 <appVersion>1.05</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>38326304</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[オフサイドについて知ってる？<br>サッカー専門家だと思う？<br>審判より良い仕事ができると思う？ <br><br>それなら、頭を使い、自分の素晴らしいサッカー知識に対する自己満足のスマイルを浮かべるための完璧なゲームを探す必要はありません。あなたに必要なサッカートリビアアプリはYou Are The Refだけです。<br><br>Four Door Lemon Ltdは大人気カルトクラシックを21世紀に向けて発射し、PlayStation Mobileデバイスに着地させたことに興奮しています。<br><br>ポール・トレヴィリオンによって50年に渡って描かれたカルト的サッカーコミックから厳選されたアートワークと、元プレミアリーグ審判キース・ハケットの監修の下、You Are The Refは究極のサッカートリビアゲームです。<br><br>特徴：<br><br>• 頭を使うチャレンジングな3種類のゲームモード<br>• 美しい手書きのイラスト <br>• ありふれたものから全く馬鹿げたようなものまで何百もの質問と、プレミアリーグサッカー史上で最も偉大な審判の一人による解答<br><br>コンテンツ容量:37 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Know your offside from your elbow?<br>Consider yourself a soccer expert? <br>Think you could do a better job than the ref?<br><br>Then look no further for the perfect game to probe your mind and give you a smug smile of satisfaction over your superior soccer summations. You Are The Ref is the only soccer trivia app you’ll need.<br><br>Four Door Lemon Ltd are thrilled to bring a much-loved cult classic hurtling firmly into the 21st century, landing squarely on PlayStation Mobile devices.<br><br>Incorporating selected artwork created over 50 years from the cult soccer strip drawn by Paul Trevillion and official guidance on the laws former Premier League referee Keith Hackett, You Are The Ref is the ultimate soccer trivia game.<br><br>Features:<br><br>• 3 brain teasing and challenging game modes<br>• Beautifully hand drawn illustrations <br>• Hundreds of questions ranging from the everyday to the flat-out ridiculous with answers from one of the greatest refereeing names in Premier League soccer<br><br>Package size: 37 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Vous maîtrisez à la perfection le piège du hors-jeu ?<br>Vous pensez être incollable sur le football ?<br>Vous pensez pouvoir faire mieux que l'arbitre ?<br><br>Alors, ne cherchez pas plus loin : ce jeu mettra vos talents à l'épreuve et vous donnera toute crédibilité dans le monde du ballon rond. You Are The Ref est l'application footballistique qu'il vous faut.<br><br>Les studios Four Door Lemon Ltd sont ravis de propulser ce jeu culte au cœur du 21e siècle, avec une version disponible sur les appareils PlayStation Mobile.<br><br>Intégrant des reproductions artistiques du célèbre dessinateur Paul Trevillion et utilisant les conseils officiels de Keith Hackett, ancien arbitre de Premier League, You Are The Ref est le jeu de culture footballistique par excellence.<br><br>Caractéristiques :<br><br>• 3 modes de jeu pour mettre vos compétences à rude épreuve<br>• De superbes illustrations dessinées<br>• Des centaines de questions très variées avec les réponses de l'un des meilleurs arbitres de l'histoire de la Premier League<br><br>Taille du paquet: 37 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Sai benissimo cos’è un fuorigioco?<br>Ti consideri un esperto di calcio? <br>Pensi che potresti fare molto meglio dell’arbitro?<br><br>Allora, hai trovato il gioco perfetto, che metterà alla prova la tua mente e che, grazie alle tue superiori conoscenze calcistiche, ti permetterà di indossare un sorriso compiaciuto. You Are The Ref è l’unica App di curiosità calcistiche di cui tu abbia bisogno.<br><br>La Four Door Lemon Ltd è lieta di portare a tutta velocità nel ventunesimo secolo sui dispositivi PlayStation Mobile un classico amatissimo.<br><br>Con i disegni creati più di 50 anni fa per la sua striscia calcistica da Paul Trevillon e la consulenza dell’ex arbitro di Premier League Keith Hackett, You Are The Ref è il gioco di curiosità sul calcio migliore che ci sia. <br><br>Caratteristiche:<br><br>• 3 modalità intense e stimolanti<br>• Bellissime illustrazioni disegnate a mano <br>• Centinaia di domande, dal quotidiano alle curiosità più strane, con le risposte di uno dei più grandi arbitri della Premier League.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 37 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¿No se te escapa ningún fuera de juego?<br>¿Te consideras una eminencia futbolística? <br>¿Crees que lo harías mejor que el árbitro?<br><br>Pues ha dado fin tu búsqueda del juego perfecto para poner a prueba tu mente y arrancarte una petulante sonrisa de satisfacción ante tus resultados futbolísticos de primera. You Are The Ref es la única aplicación de preguntas futbolísticas que necesitarás.<br><br>A Four Door Lemon Ltd le complace traer un clásico de culto muy querido de vuelta al siglo XXI, para realizar un aterrizaje perfecto en los dispositivos PlayStation Mobile.<br><br>Con ilustraciones selectas creadas a lo largo de más de 50 años a partir de la tira de fútbol de culto dibujada por Paul Trevillion, y orientación oficial sobre el reglamento del ex árbitro de la Premier League Keith Hackett, You Are The Ref es el juego definitivo de información futbolística.<br><br>Características:<br><br>• 3 modos de juego desafiantes para comerte la cabeza<br>• Preciosas ilustraciones dibujadas a mano <br>• Cientos de preguntas que pasan de lo básico a lo ridículamente concreto, con respuestas de uno de los nombres más destacados en el arbitraje de la Premier League de fútbol<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 37 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Du kannst Abseits von deinem Ellbogen unterscheiden?<br>Du siehst dich selbst als Fußballexperten? <br>Du denkst, du bist besser als der Schiedsrichter?<br><br>Dann suche nicht weiter nach dem perfekten Spiel, um deinen Verstand herauszufordern und dir ein selbstgefälliges Lächeln über dein überlegenes Fußball-Wissen abzuringen. You Are The Ref ist das einzige Fußballquiz, das du brauchst.<br><br>Four Door Lemon Ltd freut sich, einen vielgeliebten Kultklassiker in das 21. Jahrhundert zu schleudern, wo er direkt auf PlayStation Mobile landet.<br><br>Mit ausgewählten Grafiken, die über 50 Jahre für das Kult-Fußballcomic von Paul Trevillion gezeichnet wurden und mit offizieller Anleitung zu den Spielregeln vom ehemaligen Erstliga-Schiedsrichters Keith Hackett, ist You Are The Ref das ultimative Fußballspiel.<br><br>Funktionen:<br><br>• 3 spannende und herausfordernde Spielmodi<br>• Schöne, handgezeichnete Illustrationen <br>• Hunderte Fragen vom Alltäglichen bis hin zum geradezu Lächerlichen, zusätzlich dazu die Antworten von einem der größten Schiedsrichternamen in der Premier League<br><br>Paketgröße: 37 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Know your offside from your elbow?<br>Consider yourself a football expert? <br>Think you could do a better job than the ref?<br><br>Then look no further for the perfect game to probe your mind and give you a smug smile of satisfaction over your superior soccer summations. You Are The Ref is the only football trivia app you’ll need.<br><br>Four Door Lemon Ltd are thrilled to bring a much-loved cult classic hurtling firmly into the 21st century, landing squarely on PlayStation Mobile devices.<br><br>Incorporating selected artwork created over 50 years from the cult football strip drawn by Paul Trevillion and official guidance on the laws former Premier League referee Keith Hackett, You Are The Ref is the ultimate football trivia game.<br><br>Features:<br><br>• 3 brain teasing and challenging game modes<br>• Beautifully hand drawn illustrations <br>• Hundreds of questions ranging from the everyday to the flat-out ridiculous with answers from one of the greatest refereeing names in Premier League football<br><br>Package size: 37 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Vous maîtrisez à la perfection le piège du hors-jeu ?<br>Vous pensez être incollable sur le football ?<br>Vous pensez pouvoir faire mieux que l'arbitre ?<br><br>Alors, ne cherchez pas plus loin : ce jeu mettra vos talents à l'épreuve et vous donnera toute crédibilité dans le monde du ballon rond. You Are The Ref est l'application footballistique qu'il vous faut.<br><br>Les studios Four Door Lemon Ltd sont ravis de propulser ce jeu culte au cœur du 21e siècle, avec une version disponible sur les appareils PlayStation Mobile.<br><br>Intégrant des reproductions artistiques du célèbre dessinateur Paul Trevillion et utilisant les conseils officiels de Keith Hackett, ancien arbitre de Premier League, You Are The Ref est le jeu de culture footballistique par excellence.<br><br>Caractéristiques :<br><br>• 3 modes de jeu pour mettre vos compétences à rude épreuve<br>• De superbes illustrations dessinées<br>• Des centaines de questions très variées avec les réponses de l'un des meilleurs arbitres de l'histoire de la Premier League<br><br>Taille du programme: 37 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>(C) 2012 Four Foor Lemon LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Family"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
