<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00124_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>38937696</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Ten By Eight (10X8) ist ein Puzzlespiel für geduldige Gehirnchirurgen.<BR>Kacheln lösen sich nicht von alleine auf in Ten By Eight (10X8): Verschiebe die Kacheln so, dass 3 oder mehr der gleichen Farbe eine Kette bilden. Benutze daraufhin die Sternkacheln um unterschiedliche Farbketten zu verbinden. Je länger die Kette – desto mehr Punkte gibt’s. Dir stehen 3 Modi zur Verfügung: Der Zeitmodus ist auf 3 Minuten beschränkt. Der Zenmodus gibt dir ohne Zeitdruck die Möglichkeit dich eigenen Herausforderungen zu stellen, wie alle 80 Kacheln in einem Zug zu löschen. Und der Endlosmodus hört nie auf – wenn du gut genug bist die Steinkacheln zu zerstören. Dazu musst du sie mit Farbketten umzingeln. Aber Vorsicht: Berührt eine Steinkachel den Boden heißt es: Game Over. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 38 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Ten By Eight is a puzzle game strong enough for a brain surgeon and pH-balanced for a rocket scientist. You can clear as few as three tiles, though don't stop there! Swap tiles into groups of three or more. Chain up the longest match you can. Use wildcard star tiles to link a chain of one color to a chain of another color. Heat the action up in any of three modes. Timed Mode asks you how many points you can make in three minutes. Zen Mode asks you to hang out and make your own challenges (try clearing all eighty tiles in one action). And Endless Mode never ends -- if you're good enough. In Endless Mode stone tiles will appear. Surround them to destroy them; if one touches the bottom, it's game over. Also, the music is great. <BR><BR>Package size: 38 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Ten By Eight is a puzzle game strong enough for a brain surgeon and pH-balanced for a rocket scientist. You can clear as few as three tiles, though don't stop there! Swap tiles into groups of three or more. Chain up the longest match you can. Use wildcard star tiles to link a chain of one color to a chain of another color. Heat the action up in any of three modes. Timed Mode asks you how many points you can make in three minutes. Zen Mode asks you to hang out and make your own challenges (try clearing all eighty tiles in one action). And Endless Mode never ends -- if you're good enough. In Endless Mode stone tiles will appear. Surround them to destroy them; if one touches the bottom, it's game over. Also, the music is great. <BR><BR>Package size: 38 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Ten By Eight is a puzzle game strong enough for a brain surgeon and pH-balanced for a rocket scientist. You can clear as few as three tiles, though don't stop there! Swap tiles into groups of three or more. Chain up the longest match you can. Use wildcard star tiles to link a chain of one color to a chain of another color. Heat the action up in any of three modes. Timed Mode asks you how many points you can make in three minutes. Zen Mode asks you to hang out and make your own challenges (try clearing all eighty tiles in one action). And Endless Mode never ends -- if you're good enough. In Endless Mode stone tiles will appear. Surround them to destroy them; if one touches the bottom, it's game over. Also, the music is great. <BR><BR>Package size: 38 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Ten By Eight is a puzzle game strong enough for a brain surgeon and pH-balanced for a rocket scientist. You can clear as few as three tiles, though don't stop there! Swap tiles into groups of three or more. Chain up the longest match you can. Use wildcard star tiles to link a chain of one color to a chain of another color. Heat the action up in any of three modes. Timed Mode asks you how many points you can make in three minutes. Zen Mode asks you to hang out and make your own challenges (try clearing all eighty tiles in one action). And Endless Mode never ends -- if you're good enough. In Endless Mode stone tiles will appear. Surround them to destroy them; if one touches the bottom, it's game over. Also, the music is great. <BR><BR>Package size: 38 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[En Ten by Eight (10X8) las piezas no desaparecen por si solas: Puedes empezar uniendo 3 bloques: Pero porque detenerse en tres? Cambia las piezas en grupos de tres o más. Encadena la combinación más larga que puedas. Utiliza bloques estrella como comodines para unir una cadena de un color con otra cadena de otro color. Incrementa la acción con cualquiera de los tres modos de juego disponibles: Timed Mode te pide que hagas la mayor cantidad de puntos en tres minutos. Zen Mode te da todo el tiempo que tú quieras para crear tus propios desafíos (Por ejemplo: Elimina 80 bloques con una sola acción). Y Endless Mode nunca termina, si eres lo suficientemente bueno. En Endless Mode tienes bloques de piedra que tú debes rodear con combinaciones para así destruirlos. Si uno de ellos toca el fondo de <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 38 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Dans Ten By Eight, vous pouvez enlever les tuiles trois à la fois, mais pourquoi vous arrêter-là? Enchaînez les plus longues combinaisons possibles. Utilisez les tuiles étoilées pour lier deux chaines de couleurs différentes. Explorez trois modes: Le Timed Mode vous demande de totaliser un maximum de points en trois minutes. Le Zen Mode vous laisse créer vos propres défis (par exemple: enlever quatre-vingts tuiles en une seule action). Et le Endless Mode ne se termine jamais -- si vous êtes assez doués. Des tuiles de pierre apparaîtront. Entourez les d'une combinaison pour les détruire; si l'une d'entre elles touche le bas, la partie se termine. Ten By Eight est un jeu de réflexion assez puissant pour un neurochirurgien et au pH assez balancé pour un ingénieur spatial. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 38 MB - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Ten By Eight est un puzzle game où vous devez enchainer 3 blocs identiques ou plus. Grâce aux blocs "étoile", liez 2 chaines de couleur différente. Intensifiez votre cosmos sur les 3 modes disponibles. Le Mode Chrono vous demandera de scorer un maximum en 3 minutes. Le Mode Zen permettra de créer vos propres challenges (ex : faire disparaitre les 80 blocs en une fois). Et le Mode Sans Fin -- enfin si vous êtes suffisamment doués -- où vous devez encercler des blocs "pierre" à l'aide d'une chaine pour les détruire avant qu'elles n'atteignent le fond, sinon c'est le game over. Ten By Eight est un puzzle game suffisamment corsé pour donner du fil à retordre à un neurochirurgien et tout à fait calibré pour un ingénieur de la NASA. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 38 MB – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[In Ten by Eight: si può iniziare cancellando tre tessere ma perchè fermarsi? Scambia le tessere in gruppi di tre o più e incatena la fila di tessere più lunga possibile. Utilizza le tessere jolly per collegare catene di diverso colore!<BR><BR>Divertiti con tre modalità diverse: Timer, quanti punti riesci a fare in 3 minuti? Endless mode, gioca finchè la tua abilità te lo consente...ma attento alle tessere di pietra! Zen Mode, gioca e divertiti a fare punti senza paura di finire il tempo o di perdere la partita...è una modalità Zen dopotutto! Ten by Eight è un puzzle game per menti geniali! Accetti la sfida? <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 38 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[『１０X８』は二つのブロックの位置を入れ替えて、マッチをクリアするパズルゲームですが、ブロックは自動的にクリアしないわけです。結局クリアする決断を下すのはあなたです。だから、三つ以上を目指してください！もしかしたら、星ブロックを上手く使えたら、一種類のブロックマッチを別の種類のブロックのマッチに繋ぎあわせたりして、全クリアの８０ブロックマッチも無理じゃないです！<BR><BR>三つのモードもありますよ！TIMEDモードで３分の時間限定でポイントをなるべくゲット！ZENモードでリラックス、自分のペースでゲームを楽しんでください。そしてENDLESSモードは無限のモードで、何となくのタクティクスゲームになってきます。無限モードでは石ブロックは時々現れるので、石をブロックで囲めてクリアすれば石を消してください！石は下に下がればゲームオーバーで・・・ゲームオーバーは怖いですので頑張ってください！<BR><BR>三つのモードでポイントを貯めれば、ショップで沢山のカラフルな友達がゲットすることができますよ！<BR><BR>『１０X８』は、脳神経外科医でも一般人でも楽しめるパズルゲームです。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 38 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Action Button Entertainment, LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Strategy"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
