<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00012_00">
 <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>15766240</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[「レストランは清潔感が命！<br>お客様には気持ちよく食事をしてもらいたい。<br>料理を俺に任せろ！<br>とにかく汚れたテーブルを片っ端からきれいにしてくれ！<br>頼んだぞ。」店長<br><br>勝負はいかにスピーディーに店内のテーブルをワイプする（拭く）か。<br>でも慌てすぎるな！慌てると食器を壊すぞ。<br>こびりついたシツコイ汚れ、ツルツル滑る油汚れ、<br>汚れ達はなかなか手ごわいぞ！<br><br>あなたの「清潔度」「きれい好き度」が試されるゲーム。<br>Ａ型（だけでなく）清潔ワイパー達を求む！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:16 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語<br><br>著作権等:<br>SYNC Inc.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA["Cleanness" is top priority in our restaurant.<br>I want people to feel clean when eating.<br>Of course, the food must be good too. Leave that to me.<br>Your job, to keep tables crystal clean! Get to it!<br>From your manager<br><br>Wipe off dirt and keep tables clean as efficiently as possible.<br>But don't rush, you might break a nice dish or two.<br>Thick sticky dirt, oily slippery dirt, nasty looking dirt,<br>and many other pain in the xxx dirt will challenge you!<br><br>Your cleanness is put to the test.<br>Are you clean enough for some wipe kicking action?<br><br>Package size: 16 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<br><br>SYNC Inc.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[La "netteté" est priorité supérieure dans notre restaurant. <br>Je veux que les gens se sentent propre quand manger. <br>Bien sûr, la nourriture doit être bonne aussi. Laissez-moi cela. <br>Votre travail, garder cristal des tables propre! Arrivez à lui! <br>De votre Coup de torchon du directeur fermé saleté et tables de la nourriture propre aussi efficacement que possible. <br>Mais ne se dépêche pas, vous pouvez casser un plat agréable ou deux. <br>Saleté collante épaisse, saleté glissante huileuse, saleté regardant désagréable et beaucoup d'autre douleur dans la saleté du xxx vous défiera! <br><br>Votre netteté est mise à l'épreuve. <br>Est-ce que vous êtes propre assez pour quelque coup de torchon qui donne un coup de pied à action?<br><br>Taille du paquet: 16 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais<br><br>SYNC Inc.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[La "pulizia" è priorità di cima nel nostro ristorante. <br>Io voglio che persone si sentano pulito quando mangiando. <br>Il cibo anche deve essere chiaramente, buono. Lasci quell'a me. <br>Il Suo lavoro, tenere cristallo di tavole pulito! Arrivi a lui! <br>Dalla Sua Pulitina di direttore via immondizia e tiene il più efficientemente possibile tavole pulito. <br>Ma non riveste di vimini, è probabile che Lei rompa un bel piatto o due. <br>Immondizia appiccicosa e spessa, immondizia sdrucciolevole ed oleosa, immondizia che guarda sporca, e molto altro dolore nell'immondizia di xxx La sfideranno! <br><br>La Sua pulizia è messa alla prova. <br>È pulito abbastanza per della pulitina che calcia azione?<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 16 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese<br><br>SYNC Inc.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[La "limpieza" es la prioridad de la cima en nuestro restaurante. <br>Quiero que las personas se sientan limpio al comer. <br>Claro, la comida también debe ser buena. Deje eso a mí. <br>¡Su trabajo, guardar cristal de las mesas limpian! ¡Llegue a lo! <br>De su gerente Limpie suciedad y mesas de subsistencia limpie tan eficazmente como posible. <br>Pero no se apresura, podría romper un plato bueno o dos. <br>¡La suciedad pegajosa espesa, suciedad resbaladiza aceitosa, suciedad pareciendo sucia y muchos otro dolor en la suciedad del xxx lo desafiarán! <br><br>Su limpieza se pone a prueba. <br>¿Está limpio bastante para algunos limpie dando de puntapiés la acción?<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 16 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés<br><br>SYNC Inc.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA["Sauberkeit" ist höchst Priorität in unserem Restaurant. <br>Ich will, bevölkern Sie, um sich sauber zu fühlen, wenn Sie essen. <br>Natürlich muß das Essen auch gut sein. Überlassen Sie mir das. <br>Ihre Arbeit, sauber Tische-Kristall zu halten! Kommen Sie dazu! <br>Von Ihrem Manager Wipe von Schmutz und hält Tische so effizient wie möglich sauber. <br>Aber hetzt nicht, Sie könnten eine nette Schüssel oder zwei brechen. <br>Dicker klebriger Schmutz, öliger rutschiger Schmutz, scheußlicher sehender Schmutz und viel anderer Schmerz im xxx-Schmutz werden Sie herausfordern! <br><br>Ihre Sauberkeit wird auf die Probe gestellt. <br>Sind Sie für etwas Wischen sauber genug, der die Handlung tritt?<br><br>Paketgröße: 16 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch<br><br>SYNC Inc.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA["Cleanness" is top priority in our restaurant.<br>I want people to feel clean when eating.<br>Of course, the food must be good too. Leave that to me.<br>Your job, to keep tables crystal clean! Get to it!<br>From your manager<br><br>Wipe off dirt and keep tables clean as efficiently as possible.<br>But don't rush, you might break a nice dish or two.<br>Thick sticky dirt, oily slippery dirt, nasty looking dirt,<br>and many other pain in the xxx dirt will challenge you!<br><br>Your cleanness is put to the test.<br>Are you clean enough for some wipe kicking action?<br><br>Package size: 16 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<br><br>SYNC Inc.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[La "netteté" est priorité supérieure dans notre restaurant. <br>Je veux que les gens se sentent propre quand manger. <br>Bien sûr, la nourriture doit être bonne aussi. Laissez-moi cela. <br>Votre travail, garder cristal des tables propre! Arrivez à lui! <br>De votre Coup de torchon du directeur fermé saleté et tables de la nourriture propre aussi efficacement que possible. <br>Mais ne se dépêche pas, vous pouvez casser un plat agréable ou deux. <br>Saleté collante épaisse, saleté glissante huileuse, saleté regardant désagréable et beaucoup d'autre douleur dans la saleté du xxx vous défiera! <br><br>Votre netteté est mise à l'épreuve. <br>Est-ce que vous êtes propre assez pour quelque coup de torchon qui donne un coup de pied à action?<br><br>Taille du programme: 16 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais<br><br>SYNC Inc.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Action"/>
  <genre value="Games:Casual"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
