<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00198_00">

  <appVersion>1.30</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>82278240</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Håndværk, og udforske under vand!<BR>Battle, venner med og bygge som et havdyr online med mange spillere fra hele verden!<BR>Tilpas, navn, overleve, håndværk, rang op og med dit ocean pet udforske!<BR>Mange miljøer, herunder Marine, Atlantis, Slot, Fisk Bowl Gamers Tribute Kort!<BR>Indret dit Klovnfisk, Piranha, Manta Rays, Skildpadder, søheste, hajer, sæler, Starfish, tun, Globefish, vandmænd, Oyster eller Goldfish farver og trail mønstre!<BR>Rollespil og chatte online med andre som deres egne havdyr, bliver venner eller kamp mod dem for skinnende erfaring mønter, eller hold op og tage ned fjendens hajer og piratfisk!<BR>Cross Platform, 3D-miljø, farverig, online multiplayer, PVP og meget mere!<BR>PlayStation®TV kompatible. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 79 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR>Support til online spil med flere spillere: Ja (2-32 spillere)<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Kunsthandwerk, und erkunden unter Wasser!<BR>Schlacht, anzufreunden und als Meerestier bauen Online mit vielen Spielern aus der ganzen Welt!<BR>Fertigen Sie, Name, überleben, Handwerk, Rang und erkunden mit Meer Haustier!<BR>Viele Umgebungen, einschließlich, Meeres-, Atlantis, Castle, Fish Bowl und Gamers Tribute Karte!<BR>Dekorieren Sie Ihr Clownfische, Piranha, Mantas, Schildkröten, Seepferdchen, Haie, Robben, Starfish, Thunfisch, Globefish, Qualle, Oyster oder Goldfish Farben und Mustern Spur!<BR>Rollenspiele und Online-Chat mit anderen als ihre eigenen Meerestiere, zu Freunden oder Kampf gegen sie für glänzende Erfahrung Münzen oder Team Auf- und Abbau Feinde Haie und Piranhas!<BR>Plattformübergreifende, 3D-Umgebung, bunt, Online-Multiplayer, PVP und vieles mehr!<BR>PlayStation®TV kompatibel. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 79 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR>Online-Unterstützung für Multiplayer-Spiel: Ja (2-32 Spieler)<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Craft, and explore under water!<BR>Battle, befriend and build as a sea creature online with many players from around the world!<BR>Customise, name, survive, craft, rank up and explore with your ocean pet !<BR>Many environments, including, Marine, Atlantis, Castle, Fish Bowl and Gamers Tribute Map!<BR>Decorate your Clownfish, Piranha, Manta Rays, Turtles, Sea horses, Sharks, Seals, Starfish, Tuna, Globefish, Jellyfish, Oyster or Goldfish colours and trail patterns! <BR>Role play and chat online with others as their own sea animals, become friends or battle against them for shiny experience coins, or team up and take down enemy sharks and piranha!<BR>Cross Platform, 3D environment, colourful, online multiplayer, PVP and more!<BR>PlayStation®TV compatible. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Package size: 79 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2-32 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Craft, and explore under water!<BR>Battle, befriend and build as a sea creature online with many players from around the world!<BR>Customise, name, survive, craft, rank up and explore with your ocean pet !<BR>Many environments, including, Marine, Atlantis, Castle, Fish Bowl and Gamers Tribute Map!<BR>Decorate your Clownfish, Piranha, Manta Rays, Turtles, Sea horses, Sharks, Seals, Starfish, Tuna, Globefish, Jellyfish, Oyster or Goldfish colours and trail patterns! <BR>Role play and chat online with others as their own sea animals, become friends or battle against them for shiny experience coins, or team up and take down enemy sharks and piranha!<BR>Cross Platform, 3D environment, colourful, online multiplayer, PVP and more!<BR>PlayStation®TV compatible. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Package size: 79 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2-32 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Craft, and explore under water!<BR>Battle, befriend and build as a sea creature online with many players from around the world!<BR>Customise, name, survive, craft, rank up and explore with your ocean pet !<BR>Many environments, including, Marine, Atlantis, Castle, Fish Bowl and Gamers Tribute Map!<BR>Decorate your Clownfish, Piranha, Manta Rays, Turtles, Sea horses, Sharks, Seals, Starfish, Tuna, Globefish, Jellyfish, Oyster or Goldfish colours and trail patterns! <BR>Role play and chat online with others as their own sea animals, become friends or battle against them for shiny experience coins, or team up and take down enemy sharks and piranha!<BR>Cross Platform, 3D environment, colourful, online multiplayer, PVP and more!<BR>PlayStation®TV compatible. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Package size: 79 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2-32 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Craft, and explore under water!<BR>Battle, befriend and build as a sea creature online with many players from around the world!<BR>Customise, name, survive, craft, rank up and explore with your ocean pet !<BR>Many environments, including, Marine, Atlantis, Castle, Fish Bowl and Gamers Tribute Map!<BR>Decorate your Clownfish, Piranha, Manta Rays, Turtles, Sea horses, Sharks, Seals, Starfish, Tuna, Globefish, Jellyfish, Oyster or Goldfish colours and trail patterns! <BR>Role play and chat online with others as their own sea animals, become friends or battle against them for shiny experience coins, or team up and take down enemy sharks and piranha!<BR>Cross Platform, 3D environment, colourful, online multiplayer, PVP and more!<BR>PlayStation®TV compatible. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Package size: 79 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2-32 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Artesanía, y explorar bajo el agua!<BR>Batalla, se hacen amigos y construir como una criatura marina en línea con muchos jugadores de todo el mundo!<BR>Modifique para requisitos particulares, nombre, sobrevivir, artesanía, clasificar y explorar con su mascota al mar!<BR>Muchos mapas de entorno!<BR>Decora tu pez payaso, Piranha, manta rayas, tortugas, caballitos de mar, tiburones, focas, estrellas de mar, atún, Medusas, Oyster o Goldfish colores y patrones del rastro!<BR>Juego de rol y charlar en línea con los demás como sus propios animales marinos, se convierten en amigos o batalla contra ellos por monedas experiencia brillantes, o equipo y toma abajo tiburones enemigos y pirañas!<BR>Plataforma Cruz, entorno 3D, colorido, multijugador online, PVP y mucho más!<BR>PlayStation®TV compatible. V1.3 <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 79 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR>Asistencia para juegos de varios jugadores en línea: Sí (2-32 jugadores)<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Veneet, ja tutkia veden alla!<BR>Battle, ystävystyä ja rakentaa niin meri olento verkossa monet pelaajat ympäri maailmaa!<BR>Muokkaa, nimi, hengissä, veneet, listalla ylös ja tutkia teidän valtameri lemmikki!<BR>Monet ympäristöissä, mukaan lukien, Marine, Atlantis, linna, kala kulhoon ja Gamers Tribute Map!<BR>Koristele Clownfish, Piranha, Manta Rays, Turtles, merihevosia, hait, tiivisteet, Meritähti, tonnikala, GLOBEFISH, meduusoja, Oyster tai Kultakala värejä ja trail kuvioita!<BR>Roolileikit ja keskustella verkossa muiden kuin oman meren eläimet, ystävystyä tai taisteluun heitä kiiltävät kokemus kolikoita, tai joukkue ja ottaa alas vihollisen hait ja piraija!<BR>Cross Platform, 3D-ympäristössä, värikäs, online-moninpeli, PVP ja enemmän!<BR>PlayStation®TV yhteensopivia. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 79 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR>Monen pelaajan pelin verkkotuki: Kyllä  (2-32 pelaajaa)<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Artisanat, et d'explorer sous l'eau!<BR>Bataille, lier d'amitié et de construire comme une créature de la mer en ligne avec beaucoup de joueurs du monde entier!<BR>Personnaliser, nom, de survivre, de l'artisanat, de classer et d'explorer avec votre animal de l'océan!<BR>Beaucoup de cartes de l'environnement!<BR>Décorez votre Clownfish, Piranha, raies manta, tortues, hippocampes, requins, phoques, Méduse (et plus) couleurs et les modèles de piste!<BR>Le jeu de rôle et discuter en ligne avec d'autres que leurs propres animaux marins, devenir amis ou bataille contre eux pour les pièces d'expérience brillant, ou de l'équipe et prendre vers le bas les requins de l'ennemi et piranha!<BR>Cross Platform, environnement 3D, coloré, multijoueur en ligne, PVP et plus encore!<BR>PlayStation®TV compatible. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 79 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR>Mode multijoueur en ligne : Oui (2-32 joueurs)<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Artisanat, et d'explorer sous l'eau!<BR>Bataille, lier d'amitié et de construire comme une créature de la mer en ligne avec beaucoup de joueurs du monde entier!<BR>Personnaliser, nom, de survivre, de l'artisanat, de classer et d'explorer avec votre animal de l'océan!<BR>Beaucoup de cartes de l'environnement!<BR>Décorez votre Clownfish, Piranha, raies manta, tortues, hippocampes, requins, phoques, Méduse (et plus) couleurs et les modèles de piste!<BR>Le jeu de rôle et discuter en ligne avec d'autres que leurs propres animaux marins, devenir amis ou bataille contre eux pour les pièces d'expérience brillant, ou de l'équipe et prendre vers le bas les requins de l'ennemi et piranha!<BR>Cross Platform, environnement 3D, coloré, multijoueur en ligne, PVP et plus encore!<BR>PlayStation®TV compatible. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 79 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR>Assistance en ligne pour jeu multijoueur : Oui (2-32 joueurs)<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Craft, ed esplorare sotto l'acqua!<BR>Battaglia, fare amicizia e costruire come una creatura del mare in linea con molti giocatori provenienti da tutto il mondo!<BR>Personalizza, nome, sopravvivere, mestiere, rango e di esplorare con il vostro animale oceano!<BR>Molte mappe ambientali!<BR>Decora il tuo pagliaccio, Piranha, mante, tartarughe, cavalli di mare, squali, foche, Stella di mare, tonno, Globefish, Medusa, Oyster o Goldfish colori e modelli di pista!<BR>Il gioco di ruolo e chat on-line con gli altri come loro animali marini, diventare amici o la battaglia contro di loro per le monete esperienza patinate o squadra e prendere giù squali nemici e piranha!<BR>Cross Platform, ambiente 3D, colorato, multiplayer online, PVP e molto altro!<BR>PlayStation®TV compatibile. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 79 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR>Supporto giochi multiplayer online: Sì (2-32 giocatori)<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>クラフト、そして水の下で探る！<BR>バトルは、仲良くなると世界中から多くのプレーヤーとオンラインでの海の生き物のように構築する！<BR>、カスタマイズ名前は、生き残る、クラフト、ランクアップして、あなたの海のペットと一緒に探検！<BR>マリン、アトランティス、城、魚ボウル、ゲーマートリビュート地図、を含む多くの環境！<BR>あなたのカクレクマノミ、ピラニア、マンタ、カメ、海の馬、サメ、アザラシ、ヒトデ、マグロ、ふぐ、クラゲ、オイスターや金魚の色やトレイル模様を飾る！<BR>ロールプレイは、独自の海の動物のような他の人とオンラインでチャット光沢のある経験のコイン、またはチームのためにそれらに対する友人や戦いをアップになり、敵のサメやピラニアをテイクダウンして！<BR>クロスプラットフォーム、3D環境、カラフル、オンラインマルチプレイヤー、PVP、もっと！<BR>PlayStation®TV 互換性のある. V-1.3 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 79 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR>オンラインマルチプレイ: 2～32人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Håndverket, og utforske under vann!<BR>Battle, bli venner og bygge som en sjødyr online med mange spillere fra hele verden!<BR>Tilpass, navn, overleve, håndverk, rangere opp og utforske med havet kjæledyr!<BR>Mange miljøer, inkludert, Marine, Atlantis, slott, Fish Bowl og Gamers Tribute kart!<BR>Dekorere din Klovnefisk, Piranha, Manta Rays, Turtles, Sea hester, Sharks, Sel, sjøstjerne, tunfisk, Globefish, Jellyfish, Oyster eller Gullfisk farger og trail mønstre!<BR>Rollespill og chatte på nettet med andre som sine egne sjødyr, bli venner eller kjempe mot dem for skinnende erfaring mynter, eller teamet opp og ta ned fiendens haier og piraja!<BR>Cross Platform, 3D-miljø, fargerik, online multiplayer, PVP og mer!<BR>PlayStation®TV kompatibel. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 79 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR>Støtte for online flerspiller: Ja (2-32 spillere)<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Ambacht, en verken onder water!<BR>Battle, bevriend en bouwen als een zeemonster online met veel spelers uit de hele wereld!<BR>Pas, naam, overleef, ambacht, te rangschikken en te verkennen met uw oceaan huisdier!<BR>Vele omgevingen, waaronder, Marine, Atlantis, Kasteel, Fish Bowl en Gamers Tribute Kaart!<BR>Versier je Clownfish, Piranha, mantaroggen, schildpadden, zeepaardjes, haaien, zeehonden, Starfish, Tonijn, Globefish, Jellyfish, Oyster of Goldfish kleuren en trail patronen!<BR>Rollenspel en online chatten met anderen als hun eigen zeedieren, vrienden geworden of de strijd tegen hen voor glanzende ervaring munten, of het team op en neer te halen vijand haaien en piranha!<BR>Cross-platform, 3D-omgeving, kleurrijk, online multiplayer, PVP en nog veel meer!<BR>PlayStation®TV compatibel. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 79 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR>Ondersteuning voor online multiplayergame: Ja (2-32 spelers)<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Craft, i zbadać pod wodą!<BR>Bitwa, zaprzyjaźnić się i budować jak stworzenie morza online z wieloma graczami z całego świata!<BR>Dostosuj, nazwisko, przetrwać, rzemiosło, rangę i zwiedzanie z oceanu zwierzaka!<BR>Wiele środowisk, w tym, Marine, Atlantis, Zamek, Fish Bowl i Gamers Tribute mapą!<BR>Udekoruj błazenki, Piranha, manty, żółwie, koniki morskie, rekiny, foki, Rozgwiazda, tuńczyk, Globefish, Jellyfish, Oyster lub Goldfish kolory i wzory szlak!<BR>Odgrywanie ról i rozmów online z innymi osobami, jak ich własnych zwierząt morskich, stają się przyjaciółmi i walkę przeciwko nim na błyszczących monet lub doświadczenia zespołu i zdjąć wroga i piranii rekiny!<BR>Platforma Cross, środowisko 3D, kolorowe, multiplayer online, PVP i więcej!<BR>PlayStation®TV kompatybilny. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 79 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR>Tryb online dla wielu graczy: tak (2-32 graczy)<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Craft, och utforska under vatten!<BR>Slaget, bli vän och bygga en havsvarelse online med många spelare från hela världen!<BR>Skräddarsy, namn, överleva, hantverk, ranka upp och utforska din havet husdjur!<BR>Många miljöer, bland annat, marin, Atlantis, slott, Fish Bowl och Gamers Tribute Karta!<BR>Dekorera din Clown, Piranha, mantor, sköldpaddor, sjöhästar, hajar, Packningar, Starfish, Tuna, Globefish, Manet, Oyster eller Goldfish färger och trail mönster!<BR>Rollspel och chatta online med andra som sina egna djur i havet, blir vänner eller kampen mot dem för blanka erfarenhet mynt, eller laget upp och ta ner fienden hajar och piraya!<BR>Cross Platform, 3D-miljö, färgstarka, online multiplayer, PVP och mycket mer!<BR>PlayStation®TV kompatibel. V-1.3 <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 79 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR>Stöd för onlinespel med flera spelare: Ja (2-32 spelare)<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:RPG"/><genre value="Games:Simulation"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Online.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
