<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00004_00">
 <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>37998096</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[トラクター・トレイルは、農場を舞台にしたパズルゲーム！<br>トラクターのレッドといっしょに、迷路のような大地を駆け巡ろう。できるだけ多くの土地を耕して、たくさんの木を植えるのがレッドの仕事。レッドにはブレーキがついていないし、他にも困ったことがいっぱい…意地悪なカカシのおじいさんや、他のジャマ者が仕事のジャマをしてくるぞ。100以上のレベルに、全部木を植えられるかな？<br><br>パズル大好きなプレイヤーは、素早い指の動きと瞬間的な判断でパーフェクトなスコアを目指す楽しさがあります。ヒントのシステムは万全なので、気軽に遊びたいプレイヤーも、頭を使うレベルをクリアする楽しみを味わえます。トラクターをアップグレードしたり、農場のお店で役立つアイテムを購入してハイスコアを目指してください！<br><br>特徴：<br>単純なタッチスクリーン操作！<br>超難解な究極の巨大マップを含む、130のレベルが勢ぞろい！<br>各レベルパックで、新しい環境のゲームプレイに挑戦できる！<br>トウモロコシを収穫すると、お店で便利なヒントやアップグレードアイテムと交換できるシステム。アップグレードでレッドの能力を強化すれば、デコトラ（クター）になれたり、仕事のスピードがアップしたり、他にも色々改造できる！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:37 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語<br><br>著作権等:<br>©2012 Origin8 Technologies Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Tractor Trails, the farm-themed action puzzler!<br>Guide Red the Tractor around mazy fields, aiming to hit every square to plant as many trees as possible! Red's lack of brakes isn't the only problem – obstacles such as the spiteful old scarecrow aim to hinder and help in the quest to fill the hundred-plus levels with trees!<br><br>Puzzle aficionados will need fast fingers and fast thinking to achieve a perfect score, whilst a robust hint system lets more casual players to overcome brain taxing levels. Upgrade your tractor and improve scores using helpful items in the farm shop!<br><br>Features:<br>* Simple touchscreen control!<br>* 130 levels including enormous ultimate challenge mega-maps!<br>* New environmental game features in every level pack!<br>* Collect corn to exchange for handy hints and shop upgrades that improve Red's abilities - get a pimped out tractor, finish the fields faster and lots more!<br><br>Package size: 37 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>©2012 Origin8 Technologies Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Tractor Trails, le jeu mêlant action et réflexion dans l'univers de la ferme !<br>Guidez Rouge le tracteur à travers des champs biscornus, passez sur toutes les parcelles et plantez un maximum d'arbres ! L'absence de freins de Rouge n'est pas le seul problème : le vieil épouvantail grincheux viendra également lui mettre des bâtons dans les roues. À vous de l'aider pour venir à bout de plus de cent niveaux uniques !<br><br>Pour décrocher le meilleur score, les passionnés de casse-tête devront affuter leur esprit logique et avoir les doigts agiles, tandis que les néophytes pourront compter sur un système d'indices pour ne pas se griller les neurones. Améliorez votre tracteur et boostez votre score à l'aide d'équipements uniques en vente dans la grange !<br><br>Caractéristiques :<br>* Commandes tactiles ultra simples !<br>* 130 niveaux, dont les méga-cartes pour toujours plus de défi !<br>* De nouveaux éléments environnementaux à chaque niveau !<br>* Récoltez du maïs et échangez-le contre des équipements qui permettront d'améliorer Rouge pour atteindre de nouveaux sommets !<br><br>Taille du paquet: 37 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>©2012 Origin8 Technologies Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Tractor Trails è un rompicapo d'azione a tema agricolo.<br>Guida il trattore Red in campi labirintici, cercando di passare su ogni casella per piantare più alberi possibile. La mancanza di freni di Red non è l'unico problema: ostacoli come lo spaventapasseri brontolone ti intralceranno nella tua missione di riempire di alberi oltre cento livelli!<br><br>Gli appassionati di rompicapo dovranno mettere in azione cervello e dita per ottenere un punteggio perfetto, mentre un ottimo sistema di aiuti permetterà ai giocatori meno smaliziati di completare i livelli più impegnativi. Potenzia il trattore e aumenta i punteggi usando gli utili oggetti del negozio nel granaio!<br><br>Caratteristiche:<br>* Semplici comandi touchscreen!<br>* 130 livelli, tra cui mega mappe per la sfida suprema!<br>* Nuove funzioni di gioco ambientali in ogni fase!<br>* Raccogli le pannocchie in cambio di oggetti utili e acquista potenziamenti per affinare le abilità di Red: puoi ottenere un trattore turbo, completare i livelli più in fretta e molto altro ancora!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 37 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano<br><br>©2012 Origin8 Technologies Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¡Tractor Trails, el juego agrícola de rompecabezas lleno de acción!<br>Conduce a Red el tractor por campos laberínticos, tratando de llegar a todas las casillas para plantar el máximo número de árboles. Que Red no tenga frenos no es el único problema: obstáculos, como el malvado espantapájaros, dificultan y asisten en la misión de cubrir de árboles los más de cien niveles.<br><br>Los aficionados a los rompecabezas necesitarán dedos veloces y tendrán que pensar con rapidez para lograr una puntuación perfecta, mientras que el robusto sistema de pistas permite que jugadores más informales superen niveles que exigen mucha meditación. Mejora tu tractor y supera puntuaciones utilizando los prácticos artículos de la tienda de la granja.<br><br>Características:<br>* Sencillo control mediante la pantalla táctil.<br>* 130 niveles que incluyen enormes megamapas para un desafío definitivo.<br>* Nuevas características propias del entorno en cada pack de niveles.<br>* Recoge maíz para intercambiarlo por útiles pistas y comprar mejoras que aumentan las habilidades de Red: consigue un tractor tuneado, acaba los campos con más rapidez y mucho más.<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 37 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano<br><br>©2012 Origin8 Technologies Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Tractor Trails, der Actionpuzzler rund um den Bauernhof!<br>Lenke den Traktor Red so über labyrinthartige Felder, dass er keine Stelle auslässt, um möglichst viele Bäume zu pflanzen! Dabei sind Reds fehlende Bremsen allerdings nicht dein einziges Problem – Hindernisse wie die fiese alte Vogelscheuche versuchen, dich daran zu hindern, die über hundert Level mit Bäumen zu pflastern.<br><br>Puzzle-Freunde brauchen flinke Finger und Gedankenschnelle, um die perfekte Punktzahl zu erreichen, während die umfangreiche Spielhilfe Gelegenheitsspieler sicher selbst durch die kniffligsten Level führt. Und mit den nützlichen Extras aus dem Hofladen kannst du deinen Traktor und deinen Punktestand gleichermaßen aufmotzen.<br><br>Merkmale:<br>* Einfache Touchscreen-Steuerung!<br>* 130 Level, inklusive riesiger Megakarten für die ultimative Herausforderung!<br>* Neue Umgebungselemente in jedem Level-Pack!<br>* Ernte Mais, den du gegen praktische Tipps und Extras aus dem Hofladen eintauschen kannst, die Red verbessern – mit gepimptem Traktor geht die Feldarbeit gleich noch mal so gut von der Hand<br><br>Paketgröße: 37 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch<br><br>©2012 Origin8 Technologies Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Tractor Trails, the farm-themed action puzzler!<br>Guide Red the Tractor around mazy fields, aiming to hit every square to plant as many trees as possible! Red's lack of brakes isn't the only problem – obstacles such as the spiteful old scarecrow aim to hinder and help in the quest to fill the hundred-plus levels with trees!<br><br>Puzzle aficionados will need fast fingers and fast thinking to achieve a perfect score, whilst a robust hint system lets more casual players to overcome brain taxing levels. Upgrade your tractor and improve scores using helpful items in the farm shop!<br><br>Features:<br>* Simple touchscreen control!<br>* 130 levels including enormous ultimate challenge mega-maps!<br>* New environmental game features in every level pack!<br>* Collect corn to exchange for handy hints and shop upgrades that improve Red's abilities - get a pimped out tractor, finish the fields faster and lots more !<br><br>Package size: 37 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>©2012 Origin8 Technologies Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Tractor Trails, le jeu mêlant action et réflexion dans l'univers de la ferme !<br>Guidez Rouge le tracteur à travers des champs biscornus, passez sur toutes les parcelles et plantez un maximum d'arbres ! L'absence de freins de Rouge n'est pas le seul problème : le vieil épouvantail grincheux viendra également lui mettre des bâtons dans les roues. À vous de l'aider pour venir à bout de plus de cent niveaux uniques !<br><br>Pour décrocher le meilleur score, les passionnés de casse-tête devront affuter leur esprit logique et avoir les doigts agiles, tandis que les néophytes pourront compter sur un système d'indices pour ne pas se griller les neurones. Améliorez votre tracteur et boostez votre score à l'aide d'équipements uniques en vente dans la grange !<br><br>Caractéristiques :<br>* Commandes tactiles ultra simples !<br>* 130 niveaux, dont les méga-cartes pour toujours plus de défi !<br>* De nouveaux éléments environnementaux à chaque niveau !<br>* Récoltez du maïs et échangez-le contre des équipements qui permettront d'améliorer Rouge pour atteindre de nouveaux sommets !<br><br>Taille du programme: 37 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>©2012 Origin8 Technologies Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Family"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
