<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00008_00">
 <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>40287712</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[スピードには自信があるって？じゃないと困るよ。惑星全体の環境が君の手にかかっているんだから！<br>Tiracas 惑星は大気圏を必要としている。そして空気を製造する発電所の原子炉の始動には、貴重な鉱物の絶妙なバランスが必要となるんだ。<br>真空の SF 世界でモグラ叩きと皿回しのゲームプレイ要素を組み合わせた Fuel Tiracas はスピード、反応、タイムマネジメント能力の究極のテストだ！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:39 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/フランス語/スペイン語/ドイツ語/イタリア語/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>Fuel Tiracas © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[So you think you’re fast? You had better be, because an entire planet’s environment depends on it!<br>Planet Tiracas needs an atmosphere, but its air-producing power stations require a fine balance of precious minerals to kick-start their nuclear reactors. <br>Fusing ‘Whack-A-Mole’, ‘Spinning Plates’ and 'Simon Says' gameplay in a vacuum pressurised sci-fi setting, Fuel Tiracas is the ultimate test of fast reactions, memory and time management ability!<br><br>Package size: 39 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/French/Spanish/German/Italian/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>Fuel Tiracas © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Vous pensez être rapide ? L'environnement d'une planète entière dépend de vous !<br>Les réacteurs nucléaires des usines chimiques de la planète Tiracas ont besoin, pour son atmosphère, d'un mélange précis de rares minéraux. <br>Mélangeant "jeu de la taupe" et jeu d'adresse dans un univers futuriste littéralement sous pression, Fuel Tiracas met à l'épreuve votre rapidité, vos réflexes et votre gestion du temps !<br><br>Taille du paquet: 39 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Francais/Anglais(Etats-Unis)/Espagnol/Allemand/Italien/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>Fuel Tiracas © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[E così credi di essere veloce? Sarà meglio per te, perché c'è in gioco l'ambiente di un intero pianeta!<br>Il pianeta Tiracas ha bisogno di un'atmosfera, ma le centrali di produzione di aria hanno bisogno del giusto equilibrio di minerali preziosi per avviare i reattori nucleari. <br>Fuel Tiracas combina lo stile di gioco "Acchiappa la talpa", "Piatti cinesi" e "Simon dice" in un'ambientazione di fantascienza, ed è il test finale per le tue doti di reazione, memoria e gestione del tempo!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 39 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Italiano/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Francese/Spagnolo/Tedesco/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>Fuel Tiracas © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¿Crees que eres rápido? ¡Mejor que así sea porque todo el entorno de un planeta depende de ti! <br>El Planeta Tiracas necesita una atmósfera, pero las centrales de energía que producen aire precisan un equilibrio de minerales preciosos para dar inicio a los reactores nucleares.<br>Gracias a una fusión de juegos de tipo "el juego del topo" y "Spinning Plates" en un entorno ficticio presurizado al vacío, ¡Fuel Tiracas pone a prueba tus habilidades de velocidad, reacción y gestión del tiempo!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 39 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Espanol/Ingles(Estados Unidos)/Frances/Aleman/Italiano/Ingles(Reino Unido)<br><br>Fuel Tiracas © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Du denkst also, du bist schnell? Besser wäre es, denn die Umwelt eines ganzen Planeten hängt davon ab!<br>Der Planet Tiracas braucht eine Atmosphäre, aber seine Luft produzierenden Kraftwerke benötigen eine bestimmte Mischung aus Mineralien, um die Nuklearreaktoren hochzufahren.<br>Fuel Tiracas kombiniert die Spielprinzipien von ‘Whack-A-Mole’ und ‘Spinning Plates’ in einer Sci-Fi Vakuum-Umgebung und ist der ultimative Test für Schnelligkeit, Reaktion und Zeitmanagement.<br><br>Paketgröße: 39 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Franzosisch/Spanisch/Italienisch/Englisch(Grosbritannien)<br><br>Fuel Tiracas © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[So you think you’re fast? You had better be, because an entire planet’s environment depends on it!<br>Planet Tiracas needs an atmosphere, but its air-producing power stations require a fine balance of precious minerals to kick-start their nuclear reactors. <br>Fusing ‘Whack-A-Mole’, ‘Spinning Plates’ and 'Simon Says' gameplay in a vacuum pressurised sci-fi setting, Fuel Tiracas is the ultimate test of fast reactions, memory and time management ability!<br><br>Package size: 39 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United Kingdom)/English(United States)/French/Spanish/German/Italian<br><br>Fuel Tiracas © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Arcade"/>
  <genre value="Games:Casual"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Online.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
