<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00005_00">
 <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>8057472</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[ニョキニョキ伸びるアクションパズルゲーム、Nyoqixを体感せよ!<br>アナログスティックを使ってボディを自由な形状に変化させて戦う新感覚アクション。せまりくる敵を、押しつぶす、叩きつける、跳ね飛ばすといった多彩な攻撃が可能。<br><br>まるぼうしかく,パネキット,ザルバールの蒸留塔などを手がけた渡辺訓章(kuni)氏がゲームデザインを担当。グレースケールによる、ソリッドでアブストラクトなデザインを採用。ユーモラスな動きと細江慎治氏(スーパースィープ)によるサウンドが独自の世界観を演出します。<br>毎日違ったステージ構成で、ゆるゆると楽しめるゲームスタイルで、<br>国籍・年齢・性別を問わず幅広いユーザー層が楽しめる新しいジャンルのゲームです。<br><br>コンテンツ容量:7869 KB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<br><br>著作権等:<br>ZENER MOBILE 2012(C)<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Experience, unusual action puzzle game, the Nyoqix!<br>Fight freely changing the body by the analog stick,<br>Crush, Strike and Slosh the enemy, a variety of attack form is possible.<br><br>Game designed by Kuniaki Watanabe ( known for producing MaBoShi: The Three Shape Arcade, The Tower of Zarbartz and Panekit ).<br>Has cool gray scale abstract design and humorous action and a unique sound by Shinji Hosoe (super sweep).<br>Provides a different stage configuration every day.<br>Is a new genre of game to enjoy a wide range of users regardless of gender, age, nationality.<br><br>Package size: 7869 KB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/Japanese<br><br>ZENER MOBILE 2012(C)<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[L'expérience, jeu insolite de puzzle d'action, le Nyoqix!<br>Lutte contre le changer librement le corps par le stick analogique,<br>Crush, Grève et patauger l'ennemi, une variété de forme d'attaque est possible.<br><br>Jeu conçu par Kuniaki Watanabe (connu pour la production MaBoShi: The Arcade Trois Forme, La Tour de Zarbartz et Panekit).<br>A cool design gris abstrait échelle et d'action humoristique et un son unique par Shinji Hosoe (Super Sweep).<br>Fournit une configuration de scène différent chaque jour.<br>Est un nouveau genre de jeu pour profiter d'un large éventail d'utilisateurs indépendamment de leur sexe, âge, nationalité.<br><br>Taille du paquet: 7869 ko – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<br><br>ZENER MOBILE 2012(C)<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[L'esperienza, insolito puzzle game d'azione, il Nyoqix!<br>Combatti liberamente cambiando il corpo del stick analogico,<br>Crush, sciopero e slosh il nemico, una varietà di forma di attacco è possibile.<br><br>Gioco progettato da Kuniaki Watanabe (noto per la produzione di MaBoShi: The Three Shape Arcade, La Torre di Zarbartz e Panekit).<br>Ha freddo disegno astratto scala di grigi e l'azione divertente e un suono unico da Shinji Hosoe (sweep super).<br>Fornisce una configurazione diversa fase di ogni giorno.<br>E 'un nuovo genere di gioco per godere di una vasta gamma di utenti indipendentemente dal sesso, età, nazionalità.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 7869 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<br><br>ZENER MOBILE 2012(C)<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[La experiencia, la acción inusual juego de puzzle, el Nyoqix!<br>Lucha libre de cambiar el cuerpo a través del stick analógico,<br>Crush, la huelga ya chapotear el enemigo, una variedad de forma de ataque es posible.<br><br>Juego diseñado por Kuniaki Watanabe (conocida por la producción MaBoShi: La figura de tres Arcade, La Torre de Zarbartz y Panekit).<br>Tiene diseño fresco gris abstracta de escala y la acción humorística y un sonido único por Shinji Hosoe (barrido super).<br>Proporciona una configuración de la etapa diferente cada día.<br>Es un nuevo género de juego para disfrutar de una amplia gama de usuarios, independientemente de su sexo, edad, nacionalidad.<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 7869 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<br><br>ZENER MOBILE 2012(C)<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Die Erfahrung, ungewöhnliche Action-Puzzle-Spiel, das Nyoqix!<br>Kämpfen frei verändert den Körper durch den Analog-Stick,<br>Crush, schlagen und den Feind zu schwappen, ist eine Vielzahl von Angriffs-Formular möglich.<br><br>Computerspiel von Kuniaki Watanabe (bekannt für die Herstellung von MaBoShi: The Three Shape-Arcade, The Tower of Zarbartz und Panekit) ausgelegt.<br>Hat kühlen Graustufen abstrakten Design und humorvolle Handlung und einen einzigartigen Sound von Shinji Hosoe (super-Sweep).<br>Bietet eine unterschiedliche Konfiguration der Bühne jeden Tag.<br>Ist ein neues Genre des Spiels, ein breites Spektrum von Anwendern unabhängig von Geschlecht, Alter, Nationalität genießen.<br><br>Paketgröße: 7869 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<br><br>ZENER MOBILE 2012(C)<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Experience, unusual action puzzle game, the Nyoqix!<br>Fight freely changing the body by the analog stick,<br>Crush, Strike and Slosh the enemy, a variety of attack form is possible.<br><br>Game designed by Kuniaki Watanabe ( known for producing MaBoShi: The Three Shape Arcade, The Tower of Zarbartz and Panekit ).<br>Has cool gray scale abstract design and humorous action and a unique sound by Shinji Hosoe (super sweep).<br>Provides a different stage configuration every day.<br>Is a new genre of game to enjoy a wide range of users regardless of gender, age, nationality.<br><br>Package size: 7869 KB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/Japanese<br><br>ZENER MOBILE 2012(C)<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[L'expérience, jeu insolite de puzzle d'action, le Nyoqix!<br>Lutte contre le changer librement le corps par le stick analogique,<br>Crush, Grève et patauger l'ennemi, une variété de forme d'attaque est possible.<br><br>Jeu conçu par Kuniaki Watanabe (connu pour la production MaBoShi: The Arcade Trois Forme, La Tour de Zarbartz et Panekit).<br>A cool design gris abstrait échelle et d'action humoristique et un son unique par Shinji Hosoe (Super Sweep).<br>Fournit une configuration de scène différent chaque jour.<br>Est un nouveau genre de jeu pour profiter d'un large éventail d'utilisateurs indépendamment de leur sexe, âge, nationalité.<br><br>Taille du programme: 7869 ko - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<br><br>ZENER MOBILE 2012(C)<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Action"/>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
