<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00137_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.20</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>13786288</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Turbaserede taktikker kombineret med taktisk poker! Placér dine tanks, vælg dine mål og gør dine indsatser!<BR>*Kæmp dig igennem over 30 missioner i storymode.<BR>*Spil en lang række af missionstyper.<BR>*Spil mod 9 generaler, hver med sin unikke spillestil.<BR>*Fem typer af tanks, deriblandt rakettanks og mobile kommandokøretøjer.<BR>*Skræddersy og genspil alle slag i skirmishmode. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 14 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Rundenbasierte Taktiken kombiniert mit taktischem Poker! Positioniere deine Panzer, wähle deine Ziele aus und platziere deinen Einsatz!<BR><BR>* Kämpfe dich durch mehr als 30 Missionen im Story-Modus.<BR>* Spiele eine Vielfalt an Missionstypen.<BR>* Kämpfe gegen 9 Generäle, jeder mit einem einzigartigen Spielstil.<BR>* Fünf Panzertypen, inklusive Raketenpanzer und mobilen Einsatzfahrzeugen.<BR>* Individualisiere und spiele Kämpfe erneut im Gefechtsmodus. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 14 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Turn based tactics combined with tactical poker! Position your tanks, pick your targets and place your bets!<BR><BR>*Fight through more than 30 missions in Story Mode.<BR>*Play a variety of mission types.<BR>*Battle against 9 generals, each with a unique play-style.<BR>*Five tank types including rocket tanks and mobile command vehicles.<BR>*Customize and replay any battle in Skirmish Mode. <BR><BR>Package size: 14 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Turno basado en las tácticas combinadas con el póker táctico. ¡Sitúa tus tanques, elige tus objetivos y haz tus apuestas!<BR><BR>*Lucha a través de más de 30 misiones en el modo Historia<BR>*Juega varios tipos de misiones<BR>*Cinco tipos de tanques incluidos los tanques portamisiles y los vehículos teledirigidos.<BR>*Personaliza y vuelve a jugar cada batalla en el modo Escaramuza. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 14 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Vuoropohjainen taktiikkapeli yhdistettynä taktiseen pokeriin! Sijoittele tankkisi, poimi kohteesi ja aseta panokset!<BR>*Taistele läpi yli 30 tehtävän tarinamoodissa.<BR>*Pelaa useita erityyppisiä tehtäviä.<BR>*Taistele 9 kenraalia vastaan, joilla jokaisella on ainutlaatuinen pelityyli.<BR>*Viisi erilaista tankkia, mukaan lukien rakettitankkeja ja liikkuvia komentovaunuja.<BR>*Mukauta ja pelaa uudelleen mikä tahansa taistelu kahakkamoodissa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 14 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Des stratégies au tour par tour combinées à un poker tactique ! Positionnez vos tanks, choisissez vos cibles et placez vos mises !<BR><BR>* Combattez à travers plus de 30 missions en mode Histoire.<BR>* Jouez à plusieurs types de missions différentes.<BR>* Affrontez 9 généraux, chacun utilisant un style de jeu unique.<BR>* Cinq types de tanks dont les tanks lance-fusée et les véhicules de commandement mobiles.<BR>* Personnalisez et rejouez toutes les batailles en mode Bataille. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 14 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Tattiche a turni combinate con il poker tattico! Posiziona i tuoi carri armati, raccogli i tuoi obiettivi e inserisci le tue puntate!<BR><BR>* Lotta attraverso oltre 30 missioni in Modalità Storia.<BR>* Gioca una varietà di tipi di missione.<BR>* Combatti contro 9 generali, ciascuno con uno stile di gioco unico.<BR>* Cinque tipi di carri tra cui carri armati con razzi e veicoli di comando mobili.<BR>* Personalizza e riproduci qualsiasi battaglia nella modalità Schermaglia. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 14 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[ターン制の戦闘作戦が戦術的なポーカーと一体になりました！戦車を配置し、ターゲットを選んで賭けよう！<BR><BR>*ストーリーモードで30以上のミッションを戦い抜く。<BR>*様々な種類のミッションをプレイ。<BR>*各々がユニークなプレイスタイルを持っている9人の将軍と対戦。<BR>*ロケット戦車と移動指揮車両などがある5種類の戦車。<BR>*前哨戦モードの戦闘をカスタマイズ＆リプレイ。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 14 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Taktikk basert på tur, kombinert med taktisk poker! Posisjoner stridsvognene dine, velg mål og plasser bud!<BR>* Kjemp deg gjennom mer enn 30 oppdrag i Story Mode.<BR>* Spill en rekke oppdragstyper.<BR>* Kjemp mot ni generaler, alle med en unik spillestil.<BR>* Fem typer stridsvogner, inkludert rakett stridsvogner og mobilekommandokjøretøyer.<BR>* Tilpass og spill kamper flere ganger i Skirmish Mode. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 14 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Turn-based tactiek gecombineerd met tactisch poker! Plaats je tanks, kies je doelen en zet in!<BR>*Vecht je door meer dan 30 missies in de Vertelmodus.<BR>*Speel verschillende soorten missies.<BR>*Strijd tegen 9 generaals, elk met een unieke speelstijl.<BR>*Vijf soorten tanks inclusief rakettanks en mobiele commandovoertuigen.<BR>*Pas aan naar eigen smaak en speel elke strijd opnieuw in de Retailleermodus. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 14 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Omgångsbaserad taktik kombinerad med taktisk poker! Placera ut dina stridsvagnar, välj dina mål och satsa!<BR>* Slå dig fram i över 30 uppdrag i handlingsläge.<BR>* Spela flera olika uppdragstyper.<BR>* Slåss mot 9 generaler, var och en med en unik spelstil.<BR>* Fem stridsvagnsmodeller, inklusive stridsvagnar med raketer och mobila ledningsfordon.<BR>* Anpassa och spela om valfritt slag i drabbningsläge. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 14 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 TACS games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Strategy"/><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Gambling.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Gambling.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
