<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00210_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>59568464</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Du bist ein Wolf und Du warst schlimm. Deshalb wurdest Du in die tiefste Hölle mit den gefürchtetsten Feinden verbannt: die Schafe! Es sind aber keine normalen Schafe. Nein! Sie sind von Dämonen besessene und sie werden nicht zögern Dich zu töten.<BR><BR>Also Renn! Verteidige Dich! Ein Wolf ist immerhin von Natur aus ein Raubtier und kein Beutetier!<BR><BR>Brich aus den Verliesen, stell Dich den Herausforderungen  und befreie Dich aus dieser Hölle… Falls Du kannst!<BR><BR>Eigenschaften:<BR>·Intuitive und prompt reagierende Kontrolle<BR>·Drei Schwierigkeitsgrade<BR>·Immer unterschiedliche, dynamisch erzeugte Verliese<BR>·Herausforderungen mit ansteigender Schwierigkeit<BR>·Es gibt viele verschiedene Arten von Feinden zu entdecken<BR>·Und vieles mehr! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 57 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch<BR><BR>RTypeX, david.cm, Atic2a<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>You’re a wolf and you’ve been bad. That’s why you’ve been put in the deepness of a hell plagued with your most hated enemies: the sheep! But they’re not normal sheep. No… They’re possessed demonic sheep and won’t hesitate to try to kill you!<BR><BR>So run! Defend yourself! Because, after all, a wolf is by nature a predator, not a prey.<BR><BR>Break through the dungeons, solve challenges and escape this hell… If you can!<BR><BR>Features<BR>·Intuitive and responsive controls<BR>·Three difficulty levels<BR>·Always different procedural dungeons<BR>·Challenges of increasing difficulty<BR>·Many kinds of enemies to discover<BR>·And more! <BR><BR>Package size: 57 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>RTypeX, david.cm, Atic2a<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Eres un lobo y has sido malo. Es por eso que se te ha llevado a las profundidades de un infierno plagado de tus más odiados enemigos: ¡las ovejas! Pero no son ovejas normales. No… Son endemoniadas ovejas poseídas ¡y no dudarán en intentar matarte!<BR><BR>Por eso corre! Defiéndete! Porque, después de todo, un lobo es un depredador por naturaleza, no una presa.<BR><BR>Ábrete paso por las mazmorras, resuelve retos y escapa de este infierno… ¡Si puedes!<BR><BR>Features<BR>·Controles intuitivos y sensibles<BR>·Tres niveles de dificultad<BR>·Mazmorras procedurales siempre diferentes<BR>·Retos de creciente dificultad<BR>·Varios enemigos a descubrir<BR>·¡Y más! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 57 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español<BR><BR>RTypeX, david.cm, Atic2a<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Vous êtes un loup et vous avez été vilain. C'est pourquoi vous avez été envoyé dans les profondeurs de l'enfer qui sont remplies de vos pires ennemis: les moutons! Mais ce ne sont pas des moutons normaux. Non... Ce sont de diaboliques moutons possédés et ils n'hésiteront pas à vous tuer!<BR><BR>Alors courez! Défendez-vous! Parce que, après tout, un loup est un prédateur par nature, pas une proie.<BR><BR>Ouvrez vous votre chemin à travers les cachots, résolvez des défis et échappez vous de cet enfer... Si vous le pouvez!<BR><BR>Caractéristiques:<BR>·Commandes intuitives et sensibles<BR>·Trois niveaux de difficulté<BR>·Cachots différents à chaque fois<BR>·Défis de difficulté croissante<BR>·Divers ennemis à découvrir<BR>·Et plus encore! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 57 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol<BR><BR>RTypeX, david.cm, Atic2a<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Sei un lupo e sei stato cattivo. È per questo che sei stato portato nelle profondità dell'inferno pieno dei tuoi nemici più odiati: le pecore! Ma non sono pecore normali. No... Sono pecore demoniache possedute e non esiteranno ad ucciderti!<BR><BR>Quindi corri! Difenditi! Perché, dopo tutto, un lupo è un predatore per natura, non una preda.<BR><BR>Apriti il cammino attraverso dungeons, supera sfide e fuggi da questo inferno... Se ce la fai!<BR><BR>Caratteristiche:<BR>·Comandi intuitivi e sensibili<BR>·Tre livelli di difficoltà<BR>·Dungeons procedurali sempre differenti<BR>·Sfide di difficoltà crescente<BR>·Diversi nemici da scoprire<BR>·E molto di più! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 57 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo<BR><BR>RTypeX, david.cm, Atic2a<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>深い地獄に墜とされた、恐ろしいオオカミ。そこには憎むべき敵が数知れずいた。それはヒツジだったのだ！しかもただのヒツジではない。悪魔に取り憑かれ、オオカミを襲い殺すヒツジなのだ！<BR><BR>さあ走れ！生き残れ！本来オオカミは強く、ヒツジに喰われる側ではないのだ。<BR><BR>ダンジョンのあらゆる難関をくぐり抜け、ミッションをクリアし、この地獄から一刻も早く逃げ出すことはできるのか！？<BR><BR>※このゲームについて<BR>・直感的な操作で遊んでいただけます<BR>・難易度は3段階あります<BR>・毎回異なるダンジョンが登場します<BR>・ミッションはクリアする毎に難しくなります<BR>・あらゆる敵が待ち受けています<BR>・and more! <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 57 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>RTypeX, david.cm, Atic2a<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
