<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00203_00">

  <appVersion>3.20</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>138072592</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>• Med 2D anime manga stil karakter kunst og 3D-grafik. <BR>• Udforsk i første person til at fortsætte i rædselshistorie (kan indeholde skræmmer hop). <BR>• styre to karakterer, DIS og Sui, se hvordan deres historie forbinder. <BR>• Mørke, grynet omgivelser og uhyggelige lydeffekter for atmosfærisk gameplay. <BR><BR>DIS og Vigil er to venner, der besøger hjemsøgt bopæl aviserne har været dækker nylig. Ukendt for dem, men det sted er ikke så opgives som pressen gør ud ... <BR>Blive trukket ind udforske den mystiske fortid psykotisk morder, der engang kaldte stedet hjem. <BR>Besøg den oprindelige gerningssted med Police pige Sui, løse og se, hvordan hun er involveret med historien! Har hun skjuler noget? <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 132 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Tysk/Italiensk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>• Mit 2D-Anime-Manga-Stil Charakter Kunst und 3D-Grafiken. <BR>• Sehen Sie sich in der ersten Person in der Horrorgeschichte gehen (enthalten kann springen erschreckt). <BR>• Steuer zwei Zeichen, Dis und Sui, zu sehen, wie ihre Geschichte verbindet. <BR>• Dunkle, düstere und unheimliche Umgebung Audioeffekte für atmosphärische Gameplay. <BR><BR>Dis und Vigil sind zwei Freunde, die das Geister Residenz die Zeitungen wurden kürzlich abdecken zu besuchen. Unbemerkt von ihnen, aber der Ort ist nicht so verlassen wie die Presse macht aus ... <BR>In die geheimnisvolle Vergangenheit der psychotische Mörder, der einst als den Ort zu erkunden Hause gezogen werden. <BR>Besuchen Sie die Original-Tatort mit Polizei-Mädchen Sui, zu lösen und sehen, wie sie mit der Geschichte beteiligt ist! Hat sie etwas zu verbergen? <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 132 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Französisch/Italienisch/Japanisch<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>• Featuring 2D anime manga style character art and 3D visuals.<BR>• Explore in first person to proceed in the horror story (may contain jump scares).<BR>• Control two characters, DiS and Sui, see how their story connects.<BR>• Dark, gritty surroundings and eerie audio effects for atmospheric gameplay.<BR><BR>DiS and Vigil are two friends who visit the haunted residence the newspapers have been covering recently. Unbeknownst to them, however, the place is not as abandoned as the press makes out...<BR>Be drawn into exploring the mysterious past of the psychotic murderer who once called the place home.<BR>Visit the original crime scene with Police girl Sui, solve and see how she is involved with the story!  Has she been hiding something? <BR><BR>Package size: 132 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>• Featuring 2D anime manga style character art and 3D visuals.<BR>• Explore in first person to proceed in the horror story (may contain jump scares).<BR>• Control two characters, DiS and Sui, see how their story connects.<BR>• Dark, gritty surroundings and eerie audio effects for atmospheric gameplay.<BR><BR>DiS and Vigil are two friends who visit the haunted residence the newspapers have been covering recently. Unbeknownst to them, however, the place is not as abandoned as the press makes out...<BR>Be drawn into exploring the mysterious past of the psychotic murderer who once called the place home.<BR>Visit the original crime scene with Police girl Sui, solve and see how she is involved with the story!  Has she been hiding something? <BR><BR>Package size: 132 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>• Featuring 2D anime manga style character art and 3D visuals.<BR>• Explore in first person to proceed in the horror story (may contain jump scares).<BR>• Control two characters, DiS and Sui, see how their story connects.<BR>• Dark, gritty surroundings and eerie audio effects for atmospheric gameplay.<BR><BR>DiS and Vigil are two friends who visit the haunted residence the newspapers have been covering recently. Unbeknownst to them, however, the place is not as abandoned as the press makes out...<BR>Be drawn into exploring the mysterious past of the psychotic murderer who once called the place home.<BR>Visit the original crime scene with Police girl Sui, solve and see how she is involved with the story!  Has she been hiding something? <BR><BR>Package size: 132 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>• Featuring 2D anime manga style character art and 3D visuals.<BR>• Explore in first person to proceed in the horror story (may contain jump scares).<BR>• Control two characters, DiS and Sui, see how their story connects.<BR>• Dark, gritty surroundings and eerie audio effects for atmospheric gameplay.<BR><BR>DiS and Vigil are two friends who visit the haunted residence the newspapers have been covering recently. Unbeknownst to them, however, the place is not as abandoned as the press makes out...<BR>Be drawn into exploring the mysterious past of the psychotic murderer who once called the place home.<BR>Visit the original crime scene with Police girl Sui, solve and see how she is involved with the story!  Has she been hiding something? <BR><BR>Package size: 132 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>• Atracción de arte del carácter del estilo del manga del animado 2D y gráficos 3D.<BR>• Explorar en primera persona para proceder en la historia de horror (puede contener salto asusta). <BR>• Control de dos personajes, DiS y Sui, ver cómo se conecta su historia. <BR>• Oscuras, un entorno arenoso y efectos de sonido espeluznantes para gameplay atmosférica. <BR><BR>Dis y Vigil son dos amigos que visitan la residencia embrujada los periódicos han estado cubriendo recientemente. Sin saberlo ellos, sin embargo, el lugar no es tan abandonado como la prensa hace fuera ... <BR>Dejarse arrastrar a explorar el misterioso pasado del asesino psicótico que una vez llamó al lugar en casa. <BR>Visita la escena del crimen original con muchacha de la policía Sui, resolver y ver cómo ella está involucrada con la historia! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 132 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Francés/Italiano/Japonés<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>• Mukana 2D anime manga hahmojen kuvia ja 3D-grafiikka. <BR>• Tutki ensimmäisen persoonan edetä kauhutarina (saattaa sisältää hyppy pelottaa). <BR>• Ohjaus kaksi merkkiä, DiS ja Sui, miten heidän tarinansa yhdistää. <BR>• Tumma, karu ympäristö ja aavemainen ääni vaikutuksia ilmakehän pelattavuus. <BR><BR>DiS ja Vigil kaksi ystäviä, jotka vierailevat ahdisti asuinpaikka sanomalehdet ovat kattavat äskettäin. Tietämättä heistä kuitenkin paikka ei ole niin hylätty kuin lehdistö tekee ulos ... <BR>Vedetään tutkimalla salaperäinen menneisyys psykoottinen murhaaja, joka kerran kutsui paikka kotona. <BR>Käy alkuperäinen rikospaikalle Poliisi tyttö Sui, ratkaista ja miten hän on mukana tarina! Onko hän piileskellyt jotain? <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 132 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Ranska/Saksa/Italia<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>• Doté d'art caractère 2D de style manga anime et visuels 3D. <BR>• Explorer à la première personne de procéder à l'histoire d'horreur (peut contenir saut fait peur). <BR>• contrôle deux personnages, le DIS et Sui, voir comment leur histoire se connecte. <BR>• sombres, environnement rudes et les effets audio étranges pour un gameplay atmosphérique. <BR><BR>Dis et Vigil sont deux amis qui visitent la résidence hantée les journaux ont été couvrent récemment. À leur insu, cependant, l'endroit n'est pas aussi abandonnée que la presse fait sur ​​... <BR>Se laisser entraîner dans l'exploration du passé mystérieux de l'assassin psychotique qui, une fois appelé la maison place. <BR>Visitez la scène du crime d'origine avec une fille de la police Sui, résoudre et voir comment elle est impliquée avec l'histoire! <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 132 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Français/Italien/Japonais<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>• Doté d'art caractère 2D de style manga anime et visuels 3D. <BR>• Explorer à la première personne de procéder à l'histoire d'horreur (peut contenir saut fait peur). <BR>• contrôle deux personnages, le DIS et Sui, voir comment leur histoire se connecte. <BR>• sombres, environnement rudes et les effets audio étranges pour un gameplay atmosphérique. <BR><BR>Dis et Vigil sont deux amis qui visitent la résidence hantée les journaux ont été couvrent récemment. À leur insu, cependant, l'endroit n'est pas aussi abandonnée que la presse fait sur ​​... <BR>Se laisser entraîner dans l'exploration du passé mystérieux de l'assassin psychotique qui, une fois appelé la maison place. <BR>Visitez la scène du crime d'origine avec une fille de la police Sui, résoudre et voir comment elle est impliquée avec l'histoire! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 132 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Français/Italien/Japonais<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>• Caratterizzato da 2D in stile manga anime carattere arte e grafica 3D. <BR>• Esplora in prima persona per procedere nella storia dell'orrore (può contenere salto spaventa). <BR>• controllo di due personaggi, DiS e Sui, vedere come la loro storia si connette. <BR>• scuri, ambiente grintoso ed effetti audio inquietanti per gameplay atmosferica. <BR><BR>DiS e Vigil sono due amici che visitano la residenza infestata i giornali sono state coprendo di recente. All'insaputa di loro, tuttavia, il posto non è così abbandonata come la stampa fa fuori ... <BR>Essere coinvolto in esplorare il misterioso passato di assassino psicotico che una volta chiamato il posto a casa. <BR>Visita la scena del crimine originale con Polizia ragazza Sui, risolvere e vedere come lei è coinvolta con la storia! Lei è stato nascosto qualco <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 132 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Francese/Italiano/Giapponese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>•フィーチャー2Dアニメマンガスタイルの文字芸術と3Dビジュアル。 <BR>•（ジャンプは恐怖含んでいてもよい）ホラーストーリーで進行する最初の人に紹介します。 <BR>•制御二つの文字、DISとSuiは、彼らの物語がどのように接続するかを参照してください。 <BR>•ダーク、ザラザラな環境と大気のゲームプレイのための不気味なオーディオエフェクト。 <BR><BR>DISとビジル新聞が最近カバーしてきたお化け住居を訪問する二人の友人である。プレスアウトになるように彼らに知られず、しかし、場所は、放棄されていません... <BR>一度自宅の場所と呼ばれる精神病の殺人犯の神秘的な過去を探るに引き込まれる。 <BR>、警察の女の子隋、元犯罪現場を訪れ解決し、彼女は物語に関与しているかを参照してください！彼女が何かを隠していませんか？ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 132 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/フランス語/イタリア語/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>• Med 2D anime manga stil karakter kunst og 3D-grafikk. <BR>• Se i første personen til å fortsette i skrekkhistorie (kan inneholde hopp skremmer). <BR>• Kontroll to tegn, DiS og Sui, se hvordan deres historie kobler. <BR>• Mørke, skitne omgivelser og nifse lydeffekter for atmosfærisk gameplay. <BR><BR>DiS og Vigil er to venner som besøker det hjemsøkte boligen avisene har vært dekket nylig. Ukjent for dem, men stedet er ikke så forlatt som pressen gjør ut ... <BR>Bli trukket inn i å utforske den mystiske fortid i psykotisk morder som en gang kalte stedet hjem. <BR>Besøk den opprinnelige åstedet med politiet jente Sui, løse og se hvordan hun er involvert med historien! Har hun skjuler noe? <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 132 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Tysk/Italiensk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>• Met 2D anime manga stijl karakter kunst en 3D-beelden. <BR>• Ontdek in de eerste persoon om verder te gaan in de horror verhaal (kan springen schrikt bevatten). <BR>• Controle van twee personages, DiS en Sui, zien hoe hun verhaal met elkaar verbindt. <BR>• Donkere, zanderige omgeving en angstaanjagende geluidseffecten voor atmosferische gameplay. <BR><BR>DiS en Vigil zijn twee vrienden die het spookhuis de woonplaats van de kranten zijn onlangs met betrekking tot een bezoek. Buiten het medeweten van hen, maar de plaats is niet zo verlaten als de pers maakt uit ... <BR>Worden getrokken in het verkennen van de mysterieuze verleden van de psychotische moordenaar die ooit noemde de plaats naar huis. <BR>Bezoek de originele delict met politie meisje Sui, op te lossen en te zien hoe zij zich bezig met het verhaal! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 132 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Frans/Duits/Italiaans<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>• Wyposażony w stylu manga anime 2D i sztuki wizualne charakter 3D. <BR>• Przeglądaj w pierwszej osobie, aby kontynuować w horror (może zawierać skok przeraża). <BR>• Kontrola dwóch znaków, DiS i Sui, zobaczyć, jak ich historia łączy. <BR>• Ciemne, piaszczysty otoczenie i niesamowitych efektów dźwiękowych dla gry atmosferycznym. <BR><BR>DiS i Wigilia są dwaj przyjaciele, którzy odwiedzają nawiedzony zamieszkania gazety zostały obejmujące niedawno. Wiemy o nich, jednak miejsce nie jest tak opuszczony, jak prasa robi z ... <BR>Być wciągane do zwiedzania tajemnicze przeszłość psychotycznego mordercy, który kiedyś nazwał to miejsce w domu. <BR>Odwiedź oryginalną miejsce zbrodni z dziewczyną Policja Sui, rozwiązania i zobaczyć jak ona uczestniczy w historii! Ona się coś ukrywa? <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 132 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Niemiecki/Angielski/Angielski/Francuski/Włoski/Japoński<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>• Med 2D anime manga stil teckenkonst och 3D-grafik. <BR>• Upptäck i första person att gå vidare i skräckhistoria (kan innehålla hopp skrämmer). <BR>• Kontroll två karaktärer, DiS och Sui, se hur deras berättelse ansluter. <BR>• Mörka, tråkiga omgivningar och kusliga ljudeffekter för atmosfär gameplay. <BR><BR>DiS och Vigil är två vänner som besöker hemsökta bostad tidningarna har täcker nyligen. Okänt för dem, men platsen är inte lika övergivet som pressen gör ut ... <BR>Dras in utforska den mystiska förflutna av psykotisk mördare som en gång kallade platsen hemma. <BR>Besök den ursprungliga brottsplatsen med polis flicka Sui, lösa och se hur hon är involverad i historien! Har hon döljer något? <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 132 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Franska/Tyska/Italienska<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Horror"/><genre value="Games:RPG"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
