<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00013_00">
 <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>5531216</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[Vlambeerのスマッシュヒット作品、SUPER CRATE BOXがハイスコアリストに名前を重ねることだけが重要だったアーケードゲームの黄金時代の栄光を取り戻します! <br><br>野球帽を手にして、ズボンも緩くしたら、無限の数の敵キャラクターと戦い、獲得できる全ての武器の箱を集める準備が完了します。 <br><br>アーケードゲームを彷彿とさせる、しっかりとしたゲーム操作、新鮮なゲームの手順、素敵なレトロアートと、めちゃくちゃヒップでチップチューン風のサウンドトラックと遭遇する準備をしましょう。 <br><br>Super Crate BoxはIGN、EDGE、IndieGames.comやIndependent Game Festivalによる「Excellence in Design」賞にノミネートされるなど、様々な賞を受賞しています。 <br><br>現在まで8,500万個以上の箱が世界中で集められています。 <br><br>行きたい時に行く先々で箱を集めよう。 <br>今ついにSuper Crate Boxはいつでもダウンロードできるようになりました!<br><br>コンテンツ容量:5402 KB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)<br><br>著作権等:<br>Copyright (C) 2012 Vlambeer. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Vlambeer's smash hit SUPER CRATE BOX brings back the glory of -the golden arcade age when all that really mattered was getting on that high score list! Grab your baseball cap and loosen your pants, it's time to fight endless hordes of enemies and collect every weapon crate you can. Prepare for an arcade delight with tight controls, refreshing game mechanics, cracking retro art and a terribly hip chiptune soundtrack.<br><br>Super Crate Box won numerous awards, including prizes by IGN, EDGE, IndieGames.com and a nomination for 'Excellence in Design' by the Independent Games Festival. So far, over 85 million crates have been collected worldwide. <br><br>Collect crates where-ever you go, whenever you want. Now, Super Crate Box is finally available on the go!<br><br>Package size: 5402 KB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Vlambeer. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Le grand succès de Vlambeer, SUPER CRATE BOX, vous plonge au coeur de l'âge d'or des jeux d'arcade, quand le plus important était d'apparaître dans le classement des meilleurs scores ! Attrapez votre casquette de baseball et mettez-vous en condition : le moment est venu d'affronter des ennemis toujours plus nombreux et de ramasser le plus de caisses d'armes possible. Préparez-vous à passer un excellent moment avec ce jeu d'arcade, ses commandes précises, sa mécanique de jeu innovante, son magnifique design rétro et sa bande-son chiptune branchée. <br><br>Super Crate Box a remporté de nombreuses récompenses, comme celles décernées par IGN, EDGE et IndieGames.com, et a été nommé dans la catégorie « Excellence du design » lors de l'Independent Games Festival. Jusqu'à maintenant, 85 millions de caisses ont été ramassées à travers le monde. <br><br>Ramassez des caisses où que vous alliez, quand vous le souhaitez. Super Crate Box est désormais disponible en version mobile !<br><br>Taille du paquet: 5402 ko – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Vlambeer. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Con SUPER CRATE BOX, Vlambeer ci riporta ai tempi d'oro dell'arcade, quando la sola cosa che contasse era vedere il proprio punteggio nell'elenco dei record! Afferra il tuo berretto da baseball e allentati la cintura: è il momento di respingere sterminate orde di nemici e di raccogliere tutte le casse di armi sulle quali riesci a mettere le mani. Preparati a vivere un'esperienza arcade deliziosamente nostalgica, con comandi intuitivi, una dinamica di gioco piacevole, una fantastica grafica rétro e un'accattivante colonna sonora chiptune. <br><br>Super Crate Box ha vinto numerosi riconoscimenti, inclusi i premi assegnati da IGN, EDGE e IndieGames.com, e ha ricevuto una nomination nella categoria 'Excellence in Design' all'Independent Games Festival. Finora, sono state raccolte oltre 85 milioni di casse nel mondo. <br><br>Raccogli casse dove vuoi, quando vuoi: da oggi Super Crate Box è finalmente disponibile anche in versione mobile!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 5402 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Vlambeer. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[El bombazo de Vlambeer, SUPER CRATE BOX, trae de vuelta la gloria de la edad de oro del arcade, ¡cuando todo lo que importaba era salir en la lista de récords! Coge tu gorra de béisbol y afloja tus pantalones, llegó el momento de luchar contra interminables hordas de enemigos y coger todas las cajas que puedas. Prepárate para disfrutar del arcade con frenéticos controles, mecánicas de juego estimulantes, gráficos retro y una banda sonora pegadiza. <br><br>Super Crate Box ha ganado numerosos premios, como los de IGN, EDGE, IndieGames.com y una nominación por "Excelencia en Diseño" en el Independent Games Festival. Hasta ahora, se han cogido más de 85 millones de cajas por el mundo. <br><br>Coge cajas vayas donde vayas y cuando quieras. ¡Ahora, Super Crate Box disponible en cualquier sitio!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 5402 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Vlambeer. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Vlambeers Superhit SUPER CRATE BOX lässt die Pracht des goldenen Arcade-Zeitalters wiederauferstehen, in dem nur Eines wichtig war: einen Platz auf der Highscore-Liste zu ergattern! Also schnapp dir dein Basecap und krempel die Ärmel hoch, denn jetzt ist es wieder an der Zeit, gegen endlose Horden von Feinden zu kämpfen und dir jede Waffenkiste zu schnappen, die du kriegen kannst. Was dich erwartet? Ein Arcade-Sahnestückchen mit knackiger Steuerung, schicker Spielmechanik, rasanter Retro-Grafik und einem irre hippen Chiptune-Soundtrack. <br><br>Auf das Konto von Super Crate Box gehen zahlreiche Auszeichnungen, darunter Preise von IGN, EDGE, IndieGames.com sowie einer Nominierung für 'Excellence in Design' beim Independent Games Festival. Bisher wurden weltweit mehr als 85 Millionen Kisten gesammelt. <br><br>Sammle Kisten wo immer du bist und wann immer du willst. Super Crate Box gibt es jetzt endlich auch für unterwegs!<br><br>Paketgröße: 5402 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Vlambeer. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Vlambeer's smash hit SUPER CRATE BOX brings back the glory of -the golden arcade age when all that really mattered was getting on that high score list! Grab your baseball cap and loosen your pants, it's time to fight endless hordes of enemies and collect every weapon crate you can. Prepare for an arcade delight with tight controls, refreshing game mechanics, cracking retro art and a terribly hip chiptune soundtrack.<br><br>Super Crate Box won numerous awards, including prizes by IGN, EDGE, IndieGames.com and a nomination for 'Excellence in Design' by the Independent Games Festival. So far, over 85 million crates have been collected worldwide. <br><br>Collect crates where-ever you go, whenever you want. Now, Super Crate Box is finally available on the go!<br><br>Package size: 5402 KB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Vlambeer. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Le grand succès de Vlambeer, SUPER CRATE BOX, vous plonge au coeur de l'âge d'or des jeux d'arcade, quand le plus important était d'apparaître dans le classement des meilleurs scores ! Attrapez votre casquette de baseball et mettez-vous en condition : le moment est venu d'affronter des ennemis toujours plus nombreux et de ramasser le plus de caisses d'armes possible. Préparez-vous à passer un excellent moment avec ce jeu d'arcade, ses commandes précises, sa mécanique de jeu innovante, son magnifique design rétro et sa bande-son chiptune branchée. <br><br>Super Crate Box a remporté de nombreuses récompenses, comme celles décernées par IGN, EDGE et IndieGames.com, et a été nommé dans la catégorie « Excellence du design » lors de l'Independent Games Festival. Jusqu'à maintenant, 85 millions de caisses ont été ramassées à travers le monde. <br><br>Ramassez des caisses où que vous alliez, quand vous le souhaitez. Super Crate Box est désormais disponible en version mobile !<br><br>Taille du programme: 5402 ko - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Vlambeer. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Arcade"/>
  <genre value="Games:Action"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_12.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
