<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00021_00">
 <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>86549520</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[あのThumbsUPとGreen Hill の最強コラボによって誕生した、とてつもないゲーム、Panic!™ 巨大なエイリアンのスライムモンスターによって街が攻撃されている! あなたはこのヌルヌルの混乱から街を救うことができるか? Panic!™ は、PlayStation®Mobile 専用のトップダウン式アクションパズルゲームです。素早い判断力と超高速の反射神経によってスライムを阻止します。家を崩したり道路を閉鎖しながらスライムの進路を変えて生存者を守ります。油断するとスライムは勢いを増します! 素早く動けば、爆弾を落としたり救助道具を投げて生存者を救助できます。今まさにスライムに飲み込まれそうになっている生存者を救い出そう! 豊富なアクションと多才なコメディー、そしてスーパースライムを集めたPanic!™。何度も遊びたくなるオモシロさ! パニクらないよう落ち着いてエイリアンのスライムモンスターを倒そう!<br><br>コンテンツ容量:83 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語<br><br>著作権等:<br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[The ever-talented ThumbsUp and Green Hill have joined forces and created a monster…Panic!™ A giant alien slime monster has landed and is attacking the city! Can you prevent the slimy chaos and save the day? Panic!™ Is a unique top-down action puzzler exclusive to PlayStation®Mobile, requiring quick thinking and super-fast-slime-stopping reflexes. Divert slime and protect survivors by toppling houses and creating road blocks. But be careful – the slime gains momentum! If you’re fast enough, you can drop bombs and throw buoys to save those about to be swallowed, but if you’re not – slime is imminent! With plenty of action, comedy and lots of super slime, Panic!™ will keep you coming back slime and slime again! Can you conquer the alien slime monster? Or will you Panic!<br><br>Package size: 83 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Les talentueux ThumbsUp et Green Hill ont uni leurs forces pour créer un monstre… Panic!™ Un monstre slime extraterrestre gigantesque a atterri et attaque la ville ! Parviendrez-vous à empêcher le chaos gluant et à sauver la journée? Panic!™ est un casse-tête d'action original avec vue de haut, exclusif sur PlayStation®Mobile, qui demande un temps de réflexion rapide et des réflexes super vifs pour arrêter le slime. Détournez le slime et protégez les survivants en faisant écrouler des maisons et en créant des obstacles sur les routes. Mais attention – le slime prend de la vitesse! Si vous êtes assez rapide, vous pouvez larguer des bombes et jeter des bouées pour sauver ceux qui sont sur le point de se faire avaler, sinon – slime est imminente! Avec son plein d'action, d'humour et beaucoup de slime, il vous sera impossible de vous décoller de Panic!™ Pouvez-vous conquérir ce monstrueux slime extraterrestre ? Ou succomberez-vous à la Panic!<br><br>Taille du paquet: 83 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Thumbs Up e Green Hill hanno unito le forze e hanno creato un mostro... Panic!™ Un gelatinoso mostro gigante alieno è arrivato e sta attaccando la città! Riuscirai a fermare il caos e salvare la situazione? Panic!™ è un gioco rompicapo d'azione con visuale dall'alto, in esclusiva per PlayStation®Mobile, che richiede rapidità di pensiero e riflessi ultra-veloci per fermare lo slime. Devia lo slime e proteggi i superstiti, facendo crollare case e creando blocchi stradali. Ma fai attenzione: lo slime accelera! Se sarai abbastanza veloce, potrai sganciare bombe e tirare boe per salvare quelli che stanno per essere inghiottiti, ma se non lo sarai... beh, buona fortuna! Con un sacco d'azione, di divertimento e di slime, Panic!™ è un gioco molto coinvolgente. Puoi sconfiggere il mostro alieno? O andrai nel Panic!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 83 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano<br><br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Los talentos de ThumbsUp y Green Hill se han unido para crear un monstruo llamado... Panic!™. ¡Un monstruo alienígena y pegajoso acaba de aterrizar y está atacando la ciudad! ¿Podrás evitar el caos viscoso y salvar al planeta? Panic!™ es un rompecabezas cenital exclusivo para PlayStation®Mobile, para el que necesitarás buenos reflejos y pensar con rapidez para detener el material viscoso. Derriba edificios y bloquea las calles y carreteras para desviar el material viscoso y conseguir proteger a los supervivientes. Pero ten cuidado: ¡el material viscoso adquiere velocidad! Si tienes suficiente rapidez, podrás arrojar bombas, además boyas para salvar a aquellos que están a punto de ser engullidos. Si no te das prisa, ¡material viscoso es inminente! Panic!™está plagado de acción, comedia y muchísimo material viscoso, ¡un vicio pegadizo que te hará volver a por más! ¿Podrás conquistar el espeso monstruo alienígena... O acaso entrarás en Panic!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 83 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Español/Francés/Italiano<br><br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Die Supertalente ThumbsUp und Green Hill haben zusammen ein Monster erschaffen: Panic!™ Ein riesiges außerirdisches Schleimmonster ist auf der Erde gelandet und greift die Stadt an! Wird es dir gelingen, das schleimige Chaos zu verhindern und die Lage zu retten? Panic!™ ist ein einzigartiges Top-Down-Actionrätselspiel, das exklusiv für PlayStation®Mobile entwickelt wurde. Es erfordert schnelles Denken und blitzartige Schleimstopper-Reflexe. Rette die Überlebenden, indem du Häuser zum Einsturz bringst und Straßensperren errichtest, um den Schleim umzuleiten. Aber Vorsicht: Der Schleim wird immer schneller! Wenn du schnell genug bist, kannst du Bomben und Bojen werfen, um zu verhindern, dass jemand vom Schleim verschlungen wird. Mit jeder Menge Action, Spaß und Superschleim wird  Panic!™ dich einfach nicht mehr loslassen! Wirst du das schleimige Alienmonster besiegen oder in Panic!<br><br>Paketgröße: 83 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch<br><br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[The ever-talented ThumbsUp and Green Hill have joined forces and created a monster…Panic!™ A giant alien slime monster has landed and is attacking the city! Can you prevent the slimey chaos and save the day? Panic!™ Is a unique top-down action puzzler exclusive to PlayStation®Mobile, requiring quick thinking and super-fast-slime-stopping reflexes. Divert slime and protect survivors by toppling houses and creating road blocks. But be careful – the slime gains momentum! If you’re fast enough, you can drop bombs and throw buoys to save those about to be swallowed, but if you’re not – slime is imminent! With plenty of action, comedy and lots of super slime, Panic!™ will keep you coming back slime and slime again! Can you conquer the alien slime monster? Or will you Panic!<br><br>Package size: 83 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[The ever-talented ThumbsUp and Green Hill have joined forces and created a monster…Panic!™ A giant alien slime monster has landed and is attacking the city! Can you prevent the slimey chaos and save the day? Panic!™ Is a unique top-down action puzzler exclusive to PlayStation®Mobile, requiring quick thinking and super-fast-slime-stopping reflexes. Divert slime and protect survivors by toppling houses and creating road blocks. But be careful – the slime gains momentum! If you’re fast enough, you can drop bombs and throw buoys to save those about to be swallowed, but if you’re not – slime is imminent! With plenty of action, comedy and lots of super slime, Panic!™ will keep you coming back slime and slime again! Can you conquer the alien slime monster? Or will you Panic!<br><br>Package size: 83 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_AU">
   <description><![CDATA[The ever-talented ThumbsUp and Green Hill have joined forces and created a monster…Panic!™ A giant alien slime monster has landed and is attacking the city! Can you prevent the slimey chaos and save the day? Panic!™ Is a unique top-down action puzzler exclusive to PlayStation®Mobile, requiring quick thinking and super-fast-slime-stopping reflexes. Divert slime and protect survivors by toppling houses and creating road blocks. But be careful – the slime gains momentum! If you’re fast enough, you can drop bombs and throw buoys to save those about to be swallowed, but if you’re not – slime is imminent! With plenty of action, comedy and lots of super slime, Panic!™ will keep you coming back slime and slime again! Can you conquer the alien slime monster? Or will you Panic!<br><br>Package size: 83 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Les talentueux ThumbsUp et Green Hill ont uni leurs forces pour créer un monstre… Panic!™ Un monstre slime extraterrestre gigantesque a atterri et attaque la ville ! Parviendrez-vous à empêcher le chaos gluant et à sauver la journée? Panic!™ est un casse-tête d'action original avec vue de haut, exclusif sur PlayStation®Mobile, qui demande un temps de réflexion rapide et des réflexes super vifs pour arrêter le slime. Détournez le slime et protégez les survivants en faisant écrouler des maisons et en créant des obstacles sur les routes. Mais attention – le slime prend de la vitesse! Si vous êtes assez rapide, vous pouvez larguer des bombes et jeter des bouées pour sauver ceux qui sont sur le point de se faire avaler, sinon – slime est imminente! Avec son plein d'action, d'humour et beaucoup de slime, il vous sera impossible de vous décoller de Panic!™ Pouvez-vous conquérir ce monstrueux slime extraterrestre ? Ou succomberez-vous à la Panic!<br><br>Taille du programme: 83 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Panic!©2012 Ripstone Ltd and ThumbsUp Games.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Action"/>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
