<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00192_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>117394048</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Din helt - en afslappet krop (ragdoll), som kan flyve frit på himlen. Du er konstant bevæger sig fremad i niveau. Den dårlige fyre skyde på dig. Din opgave - at undvige kugler så længe som muligt. <BR>Du kan også skyde skurkene, men det kræver at få hånden, fordi det er nødvendigt at vippe kroppen, så hånden med pistolen viste sig at være, hvor det er nødvendigt, og skyde. Find din egen spillestil nu <BR>bedste score og blive mester i slow-mo! <BR>funktioner: <BR>1 fast slow-mo. Hele processen med at spillet foregår i slowmotion. <BR>2. Det unikke situationer. I løbet af spillet, er landskabet og fjender tilfældigt genereret. <BR>3. Slow-mo effekter. Rotationen af ​​kuglerne, luft bane af deres flyvning ild krudt når et skud og nogle andre pæne ting. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 112 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Russisk<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Dein Held - ein entspannter Körper (Ragdoll), die frei in den Himmel fliegen können. Sie sind ständig in Bewegung in der Ebene. Die bösen Jungs sind auf Sie schießen. Ihre Aufgabe - zu Kugeln ausweichen, so lange wie möglich. <BR>Sie können auch schießen die Bösewichte, aber es erfordert die Hand zu bekommen, weil es notwendig ist, um den Körper zu kippen, so dass die Hand mit der Waffe stellte sich heraus zu sein, wo es notwendig ist, und schießen. Finden Sie Ihren eigenen Spielstil jetzt <BR>beste Ergebnis und werde der Meister der Zeitlupe! <BR>Eigenschaften: <BR>1 Dauerzeitlupe. Der gesamte Prozess des Spiels findet in Zeitlupe. <BR>2 Die Einzigartigkeit von Situationen. Während des Spiels sind die Landschaft und Feinde zufällig erzeugt. <BR>3. Zeitlupe-Effekte. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 112 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Russisch<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Your hero - a relaxed body (ragdoll), which can fly freely in the sky. You are constantly moving forward in the level. The bad guys are shooting at you. Your task - to dodge bullets as long as possible. <BR>You can also shoot the villains, but it requires get the hand, because it is necessary to tilt the body so that the hand with the gun turned out to be where it is necessary, and shoot. Find your own style of play get <BR>best score and become the master of slow-mo! <BR>Features: <BR>1 Constant slow-mo. The whole process of the game takes place in slow motion. <BR>2 The uniqueness of situations. During the game, the landscape and enemies are randomly generated. <BR>3. Slow-mo effects. The rotation of the bullets, air trajectory of their flight fire gunpowder when a shot and some other nice things. <BR><BR>Package size: 112 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Russian<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Your hero - a relaxed body (ragdoll), which can fly freely in the sky. You are constantly moving forward in the level. The bad guys are shooting at you. Your task - to dodge bullets as long as possible. <BR>You can also shoot the villains, but it requires get the hand, because it is necessary to tilt the body so that the hand with the gun turned out to be where it is necessary, and shoot. Find your own style of play get <BR>best score and become the master of slow-mo! <BR>Features: <BR>1 Constant slow-mo. The whole process of the game takes place in slow motion. <BR>2 The uniqueness of situations. During the game, the landscape and enemies are randomly generated. <BR>3. Slow-mo effects. The rotation of the bullets, air trajectory of their flight fire gunpowder when a shot and some other nice things. <BR><BR>Package size: 112 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Russian<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Tu héroe - un cuerpo relajado (muñeco de trapo), que puede volar libremente en el cielo. Usted está constantemente moviendo hacia adelante en el nivel. Los chicos malos están disparando a usted. Su tarea - para esquivar las balas el mayor tiempo posible. <BR>También puede disparar a los villanos, pero requiere conseguir la mano, porque es necesario inclinar el cuerpo para que la mano con el arma resultó ser donde es necesario, y disparar. Encuentra tu propio estilo de juego ahora <BR>mejor puntuación y convertirse en el maestro de cámara lenta! <BR>Características: <BR>1 cámara lenta Permanente. Todo el proceso del juego tiene lugar en cámara lenta. <BR>2 La singularidad de las situaciones. Durante el juego, el paisaje y los enemigos son generados aleatoriamente. <BR>3. efectos a cámara lenta. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 112 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Ruso<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Sankari - rento elin (ragdoll), joka voi lentää vapaasti taivaalla. Olet jatkuvasti eteenpäin tason.Pahikset ampuvat sinut. Sinun tehtäväsi - väistellä luoteja mahdollisimman pitkään. <BR>Voit myös ampua vihollisia, mutta se vaatii saada käsi, koska on tarpeen kallistaa elin niin, että käsi ase osoittautui kun se on tarpeen, ja ampua. Löydä oma pelityylinsä nyt <BR>parhaat pisteet ja tulla mestari hidas-mo! <BR>ominaisuudet: <BR>1 Pysyvä hidas-mo.Koko prosessi Peli tapahtuu hidastettuna. <BR>2 ainutlaatuisuus tilanteissa. Pelin aikana, maiseman ja viholliset ovat satunnaisesti. <BR>3. hidas-mo vaikutuksia.Kierto luoteja, ilma kehityskaari lennon palo ruuti kun laukaus ja muutamia mukavia asioita. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 112 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti/Venäjä<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Votre héros - un corps détendu (de ragdoll), qui peut voler librement dans le ciel. Vous êtes constamment en mouvement vers l'avant dans le niveau. Les méchants tirent sur vous. Votre tâche - pour esquiver les balles aussi longtemps que possible. <BR>Vous pouvez également tirer sur les méchants, mais il faut avoir la main, car il est nécessaire d'incliner le corps de sorte que la main avec le pistolet s'est avéré être où elle est nécessaire, et tirer. Trouvez votre propre style de jeu maintenant <BR>meilleur score et devenir le maître de slow-mo! <BR>Caractéristiques: <BR>1 Permanent slow-mo. L'ensemble du processus du jeu se déroule au ralenti. <BR>2 L'unicité de situations. Pendant le jeu, le paysage et les ennemis sont générés aléatoirement. <BR>3. effets Slow-mo. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 112 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Russe<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Il tuo eroe - un corpo rilassato (ragdoll), che può volare liberamente nel cielo. Si sono costantemente in movimento in avanti nel livello. I cattivi ragazzi sparano a voi. Il vostro compito - per schivare le pallottole più a lungo possibile. <BR>È anche possibile sparare i cattivi, ma richiede ottenere la mano, perché è necessario inclinare il corpo in modo che la mano con la pistola si è rivelata dove è necessario, e sparare. Trova il tuo stile di gioco ora <BR>miglior punteggio e diventare il padrone di slow-mo! <BR>Caratteristiche: <BR>1 permanente slow-mo. L'intero processo del gioco si svolge al rallentatore. <BR>2 L'unicità di situazioni. Durante il gioco, il paesaggio e nemici sono generati casualmente. <BR>3. effetti di slow-mo. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 112 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Russo<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>あなたのヒーロー - リラックスした体（ラグドール）、空を自由に飛ぶことができます。あなたは、常にレベルで進めています。悪者はあなたで撮影している。あなたの仕事 - かわす弾丸にできるだけ長く。 <BR>また、悪役を撮影することができますが、それは、銃を持つ手は、それが必要である場合であること、および撮影することが判明したように身体を傾斜させる必要があるので、それは、手を取得する必要があります。今遊びの独自のスタイルを見つける <BR>最高のスコアとスローモーションのマスターになる！ <BR>特徴： <BR>1常設スローモーション。ゲームの全体のプロセスはスローモーションで行われます。 <BR>状況の2一意性。ゲーム中は、風景や敵がランダムに生成されます。 <BR>3スローモーション効果。弾丸の回転、彼らの飛行火災火薬の空気軌道時のショットといくつかの他の素晴らしいこと。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 112 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/ロシア語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Helten din - en avslappet kropp (ragdoll), som kan fly fritt i himmelen. Du er i konstant bevegelse fremover i nivået. Skurkene skyter på deg. Din oppgave - å smette unna kuler så lenge som mulig. <BR>Du kan også skyte skurkene, men det krever få hånden, fordi det er nødvendig å vippe legemet, slik at hånden med pistolen viste seg å være, hvor det er nødvendig, og skyte. Finn din egen spillestil nå <BR>beste score og bli mester i slow-mo! <BR>funksjoner: <BR>1. Permanent slow-mo. Hele prosessen av spillet foregår i slow motion. <BR>2 Det unike situasjoner. I løpet av spillet, er landskapet og fiender tilfeldig generert. <BR>3. Slow-mo effekter. Rotasjonen av kulene, air banen deres fly brann krutt når et skudd og noen andre fine ting. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 112 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Russisk<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Je held - een ontspannen lichaam (ragdoll), die vrij kunnen vliegen in de lucht. Je bent voortdurend in beweging voorwaarts in het niveau. De slechteriken schieten op je. Uw taak - om te ontwijken kogels zo lang mogelijk. <BR>U kunt schiet de schurken, maar het vereist eerst de kant, omdat het noodzakelijk is om het lichaam kantelen zodat de hand met het pistool bleek indien nodig, en schieten. Vind je eigen stijl van spelen get <BR>beste score en word de meester van de slow-mo! <BR>kenmerken: <BR>1 Constant slow-mo. Het hele proces van het spel vindt plaats in slow motion. <BR>2 Het unieke van situaties. Tijdens het spel, zijn het landschap en de vijanden willekeurig gegenereerd. <BR>3 Slow-mo effecten. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 112 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels/Russisch<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Twój bohater - zrelaksowany ciała (ragdoll), który może latać swobodnie w przestrzeni powietrznej. Jesteś ciągle w ruchu do przodu w poziomie. Źli ludzie strzelają do ciebie. Twoje zadanie - aby pociski unik jak najdłużej. <BR>Można również strzelać do złoczyńców, ale wymaga się rękę, ponieważ konieczne jest przechylić ciało tak, że ręka z pistoletem okazało się, gdzie jest to konieczne, i strzelać. Znajdź swój własny styl gry teraz <BR>najlepszy wynik i stać się mistrzem zwolnionym tempie! <BR>cechy: <BR>1 Stały Slow-Mo.Cały proces odbywa się gra w zwolnionym tempie. <BR>2 wyjątkowość sytuacji. Podczas gry, krajobraz i wrogów są generowane losowo. <BR>3. Efekty Slow-Mo.Obracanie kul, trajektoria powietrza z ich ognia lot prochu, gdy strzał i kilka innych miłych rzeczy. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 112 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski/Rosyjski<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Din hjälte - en avslappnad kropp (ragdoll), som kan flyga fritt i himlen. Du går ständigt framåt i nivån. Skurkarna skjuter på dig. Din uppgift - att dodge kulor så länge som möjligt.<BR>Du kan också skjuta skurkar, men det kräver få handen, eftersom det är nödvändigt att luta kroppen så att handen med pistolen visade sig vara där det är nödvändigt, och skjuta. Hitta din egen spelstil nu <BR>bästa poäng och bli herre över slow-mo! <BR>funktioner: <BR>1 Permanent slow-mo. Hela processen av spelet sker i slow motion. <BR>2 Det unika situationer. Under spelet, är landskapet och fiender slumpmässigt genererat. <BR>3. Slow-mo effekter. Rotationen av kulorna, air banan för deras flyg brand krut när ett skott och en del andra trevliga saker. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 112 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska/Ryska<BR><BR>2014(C) E_Shi games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_17.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
