<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00008_00">
 <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>20485584</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[PlayStationでメガヒットを記録した、名作パズルゲーム「 XI[sai] 」。<br>「 XI[sai] 」を生み出したShiftが開発したのが、この「 Magic Arrows 」です。<br>操作はとっても簡単。<br>パネルをタッチすると、矢印の向きにパネルが動きます。同じ色のパネルが縦か横に３つ揃うと、パネルが消えてスコアがもらえます。<br>連続して消せば、コンボで高得点。また、同じ色のパネルを縦と横に交差させて消すと、虹色に輝く「マジックアロー」を作ることができます。<br>この「マジックアロー」は、タッチすることでリンク効果を発動し、矢印の方向に沿ってドンドン連続してパネルを消していきます。うまくつなげば一気に消せて超快感！<br>ひたすら遊べるENDLESSモードの他、クリアすると頭も心もスッキリするPUZZLEモードも収録しました。<br>シンプルな操作で熱くなる要素満載！ ハマりすぎにご注意ください！！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:20 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<br><br>著作権等:<br>(C)2005-2012 Shift Inc. / (C)2012 HAMSTER Co.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[The famous Puzzle Game “XI[sai]” was a megahit on the PlayStation.<br>Shift, the company that brought you “XI[sai]”, presents this new game: “Magic Arrows”.<br>The controls are very simple. Touch a panel to make it move in the direction of the arrow.<br>When 3 panels of the same color line up horizontally or vertically, the panels will disappear, earning you points.<br>Remove multiple strings of panels in a combo for massive points,<br>and remove horizontal and vertical rows of panels at the same time to make a rainbow-colored “Magic Arrow” appear.<br>Touch this “Magic Arrow” and it will start moving in the direction it’s pointing in,<br>removing everything in its path. If you’re lucky, you might even clear the entire screen!<br>Play to your heart’s content in Endless Mode, or put your brain to the test in Puzzle Mode.<br>The controls are simple; putting down the game is not! Beware of total addiction!<br><br>Package size: 20 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/Japanese<br><br>(C)2005-2012 Shift Inc. / (C)2012 HAMSTER Co.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Après l’énorme succès du célèbre jeu de Puzzle « XI[sai] » sur Playstation, Shift présente son nouveau jeu : « Magic Arrows ».<br>Les commandes sont très intuitives. Touchez un bloc pour le déplacer dans la direction de la flèche correspondante.<br>Quand 3 blocs de la même couleur sont alignés horizontalement ou verticalement, les blocs disparaissent et vous rapportent des points.<br>Faites des combos en alignant de nombreux blocs et gagnez plus de points, et alignez des blocs à la fois horizontalement et verticalement pour faire apparaître une Flèche Magique aux couleurs de l’arc-en-ciel.<br>Touchez cette Flèche Magique et elle commencera à bouger dans la direction qu’elle indique, supprimant tout sur son passage. Si vous êtes chanceux, il se peut même que tous les blocs à l’écran disparaissent!<br>Jouez avec passion au « Mode Endless », ou mettez votre cerveau à l’épreuve en « Mode Puzzle ».<br><br>Taille du paquet: 20 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<br><br>(C)2005-2012 Shift Inc. / (C)2012 HAMSTER Co.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA["XI[sai]" è un puzzle game che ha avuto un successo strepitoso su PlayStation.<br>E Shift, la compagnia che ha dato vita a "XI[sai]", è lieta di presentarvi il suo nuovo prodotto, "Magic Arrows".<br>I comandi di gioco sono molto intuitivi. Toccando un pannello, questo si muove nella direzione indicata dalla freccia. Quando 3 pannelli dello stesso colore vengono allineati in orizzontale o in verticale, questi scompaiono, facendo guadagnare punti al giocatore.<br>È possibile ottenere un punteggio maggiore con le combo, allineando più serie di pannelli, e facendo scomparire contemporaneamente serie di pannelli in orizzontale e in verticale, apparirà una “freccia magica” dei colori dell’arcobaleno.<br>Toccando la “freccia magica”, spariranno tutti i pannelli che si trovano nella direzione in cui punta. Con un po’ di fortuna, puoi addirittura far sparire tutti i pannelli con un colpo solo!<br>Gioca a più non posso con la modalità Endless, oppure dai il meglio delle tue capacità intellettive giocando con la modalità Puzzle.<br>Questo gioco ha tutte le carte in regola per garantire ore e ore di divertimento.<br>Però attenti a non farvi prendere troppo la mano, o non potrete più staccarvene!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 20 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<br><br>(C)2005-2012 Shift Inc. / (C)2012 HAMSTER Co.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[El famoso puzzle "XI[sai]" fue un mega éxito en PlayStation.<br>Ahora Shift, la compañía que creó "XI[sai]", presenta su nuevo juego: "Magic Arrows".<br>Los mandos son muy simples, toca un cuadro para moverlo en dirección a la flecha. Cuando 3 cuadros del mismo color están alineados en forma horizontal o vertical, desaparecerán y obtendrás una puntuación.<br>Elimina varias líneas de cuadros en combo para obtener un gran puntaje, así como elimina líneas horizontales y verticales al mismo tiempo para crear una "flecha mágica", que brilla como el arcoíris. Toca esta “flecha mágica” y desaparecerán todos los cuadros que apunta la flecha. ¡Si eres lo suficientemente suertudo, podrás eliminar todos los cuadros en la pantalla!<br> Juégatelo todo en el modo Endless, o pon tu cerebro a prueba en el modo Puzzle. ¡Los mandos son tan sencillos que no podrás dejar de jugarlo! ¡Atención que este juego es altamente adictivo!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 20 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<br><br>(C)2005-2012 Shift Inc. / (C)2012 HAMSTER Co.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Das berühmte Rätselspiel “XI[sai]” war ein Megahit auf der PlayStation.<br>Shift, die Entwicklungsfirma, die für “XI[sai]” verantwortlich war, präsentiert ihr neues Spiel: “Magic Arrows”.<br>Die Steuerung ist ganz leicht. Berühre ein Tafel, um sie in Richtung des Pfeils zu verschieben.<br>Wenn 3 Tafeln derselben Farbe sich in einer Linie aneinanderreihen, dann verschwinden die Tafeln und du erhältst Punkte. Entferne mehrere Tafelketten hintereinander für jede Menge Punkte. Und entferne horizontale und vertikale Tafelreihen gleichzeitig, um einen regenbogenfarbenen "Magischen Pfeil" erscheinen zu lassen. Berühre diesen "Magischen Pfeil", um ihn in die Richtung zu bewengen, in die er zeigt, und alles in seinem Weg zu entfernen. Wenn du Glück hast, kannst du sogar den ganzen Bildschirm leeren!<br>Spiele im ENDLESS-Modus mit ganzem Herzen oder teste deinen Verstand im PUZZLE-Modus. <br>Die Steuerung mag einfach sein, das Spiel zu schlagen ist es nicht! Gib Acht, dieses Spiel macht süchtig!<br><br>Paketgröße: 20 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<br><br>(C)2005-2012 Shift Inc. / (C)2012 HAMSTER Co.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[The famous Puzzle Game “XI[sai]” was a megahit on the PlayStation.<br>Shift, the company that brought you “XI[sai]”, presents this new game: “Magic Arrows”.<br>The controls are very simple. Touch a panel to make it move in the direction of the arrow.<br>When 3 panels of the same color line up horizontally or vertically, the panels will disappear, earning you points.<br>Remove multiple strings of panels in a combo for massive points,<br>and remove horizontal and vertical rows of panels at the same time to make a rainbow-colored “Magic Arrow” appear.<br>Touch this “Magic Arrow” and it will start moving in the direction it’s pointing in,<br>removing everything in its path. If you’re lucky, you might even clear the entire screen!<br>Play to your heart’s content in Endless Mode, or put your brain to the test in Puzzle Mode.<br>The controls are simple; putting down the game is not! Beware of total addiction!<br><br>Package size: 20 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/Japanese<br><br>(C)2005-2012 Shift Inc. / (C)2012 HAMSTER Co.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Après l’énorme succès du célèbre jeu de Puzzle « XI[sai] » sur Playstation, Shift présente son nouveau jeu : « Magic Arrows ».<br>Les commandes sont très intuitives. Touchez un bloc pour le déplacer dans la direction de la flèche correspondante.<br>Quand 3 blocs de la même couleur sont alignés horizontalement ou verticalement, les blocs disparaissent et vous rapportent des points.<br>Faites des combos en alignant de nombreux blocs et gagnez plus de points, et alignez des blocs à la fois horizontalement et verticalement pour faire apparaître une Flèche Magique aux couleurs de l’arc-en-ciel.<br>Touchez cette Flèche Magique et elle commencera à bouger dans la direction qu’elle indique, supprimant tout sur son passage. Si vous êtes chanceux, il se peut même que tous les blocs à l’écran disparaissent!<br>Jouez avec passion au « Mode Endless », ou mettez votre cerveau à l’épreuve en « Mode Puzzle ».<br><br>Taille du programme: 20 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<br><br>(C)2005-2012 Shift Inc. / (C)2012 HAMSTER Co.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Casual"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
