<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00112_00">

  <appVersion>1.11</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>28596400</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party er puslespil for dem, der gerne en udfordring. Anbring forsigtigt din levering af pile til at guide pingvinerne fra deres igloer til målet. Det er én ting at få alle dine pingviner til slutningen sikkert, men den virkelige udfordring kommer fra at arbejde ud af, hvordan at hente alle de tabte genstande på vejen. Kan du optjener ret til at udfordre de elite 100% club niveauer ved optagning hver eneste indsamles? <BR><BR>Spillet indeholder 100 gratis puslespil, herunder Cirkus Pack som nu er gratis for alle. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 28 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Pinguin-Partei ist Puzzle-Spiel für diejenigen, die eine Herausforderung mögen. Vorsichtig Ihre Versorgung Pfeile, um die Pinguine von ihren Iglus zum Ziel zu führen. Es ist eine Sache, alle Ihre Pinguine am Ende sicher zu bekommen, aber die eigentliche Herausforderung kommt von der Arbeit aus, wie man abholen alle verlorenen Gegenstände auf dem Weg. Können Sie das Recht, die Elite 100% Clubebene durch Aufnehmen jedes einzelne Sammlerstücke herausfordern zu verdienen? <BR><BR>Das Spiel enthält 100 kostenlose Rätsel einschließlich der Circus-Pack, die jetzt für alle kostenlos ist. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 28 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party is puzzle game for those that like a challenge. Carefully place your supply of arrows to guide the penguins from their igloos to the goal. It's one thing to get all of your penguins to the end safely, but the real challenge comes from working out how to pick up all of the lost items on the way. Can you earn the right to challenge the elite 100% club levels by picking up every single collectable?<BR><BR>The game contains 100 free puzzles including the Circus Pack which is now free for all. <BR><BR>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party is puzzle game for those that like a challenge. Carefully place your supply of arrows to guide the penguins from their igloos to the goal. It's one thing to get all of your penguins to the end safely, but the real challenge comes from working out how to pick up all of the lost items on the way. Can you earn the right to challenge the elite 100% club levels by picking up every single collectable?<BR><BR>The game contains 100 free puzzles including the Circus Pack which is now free for all. <BR><BR>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party is puzzle game for those that like a challenge. Carefully place your supply of arrows to guide the penguins from their igloos to the goal. It's one thing to get all of your penguins to the end safely, but the real challenge comes from working out how to pick up all of the lost items on the way. Can you earn the right to challenge the elite 100% club levels by picking up every single collectable?<BR><BR>The game contains 100 free puzzles including the Circus Pack which is now free for all. <BR><BR>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party is puzzle game for those that like a challenge. Carefully place your supply of arrows to guide the penguins from their igloos to the goal. It's one thing to get all of your penguins to the end safely, but the real challenge comes from working out how to pick up all of the lost items on the way. Can you earn the right to challenge the elite 100% club levels by picking up every single collectable?<BR><BR>The game contains 100 free puzzles including the Circus Pack which is now free for all. <BR><BR>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party es un juego de rompecabezas para los que les gusta un desafío. Coloque cuidadosamente el suministro de flechas para guiar a los pingüinos de sus iglús a la meta. Es una cosa para obtener todos los pingüinos hasta el final de forma segura, pero el verdadero reto consiste en encontrar la manera de recoger todos los objetos perdidos en el camino. ¿Se puede ganar el derecho a impugnar la élite 100% los niveles del club recogiendo cada coleccionable? <BR><BR>El juego contiene 100 rompecabezas libres, incluyendo el paquete de circo que ahora es libre para todos. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 28 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party on pulmapeli niille, jotka haluavat haaste. Huolellisesti laitat tarjonta nuolia ohjata pingviinit iglua maaliin. Se on yksi asia saada kaikki pingviinit loppuun turvallisesti, mutta todellinen haaste tulee selvittää kuinka poimia kaikki löytötavaroita matkalla. Voit ansaita oikeus riitauttaa eliitin 100% klubien tasolla poimimalla joka ikinen kerättävissä? <BR><BR>Peli sisältää 100 vapaa palapelit lukien Circus Pack, joka on nyt ilmainen kaikille. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 28 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party est un jeu de puzzle pour ceux qui aiment les défis. Placer délicatement l'offre de flèches pour guider les pingouins de leurs igloos au but. C'est une chose d'obtenir tous vos pingouins à la fin en toute sécurité, mais le vrai défi est de travailler sur la façon de ramasser tous les objets perdus sur le chemin. Pouvez-vous gagner le droit de contester les niveaux élite du club 100% en ramassant chaque unique de collection? <BR><BR>Le jeu contient 100 puzzles gratuits, y compris le pack de cirque qui est désormais gratuit pour tous. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 28 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party est un jeu de puzzle pour ceux qui aiment les défis. Placer délicatement l'offre de flèches pour guider les pingouins de leurs igloos au but. C'est une chose d'obtenir tous vos pingouins à la fin en toute sécurité, mais le vrai défi est de travailler sur la façon de ramasser tous les objets perdus sur le chemin. Pouvez-vous gagner le droit de contester les niveaux élite du club 100% en ramassant chaque unique de collection? <BR><BR>Le jeu contient 100 puzzles gratuits, y compris le pack de cirque qui est désormais gratuit pour tous. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 28 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party è un gioco di puzzle per coloro che amano una sfida. Posizionare con cura il vostro rifornimento di frecce per guidare i pinguini dalle loro igloo alla meta. E 'una cosa per ottenere tutti i pinguini fino alla fine in modo sicuro, ma la vera sfida viene dal lavorare su come raccogliere tutti gli elementi persi sulla strada. Riesci a guadagnarsi il diritto di sfidare le élite livello di club al 100% raccogliendo ogni singola collezione? <BR><BR>Il gioco contiene 100 puzzle, tra cui il pacchetto circo che ora è gratuito per tutti. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 28 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[ペンギン・パーティーは挑戦が好きな人におすすめのパズルゲームです。ペンギン達をイグルーからゴールまで導くために、あなたの矢印を慎重に供給して配置してください。 ペンギンを全て安全にゴールまで導く事が一つですが、本当の挑戦は途中で失くしているアイテムを全て拾う事です。あなたはすべての単一の収集をピックアップしてエリート100％のクラブレベルに挑戦する権利を獲得することができますか？<BR><BR>基本ゲームは100の無料パズルを含んでいて、新しいマップが年間を通じて定期的にリリースされ、最初はサーカスパックで始まります。それぞれの新しいマップパックにはユニークなビジュアルスタイル、新たな矢印や仕掛けだけでなく、新たなパズルのホストを特色にします <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 28 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Partiet er puslespill spill for de som liker en utfordring. Plassere din tilførsel av piler nøye for å veilede pingvinene fra sine igloer til mål. Det er én ting å få alle dine pingviner til slutten trygt, men den virkelige utfordringen kommer fra å arbeide ut hvordan å plukke opp alle de tapte elementer på vei. Kan du tjene retten til å utfordre eliten 100% klubbnivå ved å plukke opp hver eneste collectable? <BR><BR>Spillet inneholder 100 gratis puslespill inkludert Circus Pack som er nå gratis for alle. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 28 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Pinguïn Party is puzzelspel voor diegenen die een uitdaging willen. Plaats voorzichtig de levering van pijlen om de pinguïns te leiden uit hun iglo naar het doel. Het is een ding om al uw pinguïns veilig naar het einde, maar de echte uitdaging komt van uit te werken hoe op te pikken alle verloren voorwerpen op de weg. Kan je verdienen het recht om de elite 100% club niveau uitdagen door het oppakken van elke collectable? <BR><BR>Het spel bevat 100 gratis puzzels waaronder de Circus Pack, dat is nu gratis voor iedereen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 28 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party to gra dla tych, którzy lubią wyzwania. Ostrożnie umieść podaży strzałek do kierowania pingwiny z ich igloo do bramki. Jest jedna rzecz, aby uzyskać wszystkie swoje pingwiny do końca bezpiecznie, ale prawdziwym wyzwaniem jest od pracy, jak podnieść wszystkich utraconych pozycji na drodze. Można otrzymać prawo do zakwestionowania elity 100% poziom klubu przez podniesienie każdego kolekcjonerski? <BR><BR>Gra zawiera 100 darmowe puzzles tym Circus Paczka, która jest teraz za darmo dla wszystkich. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 28 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Penguin Party är pusselspel för dem som gillar en utmaning. Placera försiktigt din leverans av pilarna för att styra pingvinerna från sina igloos till målet. Det är en sak att få alla dina pingviner till slutet på ett säkert sätt, men den verkliga utmaningen kommer från att arbeta ut hur att plocka upp alla de förlorade objekt på vägen. Kan du tjänar rätt att utmana eliten 100% klubbnivå genom att plocka upp varenda samlarobjekt? <BR><BR>Spelet innehåller 100 fria pussel inklusive Circus Pack som nu är gratis för alla. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 28 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Xmpt Games Inc.  All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
