<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00197_00">

  <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>1077515680</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Flight World er ikke en flysimulator i traditionel forstand! <BR>Dette er en kommerciel jet liner spil med innovative spil designet til PlayStation®Vita. De særlige funktioner vil holde dig beskæftiget og underholdt, som du vil blive udfordret til også opretholde komfort rutetrafik inde i flyet. <BR><BR>Flyv i Nordamerika, Europa, Asien og Australien. <BR><BR>(Sydamerika og Afrika er ikke inkluderet på grund af størrelse) <BR><BR>spillet <BR>• Opbyg din flåde i karriere mode, verdensur og realtime internet vejr. <BR>• Fly enten ved hjælp af manuel eller autopilot, efter flyveleder anvisninger for at nå din destination <BR>• Tjen penge ved at sælge billetter og besvare stewardesse opkald, mens de flyver. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 1028 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR>- Bevægelsessensor<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Flight World ist nicht ein Flugsimulator in einem traditionellen Sinn! <BR>Dies ist eine kommerzielle Jet-Liner-Spiel mit innovativen Spiel für PlayStation®Vita entwickelt. Die Besonderheiten werden Sie beschäftigt und unterhalten, wie Sie herausgefordert werden, um auch den Komfort des Bordservice im Flugzeug zu halten zu halten. <BR><BR>Fliegen in Nordamerika, Europa, Asien und Australien. <BR><BR>(Südamerika und Afrika sind nicht aufgrund der Größe im Lieferumfang enthalten) <BR><BR>Spiel <BR>• Erstellen Sie Ihre Flotte im Karriere-Modus, Weltzeituhr und Echtzeit-Internet-Wetter. <BR>• Fliegen Sie entweder über manuelle oder Autopilot, folgende Hinweise Fluglotsen an Ihr Ziel zu erreichen <BR>• Stellen Sie Geld durch den Verkauf der Tickets und die Beantwortung Flugbegleiterin Anrufe während des Fluges. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 1028 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR>- Bewegungssensor<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Flight World is not a flight simulator in a traditional sense!<BR>This is a commercial jet liner game with innovative game play designed for PlayStation®Vita. The special features will keep you busy and entertained as you will be challenged to also maintain the comfort of the flight service inside the aircraft.<BR><BR>Fly in North America, Europe, Asia and Australia.<BR><BR>(South America and Africa are not included due to size)<BR><BR>Game play<BR>• Build your fleet in career mode, world clock and realtime internet weather.<BR>• Fly either using manual or autopilot, following air traffic controller's instructions to reach your destination<BR>• Make money by selling tickets and answering flight attendant calls while flying. <BR><BR>Package size: 1028 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Flight World is not a flight simulator in a traditional sense!<BR>This is a commercial jet liner game with innovative game play designed for PlayStation®Vita. The special features will keep you busy and entertained as you will be challenged to also maintain the comfort of the flight service inside the aircraft.<BR><BR>Fly in North America, Europe, Asia and Australia.<BR><BR>(South America and Africa are not included due to size)<BR><BR>Game play<BR>• Build your fleet in career mode, world clock and realtime internet weather.<BR>• Fly either using manual or autopilot, following air traffic controller's instructions to reach your destination<BR>• Make money by selling tickets and answering flight attendant calls while flying. <BR><BR>Package size: 1028 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Flight World is not a flight simulator in a traditional sense!<BR>This is a commercial jet liner game with innovative game play designed for PlayStation®Vita. The special features will keep you busy and entertained as you will be challenged to also maintain the comfort of the flight service inside the aircraft.<BR><BR>Fly in North America, Europe, Asia and Australia.<BR><BR>(South America and Africa are not included due to size)<BR><BR>Game play<BR>• Build your fleet in career mode, world clock and realtime internet weather.<BR>• Fly either using manual or autopilot, following air traffic controller's instructions to reach your destination<BR>• Make money by selling tickets and answering flight attendant calls while flying. <BR><BR>Package size: 1028 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Flight World is not a flight simulator in a traditional sense!<BR>This is a commercial jet liner game with innovative game play designed for PlayStation®Vita. The special features will keep you busy and entertained as you will be challenged to also maintain the comfort of the flight service inside the aircraft.<BR><BR>Fly in North America, Europe, Asia and Australia.<BR><BR>(South America and Africa are not included due to size)<BR><BR>Game play<BR>• Build your fleet in career mode, world clock and realtime internet weather.<BR>• Fly either using manual or autopilot, following air traffic controller's instructions to reach your destination<BR>• Make money by selling tickets and answering flight attendant calls while flying. <BR><BR>Package size: 1028 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Flight World no es un simulador de vuelo en un sentido tradicional! <BR>Este es un juego de forro avión comercial con juego innovador diseñado para PlayStation®Vita. Las características especiales le mantendrá ocupado y entretenido ya que se enfrentan al reto de mantener también la comodidad del servicio de vuelo dentro de la aeronave. <BR><BR>Volar en América del Norte, Europa, Asia y Australia. <BR><BR>(América del Sur y África no se incluyen debido a su tamaño) <BR><BR>El juego <BR>• Construye tu flota en el modo carrera, reloj mundial y el clima en tiempo real de Internet. <BR>• Vuela ya sea manual o usando el piloto automático, siguiendo las instrucciones del controlador de tráfico aéreo para llegar a su destino <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 1028 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR>- Sensor de movimiento<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Flight World ei ole lentosimulaattori perinteisessä merkityksessä! <BR>Tämä on kaupallinen jet liner peli innovatiivinen peli on suunniteltu PlayStation®Vita.Erityispiirteet pitävät kiireisenä ja viihdettä kun haastetaan myös säilyttää mukavasti lennon palvelun lentokoneen sisällä. <BR><BR>Lentää Pohjois-Amerikassa, Euroopassa, Aasiassa ja Australiassa. <BR><BR>(Etelä-Amerikka ja Afrikka eivät sisälly koon perusteella) <BR><BR>pelin kulku <BR>• Rakenna laivaston uratila, maailmankello ja reaaliaikainen internet sää. <BR>• Fly joko manuaalisesti tai automaattiohjaus, seuraavat lennonjohtajan ohjeiden perillä <BR>• Tee rahaa myymällä lippuja ja vastaamalla lentoemäntä puheluita lentäessään. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 1028 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR>- Liikeohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Flight World n'est pas un simulateur de vol dans un sens traditionnel! <BR>Il s'agit d'un jet jeu de ligne commerciale avec le jeu original conçu pour la PlayStation®Vita. Les caractéristiques particulières seront vous tenir occupé et de se divertir comme vous serez mis au défi de maintenir également le confort du service de vol à l'intérieur de l'avion. <BR><BR>Fly en Amérique du Nord, en Europe, en Asie et en Australie. <BR><BR>(Amérique du Sud et l'Afrique ne sont pas inclus en raison de la taille) <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 1028 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR>- Détection de mouvements<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Flight World n'est pas un simulateur de vol dans un sens traditionnel! <BR>Il s'agit d'un jet jeu de ligne commerciale avec le jeu original conçu pour la PlayStation®Vita. Les caractéristiques particulières seront vous tenir occupé et de se divertir comme vous serez mis au défi de maintenir également le confort du service de vol à l'intérieur de l'avion. <BR><BR>Fly en Amérique du Nord, en Europe, en Asie et en Australie. <BR><BR>(Amérique du Sud et l'Afrique ne sont pas inclus en raison de la taille) <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 1028 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR>- Détecteur de mouvements<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Flight World non è un simulatore di volo in senso tradizionale! <BR>Questo è un gioco di linea jet commerciale con il gioco innovativo progettato per PlayStation®Vita. Le caratteristiche speciali vi terrà occupati e divertire come sarete sfidati a mantenere anche il comfort del servizio di volo all'interno del velivolo. <BR><BR>Vola in Nord America, Europa, Asia e Australia. <BR><BR>(Sud America e Africa non sono inclusi a causa delle dimensioni) <BR><BR>Il gioco <BR>• Costruisci la tua flotta in modalità carriera, orologio mondiale e tempo internet in tempo reale. <BR>• Fly sia mediante strumenti manuali o pilota automatico, seguendo le istruzioni del controllore del traffico aereo per raggiungere la destinazione <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 1028 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR>- Sensore di movimento<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>フライト·ワールドは、伝統的な意味でのフライトシミュレータではありません！ <BR>これはPlayStation®Vita用に設計された革新的なゲームプレイと民間ジェットライナーゲームです。特別な機能は、忙しいあなたも、航空機内部の飛行サービスの快適さを維持するために挑戦されるように楽しまを維持します。 <BR><BR>北米、欧州、アジア、オーストラリアに飛ぶ。 <BR><BR>（南米、アフリカ、サイズのために含まれません） <BR><BR>ゲームプレイ <BR>•キャリアモード、世界時計、リアルタイムのインターネット天候であなたの艦隊を構築します。 <BR>•目的地に到達するための航空交通管制官の指示書に従って使用して手動または自動操縦、どちらフライ <BR>•チケットを販売し、飛行中の客室乗務員の呼び出しに答えることでお金を稼ぐ。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 1028 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR>- モーションセンサー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Flight World er ikke en flysimulator i en tradisjonell forstand! <BR>Dette er en kommersiell jet liner spill med nyskapende spill utviklet for PlayStation®Vita. De spesielle funksjonene vil holde deg opptatt og underholdt som du vil bli utfordret til også å opprettholde komforten av flyturen tjenesten inne i flyet. <BR><BR>Fly i Nord-Amerika, Europa, Asia og Australia. <BR><BR>(Sør-Amerika og Afrika er ikke inkludert på grunn av størrelse) <BR><BR>spillet <BR>• Bygg din flåte i karrieremodus, verdensklokke og realtime internett vær. <BR>• Fly enten ved bruk av manuell eller autopilot, etter flygeleder instruksjoner for å nå dine mål <BR>• Tjen penger ved å selge billetter og besvare flyvertinne samtaler mens du flyr. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 1028 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR>- Bevegelsessensor<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Flight World is niet een vluchtsimulator in een traditionele zin! <BR>Dit is een commerciële jet liner spel met innovatieve gameplay ontworpen voor de PlayStation®Vita. De speciale functies zal je bezig en vermaakt als je wordt uitgedaagd om ook het comfort van de flight service in het vliegtuig te behouden houden. <BR><BR>Vlieg in Noord-Amerika, Europa, Azië en Australië. <BR><BR>(Zuid-Amerika en Afrika zijn niet opgenomen vanwege de grootte) <BR><BR>spel te spelen <BR>• Bouw je vloot in de career mode, wereldklok en realtime internet weer. <BR>• Vlieg hetzij met behulp van handmatige of automatische piloot, volgens de instructies van luchtverkeersleider om uw bestemming te bereiken <BR>• Verdien geld door de verkoop van tickets en het beantwoorden van stewardess gesprekken tijdens het vliegen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 1028 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR>- Bewegingssensor<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Lot Świat nie jest symulator lotu, w tradycyjnym znaczeniu! <BR>To jest reklama gry odrzutowiec z innowacyjną grę przeznaczony dla PlayStation®Vita. Cechy szczególne można zachować zajęty i rozrywkę, jak będzie zadanie również utrzymać komfort obsługi lotu wewnątrz samolotu. <BR><BR>Latać w Ameryce Północnej, Europie, Azji i Australii. <BR><BR>(Ameryka Południowa i Afryka nie są uwzględnione ze względu na wielkość) <BR><BR>Rozgrywka <BR>• Zbuduj swoją flotę w trybie kariery, zegar światowy i realtime pogody Internetu. <BR>• Fly albo manualnie lub autopilota, zgodnie z instrukcjami kontrolera ruchu lotniczego w celu dotarcia do miejsca docelowego <BR>• Zarabiaj pieniądze poprzez sprzedaż biletów i odbieranie połączeń stewardessa podczas lotu. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 1028 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR>- Czujnik ruchu<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Flight World är inte en flygsimulator i traditionell mening! <BR>Detta är en kommersiell jet liner spel med innovativa spel utformad för PlayStation®Vita. De särskilda funktioner kommer att hålla dig upptagen och underhöll som du kommer att utmanas att också bibehålla komforten av flygtjänsten inne i flygplanet. <BR><BR>Fly i Nordamerika, Europa, Asien och Australien. <BR><BR>(Sydamerika och Afrika ingår inte beroende på storlek) <BR><BR>spelet <BR>• Bygg upp din flotta i karriärläget, världsklocka och realtids internet väder. <BR>• Fly antingen med manuell eller autopilot, efter flygledarens instruktioner för att nå din destination <BR>• Tjäna pengar genom att sälja och besvara flygvärdinna samtal under flygning biljetter. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 1028 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR>- Rörelsesensor<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>2014 Johan Valfridsson<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Simulation"/><genre value="Games:Strategy"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
