<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00234_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>117414080</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Snotbolden Flem er strandet i en fremmed ny verden efter det Store Nys! Led Flem gennem fire sæsoner, og hjælp ham med at finde hans forsvundne folk i den mytiske Lommetørklæde Riget.<BR><BR>Flem er et klassisk platformspil med et speedrun-fokus. Løb og spring gennem fire sæsoner og samtidig undgå farer . Oplev Flem skjulte snotkræfter, herunder evnen til at forvandle sig til en sky. Vind medaljer baseret på din bedste tid gennem hvert niveau og konkurrer med andre spillere via leaderboards.<BR><BR>FUNKTIONER<BR>* Platformudfordringer, der er nemt at lære, men svært at mestre.<BR>* Løb, spring, fyg og flyv gennem 40 niveauer på tværs af fire årstider.<BR>* Race og vind medaljer på hvert niveau.<BR>* Lystig 8 -bit inspireret lydspor. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 112 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2015 Henchman &amp; Goon AS<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Flem der Popel ist vom Großen Nieser in eine fremde neue Welt geschleudert worden! Hilf ihm auf seiner Reise durch die vier Jahreszeiten, um seine Brüder und Schwestern im Land der Ewigen Taschentücher zu finden!<BR><BR>Renne und hüpfe durch vier Jahreszeiten und weiche dabei Gefahren aus. Entdecke Flems geheimnisvolle Popel-Kräfte, darunter auch die Fähigkeit, sich in eine Wolke zu verwandeln. Je nach der Zeit, die du für einen Level brauchst, erhältst du Medaillen, und in den Bestenlisten kannst du deine Zeiten mit denen anderer Spieler vergleichen!<BR><BR>* Schwer zu meistern Plattformspiel.<BR>* Vier Jahreszeiten und 40 Level, durch die du rennen, hüpfen und fliegen musst.<BR>* Zeitherausforderungen, Medaillen und Bestenlisten für jeden Level.<BR>* 8-bit inspirierter musik. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 112 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2015 Henchman &amp; Goon AS<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Oh Nose! The booger Flem is stranded in a strange new world after the calamity of the Great Sneeze! Help him on his journey through four seasons to find his lost people in the Land of Eternal Tissue.<BR><BR>Flem offers classic platforming with a speedrun flavor. Run and jump through four seasons while avoiding the hostile environment and discover Flem's hidden snot powers, including the ability to turn himself into a cloud. Earn medals based on your best time through each level and compete with other players through leaderboards. Are you gonna go for gold or just try to stay alive?<BR><BR>FEATURES <BR>* Easy to learn, hard to master platforming. <BR>* 40 levels over four seasons to run, jump, dash and fly through. <BR>* Time trials, medals and leaderboards for every level. <BR>* Cheery 8-bit inspired soundtrack. <BR><BR>Package size: 112 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2015 Henchman &amp; Goon AS<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Flem, el moco, acaba de aterrizar en un nuevo y desconcertante mundo tras el desastroso paso del Gran Estornudo.<BR><BR>Flem es un juego de plataformas clásico con un toque de speedrun. Salta y corre a lo largo de las cuatro estaciones en medio de un entorno hostil y descubre los poderes secretos del moco Flem, como su habilidad para convertirse en una nube. Consigue medallas registrando el mejor tiempo en un nivel y compite con otros jugadores en la clasificación.<BR><BR>* Un juego de plataformas que te lo pone muy fácil para empezar, pero difícil para llegar a lo más alto.<BR>* 40 niveles repartidos por cuatro estaciones donde podrás correr, saltar, esprintar y volar.<BR>* Pruebas contrarreloj, medallas y clasificaciones en cada nivel.<BR>* Divertida música inspirada en las composiciones de 8 bits. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 112 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2015 Henchman &amp; Goon AS<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Ce nez pas possible! Le blob de mucus Flem s’est échoué dans un monde étrange, après le Grand Cataclysme Pharyngique! <BR><BR>Flem est un jeu de plateforme classique qui rappelle le speedrun. Courez et sautez à travers les quatre saisons, évitez les obstacles et découvrez les pouvoirs cachés de la morve Flem, dont celui de se transformer en nuage. Établissez de nouveaux records de temps pour remporter des médailles et mesurez-vous aux autres joueurs du classement.<BR><BR>CARACTÉRISTIQUES<BR>* Un jeu de plateforme facile à comprendre et difficile à maîtriser.<BR>* Courez, sautez, foncez, volez et parcourez  40 niveaux à travers les quatre saisons.<BR>* Des contre-la-montre, des médailles et des classements pour chaque niveau.<BR>* Une bande-son 8-bits originale et entraînante. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 112 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2015 Henchman &amp; Goon AS<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Dopo il disastro del Grande Starnuto la caccola Flem è rimasta bloccata in uno strano, nuovo mondo!<BR><BR>Flem offre una classica azione di gioco a piattaforme. Corri e salta per quattro stagioni: cerca di evitare l'ambiente ostile e scopri i poteri nascosti della caccola Flem, compresa quella di trasformarsi in una nuvola. Ottieni il miglior tempo per i diversi livelli e vinci medaglie, poi fronteggiati con altri giocatori per il piazzamento più alto in classifica.<BR><BR>* Sarà facile imparare a usare questo gioco a piattaforme, ma difficile diventare degli esperti.<BR>* 40 livelli divisi per le quattro stagioni in cui dovrai saltare, scattare e che dovrai attraversare in volo.<BR>* Prove a tempo, medaglie e classifiche per ciascun livello.<BR>* Colonna sonora allegra, ispirata al mondo 8 bit. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 112 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2015 Henchman &amp; Goon AS<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>鼻の罠！「ハクション暴風雨」という大惨事の後、鼻くそのフレムは奇妙な新世界に迷い込んでしまいました。永遠のティッシュ・ランドで四季を通じてフレムが仲間を探す手助けをしましょう！<BR><BR>フレムは昔ながらの横スクロールにスピードランの醍醐味を追加したゲームです。危険な障害を避けながら、走りとジャンプで四季を駆け抜けるのです！さらに自分を雲に変えてしまうなどのフレムの隠された鼻水パワーを発見しましょう。各ステージのベストタイムに基づいてメダルをゲットして、ランキングで他のプレイヤーと競いましょう！ゴールドメダルを目指しますか？それとも生き延びるので精一杯？！<BR><BR>特徴<BR>簡単に手に取って遊ぶことができるけど、マスターするのは大変な横スクロールアクション。<BR>走って、ジャンプして、飛んで駆け抜けることができる四季は40ステージ以上。<BR>すべてのステージにタイムトライアル、メダル、ランキングがあるぞ。<BR>8bitの影響を受けたとってもオチャメなサウンドトラック。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 112 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(C) 2015 Henchman &amp; Goon AS<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Snørrballen Flem er strandet i en merkelig ny verden etter det Store Nyset! Led Flem gjennom fire årstider og hjelp ham å finne sitt forsvunnende folk i det mytiske Lommetørkleriket.<BR><BR>Flem er et klassisk plattformspill med et speedrun-fokus . Løp og hopp gjennom fire årstider mens du unngår farer. Oppdag Flems skjulte snørrkrefter, inkludert evnen til å forvandle seg til en sky. Vinn medaljer basert på din beste tid gjennom hvert nivå og konkurrer med andre spillere gjennom topplister.<BR> <BR>FUNKSJONER<BR>* Platformutfordringer som er lett å lære , men vanskelig å mestre.<BR>* Løp, hopp, fyk og fly gjennom 40 nivåer over fire årstider..<BR>* Temporitt , medaljer og topplister for hvert nivå .<BR>* Livlig 8 -bit inspirert lydspor. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 112 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2015 Henchman &amp; Goon AS<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Oké, nu even zere neus. Bulletje Flem is gestrand in een vreemde nieuwe wereld na de ramp van de Grote Nies! Help hem op zijn reis door vier seizoenen om zijn verloren volk te vinden in het Land van Eeuwige Tissue.<BR><BR>Flem biedt klassieke platforming met een vleugje speedrun. Ren en spring door vier seizoenen terwijl je de vijandelijke omgeving mijdt en Flems verborgen snotkrachten ontdekt, inclusief de mogelijkheid om zichzelf in een wolk te veranderen. Verdien medailles op basis van je beste tijd in elk level en speel tegen andere spelers in het klassement.<BR><BR>* Een makkelijk te leren, maar moeilijk te winnen platformgame. <BR>* Ren, spring, storm en vlieg door 40 levels in vier seizoenen. <BR>* Tijdritten, medailles en klassementen voor elk level. <BR>* Vrolijke 8-bits soundtrack. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 112 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels<BR><BR>Copyright(C) 2015 Henchman &amp; Goon AS<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
