<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00232_00">

  <appVersion>2.02</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>101123680</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Leder du efter nogle hurtige skydeaction, og derefter give The Game Lab Project en go. Du spiller som enten Bob eller Bobby, to regulære fyre, der kan lide deres kaffe. Når du ikke drikker kaffe, Bob og Bobby gerne gå ind i den virtuelle arena og tage på nogle virtuelle soldater eller zombier. Vil du tage det roligt, og derefter give Arcade Cabinet en prøve og spille Bob og Bobby foretrukne barndom spil, kaffe Catcher. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 97 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Auf der Suche nach ein paar schnelle Shooter-Action, dann geben Sie die Lab-Projekt Spiel ein zu gehen. Man spielt entweder als Bob oder Bobby, zwei reguläre Jungs, die ihren Kaffee mögen. Wenn nicht Kaffee trinken, Bob und Bobby gerne in die virtuelle Arena gehen und auf einigen virtuellen Soldaten oder Zombies. Willst du es einfach zu nehmen, dann geben dem Arcade Cabinet ausprobieren und spielen Bob und Lieblings Kindheit Spiel Bobbys, Kaffee Catcher. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 97 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Looking for some quick shooting action, then give The Game Lab Project a go. You play as either Bob or Bobby, two regular guys who like their coffee. When not drinking coffee, Bob and Bobby like to go into the virtual arena and take on some virtual soldiers or zombies. Want to take it easy, then give the Arcade Cabinet a try and play Bob and Bobby's favorite childhood game, Coffee Catcher. <BR><BR>Package size: 97 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Buscando un poco de acción de tiro rápido, a continuación, dar el Proyecto Lab juego una oportunidad. Usted juega como sea Bob o Bobby, dos chicos normales que les gusta su café. Cuando no beber café, Bob y Bobby les gusta ir a la arena virtual y asumir algunos soldados virtuales o zombies. ¿Quieres que tomarlo con calma, a continuación, dar el Arcade Cabinet una oportunidad y jugar Bob y juego favorito de la infancia de Bobby, Café Catcher. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 97 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Etsitkö nopeita ammuntaa, anna Game Lab-hankkeen mennä. Pelaat joko Bob tai Bobby, kaksi tavallista kaveria, jotka haluavat heidän kahvia. Kun ei juo kahvia, Bob ja Bobby haluavat mennä virtuaaliareena ja ottaa joitakin virtuaalisia sotilaita tai zombeja. Haluatko ottaa rennosti, sitten antaa Arcade Cabinet kokeilla ja leikkiä Bob ja Bobby suosikki lapsuuden peli, Kahvi Catcher. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 97 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>La recherche d'une action de tir rapide, puis donner au projet Lab jeu une fois. Vous incarnez soit Bob ou Bobby, deux gars ordinaires qui aiment leur café. Lorsqu'ils ne sont pas de boire du café, Bob et Bobby aiment aller dans l'arène virtuelle et prendre sur des soldats ou des zombies virtuels. Vous voulez prendre, il est facile, puis donner la borne d'arcade un essai et jouer Bob et jeu d'enfance préféré de Bobby, café Catcher. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 97 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Alla ricerca di qualche azione di tiro rapido, quindi dare a The Lab progetto di gioco un andare. Si gioca sia come Bob o Bobby, due ragazzi normali che amano il loro caffè. Quando non bere caffè, Bob e Bobby piace andare nell'arena virtuale e affrontare alcuni soldati virtuali o zombie. Vuoi prendere facilmente, poi dare l'Arcade Cabinet una prova e giocare Bob e gioco d'infanzia preferito di Bobby, Coffee Catcher. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 97 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>いくつかの簡単なシューティングアクションを探して、その後ゲームラボプロジェクトをやってみる。あなたは彼らのコーヒーが好きで、ボブやボビーのいずれかとして、2つの正規の男を演じる。コーヒーを飲んでいないときは、ボブとボビーは、仮想アリーナに入り、一部の仮想兵士やゾンビを取るのが好きです。その後、簡単にそれを取るアーケードキャビネットを試してみて、ボブとボビーのお気に入りの幼年期のゲーム、コーヒーキャッチャーをプレイしたい。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 97 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Leter du etter noen rask skyting, så gi The Game Lab Prosjekt en gå. Du spiller som enten Bob eller Bobby, to vanlige gutter som liker deres kaffe. Når du ikke drikker kaffe, Bob og Bobby liker å gå inn i den virtuelle arenaen og ta på noen virtuelle soldater eller zombier. Lyst til å ta det med ro, så gi Arcade Cabinet en prøve og spille Bob og Bobby favoritt barndommen spillet, Coffee Catcher. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 97 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Op zoek naar een aantal snelle actie schieten, dan geven The Game Lab Project een gaan. Je speelt als ofwel Bob of Bobby, twee gewone jongens die hun koffie graag. Als koffie niet te drinken, Bob en Bobby willen gaan in de virtuele arena en neem het op sommige virtuele soldaten of zombies. Wil het rustig aan te doen, dan geven de Arcade Cabinet een keer te proberen en te spelen Bob en favoriete kindertijd Bobby's spel, Coffee Catcher. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 97 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Szukam jakiegoś szybkiego działania fotografowania, a następnie dać laboratorium Przedsięwzięcie grze iść. Wcielamy się zarówno Boba lub Bobby'ego, dwóch facetów, którzy lubią regularne ich kawę. Kiedy nie pije kawy, Bob i Bobby chciał wejść do wirtualnej arenie i wziąć na niektórych żołnierzy wirtualnych lub zombie. Chcesz wziąć to łatwe, a potem dać Arcade Cabinet spróbować i zagrać Boba i Bobby'ego ulubione gry z dzieciństwa, Coffee Catcher. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 97 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Letar du efter några snabba skytte åtgärder, sedan ge The Game Lab Project en go. Du spelar antingen som Bob och Bobby, två vanliga killar som gillar deras kaffe. När du inte dricker kaffe, Bob och Bobby gillar att gå in i den virtuella arenan och ta på några virtuella soldater eller zombies. Vill du ta det lugnt, sedan ge Arcade Cabinet ett försök och spela Bob och Bobby favorit barndom spel, kaffe Catcher. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 97 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska<BR><BR>© 2014 Jacky King<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Shooter"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_27.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_28.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_29.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_26.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_24.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_31.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_25.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_16.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
