<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00175_00">

  <appVersion>1.05</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>43933824</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Set i nær fremtid, når mennesker har med succes skabt kraftfulde rumalder teknologi bare for at finde ud af, at vi ikke er helt alene derude. Du vil deltage i flere top hemmelige missioner for at ødelægge fjendens installationer eller forsvare strategisk vigtige steder. Spillet er en kombination af hurtig arkade stil shooter med grundlæggende strategi og forvaltning af naturressourcer. Hvert niveau er en selvstændig miljø og kan spilles i 1. eller 3. person visning (undtagen Base Defence). Din succes vil afhænge af dit rum kampfærdigheder samt homebase forsvar taktik og aktiver ledelse. Du vil også finde i alt 26 minutters musik, herunder 4 Indie Underground tracks, komplet med brugerdefinerede afspiller +. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 42 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Polsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[In naher Zukunft, wenn die Menschen haben erfolgreich mächtige Weltraumzeitalter-Technologie erstellt, nur um herauszufinden, dass wir nicht ganz allein da draußen. Sie werden an verschiedenen streng geheimen Missionen, um feindliche Anlagen zerstören oder verteidigen strategisch wichtigen Standorten. Das Spiel ist eine Kombination aus schnellen Arcade-Stil-Shooter mit grundlegenden Strategie und Ressourcen-Management. Jede Ebene ist eine in sich geschlossene Umgebung und kann in der 1. oder 3. Person-Ansicht (außer Base Defence) gespielt werden. Ihr Erfolg wird von Ihrem Raumkampffähigkeiten sowie Homebase Verteidigung Taktik und Vermögensverwaltung ab. Sie finden auch, insgesamt 26 Minuten Musik, darunter 4 U-Indie-Tracks, komplett mit benutzerdefinierten Player+. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 42 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Polnisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Set in near future, when humans have successfully created powerful space age technology just to find out that we are not all alone out there. You will take part in several top secret missions to destroy enemy installations or defend strategically significant locations. The game is a combination of fast arcade style shooter with basic strategy and resources management. Each level is a self contained environment and can be played in 1st or 3rd person view (except Base Defence). Your success will depend from your space combat skills as well as homebase defence tactics and assets management. You will also find total of 26 minutes of music including 4 Indie Underground tracks, complete with custom Player+. <BR><BR>Package size: 42 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Polish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Set in near future, when humans have successfully created powerful space age technology just to find out that we are not all alone out there. You will take part in several top secret missions to destroy enemy installations or defend strategically significant locations. The game is a combination of fast arcade style shooter with basic strategy and resources management. Each level is a self contained environment and can be played in 1st or 3rd person view (except Base Defence). Your success will depend from your space combat skills as well as homebase defence tactics and assets management. You will also find total of 26 minutes of music including 4 Indie Underground tracks, complete with custom Player+. <BR><BR>Package size: 42 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Polish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Set in near future, when humans have successfully created powerful space age technology just to find out that we are not all alone out there. You will take part in several top secret missions to destroy enemy installations or defend strategically significant locations. The game is a combination of fast arcade style shooter with basic strategy and resources management. Each level is a self contained environment and can be played in 1st or 3rd person view (except Base Defence). Your success will depend from your space combat skills as well as homebase defence tactics and assets management. You will also find total of 26 minutes of music including 4 Indie Underground tracks, complete with custom Player+. <BR><BR>Package size: 42 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Polish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Set in near future, when humans have successfully created powerful space age technology just to find out that we are not all alone out there. You will take part in several top secret missions to destroy enemy installations or defend strategically significant locations. The game is a combination of fast arcade style shooter with basic strategy and resources management. Each level is a self contained environment and can be played in 1st or 3rd person view (except Base Defence). Your success will depend from your space combat skills as well as homebase defence tactics and assets management. You will also find total of 26 minutes of music including 4 Indie Underground tracks, complete with custom Player+. <BR><BR>Package size: 42 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Polish<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Ambientada en un futuro próximo, cuando los seres humanos han creado con éxito una potente tecnología de la era espacial sólo para descubrir que no estamos solos por ahí. Va a participar en varias misiones de alto secreto para destruir instalaciones enemigas o defender ubicaciones estratégicamente importantes. El juego es una combinación de shooter estilo arcade rápido con la estrategia básica y gestión de los recursos. Cada nivel es un entorno independiente y se puede jugar en opinión de la persona primero o tercero (excepto Defensa Base). Su éxito dependerá de tus habilidades de combate espacial, así como tácticas de defensa homebase y gestión de activos. Usted también encontrará total de 26 minutos de música que incluyen 4 pistas Indie Underground, completo con encargo del jugador +. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 42 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Polaco<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Aseta lähitulevaisuudessa, kun ihmiset ovat menestyksekkäästi luonut voimakas avaruusajan teknologiaa vain selvittää, että emme ole yksin siellä. Olet osallistuu useita Top Secret Missions tuhota vihollisen laitoksia tai puolustaa strategisesti merkittävissä.Peli on yhdistelmä nopea arcade tyyli ampujalle perusstrategia ja luonnonvarojen hallinnan. Jokainen taso on itsenäinen ympäristö ja voi pelata ensimmäinen tai kolmas henkilö näkymä (paitsi Base Defence). Sinun menestys riippuu omista tilaa taistella taitoja sekä kotipesä puolustuksen taktiikkaa ja omaisuuden hallintaa. Löydät myös yhteensä 26 minuuttia musiikkia myös 4 Indie Underground kappaletta, jossa on custom-soitin +. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 42 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti/Puola<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Situé dans un futur proche, quand les humains ont réussi à créer une puissante technologie de l'ère spatiale juste de découvrir que nous ne sommes pas tout seul là-bas. Vous prendrez part à plusieurs missions top secret pour détruire les installations ennemies ou défendre des endroits stratégiques importantes. Le jeu est une combinaison de jeu de tir de style arcade rapide avec la stratégie de base et la gestion des ressources.Chaque niveau est un environnement autonome et peut être joué en vue 1ère personne ou 3ème (sauf défense de la base). Votre réussite dépendra de votre espace compétences de combat ainsi que des tactiques de défense homebase et la gestion des actifs.Vous trouverez également total de 26 minutes de musique dont 4 pistes Indie souterrains,complets avec la coutume Player+ <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 42 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Polonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Situé dans un futur proche, quand les humains ont réussi à créer une puissante technologie de l'ère spatiale juste de découvrir que nous ne sommes pas tout seul là-bas. Vous prendrez part à plusieurs missions top secret pour détruire les installations ennemies ou défendre des endroits stratégiques importantes. Le jeu est une combinaison de jeu de tir de style arcade rapide avec la stratégie de base et la gestion des ressources.Chaque niveau est un environnement autonome et peut être joué en vue 1ère personne ou 3ème (sauf défense de la base). Votre réussite dépendra de votre espace compétences de combat ainsi que des tactiques de défense homebase et la gestion des actifs.Vous trouverez également total de 26 minutes de musique dont 4 pistes Indie souterrains,complets avec la coutume Player+ <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 42 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Polonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Situato in un prossimo futuro, quando gli esseri umani hanno creato con successo la potente tecnologia dell'era spaziale solo per scoprire che non siamo solo là fuori. Potrete prendere parte a diverse missioni top secret per distruggere le installazioni nemiche o difendere posizioni strategicamente rilevanti. Il gioco è una combinazione di stile arcade veloce sparatutto con la strategia di base e di gestione delle risorse. Ogni livello è un ambiente autonomo e può essere giocato in prima o terza persona vista (tranne Difesa Base). Il vostro successo dipenderà dalle vostre abilità di combattimento spaziale,nonché le tattiche punto d'appoggio per la difesa e la gestione dei beni. Troverete anche totale di 26 minuti di musica,tra cui 4 brani Indie metropolitana,completi di ordinazione Player+ <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 42 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Polacco<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[近い将来に設定され、人間が成功し、強力な宇宙時代の技術を作成した時にちょうど私達がそこにすべて一人ではないことを見つけるために。あなたは敵のインストールを破壊するか、戦略的に重要な場所を守るために、いくつかの秘密トップのミッションに参加する。ゲームは、基本的な戦略と資源管理と高速なアーケードスタイルのシューティングゲームを組み合わせたものです。各レベルは、自己完結型の環境であり、（ベース防衛を除く）第一または第三者ビューで再生することができます。あなたの成功はあなたの宇宙戦闘スキルだけでなく、本拠地の防衛戦術と資産管理から依存します。また、カスタムプレーヤー+との完全な4インディーズアンダーグラウンドトラックを含む音楽の26分の合計を見つける。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 42 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/ポーランド語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Sett i nær fremtid, når mennesker har opprettet kraftig romalderen teknologi bare for å finne ut at vi ikke er alene der ute. Du vil ta del i flere topp hemmelig oppdrag for å ødelegge fiendens installasjoner eller forsvare strategisk viktige steder. Spillet er en kombinasjon av rask arcade style shooter med grunnleggende strategi og ressurser. Hvert nivå er en selvstendig miljø og kan spilles i første eller tredje person view (unntatt Base Defence). Din suksess vil avhenge av dine plasskampferdigheter samt homebase forsvar taktikk og formuesforvaltning. Du vil også finne totalt 26 minutter med musikk, inkludert fire Indie Underground låter, komplett med tilpassede Player+. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 42 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Polsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Stel in de nabije toekomst, waarin mensen met succes hebt gemaakt krachtige space age technologie om erachter te komen dat we niet helemaal alleen daar. Je neemt deel aan diverse top secret missies om vijandelijke installaties te vernietigen of te verdedigen strategisch belangrijke locaties. Het spel is een combinatie van snelle arcade-stijl shooter met basisstrategie en resources management. Elk niveau is een op zichzelf staand omgeving en kan gespeeld worden in de 1e of 3e person view (behalve Base Defence). Uw succes hangt af van uw ruimte te bestrijden vaardigheden als thuisbasis verdediging tactiek en vermogensbeheer. Ook vindt u in totaal 26 minuten muziek waarvan 4 Indie Underground tracks, compleet met aangepaste Player+. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 42 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels/Pools<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Beläget i en nära framtid, då människan framgångsrikt har skapat kraftfulla rymdåldern teknik bara för att upptäcka att vi inte är helt ensam där ute. Du kommer att delta i flera topp hemligt uppdrag att förstöra fiendens installationer eller försvara strategiskt viktiga platser. Spelet är en kombination av snabb arkad stil skytten med grundläggande strategi och ledning resurser. Varje nivå är en fristående miljö och kan spelas upp i 1: a eller 3: e person view (utom Base Defence). Din framgång beror från dina rymden bekämpa färdigheter samt homebase försvar taktik och ledning tillgångar. Du hittar också totalt 26 minuter musik varav 4 Indie Underground spår, komplett med anpassade Player+. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 42 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska/Polska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 CoderionSoft<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Shooter"/><genre value="Games:Strategy"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_22.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_23.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_24.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
