<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00012_00">

  <appVersion>1.06</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.20</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>148484944</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Der er mangel på mælk i verden, kattene ser sig derfor nødsaget til at søge nye veje for at få deres fix.<BR><BR>Du har samlet et hold af bore-katte, som har overvundet deres frygt for vand, så de kan bore ned under havbunden. Her vil de forsøge at udvinde enorme reserver af noget, der ser ud til at være naturlige dannelser af fuldfed mælk.<BR><BR>Gør dig klar til et tempofyldt spil, hvor du ved hjælp af din u-båd skal beskytte killingerne fra mekaniske hav-monstre der forstyrrer arbejdet.<BR><BR>Mælken skal flyde. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 142 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Durch eine plötzliche Verknappung von Milch, sind Katzen auf der ganzen Welt gezwungen, suchen nach neuen Quellen, um ihre Fix erhalten.<BR><BR>Sie und Ihr Team von Milch Bergbau Kätzchen haben Angst vor dem Wasser, um einen Drilldown unter dem Ozean und Meeresboden beginnen Extrahieren enormen Reserven des scheinbar natürlich bildenden Vollmilch sein, zu überwinden.<BR><BR>Machen Sie sich bereit für schnellen U-Boot-Aktion, die Verteidigung der Kätzchen aus störende mechanische Meeresbewohner.<BR>Die Milch muss fließen! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 142 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Due to a sudden shortage of milk, cats around the world are forced to seek out new sources to get their fix.<BR><BR>You and your team of milk mining kittens have overcome a fear of water to drill down under the ocean seabed and begin extracting vast reserves of what seems to be naturally forming full-fat milk.<BR><BR>Get ready for fast paced submarine action, defending the kittens from disruptive mechanical sea creatures.<BR>The milk must flow! <BR><BR>Package size: 142 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Debido a una repentina escasez de leche, los gatos de todo el mundo se ven obligados a buscar nuevas fuentes para obtener su dosis.<BR><BR>Usted y su equipo de los gatitos de minería de la leche han superado un miedo al agua para ver los detalles bajo el océano y comenzar a extraer las vastas reservas de lo que parece ser de origen natural que forma la leche entera.<BR><BR>¡Prepárate para la acción rápida submarino ritmo, la defensa de los gatitos de los perturbadores criaturas marinas mecánicos.<BR>La leche debe fluir! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 142 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Äkillisen maitopulan takia koko maailman kissat joutuvat etsimään uusia maidonlähteitä lempijuomansa saannin turvaamiseksi.<BR><BR>Sinä ja joukko maitoa metsästäviä kissanpentuja on voittanut vedenpelkonsa ja porautuu valtameren alle ja alkaa pumpata ylös valtavia määriä näemmä luonnon luomaa täysmaitoa.<BR><BR>Valmistaudu vauhdikkaaseen sukellusveneseikkailuun ja suojele kissanpentuja mekaanisten meriolioiden hyökkäyksiltä.<BR>Maitovirtaa ei saa pysäyttää! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 142 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[En raison d'une soudaine pénurie de lait, les chats à travers le monde sont contraints de chercher de nouvelles sources pour obtenir leur dose.<BR><BR>Vous et votre équipe de chatons minières du lait ont surmonté une peur de l'eau pour descendre sous l'océan des fonds marins et de commencer à extraire de vastes réserves de ce qui semble être naturellement formation riche en matière grasse du lait.<BR><BR>Préparez-vous pour l'action sous-marine au rythme rapide, la défense des chatons de perturbateurs créatures marines mécaniques.<BR>Le lait doit couler! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 142 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[A causa di un'improvvisa carenza di latte, i gatti di tutto il mondo sono costretti a cercare nuove fonti.<BR><BR>Tu e la tua squadra di gattini in cerca di latte avete superato la paura dell'acqua per scendere sul fondo dell'oceano e estrarre quello che sembra essere una riserva naturale di latte intero.<BR><BR>Tieniti pronto per una azione rapida sottomarina per difendere i gattini da pericolosissime creature meccaniche marine.<BR>Che latte sia! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 142 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[世界中の猫たちは牛乳の供給不足で大変困っています。<BR>貴方は猫達のミルク採掘チームと水恐怖症を乗り越え、力合わせて海底より地球の自然乳を発見せよ！<BR><BR>故に海の機械生物から猫達の見守りも頼む！<BR>水中に進み潜水艦の多彩なアクションをお楽しみに <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 142 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[På grunn av en plutselig mangel på melk, er katter rundt om i verden tvunget til å oppsøke nye kilder av melk<BR><BR>Du og ditt team av spesial trente kattunger har overvunnet frykten for vann for å bore i havbunnen for å trekke enorme reserver av det som later til å være naturlig dannet helmelk.<BR><BR>Gjør deg klar for fartsfylt ubåt action men husk å forsvar kattungene dine fra mekaniske sjødyr!<BR>Melken må flyte! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 142 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Vanwege een plotseling tekort aan melk, zijn katten wereldwijd genoodzaakt nieuwe bronnen to zoeken om aan hun trekken te komen.<BR><BR>Jij en je team van melk-mijnbouw katjes hebben jullie natuurlijke angst voor water weten to overkomen, om onder de zeebodem te boren naar wat lijkt natuurlijk onstane volle melk!<BR><BR>Zet je schrap voor razend snelle onderzeeër actie, en verdedig de katten tegen de verstorende mechanische zeewezens.<BR>De melk moet vloeien! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 142 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[På grund av en plötslig mjölkbrist, så är katter runtom i världen tvungna att söka efter nya källor som kan tillfredställa deras begär.<BR><BR>Du och dina mjölkbrytarkatter har övervunnit er fruktan för vatten för att borra ner under havsbotten och börja utvinna vad som verkar vara enorma källor av naturligt bildande fullfet mjölk.<BR><BR>Förbered dig för ubåts-action i högt tempo då du försvarar kissarna från de destruktiva mekaniska sjöodjuren.<BR><BR>Mjölken måste flöda! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 142 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012 Tikipod Limited. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Shooter"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
