<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00125_00">

  <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>12336320</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="ja"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Minesweeper ist ein Puzzle-Spiel, das das Netz gibt es keine mir öffnet.<BR>Die Zahlen in der Startaufstellung ist ein Hinweis.<BR><BR>Dieses Spiel können Sie spielen die Schwierigkeit der drei.<BR>   Level 1 Anfänger: 9x9 10 Minen<BR>   Level 2 Intermediate: 16x16 40 Minen<BR>   Level 3 Advanced: 30x16 99 Minen<BR><BR>Sie können die Minesweeper überall genießen jederzeit.<BR><BR>Version 1.0.2<BR>   Anlaufzeit ist schneller.<BR>   Zu Beginn des Spiels gibt es keine Minen in der Umgebung Netz.<BR>   Andere, kleine Modifikation. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 12 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 HEART ART. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Minesweeper is a puzzle game that will open the grid there is no mine.<BR>Numbers in the grid is a hint.<BR><BR>This game, you can play the difficulty of three.<BR>  Level 1 Beginner:      9x 9 10 mines<BR>  Level 2 Intermediate: 16x16 40 mines<BR>  Level 3 Advanced:     30x16 99 mines<BR><BR>You can enjoy the Minesweeper anywhere at any time.<BR><BR>version 1.0.2<BR>  Start-up time is faster.<BR>  At the start of game, there are no mines in the surrounding grid.<BR>  Other, small modification. <BR><BR>Package size: 12 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 HEART ART. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Buscaminas es un juego de puzzle que se abrirá la red no hay minas.<BR>Los números en la red es una pista.<BR><BR>Este juego se puede jugar a la dificultad de tres.<BR>   Nivel 1 Principiante: 9x9 10 minas<BR>   Nivel 2 Intermedio: 16x16 40 minas<BR>   Nivel 3 avanzado: 30x16 99 minas<BR><BR>Usted puede disfrutar del Buscaminas en cualquier lugar en cualquier momento.<BR><BR>versión 1.0.2<BR>   Tiempo de arranque es más rápido.<BR>   Al inicio del juego, no hay minas en la red circundante.<BR>   Otros, pequeña modificación. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 12 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 HEART ART. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Minesweeper est un jeu de puzzle qui va ouvrir la grille il n'est pas le mien.<BR>Numéros dans la grille est un indice.<BR><BR>Ce jeu, vous pouvez jouer la difficulté de trois.<BR>   Niveau 1 Débutant: 9x9 10 mines<BR>   Niveau 2 Intermédiaire: 16x16 40 mines<BR>   Niveau 3 Avancé: 30x16 99 mines<BR><BR>Vous pourrez profiter du Démineur n'importe où à n'importe quel moment.<BR><BR>La version 1.0.2<BR>   Temps de démarrage est plus rapide.<BR>   Au début du jeu, il n'y a pas de mines dans la grille entourant.<BR>   Autre, petite modification. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 12 MB – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 HEART ART. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Minesweeper è un gioco di puzzle che aprirà la griglia non è il mio.<BR>Numeri nella griglia è un suggerimento.<BR><BR>Questo gioco, si può giocare la difficoltà di tre.<BR>   Livello 1 principianti: 9x9 10 miniere<BR>   Livello 2 Intermedio: 16x16 40 miniere<BR>   Livello 3 avanzato: 30x16 99 miniere<BR><BR>Si può godere il Minesweeper ovunque e in qualsiasi momento.<BR><BR>versione 1.0.2<BR>   Tempo di avvio è più veloce.<BR>   All'inizio del gioco, non vi sono miniere della griglia circostanti.<BR>   Altro, piccola modifica. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 12 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 HEART ART. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[マインスイーパは、マスに示された数字を手がかりに、地雷の無いマスを開いていくパズルゲームです。<BR>慣れ親しんだ、初級（9x9:10）、中級（16x16:40）、上級（30x16:99）の３つのレベルを用意しました。<BR>１０位までのクリア時間とプレイ時間が記録されます。<BR>PlayStation®Vitaがあれば、十字キーとボタンで、いつでもどこでもマインスイーパを楽しめます。<BR><BR>■ver1.0.2での変更点<BR>	起動時間が早くなりました。<BR>	ゲーム中の処理落ちを減らしました。<BR>	開始時に、周囲のマスに地雷が無いようになりました。<BR>	その他、細かな修正をしました。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 12 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2013 HEART ART. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
