<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00023_00">
 <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>100774736</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[熊が戻って来た。<br>脳も凍るような全50種のﾊﾟｽﾞﾙ・レベルをポーラーが制覇するのを手伝おう。<br>氷に覆われた不毛の地を、凍った海を、トワイライトの森を抜けて世界の果てまで、そしてオイル・リグに上陸するまで、20時間以上に渡るゲームプレー*。<br>この難しい状況を打破するには、雪、アイス、メタル、そしてダイナマイトのブロックを駆使しよう。各パズルにつきムーブ・ターゲットとタイム・ターゲットを制覇して、ゴールド・スター150個全て集めよう。<br>*-普通の人間一人にかかる時間、ゲームプレイに実際かかった時間は、挑戦しているパズルやプレーヤー本人の忍者術次第で変わります。<br><br>コンテンツ容量:97 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語/日本語/韓国語<br><br>著作権等:<br>© Eiconic Games Limited 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[The bear is back!<br>Help Polar solve all 50 brain-freezing puzzle levels.<br>Over 20 hours of gameplay* spanning the Icy Wastes, across The Frozen Sea, through The Twilight Forest to the Edge of the World and on to the Oil Rig.<br>Use snow, ice, metal and dynamite blocks to crack these conundrums. Achieve the Move and Time targets for each puzzle and collect all 150 Gold Stars.<br> * - number of hours based on a normal human being, actual hours of gameplay may vary depending on the puzzle solving, ninja skills of the player.<br><br>Package size: 97 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese/Korean<br><br>© Eiconic Games Limited 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[L'ours est de retour !<br>Aidez Polar à garder son sang froid pour résoudre les 50 puzzles.<br>Plus de 20 heures de jeu* sur les étendues glacées, par-dessus la mer gelée, à travers la forêt du crépuscule jusqu’au bout du monde et sur une plate-forme pétrolière.<br>Utilisez la neige, la glace, le métal et la dynamite pour résoudre les énigmes. Terminez chaque puzzle selon le temps ou le nombre de coups indiqué et obtenez les 150 étoiles d’or.<br>* - nombre d’heures pour un être humain normal. La durée peut varier en fonction des compétences du joueur à résoudre les puzzles.<br><br>Taille du paquet: 97 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Japonais/Coréen<br><br>© Eiconic Games Limited 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[L'orso è tornato!<br>Aiuto l'orso polare a risolvere 50 livelli di puzzle che ti congeleranno la mente.<br>Più di 20 ore di gioco* durante le quali attraverserai le Distese ghiacciate, il Mare congelato, la Foresta del crepuscolo, fino ad arrivare alla Piattaforma petrolifera.<br>Usa i blocchi di neve, ghiaccio, metallo e dinamite per risolvere gli enigmi. Rispetta il limite di mosse e di tempo per ogni puzzle e raccogli tutte le 150 stelle d'oro.<br>* - numero di ore basato sulle capacità di un normale essere umano, il numero reale di ore di gioco può variare in base all'abilità del giocatore e alla sua capacità di risolvere i puzzle.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 97 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Giapponese/Coreano<br><br>© Eiconic Games Limited 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¡El oso ha vuelto!<br>Ayuda a Polar a resolver 50 niveles de puzles que te dejarán helado.<br>Más de 20 horas de juego* en las que visitarás los Páramos de escarcha, atravesarás el Mar helado y el Bosque crepuscular,  llegarás al Fin del mundo y hasta la Plataforma petrolífera.<br>Usa nieve, hielo, metal y dinamita para resolver los enigmas. Consigue realizar cada puzle dentro del Tiempo y número de Movimientos objetivo para ganar las 150 estrellas de oro.<br>* - número de horas aproximado que le lleva de media a una persona. Las horas de juego totales dependerán de las habilidades ninjas y para resolver puzles y del jugador.<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 97 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Japonés/Coreano<br><br>© Eiconic Games Limited 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Der Bär ist wieder da!<br>Hilf Polar dabei, alle 50 eiskalte Puzzle-Level zu lösen.<br>Über 20 Stunden Spielspaß* in der Eiswüste, auf dem gefrorenen See, dem schummrigen Wald, am Ende der Welt und auf der Bohrinsel.<br>Verwende Schnee-, Eis-, Metall- und Dynamitkisten, um diese Rätsel zu knacken. Löse sie in den wenigsten Zügen und der kürzesten Zeit und sammle alle 150 Goldsterne.<br>* Zeit für einen normal menschlichen Spieler, tatsächliche Spielzeit abhängig von den Ninja-Fähigkeiten des Spielers beim Rätsellösen.<br><br>Paketgröße: 97 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Japanisch/Koreanisch<br><br>© Eiconic Games Limited 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[The bear is back!<br>Help Polar solve all 50 brain-freezing puzzle levels.<br>Over 20 hours of gameplay* spanning the Icy Wastes, across The Frozen Sea, through The Twilight Forest to the Edge of the World and on to the Oil Rig.<br>Use snow, ice, metal and dynamite blocks to crack these conundrums. Achieve the Move and Time targets for each puzzle and collect all 150 Gold Stars.<br> * - number of hours based on a normal human being, actual hours of gameplay may vary depending on the puzzle solving, ninja skills of the player.<br><br>Package size: 97 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese/Korean<br><br>© Eiconic Games Limited 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[L'ours est de retour !<br>Aidez Polar à garder son sang froid pour résoudre les 50 puzzles.<br>Plus de 20 heures de jeu* sur les étendues glacées, par-dessus la mer gelée, à travers la forêt du crépuscule jusqu’au bout du monde et sur une plate-forme pétrolière.<br>Utilisez la neige, la glace, le métal et la dynamite pour résoudre les énigmes. Terminez chaque puzzle selon le temps ou le nombre de coups indiqué et obtenez les 150 étoiles d’or.<br>* - nombre d’heures pour un être humain normal. La durée peut varier en fonction des compétences du joueur à résoudre les puzzles.<br><br>Taille du programme: 97 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Japonais/Coréen<br><br>© Eiconic Games Limited 2012<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Casual"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
