<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00267_00">

  <appVersion>1.10</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>37307664</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Forbered din hjerne på det nyeste kortbaserede hjernevriderspil. Prøv at finde PAIRS og TRIOS eller forsøg at gentage en kortsekvens i SIMON spillet. Tre sjove spil der holder din hjerne igang mens du nyder det fantastiske design... Lås op for og saml de 64 eksklusive veganerkort!<BR><BR>Spilegenskaber:<BR><BR>- 3 forskellige spilleformer: PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON<BR>- 2 nye spilleformer der kan låses op for<BR>- 64 nivauer med øgende sværhedsgrad<BR>- 64 unikke håndtegnede kort der kan låses op og indsamles<BR>- Fantastisk design med ekstrem detaljegrad<BR>- Timevis af sjov og hjernegymnastik<BR>- 8 Sprog: engelsk, spansk, fransk, italiensk, tysk, russisk, japansk og forenklet kinesisk. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 36 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Russisk/Kinesisk - forenklet<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Bereite dein Verstand auf das letzte gedächnistrainierende Kartenspiel vor. Versuche PAARE und TRIOS zu finden oder wiederhole die Kartenreihenfolge in SIMON Spiel. Drei lustige Spiele mit tollem Disign um das Gedächnis zu trainieren…Entsperre und Sammle die 64 exklusiven veganischen Karten!<BR><BR>Spielmerkmale:<BR><BR>- 3 verschiedene Spielmodi: PAARE, TRIOS, SIMON.<BR>- 2 neue Spielmodi freischalten<BR>- 64 Level mit Ansteigender Schwierigkeit <BR>- 64 Einzigartige handgemalte Karten zum Freischalten und Sammeln<BR>- Einmaliges Design mit Qualität bis ins kleinste Detail<BR>- Spaß und mentales Training zur selben Zeit!<BR>- 8 Sprachen: Englisch, Spanisch, Französisch, Italienisch, Deutsch, Russisch, Japanisch, Chinesisch <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 36 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Russisch/Japanisch/Vereinfachtes Chinesisch<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Prepare your Mind for the latest Cards-based Mind-Training. Try to find PAIRS and TRIOS or just try to Repeat a Cards Sequence in SIMON game. Three funny Games to keep your Mind busy while contemplating an Awesome design... Unlock and Collect the 64 exclusive vegan Cards! <BR><BR>Game Features:<BR><BR>- 3 Different Game Modes: PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON<BR>- 2 New Game Modes to Unlock<BR>- 64 Levels to Play with Increasing Difficulty<BR>- 64 Unique Hand-Drawn Cards to Unlock and Collect<BR>- Awesome Design with Extreme Care for Detail<BR>- Hours of Fun and Mind Training<BR>- 8 Languages: English, Spanish, French, Italian, German, Russian, Japanese, Simplified Chinese <BR><BR>Package size: 36 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Russian/Japanese/Simplified Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Prepare your Mind for the latest Cards-based Mind-Training. Try to find PAIRS and TRIOS or just try to Repeat a Cards Sequence in SIMON game. Three funny Games to keep your Mind busy while contemplating an Awesome design... Unlock and Collect the 64 exclusive vegan Cards! <BR><BR>Game Features:<BR><BR>- 3 Different Game Modes: PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON<BR>- 2 New Game Modes to Unlock<BR>- 64 Levels to Play with Increasing Difficulty<BR>- 64 Unique Hand-Drawn Cards to Unlock and Collect<BR>- Awesome Design with Extreme Care for Detail<BR>- Hours of Fun and Mind Training<BR>- 8 Languages: English, Spanish, French, Italian, German, Russian, Japanese, Simplified Chinese <BR><BR>Package size: 36 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Russian/Japanese/Simplified Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Prepare your Mind for the latest Cards-based Mind-Training. Try to find PAIRS and TRIOS or just try to Repeat a Cards Sequence in SIMON game. Three funny Games to keep your Mind busy while contemplating an Awesome design... Unlock and Collect the 64 exclusive vegan Cards! <BR><BR>Game Features:<BR><BR>- 3 Different Game Modes: PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON<BR>- 2 New Game Modes to Unlock<BR>- 64 Levels to Play with Increasing Difficulty<BR>- 64 Unique Hand-Drawn Cards to Unlock and Collect<BR>- Awesome Design with Extreme Care for Detail<BR>- Hours of Fun and Mind Training<BR>- 8 Languages: English, Spanish, French, Italian, German, Russian, Japanese, Simplified Chinese <BR><BR>Package size: 36 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Russian/Japanese/Simplified Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Prepare your Mind for the latest Cards-based Mind-Training. Try to find PAIRS and TRIOS or just try to Repeat a Cards Sequence in SIMON game. Three funny Games to keep your Mind busy while contemplating an Awesome design... Unlock and Collect the 64 exclusive vegan Cards! <BR><BR>Game Features:<BR><BR>- 3 Different Game Modes: PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON<BR>- 2 New Game Modes to Unlock<BR>- 64 Levels to Play with Increasing Difficulty<BR>- 64 Unique Hand-Drawn Cards to Unlock and Collect<BR>- Awesome Design with Extreme Care for Detail<BR>- Hours of Fun and Mind Training<BR>- 8 Languages: English, Spanish, French, Italian, German, Russian, Japanese, Simplified Chinese <BR><BR>Package size: 36 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Russian/Japanese/Simplified Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Prepárate para el último Juego de Entreno Mental basado en Cartas. Intenta encontrar las PAREJAS y TRIOS o repite la Secuencia de Cartas con el juego de SIMON. Tres divertidos Juegos para mantener la Mente en forma mientras contemplas un Atractivo Diseño... Desbloquea y Colecciona las 64 Cartas Veganas Exclusivas! <BR><BR>Características del Juego:<BR><BR>- 3 Modos de Juego Diferentes: PAREJAS, TRIOS, SIMON.<BR>- 2 Nuevos Modos de Juego para Desbloquear<BR>- 64 Niveles de Juego con Dificultad Creciente<BR>- 64 Cartas Únicas, Dibujadas a Mano, para Desbloquear y Coleccionar<BR>- Atractivo Diseño con un Cuidado Extremo del Detalle<BR>- Horas de Diversión y Entreno Mental<BR>- 8 Idiomas: Inglés, Español, Francés, Italiano, Alemán, Ruso, Japonés, Chino <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 36 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Ruso/Japonés/Chino simplificado<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Viritä mielesi uusinta pelikorttipohjaista mielentreenaus peliä varten. Yritä löytää pareja ja kolmosia tai yritä vain toistaa korttien järjestystä SIMON pelimuodossa. Kolme hauskaa peliä, jotka pitävät mielesi virkeänä samalla kun mietiskelet pelin upeaa ulkoasua. Avaa ja kerää kaikki 64 ainutlaatuista vegan korttia.<BR> <BR>Pelin piirteet:<BR> <BR>- 3 erinlaista pelimuotoa: PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON<BR>- 2 uutta pelimuotoa avattavaksi<BR>- 64 vähitellen vaikeutuvaa tadoa<BR>- 64 uniikkia käsin piirrettyjä kortteja avattavaksi ja keräiltäväksi<BR>- Upeat piirteet erityisen hienoilla yksityiskohdilla<BR>- Useiksi tunneiksi hauskuutta ja mielentreenausta<BR>- 8 kieltä: Englanti, Espanja, Ranska, Italia, Saksa, Venäjä, Japani ja yksinkertaistettu Kiina <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 36 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Ranska/Espanja/Saksa/Italia/Venäjä/Kiina - yksinkertaistettu<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Prépare ton Esprit pour le dernier Jeu d’Entraînement Mental basé sur les Cartes. Essaye de trouver les PAIRES et les TRIOS et répète la Séquence de Cartes avec le jeu de Simon. Trois Jeux divertissants pour maintenir l'Esprit en forme en même temps que tu contemples un magnifique design... Débloques et Collectes les 64 Cartes Exclusives !<BR><BR>Caractéristiques du jeu :<BR><BR>- 3 Modes de Jeux Différents : PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON.<BR>- 2 Nouveaux Modes de Jeux pour                 <BR>- 64 Niveaux de Jeu avec Difficulté Croissante<BR>- 64 Cartes Uniques, Dessinées à la Main, pour Débloquer et Collecter   <BR>- Un Design Magnifique avec un Soin Extrême du Détail<BR>- Des Heures d'Amusement et d'Entraînement Mental<BR>- 8 Langues: Anglais, Espagnol, Français, Italien, Allemand, Russe, Japonais, Chinois Simplifié <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 36 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Russe/Japonais/Chinois simplifié<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Prépare ton Esprit pour le dernier Jeu d’Entraînement Mental basé sur les Cartes. Essaye de trouver les PAIRES et les TRIOS et répète la Séquence de Cartes avec le jeu de Simon. Trois Jeux divertissants pour maintenir l'Esprit en forme en même temps que tu contemples un magnifique design... Débloques et Collectes les 64 Cartes Exclusives !<BR><BR>Caractéristiques du jeu :<BR><BR>- 3 Modes de Jeux Différents : PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON.<BR>- 2 Nouveaux Modes de Jeux pour                 <BR>- 64 Niveaux de Jeu avec Difficulté Croissante<BR>- 64 Cartes Uniques, Dessinées à la Main, pour Débloquer et Collecter   <BR>- Un Design Magnifique avec un Soin Extrême du Détail<BR>- Des Heures d'Amusement et d'Entraînement Mental<BR>- 8 Langues: Anglais, Espagnol, Français, Italien, Allemand, Russe, Japonais, Chinois Simplifié <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 36 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Russe/Japonais/Chinois simplifié<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Prepara la tua Mente per l'ultimo gioco di Allenamento Mentale basato su Carte. Tenta di trovare le COPPIE e TRIS o ripette la Sequenza di Carte con il gioco SIMON. Tre divertiti Giochi per tenere la Mente in forma mentre contempli uno Squisito Design... Sblocca e Colleziona le 64 Carte Vegane Esclusive!<BR><BR>Caratteristiche del Gioco:<BR><BR>- 3 Modalità di Gioco Diverse: COPPIE, TRII, SIMON.<BR>- 2 Nuove Modalità di Gioco per Sbloccare<BR>- 64 Livelli di Gioco don Difficoltà Incremetale<BR>- 64 Carte uniche, Disegnate a Mano, per Sbloccare e Collezionare<BR>- Squisito Design con Attenzione Strema per il Dettaglio<BR>- Ore di Divertimento e Allenamento Mentale<BR>- 8 Lingue: Inglese, Spagnolo, Francese, Italiano, Tedesco, Russo, Giapponese, Cinese Semplificato <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 36 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Russo/Giapponese/Cinese semplificato<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>メンタルトレーニングするための最新カードゲームに、心を集中させてみてください。<BR>ペアやトリオのカードを見つけたり、サイモンゲームでカードの配列を繰り返して下さい。<BR>洗練されたデザインを考えながら、あなたの精神を充実させる3つの楽しいゲームです。ロックを解除して64枚のオリジナル野菜カードを集めてみてください！<BR><BR>ゲームの特徴：<BR><BR>- 3種類のゲームモード：ペア、スリー、サイモン<BR>- 2つの新しいゲームモードがロックを解除する<BR>- 難易度がアップしていく64のレベル<BR>- ロックされていない、集める64のカードは手描きで個性的<BR>- 細かいところに気を配った洗練されたデザイン<BR>- 娯楽とメンタルトレーニングの時間<BR>- 8言語：、イタリア語、ドイツ語、ロシア語、日本語、英語、スペイン語、フランス語、中国語（簡体字） <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 36 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語/ロシア語/日本語/中国語(簡体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Forbered deg på det siste av Kort basert hjernetrim. Prøv å finne par og trios Eller bare repeter en kort kombinasjon i  Simon spillet. Tre morsome spill for å underholde deg mens du betrakter det stilige designe.... Åpne og samle 64 eksklusive vegan Kort.<BR><BR>Spillet inneholder:<BR><BR>- 3 forskjellige spill moduser: Pairs, trios, simon.<BR>- 2 nye spill moduser som åpnes<BR>- 64 nivåer å spille med økende vannskelighetsgrad<BR>- 64 unike hånd- trukkede kort å åpne og samle.<BR>- Stilig design med ekstremt fokus på detaljer.<BR>- timer med moro og hjernetrim.<BR>- 8 Språk: Engelsk, Spansk, Fransk, Italiensk, Tysk, Russisk, Japansk, forenklet Kinesisk. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 36 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Russisk/Kinesisk - Forenklet<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Bereid je brein voor op de nieuwste mind-training gebaseerd op kaarten. Probeer PAIRS en TRIOS te vinden of probeer een reeks kaarten te herhalen in het SIMON spel. Drie leuke spelletjes met een geweldige vormgeving om je brein bezig te houden... Ontgrendel en verzamel de 64 exclusieve vegan kaarten.<BR><BR>Eigenschappen van het spel:<BR><BR>- 3 verschillende spelmodi: PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON<BR>- 2 nieuwe spelmodi om te ontgrendelen<BR>- 64 niveaus om te spelen met oplopende moeilijkheid<BR>- 64 unieke handgetekende kaarten om te ontgrendelen en verzamelen<BR>- Ontzagwekkend ontwerp met extreem oog voor detail<BR>- Uren plezier en mind-training<BR>- 8 talen: Engels, Spaans, Frans, Italiaans, Duits, Russisch, Japans, vereenvoudigd Chinees <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 36 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Frans/Spaans/Duits/Italiaans/Russisch/Chinees - Vereenvoudigd<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Przygotuj się na zlożony z kart trening umysłu ostatnich dni. Spróbuj odnaleźć PAIRy i TRIOTy albo poprostu powtórz sekwencję SIMONów. Trzy zabawne gry aby ćwiczyć umysł i podziwiać super grafikę gry... Odblokuj i skolekcjonuj ekskluzywne wegańskie Karty!<BR> <BR>Charakterystyki gry:<BR><BR>- 3 różne Moduły Gry: PAIRS, TRIOS, SIMON<BR>- 2 nowe nowe moduły do odblokowania<BR>- 64 poziomy gry o o rosnącej trudności<BR>- 64 oryginalne ręecznie rysowane karty, aby odblokować i zgromadzić<BR>- Niesamowita grafika, wykonana z dbałością o każdy najmniejszy szczegół<BR>- Godziny rozrywki i treningu umysłu<BR>- 8 języków: angielski, hiszpański, francuski, włoski, niemiecki, rosyjski, japoński, uproszczony chiński <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 36 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Niemiecki/Angielski/Angielski/Hiszpański/Francuski/Włoski/Japoński/Rosyjski/Chiński - uproszczony<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Förbered ditt Sinne inför den senaste kortbaserade sinnes-träningen. Försök hitta PAR och TRIO eller upprepa helt enkelt en sekvens av kort i SIMON spelet. Tre roliga spel för att hålla ditt Sinne upptaget medan du beundrar en fantastisk design… Upplås och samla de 64 exklusiva vegana korten!<BR><BR>Spelets särdrag:<BR><BR>-	3 olika Spel former: PAR, TRIO, SIMON<BR>-	2 nya Spel former att upplåsa<BR>-	64 nivåer med ökande svårhet<BR>-	64 unika handmålade kort att upplåsa och samla<BR>-	Fantastisk design med extrem omsorg för detaljer<BR>-	Timmar av sinnes-träning och nöje<BR>-	8 språk: Engelska, Spanska, Franska, Italienska, Tyska, Ryska, Japanska, Enkel Kinesiska <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 36 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Franska/Spanska/Tyska/Italienska/Ryska/Kinesiska - förenklad<BR><BR>Copyright (c) 2015 emegeme. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:BrainTraining"/><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
