<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00140_00">

  <appVersion>1.04</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>16996992</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather, din vejr hjælper på PlayStation(R)Vita, gør det nemt for dig at tjekke vejret i hele verden. <BR><BR>Discription: <BR>Hjem, eller i udlandet, du ønsker at tjekke vejr med din PlayStation(R)Vita? <BR>SolaWeather gøre det muligt for dig at tjekke vejret på PlayStation(R)Vita, gør du nyder din tid med PlayStation(R)Vita. <BR><BR>funktion: <BR>- Skærm (Display vejr i dag, og vejret i de kommende tre dage) <BR>- Søg (Indtast navn City, og få vejret der) <BR>- Clean (Rens sider i SolaWeather, gør du være på det sted, du søgte, og fri dit sind) <BR>- Let (SolaWeather er let at bruge for dig at tjekke vejr) <BR><BR>Feedback: <BR>Send venligst din feedback til: support@devpss.com <BR>Vi vil svare på din feedback og håndtere problemerne ASAP. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 17 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Kamera<BR>- Positionsdata<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - forenklet/Kinesisk - traditionelt<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Kleiner Hilfer vom Wetter auf PlayStation(R)Vita kann Ihnen leichte Abfrage geben.<BR><BR>Produktbeschreibung:<BR>Wenn Sie zu Hause spielen oder reisen, möchtest du durch PlayStation(R)Vita das Wetter abfragen？ SolaWeather macht es möglich, das Wetter auf PlayStation(R)Vita zu überprüfen. Dann PlayStation(R)Vita will bessere Integration in Ihrem Leben geben.<BR><BR>Produkteigenschaften:<BR>- Wetteranzeige (Startseite zeigt das aktuelle Wetter und das Wetter von den nächsten drei Tagen)<BR>- Unterstützungsabfragen (Einfache Eingabe den Namen einer Stadt, wird die Wetterbedingungen weltweit da)<BR>- Bedienung ist bequem, einfach und übersichtlich und leicht gelernt. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 17 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Kamera<BR>- Standortdaten<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch/Vereinfachtes Chinesisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather, your weather helper on PlayStation(R)Vita, make it easy for you to check the weather worldwide.<BR><BR>Discription:<BR>Home, or abroad, you want to check weather with your PlayStation(R)Vita?<BR>SolaWeather make it possible for you to check weather on PlayStation(R)Vita, making you enjoy your time with PlayStation(R)Vita.<BR><BR>Feature:<BR>- Display(Display weather today, and weather in future three days)<BR>- Search(Type in City name, and get the weather there)<BR>- Clean(Clean pages in SolaWeather, make you be in the place you searched, and free your mind)<BR>- Easy(SolaWeather is easy to use for you to check weather)<BR><BR>Feedback:<BR>Please send your feedback to:support@devpss.com<BR>We will respond to your feedback and deal with the problems asap. <BR><BR>Package size: 17 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR>- Location Data<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather, your weather helper on PlayStation(R)Vita, make it easy for you to check the weather worldwide.<BR><BR>Discription:<BR>Home, or abroad, you want to check weather with your PlayStation(R)Vita?<BR>SolaWeather make it possible for you to check weather on PlayStation(R)Vita, making you enjoy your time with PlayStation(R)Vita.<BR><BR>Feature:<BR>- Display(Display weather today, and weather in future three days)<BR>- Search(Type in City name, and get the weather there)<BR>- Clean(Clean pages in SolaWeather, make you be in the place you searched, and free your mind)<BR>- Easy(SolaWeather is easy to use for you to check weather)<BR><BR>Feedback:<BR>Please send your feedback to:support@devpss.com<BR>We will respond to your feedback and deal with the problems asap. <BR><BR>Package size: 17 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR>- Location Data<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather, your weather helper on PlayStation(R)Vita, make it easy for you to check the weather worldwide.<BR><BR>Discription:<BR>Home, or abroad, you want to check weather with your PlayStation(R)Vita?<BR>SolaWeather make it possible for you to check weather on PlayStation(R)Vita, making you enjoy your time with PlayStation(R)Vita.<BR><BR>Feature:<BR>- Display(Display weather today, and weather in future three days)<BR>- Search(Type in City name, and get the weather there)<BR>- Clean(Clean pages in SolaWeather, make you be in the place you searched, and free your mind)<BR>- Easy(SolaWeather is easy to use for you to check weather)<BR><BR>Feedback:<BR>Please send your feedback to:support@devpss.com<BR>We will respond to your feedback and deal with the problems asap. <BR><BR>Package size: 17 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR>- Location Data<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather, your weather helper on PlayStation(R)Vita, make it easy for you to check the weather worldwide.<BR><BR>Discription:<BR>Home, or abroad, you want to check weather with your PlayStation(R)Vita?<BR>SolaWeather make it possible for you to check weather on PlayStation(R)Vita, making you enjoy your time with PlayStation(R)Vita.<BR><BR>Feature:<BR>- Display(Display weather today, and weather in future three days)<BR>- Search(Type in City name, and get the weather there)<BR>- Clean(Clean pages in SolaWeather, make you be in the place you searched, and free your mind)<BR>- Easy(SolaWeather is easy to use for you to check weather)<BR><BR>Feedback:<BR>Please send your feedback to:support@devpss.com<BR>We will respond to your feedback and deal with the problems asap. <BR><BR>Package size: 17 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR>- Location Data<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Puede ver el tiempo de cualquiera ciudad con el pequeño ayudante del tiempo en PlayStation(R)Vita. <BR><BR>¿Quiere ver el tiempo a traves de PlayStation(R)Vita cuando está jugando en casa o en viaje? Puede ver el tiempo en PlayStation(R)Vita con SolaWeather que puede integrar mejor a tu vida. <BR><BR>- Mostrar el tiempo(Inicio muestra el tiempo actual y el tiempo de los próximos tres días) <BR>- Apoyar la búsqueda (puede conocer la situación del tiempo del mundo sólo escribe el nombre de la ciudad fácilmente)<BR>- Fácil de operar (Las operaciones son simple y más claras,es muy fácil de operarla.) <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 17 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Cámara<BR>- Datos de ubicación<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés/Chino simplificado/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather, sää auttaja PlayStation (R) Vita, helpottavat voit tarkistaa sää maailmanlaajuisesti. <BR><BR>discription: <BR>Kotona tai ulkomailla, haluat tarkistaa sää PlayStation (R) Vita? <BR>SolaWeather mahdollistavat voit tarkistaa sää PlayStation (R) Vita, joten viihdyt PlayStation (R) Vita. <BR><BR>ominaisuus: <BR>- Näyttö (Display sää tänään, ja sää tulevaksi kolmen päivän kuluessa) <BR>- Haku (Kirjoita kaupungin nimi, ja saat sää siellä) <BR>- Clean (Puhdista sivuja SolaWeather, tehdä sinusta olla paikka etsinyt, ja vapaa mieli) <BR>- Easy (SolaWeather on helppokäyttöinen voit tarkistaa sää) <BR><BR>Palaute: <BR>Lähetä palautteesi osoitteeseen: support@devpss.com <BR>Vastaamme palautetta ja käsitellä ongelmia asap. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 17 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Kamera<BR>- Sijaintitiedot<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Kiina - yksinkertaistettu/Kiina - perinteinen<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather dans PlayStation(R)Vita vous permet de savoir le météo de n’importe quelle ville.<BR><BR>Voulez-vous consulter la prévision de météo via PlayStation(R)Vita lors que vous jouez un jeu chez vous ou en voyage? Sola Weather vous vous permet le réaliser dans PlayStation(R)Vita à tout moment et PlayStation(R)Vita devient une partie indispensable de votre vie.<BR><BR>-  Affichage météo (sur le premier page, s’affichent le météo du jour présent et celui des 3 jours avenir)<BR>-  Consultation (entrer le nom de ville, vous pour vous informer les météos de toutes les localités dans le monde)<BR>-  Facile de manipuler  (le procédé n’est pas difficile donc c’est facile de le manipuler) <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 17 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Appareil photo<BR>- Données géographiques<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather dans PlayStation(R)Vita vous permet de savoir le météo de n’importe quelle ville.<BR><BR>Voulez-vous consulter la prévision de météo via PlayStation(R)Vita lors que vous jouez un jeu chez vous ou en voyage? Sola Weather vous vous permet le réaliser dans PlayStation(R)Vita à tout moment et PlayStation(R)Vita devient une partie indispensable de votre vie.<BR><BR>-  Affichage météo (sur le premier page, s’affichent le météo du jour présent et celui des 3 jours avenir)<BR>-  Consultation (entrer le nom de ville, vous pour vous informer les météos de toutes les localités dans le monde)<BR>-  Facile de manipuler  (le procédé n’est pas difficile donc c’est facile de le manipuler) <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 17 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Appareil photo<BR>- Données géographiques<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Il meteo assistente di ‘PlayStation(R)Vita’, ti facilita le informazioni sulle condizioni meteorologiche di qualsiasi città.<BR><BR>Vuoi informarti ”che tempo fa” tramite ‘PlayStation(R)Vita’ mentre giocando games a casa oppure viaggiando per la strada? SOLA WEATHER ti facilita le informazioni sul meteo su ‘PlayStation(R)Vita’, e te lo integra meglio nella tua PlayStation(R)Vita quotidiana.<BR><BR>- Previsione meteo ( Home visualizza il tempo corrente e il tempo dei prossimi tre giorni)<BR>- Cerca località (digitare i nomi delle città e saprai le condizioni meteorologiche nel tutto il mondo)<BR>- Facile da usare (Funzionamento semplice e chiaro, più accessibile.) <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 17 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Fotocamera<BR>- Dati sulla posizione<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese/Cinese semplificato/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[PlayStation(R)Vitaの気象アシスタントではあらゆる都市のお天気を便利に調べることができます。<BR>製品説明：<BR>御宅でゲームをするとき、旅行をするとき、PlayStation(R)Vitaでお天気を調べたいですか？”知天気”を利用してPlayStation(R)Vitaでお天気をリアルタイムに調べることができます。<BR><BR>製品特色:<BR>-天気表示（ホームには現時点および未来３日の天気を表示しています）<BR>-検索対応（市名を入力して検索するだけで、世界中の気象情報が分かります）<BR>-簡単なインターフェース (さっぱりインターフェース、記録の時、気持ちも良くなります)<BR>-簡単な操作 ( 簡単ではっきりしている操作は更に便利になります)<BR><BR>製品フィードバック<BR>製品に対するご提案には、support@devpss.comに送ってください。できるだけ早く問題を処理して返事いたします。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 17 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- カメラ<BR>- 位置データ<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語/中国語(簡体字)/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather, din vær hjelper på PlayStation (R) Vita, gjør det enkelt for deg å sjekke været over hele verden. <BR><BR>Discription: <BR>Hjem, eller i utlandet, vil du sjekke været med din PlayStation (R) Vita? <BR>SolaWeather gjør det mulig for deg å sjekke været på PlayStation (R) Vita, noe som gjør at du nyte din tid med PlayStation (R) Vita. <BR><BR>Feature: <BR>- Skjerm (Display vær i dag, og været i fremtidige tre dager) <BR>- Søk (Type i byen navn, og få været der) <BR>- Clean (Rengjør sider i SolaWeather, gjør du være på det stedet du søkte, og Free Your Mind) <BR>- Easy (SolaWeather er lett å bruke for deg å sjekke vær) <BR><BR>Tilbakemelding: <BR>Vennligst send din tilbakemelding til: support@devpss.com <BR>Vi vil svare på din tilbakemelding og håndtere problemene ASAP. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 17 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kamera<BR>- Posisjonsdata<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - Forenklet/Kinesisk - Tradisjonell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather, je weer helper op PlayStation (R) Vita, maken het gemakkelijk voor u om het weer over de hele wereld te controleren. <BR><BR>Omschrijving: <BR>Thuis, of in het buitenland, wilt u weer met uw PlayStation (R) Vita? <BR>SolaWeather maken het mogelijk voor u om weer te checken op de PlayStation (R) Vita, waardoor u genieten van uw tijd met PlayStation (R) Vita. <BR><BR>feature: <BR>- Scherm (Display weer vandaag, en het weer in de toekomst drie dagen) <BR>- Zoeken (Type in naam van de stad, en krijg het weer daar) <BR>- Clean (Clean pagina's in SolaWeather, maak je in de plaats die u zocht, en gratis je geest) <BR>- Gemakkelijk (SolaWeather is gemakkelijk te gebruiken voor u om weer te checken) <BR><BR>feedback: <BR>Stuur uw feedback naar: support@devpss.com <BR>We zullen reageren op uw feedback en omgaan met de problemen <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 17 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR>- Locatiedata<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Chinees - Vereenvoudigd/Chinees - Traditioneel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[SolaWeather, din väder hjälpare på PlayStation (R) Vita, gör det enkelt för dig att kolla vädret i hela världen. <BR><BR>Discription: <BR>Home, eller utomlands, vill du kolla vädret med din PlayStation (R) Vita? <BR>SolaWeather gör det möjligt för dig att kolla vädret på PlayStation (R) Vita, vilket gör att du njuta av din tid med PlayStation (R) Vita. <BR><BR>Feature: <BR>- Display (Display väder i dag, och vädret i kommande tre dagar) <BR>- Sökning (Skriv in namn stad, och få vädret där) <BR>- Rengör (Clean sidor i SolaWeather, gör du på den plats du sökt, och befria dig) <BR>- Easy (SolaWeather är lätt att använda för dig att kolla vädret) <BR><BR>Återkoppling: <BR>Vänligen skicka dina synpunkter till: support@devpss.com <BR>Vi kommer att besvara din feedback och ta itu med de problem asap. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 17 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Kamera<BR>- Platsdata<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Kinesiska - förenklad/Kinesiska - traditionell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Weather"/><genre value="Apps:Utilities"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
