<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00203_00">

  <appVersion>3.32</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>229278096</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>• Udforsk i første person til at fortsætte i rædselshistorie.<BR>• Med 2D anime manga stil karakter kunst og 3D-miljøer.<BR>• styre to karakterer DIS og Sui, se hvordan deres historie forbinder.<BR>• Mørk, grynet omgivelser og uhyggelige lydeffekter til atmosfærisk gameplay.<BR>• Retro indie horror, med en historie til at dræbe for.<BR><BR>DiS og Vigil er to venner, der besøger den hjemsøgt hus. Besøg den oprindelige gerningssted med Police pige Sui, løse og se, hvordan hun er involveret med historien! Har hun været skjuler noget, er DIS Sui og Vigil tilsluttet en eller anden måde?<BR><BR>v3.32<BR>Oversættelser forbedret, kapitel 4 tilføjede, rettelser og forbedringer og meget mere! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 219 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Tysk/Italiensk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>• Entdecken Sie in der ersten Person in der Horrorgeschichte fort.<BR>• Mit 2D anime manga Stil Zeichenkunst und 3D-Umgebungen.<BR>• Steuer zwei Zeichen, DiS und Sui, zu sehen, wie ihre Geschichte verbindet.<BR>• Dunkle, düstere und unheimliche Umgebung Audio-Effekte für atmosphärische Gameplay.<BR>• Retro Indie Horror, mit einer Geschichte, um zu töten.<BR><BR>DiS und Vigil sind zwei Freunde, die das Geisterhaus zu besuchen. Besuchen Sie die Original-Tatort mit Polizei-Mädchen Sui, zu lösen und zu sehen, wie sie mit der Geschichte beteiligt ist! Hat sie etwas zu verbergen, sind DiS, Sui und Vigil irgendwie miteinander verbunden?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Übersetzungen verbessert, Kapitel 4 aufgenommen, Korrekturen und Verbesserungen und vieles mehr! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 219 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Französisch/Italienisch/Japanisch<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>• Explore in first person to proceed in the horror story. <BR>• Featuring 2D anime manga style character art and 3D environments. <BR>• Control two characters, DiS and Sui, see how their story connects. <BR>• Dark, gritty surroundings and eerie audio effects for atmospheric gameplay. <BR>• Retro indie horror, with a story to kill for. <BR><BR>DiS and Vigil are two friends who visit the haunted house. Visit the original crime scene with Police girl Sui, solve and see how she is involved with the story! Has she been hiding something, are DiS, Sui and Vigil connected somehow?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Translations improved, Chapter 4 added, fixes and improvements and much more! <BR><BR>Package size: 219 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>• Explore in first person to proceed in the horror story. <BR>• Featuring 2D anime manga style character art and 3D environments. <BR>• Control two characters, DiS and Sui, see how their story connects. <BR>• Dark, gritty surroundings and eerie audio effects for atmospheric gameplay. <BR>• Retro indie horror, with a story to kill for. <BR><BR>DiS and Vigil are two friends who visit the haunted house. Visit the original crime scene with Police girl Sui, solve and see how she is involved with the story! Has she been hiding something, are DiS, Sui and Vigil connected somehow?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Translations improved, Chapter 4 added, fixes and improvements and much more! <BR><BR>Package size: 219 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>• Explore in first person to proceed in the horror story. <BR>• Featuring 2D anime manga style character art and 3D environments. <BR>• Control two characters, DiS and Sui, see how their story connects. <BR>• Dark, gritty surroundings and eerie audio effects for atmospheric gameplay. <BR>• Retro indie horror, with a story to kill for. <BR><BR>DiS and Vigil are two friends who visit the haunted house. Visit the original crime scene with Police girl Sui, solve and see how she is involved with the story! Has she been hiding something, are DiS, Sui and Vigil connected somehow?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Translations improved, Chapter 4 added, fixes and improvements and much more! <BR><BR>Package size: 219 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>• Explore in first person to proceed in the horror story. <BR>• Featuring 2D anime manga style character art and 3D environments. <BR>• Control two characters, DiS and Sui, see how their story connects. <BR>• Dark, gritty surroundings and eerie audio effects for atmospheric gameplay. <BR>• Retro indie horror, with a story to kill for. <BR><BR>DiS and Vigil are two friends who visit the haunted house. Visit the original crime scene with Police girl Sui, solve and see how she is involved with the story! Has she been hiding something, are DiS, Sui and Vigil connected somehow?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Translations improved, Chapter 4 added, fixes and improvements and much more! <BR><BR>Package size: 219 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/French/Italian/Japanese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>• Explorar en primera persona para proceder en la historia de terror.<BR>• Atracción de arte de carácter estilo manga anime 2D y escenarios en 3D.<BR>• Control de dos personajes, Dis y Sui, ver cómo se conecta su historia.<BR>• Oscura, un entorno arenoso y efectos de audio espeluznantes para jugabilidad atmosférica.<BR>• terror indie retro, con una historia para matar.<BR><BR>Dis y vigilia son dos amigos que visitan la casa embrujada. Visita la escena del crimen original con muchacha de la policía Sui, resolver y ver cómo ella está involucrada con la historia! Ella ha estado ocultando algo, se DiS, Sui y Vigilia conectados de alguna manera?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Traducciones mejoraron, Capítulo 4 añadido, correcciones y mejoras y mucho más! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 219 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Francés/Italiano/Japonés<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>• Tutki ensimmäinen henkilö edetä kauhutarina.<BR>• Mukana 2D anime manga hahmojen taidetta ja 3D ympäristöissä.<BR>• Ohjaus kaksi merkkiä, DiS ja Sui, miten heidän tarinansa yhdistää.<BR>• Tumma, karu ympäristö ja aavemainen äänitehosteita ilmakehän pelattavuus.<BR>• Retro indie kauhu, jossa tarina tappaa varten.<BR><BR>DiS ja Vigil kaksi ystäviä, jotka vierailevat kummitustalo. Käy alkuperäinen rikospaikalta kanssa Poliisi tyttö Sui, ratkaista ja nähdä, miten hän on mukana tarina! Onko hän ollut piilossa jotain, ovat DiS, Sui ja Vigil kytketty jotenkin?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Käännökset parantunut, luku 4 lisätty, korjauksia ja parannuksia ja paljon muuta! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 219 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Ranska/Saksa/Italia<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>• Explorer à la première personne de procéder dans l'histoire d'horreur.<BR>• Doté d'un caractère art 2D de style manga anime et les environnements 3D.<BR>• Contrôle deux personnages, le DIS et Sui, voir comment leur histoire se connecte.<BR>• sombres, environnement rudes et effets audio étranges pour gameplay atmosphérique.<BR>• horreur indie rétro, avec une histoire à tuer pour.<BR><BR>Dis et Vigil sont deux amis qui visitent la maison hantée. Visitez la scène du crime d'origine avec une fille de la police Sui, de résoudre et de voir comment elle est impliquée avec l'histoire! At-elle été cachait quelque chose, sont DiS, Sui et Vigil connectés en quelque sorte?<BR><BR>v3.32<BR>Traductions améliorées, Chapitre 4 ajoutée, corrections et améliorations et bien plus encore! <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 219 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Français/Italien/Japonais<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>• Explorer à la première personne de procéder dans l'histoire d'horreur.<BR>• Doté d'un caractère art 2D de style manga anime et les environnements 3D.<BR>• Contrôle deux personnages, le DIS et Sui, voir comment leur histoire se connecte.<BR>• sombres, environnement rudes et effets audio étranges pour gameplay atmosphérique.<BR>• horreur indie rétro, avec une histoire à tuer pour.<BR><BR>Dis et Vigil sont deux amis qui visitent la maison hantée. Visitez la scène du crime d'origine avec une fille de la police Sui, de résoudre et de voir comment elle est impliquée avec l'histoire! At-elle été cachait quelque chose, sont DiS, Sui et Vigil connectés en quelque sorte?<BR><BR>v3.32<BR>Traductions améliorées, Chapitre 4 ajoutée, corrections et améliorations et bien plus encore! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 219 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Français/Italien/Japonais<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>• Esplora in prima persona per procedere nella storia dell'orrore.<BR>• Con 2D anime stile manga arte carattere e ambienti 3D.<BR>• Controllo di due personaggi, DiS e Sui, vedere come la loro storia si connette.<BR>• scuri, un ambiente grintoso ed effetti audio inquietanti per gameplay atmosferica.<BR>• Retro orrore indie, con una storia di uccidere per.<BR><BR>DiS e Vigil sono due amici che visitano la casa stregata. Visita la scena del crimine originale con Polizia ragazza Sui, risolvere e vedere come lei è coinvolta con la storia! Lei è stato nascosto qualcosa, sono DiS, Sui e Vigil collegati in qualche modo?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Traduzioni migliorate, capitolo 4 ha aggiunto, correzioni e miglioramenti e molto altro ancora! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 219 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Francese/Italiano/Giapponese<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>•ホラーストーリーで進行する最初の人に紹介します。<BR>•特長2Dアニメマンガスタイルの文字アートや3D環境。<BR>•制御二つの文字、DISと隋は、彼らの物語が接続する方法を参照してください。<BR>•ダーク、砂のような環境と大気のゲームプレイのための不気味なオーディオエフェクト。<BR>•のために殺すためにストーリーを持つレトロなインディーホラー、。<BR><BR>DISとビジルは、お化け屋敷を訪れる2友人です。 、警察の女の子隋とオリジナルの犯罪現場を訪れ解決し、彼女は物語に関与しているかを見る！ DIS、隋とビジルが何らかの形で接続されている彼女は、何かを隠していませんか？<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>翻訳は、第4章が追加され、修正や改良とはるかに改善された！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 219 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/フランス語/イタリア語/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>• Utforsk i første personen til å fortsette i skrekkhistorie.<BR>• Med 2D anime manga stil karakter kunst og 3D-miljøer.<BR>• Kontroll to tegn, DiS og Sui, se hvordan deres historie kobler.<BR>• Mørke, skitne omgivelser og uhyggelige lydeffekter for atmosfærisk gameplay.<BR>• Retro indie horror, med en historie å drepe for.<BR><BR>DiS og Vigil er to venner som besøker det hjemsøkte huset. Besøk den opprinnelige åstedet med Politiet jente Sui, løse og se hvordan hun er involvert med historien! Har hun skjuler noe, er DiS, Sui og Vigil tilkoblet en eller annen måte?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Oversettelser forbedret, kapittel 4 til, fikser og forbedringer og mye mer! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 219 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Tysk/Italiensk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>• Ontdek in de eerste persoon om verder te gaan in de horror verhaal.<BR>• Met 2D anime manga stijl karakter kunst en 3D-omgevingen.<BR>• Controle twee personages, DiS en Sui, zie hoe hun verhaal met elkaar verbindt.<BR>• Donkere, zanderige omgeving en griezelige audio-effecten voor atmosferische gameplay.<BR>• Retro indie horror, met een verhaal om te doden voor.<BR><BR>DiS en Vigil zijn twee vrienden die het spookhuis te bezoeken. Bezoek de oorspronkelijke delict met politie meisje Sui, op te lossen en te zien hoe ze zich bezig met het verhaal! Heeft ze iets te verbergen, zijn DiS, Sui en Vigil verbonden of andere manier?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Vertalingen verbeterd, hoofdstuk 4 toegevoegd, fixes en verbeteringen en nog veel meer! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 219 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Frans/Duits/Italiaans<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>• Przeglądaj w pierwszej osobie postępować w horror.<BR>• Wyposażony w stylu manga anime 2D charakter sztuki i środowisk 3D.<BR>• Kontrola dwa znaki, Sui DiS, zobaczyć, jak ich historia łączy.<BR>• Ciemne, piaszczysty otoczenie i mroczne efekty dźwiękowe dla gry atmosferycznego.<BR>• Retro indie horror, z historią zabić za.<BR><BR>DiS i czuwanie są dwaj przyjaciele, którzy odwiedzają Nawiedzony dom. Odwiedź oryginalną miejsce zbrodni z dziewczyną Policja Sui, rozwiązać i zobaczyć, jak ona jest zaangażowana w historii! Czy ona ukrywa coś, są DiS Sui i czuwanie połączone w jakiś sposób?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Tłumaczenia poprawie, Rozdział 4 dodaje, poprawki i ulepszenia i wiele więcej! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 219 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Niemiecki/Angielski/Angielski/Francuski/Włoski/Japoński<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>• Utforska i första personen att gå vidare i skräckhistoria.<BR>• Med 2D anime mangastil teckenkonst och 3D-miljöer.<BR>• Kontroll två karaktärer, DiS och Sui, se hur deras berättelse ansluter.<BR>• Mörka, tråkiga omgivningar och kusliga ljudeffekter för atmosfär gameplay.<BR>• Retro indie skräck, med en historia att döda för.<BR><BR>DiS och Vigil är två vänner som besöker spökhus. Besök den ursprungliga brottsplatsen med polisen flicka Sui, lösa och se hur hon är involverad med berättelsen! Har hon varit döljer något, är DiS, Sui och Vigil anslutna något sätt?<BR><BR>V3.32<BR>Översättningar förbättrats, kapitel 4 tillade, korrigeringar och förbättringar och mycket mer! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 219 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Franska/Tyska/Italienska<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Horror"/><genre value="Games:RPG"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
