<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00028_00">
 <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>42758848</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[Surge は、独自の構造・深い戦略・オンラインスコアを備えた、癖になるタイル・マッチング・ゲームで、ハラハラドキドキさせてくれます！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:41 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語<br><br>著作権等:<br>Surge © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Surge takes addictive tile matching gameplay and implants a hardcore pulse with unique mechanics, strategic depth and online scores! A new energy source provides humanity with enormous electrical power, but by-product materials build up fast, and must be constantly cleared to keep pressure levels in check. Shatter the dangerous by-products by routing electrical surges between matching block types, and then vent pressure in huge blasts! Surge puts sizzling electrical energy at your fingertips!<br><br>Package size: 41 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Surge © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Surge propose une expérience de jeu addictive et unique basée sur les correspondances, agrémentée de stratégie et de scores en ligne ! L'humanité dispose d'une nouvelle source d'énergie électrique, mais les résidus qui s'accumulent doivent être évacués afin de garder les niveaux de pression sous contrôle. Supprimez les résidus dangereux en faisant circuler des vagues d'énergie entre les blocs similaires et activez les soupapes de pression ! Avec Surge, maîtrisez l'énergie du bout des doigts !<br><br>Taille du paquet: 41 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Surge © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Surge trasforma il gameplay di abbinamento tessere con meccaniche esclusive, intensità strategica e punteggi online! L'umanità produce elettricità grazie a una nuova fonte di energia, ma i materiali residui si addensano rapidamente e i livelli di tensione vanno tenuti sotto controllo. Distruggi i pericolosi residui deviando le sovratensioni elettriche attraverso blocchi dello stesso tipo ed espelli la tensione in grandiose esplosioni. Con Surge, l'energia elettrica passa attraverso le tue dita!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 41 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano<br><br>Surge © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¡Surge mejora el ya adictivo sistema de combinación de casillas usando mecánicas únicas, profundidad estratégica y puntuaciones online!  Una nueva fuente de energía otorga a la humanidad una increíble potencia eléctrica, pero los subproductos se acumulan y deben ser eliminados constantemente para mantener los niveles de presión... ¡Destrúyelos creando oleadas eléctricas entre tipos de bloques iguales y descarga la presión en potentes ráfagas! ¡Siente cómo crepita la energía eléctrica con Surge!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 41 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano<br><br>Surge © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Surge vereint das süchtig machende Gameplay von Matching-Games mit einzigartigen Spielmechaniken, neuer Dynamik, strategischer Tiefe und Online-Bestenlisten! Eine neue Energiequelle versorgt die Menschheit mit Elektrizität, aber Nebenprodukte sammeln sich rasch an und müssen entfernt werden, damit sich nicht zu viel Druck aufbaut. Zerstöre die gefährlichen Nebenprodukte, indem du elektrische Impulse zu gleichen Blöcken leitest und lasse dann über die Ventile Druck ab! Surge – knisternde Energie!<br><br>Paketgröße: 41 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch<br><br>Surge © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Surge takes addictive tile matching gameplay and implants a hardcore pulse with unique mechanics, strategic depth and online scores! A new energy source provides humanity with enormous electrical power, but by-product materials build up fast, and must be constantly cleared to keep pressure levels in check. Shatter the dangerous by-products by routing electrical surges between matching block types, and then vent pressure in huge blasts! Surge puts sizzling electrical energy at your fingertips!<br><br>Package size: 41 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Surge © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Surge propose une expérience de jeu addictive et unique basée sur les correspondances, agrémentée de stratégie et de scores en ligne ! L'humanité dispose d'une nouvelle source d'énergie électrique, mais les résidus qui s'accumulent doivent être évacués afin de garder les niveaux de pression sous contrôle. Supprimez les résidus dangereux en faisant circuler des vagues d'énergie entre les blocs similaires et activez les soupapes de pression ! Avec Surge, maîtrisez l'énergie du bout des doigts !<br><br>Taille du programme: 41 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Surge © 2012 FuturLab Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Casual"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Online.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
