<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00227_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>31290048</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="de"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Flyv med Flappy retro , en lille fugl i frihed og ikke røre de hindringer .<BR><BR>En parodi på nummer 1 hit spil!<BR><BR>På grund af den udfordrende vanskeligheden ved Flappy Retro bestemt ikke keder sig og konkurrere med dine venner med din high score !<BR><BR>Den enkle kontrol selv de mindste børn er i Flappy Retro på din bekostning.<BR><BR>Kom og spil Flappy Retro hjælpe ham til at lære at flyve med sine små vinger .<BR><BR>Funktioner af Flappy Retro :<BR><BR>+ Simple kontroller ( trykke på skærmen for at flyve )<BR>+ Vanedannende gameplay<BR>+ En af de bedste Afslappet og top arcade spil<BR>+ Endless Level<BR>+ Let noobmode<BR>+ Overbyde din highscore<BR>+ Unikt design<BR>+ Simple kontroller ( one-touch kontrol : Type flagrer rundt vingen lad ) <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 30 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Fliege mit Flappy Retro, einem kleinen Vogel, in die Freiheit und berühre die Hindernisse nicht.<BR><BR>Eine Parodie des Nr. 1 Spiele Hit!<BR><BR>Durch den herausfordernden Schwierigkeitsgrad von Flappy Retro kommt bestimmt keine Langeweile auf und miss dich mit deinen Freunden mit deinem Highscore!<BR><BR>Durch die einfache Steuerung kommen auch die kleinsten Kinder bei Flappy Retro auf Ihre Kosten.<BR><BR>Komm und spiel Flappy Retro und hilf ihm dabei mit seinen kleinen Flügeln fliegen zu lernen.<BR><BR>Features von Flappy Retro:<BR><BR>+ Einfache Steuerung (berühre den Touchscreen um zu fliegen)<BR>+ Süchtig machendes Spielprinzip<BR>+ Eines der besten Gelegenheitsspiele sowie top Arcadespiele<BR>+ Endloses Level<BR>+ Einfacher Noobmode<BR>+ Überbiete deinen Highscore<BR>+ Einzigartiges Design<BR>+ Einfache Steuerung (One-Touch-Steuerung) <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 30 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Fly with Flappy retro , a little bird in the freedom and do not touch the obstacles.<BR><BR>A parody of the Number 1 hit game !<BR><BR>Due to the challenging difficulty of Flappy Retro determined will not be bored and compete with your friends with your high score!<BR><BR>The simple control even the smallest children are at Flappy Retro at your expense.<BR><BR>Come and play Flappy Retro helping him to learn to fly with his little wings.<BR><BR>Features of Flappy Retro:<BR><BR>+ Simple controls ( touch the screen to fly )<BR>+ Addictive gameplay<BR>+ One of the best Casual and top arcade games<BR>+ Endless Level<BR>+ Easy noobmode<BR>+ Outbid your highscore<BR>+ Unique design <BR><BR>Package size: 30 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Vuela con retro Flappy , un pajarito en la libertad y no toque los obstáculos.<BR><BR>Una parodia del exitoso juego número 1 !<BR><BR>Debido a la dificultad desafiante de Flappy Retro determinado no se aburrirá y competir con sus amigos con su puntuación más alta!<BR><BR>El control de simples hasta los niños más pequeños son en Flappy retro a su cargo.<BR><BR>Ven a jugar Flappy Retro ayudándole a aprender a volar con sus pequeñas alas .<BR><BR>Características de Flappy Retro :<BR><BR>+ Controles sencillos ( tocar la pantalla para volar)<BR>+ Adictivo juego<BR>+ Uno de los mejores juegos de arcade y superior<BR>+ Nivel Endless<BR>+ Noobmode Fácil<BR>+ Sobrepujado su puntuación más alta<BR>+ El diseño único<BR>+ Los sencillos controle <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 30 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Fly kanssa Flappy retro ,pieni lintuvapauden ja eivät kosketaesteitä .<BR><BR>ParodiaNumber 1 osuma pelin !<BR><BR>Johtuenhaastava vaikeus Flappy Retro määräytyy ole tylsää ja kilpailla ystävillesi ennätyksen!<BR><BR>Yksinkertainen ohjaus pienimmätkin lapset ovat Flappy Retro omalla kustannuksellaan .<BR><BR>Tule ja pelaa Flappy Retro auttaa häntä oppia lentämään hänen pikku siivet .<BR><BR>Ominaisuudet Flappy Retro :<BR><BR>+ Yksinkertainen valvonta ( koskettamalla näyttöä lentää )<BR>+ Addictive pelattavuus<BR>+ Yksi parhaista Casual ja top arcade -pelejä<BR>+ Endless Level<BR>+ Helppo noobmode<BR>+ Ylitä huipputulos<BR>+ Ainutlaatuinen muotoilu<BR>+ Yksinkertainen valvonta ( Yksi- kosketussäätimet : tyyppi säröt ympärisiipi anna )<BR>+ Häiriötekijöitä peli <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 30 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Volez avec Flappy rétro , un petit oiseau dans la liberté et de ne pas toucher les obstacles .<BR><BR>Une parodie de la numéro 1 jeu à succès!<BR><BR>En raison de la difficulté du défi Flappy Retro déterminée ne seront pas ennuyer et de rivaliser avec vos amis avec votre meilleur score !<BR><BR>Le contrôle simple, même les plus petits enfants sont à Flappy rétro à vos frais .<BR><BR>Venez jouer Flappy Retro l'aider à apprendre à voler avec ses petites ailes .<BR><BR>Caractéristiques de Flappy Retro :<BR><BR>+ Des commandes simples ( touchez l'écran pour voler)<BR>+ Gameplay addictif<BR>+ Un des meilleurs jeux d'arcade occasionnels et supérieur<BR>+ Niveau sans fin<BR>+ Noobmode Facile <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 30 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Vola con Flappy retrò , un uccellino nella libertà e non toccare gli ostacoli .<BR><BR>Una parodia del gioco numero 1 hit !<BR><BR>A causa della difficoltà impegnativo Flappy Retro determinato non ci si annoia e competere con i tuoi amici con il punteggio più alto !<BR><BR>Il semplice controllo anche i bambini più piccoli sono a Flappy Retro a vostre spese .<BR><BR>Vieni a giocare Flappy Retro aiutandolo a imparare a volare con le sue piccole ali .<BR><BR>Caratteristiche di Flappy Retro :<BR><BR>+ Comandi semplici ( toccare lo schermo per volare )<BR>+ Gameplay Addictive<BR>+ Uno dei migliori giochi arcade casual e superiore<BR>+ Level Endless<BR>+ Noobmode Facile<BR>+ Superata tuo record<BR>+ Design unico <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 30 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>ゆるいレトロ、自由で小鳥を飛ぶと障害物に触れないでください。<BR><BR>ナンバー1ヒットゲームのパロディ！<BR><BR>により決定されゆるいレトロの挑戦的な難しさに退屈されず、あなたのハイスコアでお友達と競争！<BR><BR>簡単な制御であっても、最小の子どもたちは、あなたの費用でゆるいレトロである。<BR><BR>是非、彼は彼の小さな翼で飛ぶことを学ぶに貢献ゆるいレトロを果たしている。<BR><BR>ゆるいレトロの特徴：<BR><BR>+シンプルなコントロールが（飛ぶために画面をタッチ）<BR>+習慣性のgameplay<BR>最高のカジュアルとトップアーケードゲームの+ One<BR>+エンドレスレベル<BR>+簡単noobmode<BR>+あなたのハイスコアを高値<BR>+ユニークなデザイン<BR>+シンプルなコントロール（ワンタッチコントロール：翼はせまわりタイプフラッター）<BR>+気晴らしのゲーム <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 30 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Fly med Flappy retro, en liten fugl i frihet og ikke berøre hindringer .<BR><BR>En parodi på nummer 1 hit spillet !<BR><BR>På grunn av den utfordrende problemer av Flappy Retro bestemt vil ikke bli lei og konkurrere med vennene dine med din høy score!<BR><BR>Den enkle kontroll selv de minste barna er i Flappy Retro på din bekostning .<BR><BR>Komme og spille Flappy Retro hjelpe ham å lære å fly med sine små vinger .<BR><BR>Funksjoner av Flappy Retro :<BR><BR>+ Enkle kontroller ( berøre skjermen for å fly )<BR>+ Vanedannende gameplay<BR>+ En av de beste Casual og topp arkadespill<BR>+ Endless nivå<BR>+ Enkel noobmode<BR>+ Overby din highscore<BR>+ Unik design<BR>+ Enkle kontroller ( ett- touch-kontroller : type flagre rundt vingen la )<BR>+ Distraksjoner spill <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 30 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Vlieg met Flappy retro , een vogeltje in de vrijheid en niet de obstakels niet aanraken .<BR><BR>Een parodie van de nummer 1 hit spel!<BR><BR>Als gevolg van de uitdagende moeilijkheidsgraad van Flappy Retro bepaald niet te vervelen en concurreren met je vrienden met uw hoge score !<BR><BR>De eenvoudige bediening , zelfs de kleinste kinderen zijn op Flappy Retro op uw kosten.<BR><BR>Kom en speel Flappy Retro helpt hem om te leren vliegen met zijn kleine vleugels.<BR><BR>Kenmerken van Flappy Retro :<BR><BR>+ Eenvoudige bediening ( raak het scherm om te vliegen )<BR>+ Verslavende gameplay<BR>+ Een van de beste Casual en top arcade games<BR>+ Eindeloos Niveau<BR>+ Makkelijk noobmode<BR>+ Overbieden je highscore<BR>+ Uniek ontwerp <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 30 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Leć z Flappy retro, mały ptak na wolności i nie dotykać przeszkód .<BR><BR>Parodią przebojowej gry Ilość 1 !<BR><BR>Z powodu trudnej trudności Flappy Retro ustalona nie będzie się nudzić i konkurować ze swoimi przyjaciółmi z wysoki wynik !<BR><BR>Proste sterowanie nawet najmniejsze dzieci są w Flappy Retro Twoim kosztem.<BR><BR>Przyjdź i grać flappy Retro pomaga mu nauczyć się latać z jego małych skrzydeł .<BR><BR>Cechy Flappy Retro :<BR><BR>+ Proste sterowanie ( dotknij ekranu, aby latać )<BR>+ Wciągająca fabuła<BR>+ Jeden z najlepszych zwykłych i najlepszych gier arcade<BR>+ Kompletne Poziom<BR>+ Łatwy noobmode<BR>+ Przebitym swój wynik<BR>+ Unikalny projekt<BR>+ Proste sterowanie ( jedno- przyciski dotykowe : Typ trzepotanie wokółskrzydła pozwalają <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 30 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Flyg med Flappy retro , en liten fågel i frihet och inte röra de hinder .<BR><BR>En parodi av Number 1 succéspelet !<BR><BR>På grund av den utmanande svårigheten att Flappy Retro bestäms inte att bli uttråkad och tävla med dina vänner med din höga poäng !<BR><BR>Den enkla kontroll även de minsta barnen är på Flappy Retro på din bekostnad .<BR><BR>Kom och spela Flappy Retro hjälpa honom att lära sig att flyga med sina små vingar .<BR><BR>Dragen av Flappy Retro :<BR><BR>+ Enkla kontroller ( peka på skärmen för att flyga )<BR>+ Beroendeframkallande gameplay<BR>+ En av de bästa Casual och topp arkadspel<BR>+ Ändlös Nivå<BR>+ Enkel noobmode<BR>+ Bjud över din highscore<BR>+ Unik design<BR>+ Enkla kontroller ( snabbvalskontroller: typ fladder runt vingen låt ) <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 30 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Casual"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
