<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00289_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>113968272</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Fremskyndelse. Langsommere. Dreje til venstre. Dreje til højre. Disse er blot fire af de spændende ting du kan gøre i Åh, Deer !, den nye kørespil fra Necrosoft Games. Du er en familie på vej til mormors hus - men vejen er oversvømmet med hjorte! Hvad skal man gøre !? Valget er i dine hænder. Vil du være et forbillede, og undgå dem alle, eller en maverick, græsslåning alt ned i din vej? Du vil grine, du vil græde, vil du drive din stationcar. Og måske kan du lære bare lidt noget om dig selv i processen.<BR><BR>Få det nu før butikken forsvinder! Denne tekst blev oversat fra engelsk af en dum maskine, sorry! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 109 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Portugisisk/Portugisisk/Russisk/Polsk/Finsk/Dansk/Norsk/Svensk/Koreansk/Kinesisk - forenklet/Kinesisk - traditionelt<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Beschleunigen. Verlangsamen. Links abbiegen. Rechts abbiegen. Das sind nur vier der spannenden Dinge, die Sie in Oh, Deer !, dem neuen Rennspiel von Necrosoft Spiele machen kann. Sie sind eine Familie auf dem Weg zum Haus ihrer Großmutter - aber der Weg ist mit Reh überschwemmt! Was zu tun ist !? Die Auswahl ist in Ihren Händen. Willst du ein Vorbild sein, und vermeiden Sie sie alle, oder ein Einzelgänger, mäht alles in Ihrem Weg? Du wirst lachen, du wirst weinen, du wirst deine Kombi driften. Und vielleicht werden Sie nur ein wenig etwas über sich selbst in den Prozess zu lernen.<BR><BR>Jetzt, bevor der Laden verschwindet! Dieser Text wurde aus dem Englischen durch eine dumme Maschine übersetzt, sorry! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 109 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Dänisch/Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Niederländisch/Norwegisch/Polnisch/Portugiesisch(Portugal)/Portugiesisch(Brasilien)/Russisch/Finnisch/Schwedisch/Japanisch/Koreanisch/Vereinfachtes Chinesisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Speeding up. Slowing down. Turning left. Turning right. These are just four of the exciting things you can do in Oh, Deer!, the new driving game from Necrosoft Games. You're a family on your way to grandma's house – but the road is flooded with deer! What to do!? The choice is in your hands. Will you be a paragon, and avoid them all, or a maverick, mowing down everything in your path? You'll laugh, you'll cry, you'll drift your station wagon. And maybe you'll learn just a little something about yourself in the process. <BR><BR>Get it now before the store disappears! <BR><BR>Package size: 109 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Polish/Portuguese(Portugal)/Portuguese(Brazil)/Russian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese/Korean/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Speeding up. Slowing down. Turning left. Turning right. These are just four of the exciting things you can do in Oh, Deer!, the new driving game from Necrosoft Games. You're a family on your way to grandma's house – but the road is flooded with deer! What to do!? The choice is in your hands. Will you be a paragon, and avoid them all, or a maverick, mowing down everything in your path? You'll laugh, you'll cry, you'll drift your station wagon. And maybe you'll learn just a little something about yourself in the process. <BR><BR>Get it now before the store disappears! <BR><BR>Package size: 109 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Polish/Portuguese(Portugal)/Portuguese(Brazil)/Russian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese/Korean/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Speeding up. Slowing down. Turning left. Turning right. These are just four of the exciting things you can do in Oh, Deer!, the new driving game from Necrosoft Games. You're a family on your way to grandma's house – but the road is flooded with deer! What to do!? The choice is in your hands. Will you be a paragon, and avoid them all, or a maverick, mowing down everything in your path? You'll laugh, you'll cry, you'll drift your station wagon. And maybe you'll learn just a little something about yourself in the process. <BR><BR>Get it now before the store disappears! <BR><BR>Package size: 109 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Polish/Portuguese(Portugal)/Portuguese(Brazil)/Russian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese/Korean/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Speeding up. Slowing down. Turning left. Turning right. These are just four of the exciting things you can do in Oh, Deer!, the new driving game from Necrosoft Games. You're a family on your way to grandma's house – but the road is flooded with deer! What to do!? The choice is in your hands. Will you be a paragon, and avoid them all, or a maverick, mowing down everything in your path? You'll laugh, you'll cry, you'll drift your station wagon. And maybe you'll learn just a little something about yourself in the process. <BR><BR>Get it now before the store disappears! <BR><BR>Package size: 109 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Polish/Portuguese(Portugal)/Portuguese(Brazil)/Russian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese/Korean/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Acelerando. Disminuir la velocidad. Girando a la izquierda. Girando a la derecha. Estos son sólo cuatro de las cosas interesantes que usted puede hacer en Oh, Deer!, el nuevo juego de conducción de Necrosoft Games. Juegan como una familia en su camino a casa de la abuela - pero el camino está inundado con los ciervos! Que hacer !? La elección está en sus manos. ¿Va a ser un dechado, y evitar todos ellos, o un inconformista, derribando todo a tu paso? Te vas a reír, te grito, se le deriva a su camioneta. Y tal vez usted aprenderá un poco algo sobre ti mismo en el proceso.<BR><BR>Consíguelo ahora antes de que desaparezca la tienda! Esto se tradujo del Inglés por una máquina estúpida, lo siento! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 109 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Danés/Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Holandés/Noruego/Polaco/Portugués(Portugal)/Portugués(Brasil)/Ruso/Finlandés/Sueco/Japonés/Coreano/Chino simplificado/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Nopeuttaminen. Hidastumassa. Kääntyy vasemmalle. Kääntyy oikealle. Nämä ovat vain neljä jännittäviä asioita voit tehdä Oh, Deer !, uuden ajo peli Necrosoft Games. Olet perhe matkalla isoäidin talon - mutta tie on tulvinut hirvi! Mitä tehdä !?Valinta on sinun käsissäsi. Aiotteko olla esikuva, ja välttää niitä kaikkia, tai Maverick, niitto alas kaiken teidän tiellä? Saat nauraa, voit itkeä, voit ajelehtia oman farmari. Ja ehkä opit hieman jotain itsestäsi prosessissa.<BR><BR>Hanki se nyt ennen myymälässä katoaa! Tämä teksti on käännetty Englanti on tyhmä kone, sorry! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 109 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Ranska/Espanja/Saksa/Italia/Hollanti/Portugali/Portugali/Venäjä/Puola/Suomi/Tanska/Norja/Ruotsi/Korea/Kiina - yksinkertaistettu/Kiina - perinteinen<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Accélérant. Ralentir. En tournant à gauche. En tournant à droite. Ce ne sont que quatre des choses passionnantes que vous pouvez faire dans Oh, cerf !, le nouveau jeu de conduite de Necrosoft Jeux. Vous êtes une famille sur votre chemin à la maison de grand-mère - mais la route est inondée avec des cerfs! Que faire !? Le choix est entre vos mains. Serez-vous un parangon, et de les éviter tous, ou un franc-tireur, fauchant tout sur votre chemin? Vous allez rire, vous allez pleurer, vous dérivez votre station wagon. Et peut-être vous apprendrez juste un petit quelque chose sur vous-même dans le processus.<BR><BR>Téléchargez avant le magasin disparaît! Ce texte a été traduit de l'anglais par une machine stupide, désolé! <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 109 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Danois/Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Néerlandais/Norvégien/Polonais/Portugais(Portugal)/Portugais(Brésil)/Russe/Finnois/Suédois/Japonais/Coréen/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Accélérant. Ralentir. En tournant à gauche. En tournant à droite. Ce ne sont que quatre des choses passionnantes que vous pouvez faire dans Oh, cerf !, le nouveau jeu de conduite de Necrosoft Jeux. Vous êtes une famille sur votre chemin à la maison de grand-mère - mais la route est inondée avec des cerfs! Que faire !? Le choix est entre vos mains. Serez-vous un parangon, et de les éviter tous, ou un franc-tireur, fauchant tout sur votre chemin? Vous allez rire, vous allez pleurer, vous dérivez votre station wagon. Et peut-être vous apprendrez juste un petit quelque chose sur vous-même dans le processus.<BR><BR>Téléchargez avant le magasin disparaît! Ce texte a été traduit de l'anglais par une machine stupide, désolé! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 109 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Danois/Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Néerlandais/Norvégien/Polonais/Portugais(Portugal)/Portugais(Brésil)/Russe/Finnois/Suédois/Japonais/Coréen/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Accelerare. Rallentare. Svoltando a sinistra. Svoltando a destra. Questi sono solo quattro delle cose interessanti che si possono fare in Oh, Deer !, il nuovo gioco di guida da Necrosoft Games. Siete una famiglia sulla buona strada per casa della nonna - ma la strada è allagata con cervi! Cosa fare !? La scelta è nelle vostre mani. Sarai un paragon, ed evitarli tutti, o un cane sciolto, falciando tutto nel tuo percorso? Potrai ridere, ti grido, ti deriva tuo station wagon. E forse imparerete solo un po 'qualcosa di te nel processo.<BR><BR>Scaricalo ora prima il negozio scompare! Questo testo è stato tradotto da Inglese da una macchina stupida, mi spiace! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 109 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Danese/Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Olandese/Norvegese/Polacco/Portoghese(Portogallo)/Portoghese(Brasile)/Russo/Finlandese/Svedese/Giapponese/Coreano/Cinese semplificato/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>高速化。減速。左折。右折。これらはあなたがああ、鹿!, Necrosoft Gamesから新しいドライビングゲームで行うことができますエキサイティングなもののわずか4です。あなたはおばあちゃんの家にあなたの方法で家族をしている - しかし、道は鹿が殺到しています！何をすべきか!?選択はあなたの手の中にあります。あなたが模範であり、あなたのパスにすべてのものを下刈り、それらをすべて、または異端を避けるためだろうか？あなたは、あなたのステーションワゴンドリフトよ、あなたが泣くよ、笑うでしょう。そして多分あなたは、プロセス内の自分自身について少しだけ何かを学びます。<BR><BR>ストアが消える前に今それを入手！このテキストは愚かな機械で、英語から翻訳された、申し訳ありません！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 109 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>デンマーク語/ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語/オランダ語/ノルウェー語/ポーランド語/ポルトガル語(ポルトガル)/ポルトガル語(ブラジル)/ロシア語/フィンランド語/スウェーデン語/日本語/韓国語/中国語(簡体字)/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Påskynde. Bremse ned. Svinge til venstre. Svinge mot høyre. Dette er bare fire av de spennende tingene du kan gjøre i Oh, Deer !, den nye bilspill fra Necrosoft Games. Du er en familie på vei til bestemors hus - men veien er oversvømmet med hjort! Hva å gjøre !? Valget er i dine hender. Vil du være en Paragon, og unngå dem alle, eller en Maverick, klippe ned alt på din vei? Du vil le, du vil gråte, vil du drive din stasjonsvogn. Og kanskje du vil lære litt noe om deg selv i prosessen.<BR><BR>Få det nå før butikken forsvinner! Denne teksten ble oversatt fra engelsk av en dum maskin, sorry! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 109 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Portugisisk/Portugisisk/Russisk/Polsk/Finsk/Dansk/Norsk/Svensk/Koreansk/Kinesisk - Forenklet/Kinesisk - Tradisjonell<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Versnellen. Vertragen. Linksaf. Rechtsaf. Dit zijn slechts vier van de spannende dingen die je kunt doen in Oh, Herten !, de nieuwe rij-spel van Necrosoft Games. Je bent een gezin op weg naar het huis van oma's - maar de weg wordt overspoeld met herten! Wat te doen !? De keuze ligt in jouw handen. Zult u een toonbeeld te zijn, en te voorkomen dat ze allemaal, of een buitenbeentje, maaien alles op wat op je pad? Je zult lachen, je zult huilen, u zult uw stationwagon drift. En misschien leer je gewoon een beetje iets over jezelf in het proces.<BR><BR>Nu voordat de winkel verdwijnt! Deze tekst is vertaald uit het Engels door een domme machine, sorry! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 109 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Frans/Spaans/Duits/Italiaans/Nederlands/Portugees/Portugees/Russisch/Pools/Fins/Deens/Noors/Zweeds/Koreaans/Chinees - Vereenvoudigd/Chinees - Traditioneel<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Przyspieszać. Spowolnienie. Skręcając w lewo. Skręcając w prawo. To tylko cztery z ekscytujących rzeczy, które możesz zrobić w Och, Deer !, nowej grze jazdy od Necrosoft Games. Jesteś rodziny w drodze do babci - ale droga jest zalana jelenia! Co robić !?Wybór jest w Twoich rękach. Będzie paragon i unikać ich wszystkich, lub Maverick, koszenie dół wszystko na swojej drodze? Będziesz się śmiać, będziesz płakać, będziemy dryfować swój kombi. A może nauczysz się tylko trochę coś o sobie w tym procesie.<BR><BR>Pobierz teraz, zanim zniknie sklep! Ten tekst został przetłumaczony z języka angielskiego przez głupią maszyną, przepraszam! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 109 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Duński/Niemiecki/Angielski/Angielski/Hiszpański/Fiński/Francuski/Włoski/Japoński/Koreański/Norweski/Holenderski/Polski/Portugalski/Portugalski/Rosyjski/Szwedzki/Chiński - uproszczony/Chiński - tradycyjny<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Snabbare. Saktar ner. Svänga vänster. Turning höger. Dessa är bara fyra av de spännande saker du kan göra i Oh, Deer !, den nya bilspel från Necrosoft Games. Du är en familj på väg till mormors hus - men vägen är översvämmad med rådjur! Vad ska man göra !? Valet är i dina händer. Kommer du att vara en förebild, och undvika dem alla, eller en ensamvarg, meja ner allt i din väg? Du kommer att skratta, du kommer att gråta, du driver ditt kombi. Och kanske får du lära dig bara en liten sak om dig själv i processen.<BR><BR>Hämta nu innan butiken försvinner! Denna text har översatts från engelska av en dum maskin, sorry! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 109 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Franska/Spanska/Tyska/Italienska/Holländska/Portugisiska/Portugisiska/Ryska/Polska/Finska/Danska/Norska/Svenska/Koreanska/Kinesiska - förenklad/Kinesiska - traditionell<BR><BR>Copyright 2015 Necrosoft Games<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Racing"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
