<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00009_00">
 <appVersion>1.10</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>19769632</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[家族で外出した際の食事をどうするか？<br>彼女を帰したくない夜に引き留める？<br>禁煙への決意が定まらないあなたに･･･<br>そんな悩める瞬間に、白と黒２匹のクマが判断を下してくれます。<br><br>また、グループ活動で不公平なくチーム分けたい時や、<br>決まらない宴会の幹事を決めたい時など、大人数でのニーズにもバッチリ対応。<br>もちろん、永遠のライバルとの因縁も、一対一のバトルで白黒をガッツリつけます。<br><br>コンテンツ容量:19 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1-16人<br>オンラインマルチプレイ:2人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語/日本語<br><br>著作権等:<br>Copyright (C) 2012 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Where do you go when you want to eat out with your family?<br>Do you stop your girlfriend from going home when you want her to stay for the night?<br>Are you not sure if you want to quit smoking or not?<br>All these questions can be answered by a black and a white bear.<br><br>This app can also be used if you want to make fairly divided teams for group activities, <br>or if you want to decide who's going to organize a party.<br>And of course it will also help you decide who's really best: <br>You or your eternal rival?<br><br>Package size: 19 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1-16Player(S)<br>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2 Players)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Vas-tu souvent au restaurant avec ta famille ?<br>Empêches-tu ton/ta copain/copine de rentrer quand tu veux passer la nuit avec lui/elle ?<br>Penses-tu arrêter de fumer ou non ?<br>Toutes ces questions ont une réponse avec un ours noir ou blanc. <br><br>Cette application peut aussi être utilisée si tu veux faire des équipes plutôt divisées pour des activités de groupes,<br>ou si tu veux décider qui va organiser une soirée.<br>Évidemment, elle t'aidera aussi à décider qui est vraiment le/la meilleur(e) :<br>toi, ou ton éternel(le) rival(e) ?<br><br>Taille du paquet: 19 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1-16joueur(s)<br>Assistance en ligne pour jeu multijoueur : Oui (2 joueurs)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Japonais<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Dove ti piace andare con la tua famiglia?<br>Come è il tuo rapporto di coppia?<br>Vuoi davvero smettere di fumare?<br>A queste ed altre domande puoi rispondere con un orso nero od un orso bianco.<br><br>Puoi utilizzare questa applicazione anche per creare team per attività di gruppo.<br>O andare a divertirti con gli amici.<br>E finalmente il migliore tra tutti verrà deciso: tu od il tuo acerrimo rivale?<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 19 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1-16giocatore/i<br>Supporto giochi multiplayer online: Sì (2 giocatori)<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Giapponese<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¿A dónde vas cuando quieres comer afuera con tu familia?<br>¿Detienes a tu novia de irse a su casa cuando quieres que se quede en la tuya?<br>¿No estás seguro que quieres dejar de fumar?<br>Todas estas preguntas pueden ser respondidas con un cuestionario.<br><br>Esta aplicación puede ser utilizada si quieres dividir equipos para actividades de grupo,<br>o si quieres decidir quién va a organizar la fiesta.<br>Además, te ayudará a decidir quién es el mejor: <br>¿Tú o tu eterno rival?<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 19 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1-16jugador(es)<br>Asistencia para juegos de varios jugadores en línea: Sí (2 jugador(es))<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Japonés<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Wohin gehst du mit deiner Familie essen?<br>Hältst du deinen Partner davon auf, aufzubrechen, wenn er/sie über Nacht bleiben soll?<br>Bist du dir nicht sicher, ob du mit dem Rauchen aufhören sollst?<br>All diese Fragen können von einem schwarzen und einem weißen Bären beantwortet werden.<br><br>Diese App kann also verwendet werden, wenn du eine Gruppe in passende Teams aufteilen möchtest,<br>oder wenn du entscheiden möchtest, wer eine Party organisieren soll.<br>Und natürlich wird sie dir auch helfen, herauszufinden wer wirklich der Beste ist:<br>Du oder dein größter Rivale?<br><br>Paketgröße: 19 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1-16Spieler<br>Online-Unterstützung für Multiplayer-Spiel: Ja (2 Spieler)<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Japanisch<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Vas-tu souvent au restaurant avec ta famille ?<br>Empêches-tu ton/ta copain/copine de rentrer quand tu veux passer la nuit avec lui/elle ?<br>Penses-tu arrêter de fumer ou non ?<br>Toutes ces questions ont une réponse avec un ours noir ou blanc. <br><br>Cette application peut aussi être utilisée si tu veux faire des équipes plutôt divisées pour des activités de groupes,<br>ou si tu veux décider qui va organiser une soirée.<br>Évidemment, elle t'aidera aussi à décider qui est vraiment le/la meilleur(e) :<br>toi, ou ton éternel(le) rival(e) ?<br><br>Taille du programme: 19 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1-16joueur(s)<br>Mode multijoueur en ligne : Oui (2 joueurs)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Japonais<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Party"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Online.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
