<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00102_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>24386992</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Die unendlichen Weiten des Weltraums.<BR><BR>Du bist ein Planet, der gerade erst entstanden ist.<BR><BR>Unglücklicherweise haben es ein paar angrifflustige Planeten auf dich abgesehen.<BR><BR>Du kannst dich nur wehren, indem du dich auf sie "stürzt".<BR><BR>Nehme Beschleunigung auf und ramme die feindlichen Planeten!<BR><BR>Besonderheiten:<BR><BR>- Einfache Steuerung<BR>  Benutze den Analogstick, um zu beschleunigen/abzubremsen und Feinde zu rammen.<BR><BR>- Einfache Regeln<BR>  Um Schaden auszuteilen, musst du nur eine höhere Geschwindigkeit als deine Feinde haben, wenn du sie rammst.<BR>  Zerstöre alle feindlichen Planeten in einem Gebiet, um die nächste Stufe zu erreichen.<BR><BR>- Zweispieler-Modus<BR>  Ihr könnt auch zu zweit gegeneinander antreten. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 24 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1-2 Spieler<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright 2012 Tomonori Misawa<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[This is the vast expanse of space.<BR><BR>You are a planet that has only just come into existence.<BR><BR>Unfortunately, some troublemaking planets are attacking you.<BR><BR>The only way you can fight back is by "crashing" into them.<BR><BR>Now, gather up speed and slam into those enemy planets!<BR><BR>Features:<BR><BR>- Simple controls<BR>  Use the analogue stick to accelerate/decelerate and crash into enemies.<BR><BR>- Simple Rules<BR>  All you need to do to deal damage is to gain a higher speed than your enemies when crashing into them.<BR>  Destroy all the enemy planets in an area to clear the stage.<BR><BR>- 2 Player Mode<BR>  You can play competitively with 2 players. <BR><BR>Package size: 24 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1-2 Players<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2012 Tomonori Misawa<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Este es un vasto e inmenso universo.<BR><BR>Eres un planeta que acaba de nacer.<BR><BR>Desafortunadamente, algunos planetas gamberras te están atacando.<BR><BR>Y la única forma de contraatacar es "chocando" en con estos.<BR><BR>¡Ahora, acelera y choca contra estos planetas enemigos!<BR><BR>Características:<BR><BR>- Controles simples<BR>  Utiliza el joystick análogo para acelerar/desacelerar y chocar contra los enemigos.<BR><BR>- Reglas simples<BR>  Todo lo que necesitas para hacer daño es acelerar más rápido que tus enemigos y chocar en contra de ellos.<BR>  Destruye todos los planetas enemigos en una zona para terminar el nivel.<BR><BR>- Modo de 2 jugadores<BR>  Dos jugados pueden jugar competitivamente. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 24 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1-2 jugadores<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright 2012 Tomonori Misawa<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Voici la vaste étendue de l'espace.<BR><BR>Vous êtes une planète qui vient juste de naître.<BR><BR>Malheureusement, des planètes malveillantes vous attaquent.<BR><BR>Votre seule façon de contre-attaquer est de vous "écraser" contre elles.<BR><BR>Allez, prenez de la vitesse et chargez ces planètes ennemies !<BR><BR>Caractéristiques :<BR><BR>- Contrôles simples<BR>  Utilisez le stick analogique pour accélérer/décélérer et vous écraser contre les ennemis.<BR><BR>- Règles simples<BR>  Pour causer des dégâts, vous devez simplement avoir pris plus de vitesse que vos ennemis lorsque vous vous écrasez contre eux.<BR>  Détruisez toutes les planètes ennemies dans une zone pour terminer le niveau.<BR><BR>- Mode 2 joueurs<BR>  Vous pouvez jouer en compétition à 2 joueurs. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 24 MB – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1-2 joueurs<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2012 Tomonori Misawa<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Questo è l'universo immenso.<BR><BR>E tu sei un pianeta appena nato.<BR><BR>Stai per essere attaccato da pianeti ostili.<BR><BR>L'unico modo che hai per contrattaccare è "caricarli".<BR><BR>Sei pronto per partire alla carica dei nemici?<BR><BR>Caratteristiche:<BR><BR>- Comandi intuitivi<BR>  Usa le levette analogiche per accelerare/decelerare e caricare i nemici.<BR><BR>- Semplici regole <BR>  Per arrecare danni occorre semplicemente guadagnare una velocità maggiore rispetto al nemico e caricarlo.<BR>  Distruggi tutti i pianeti nemici in ogni stage per passare a quello successivo.<BR><BR>- Modalità 2 giocatori<BR>  Puoi confrontarti anche con un altro giocatore sfidandolo. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 24 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1-2 giocatori<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright 2012 Tomonori Misawa<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[ここは広大な宇宙。<BR><BR>あなたは誕生したばかりの惑星です。<BR><BR>こまったことに、ならずものの惑星はあなたに攻撃をしかけてきます。<BR><BR>あなたが、やつらを撃退する方法はただ一つ、”体当たり”です。<BR><BR>さぁ、勢いをつけて、敵惑星に体当たりをしましょう<BR><BR>特徴：<BR>・操作は簡単<BR>　アナログスティックで加速・減速して、敵に体当たり<BR><BR>・ルールはシンプル<BR>　ダメージを与えるには敵より早いスピードで体当たりするだけ<BR>　空間にいる敵惑星を全部やっつければクリア<BR><BR>・２Pモードあり<BR>　２人で対戦も楽しめます <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 24 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1～2人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright 2012 Tomonori Misawa<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
