<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00187_00">

  <appVersion>2.10</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>105662112</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Du spiller som en Raptor til at udforske, overleve og Hunt i store smukke omgivelser. <BR>Kæmp mod en Mecha T-Rex på månen i lav tyngdekraft! <BR>Lås kortet Secret Hub at spille som Spinosaurus og T-Rex. <BR>Gem et æg, bære den rundt, hæve og klække det til en baby, der vil følge dig! <BR>Lås mange tilpasninger ved at besejre Dinosaurer og indsamle DNA-pickupper. <BR>Indret dit Hub (Hjem) ved at skubbe genstande såsom lejrbål, bord, stol, frugt hus og meget mere! <BR>Bær lederne af dine besejrede Carnivore rivaler, Spinosaurus og Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skind, 9 Heads, 9 kæledyr, 9 Dekorationer, 9 arter af dinosaurer! <BR><BR>Engelsk ikke afgørende for at nyde spillet. <BR>Touch screen forenelig, men ikke nødvendigt. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 101 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Sie spielen wie ein Raubvogel zu erkunden, zu überleben und jagen in großen, schönen Umgebungen. <BR>Kampf gegen eine Mecha T-Rex auf dem Mond in geringer Schwerkraft! <BR>Entsperren das Geheimnis Hub Karte als Spinosaurus und T-Rex zu spielen. <BR>Speichern Sie ein Ei, mit sich herumtragen, zu erhöhen und schlüpfen in ein Baby, dass Sie folgen wird! <BR>Entsperren viele Anpassungen durch den Sieg über Dinosaurier und Sammeln DNA Pickups. <BR>Dekorieren Sie Ihr Hub (Home), indem Sie Objekte wie Lagerfeuer, Tisch, Stuhl, Obst Haus und vieles mehr! <BR>Tragen Sie die Köpfe Ihrer besiegt Carnivore Rivalen, Spinosaurus und Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Haustiere, 9 Dekorationen, 9 Arten der Dinosaurier! <BR><BR>Englisch Sprache nicht wichtig, das Spiel zu genießen. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 101 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>You play as a Raptor to Explore, Survive and Hunt in large beautiful environments.<BR>Battle against a Mecha T-Rex on the moon in low gravity!<BR>Unlock the Secret Hub map to play as Spinosaurus and T-Rex.<BR>Save an egg, carry it around, raise and hatch it into a baby that will follow you!<BR>Unlock many customisations by defeating Dinosaurs and collecting DNA pickups.<BR>Decorate your Hub (Home) by pushing objects such as campfire, table, chair, fruit house and more!<BR>Wear the heads of your defeated Carnivore rivals, Spinosaurus and Tyrannosaurus Rex!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Decorations, 9 species of Dinosaurs!<BR><BR>Update 2.1 brings you features, fixes and adjustments from your requests and reviews, thank you for playing! Best regards, Steve the Developer. <BR><BR>Package size: 101 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>You play as a Raptor to Explore, Survive and Hunt in large beautiful environments.<BR>Battle against a Mecha T-Rex on the moon in low gravity!<BR>Unlock the Secret Hub map to play as Spinosaurus and T-Rex.<BR>Save an egg, carry it around, raise and hatch it into a baby that will follow you!<BR>Unlock many customisations by defeating Dinosaurs and collecting DNA pickups.<BR>Decorate your Hub (Home) by pushing objects such as campfire, table, chair, fruit house and more!<BR>Wear the heads of your defeated Carnivore rivals, Spinosaurus and Tyrannosaurus Rex!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Decorations, 9 species of Dinosaurs!<BR><BR>Update 2.1 brings you features, fixes and adjustments from your requests and reviews, thank you for playing! Best regards, Steve the Developer. <BR><BR>Package size: 101 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>You play as a Raptor to Explore, Survive and Hunt in large beautiful environments.<BR>Battle against a Mecha T-Rex on the moon in low gravity!<BR>Unlock the Secret Hub map to play as Spinosaurus and T-Rex.<BR>Save an egg, carry it around, raise and hatch it into a baby that will follow you!<BR>Unlock many customisations by defeating Dinosaurs and collecting DNA pickups.<BR>Decorate your Hub (Home) by pushing objects such as campfire, table, chair, fruit house and more!<BR>Wear the heads of your defeated Carnivore rivals, Spinosaurus and Tyrannosaurus Rex!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Decorations, 9 species of Dinosaurs!<BR><BR>Update 2.1 brings you features, fixes and adjustments from your requests and reviews, thank you for playing! Best regards, Steve the Developer. <BR><BR>Package size: 101 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>You play as a Raptor to Explore, Survive and Hunt in large beautiful environments.<BR>Battle against a Mecha T-Rex on the moon in low gravity!<BR>Unlock the Secret Hub map to play as Spinosaurus and T-Rex.<BR>Save an egg, carry it around, raise and hatch it into a baby that will follow you!<BR>Unlock many customisations by defeating Dinosaurs and collecting DNA pickups.<BR>Decorate your Hub (Home) by pushing objects such as campfire, table, chair, fruit house and more!<BR>Wear the heads of your defeated Carnivore rivals, Spinosaurus and Tyrannosaurus Rex!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Decorations, 9 species of Dinosaurs!<BR><BR>Update 2.1 brings you features, fixes and adjustments from your requests and reviews, thank you for playing! Best regards, Steve the Developer. <BR><BR>Package size: 101 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Usted juega como un Raptor para explorar, sobrevivir y Hunt en grandes escenarios de gran belleza. <BR>Batalla contra un Mecha T-Rex en la luna en baja gravedad! <BR>Desbloquear el mapa Secret Hub jugar como Spinosaurus y T-Rex. <BR>Ahorra un huevo, llevarlo, subir y salir del cascarón en un bebé que seguirá a usted! <BR>Desbloquear muchas personalizaciones al derrotar a los dinosaurios y recoger las pastillas de ADN. <BR>Decora tu Hub (Inicio) empujando objetos como fogata, mesa, silla, casa de frutas y mucho más! <BR>Use las cabezas de sus rivales derrotados Carnivore, Spinosaurus y Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skins, 9 Jefes, 9 Mascotas, 9 Decoraciones, 9 especies de dinosaurios! <BR><BR>Idioma Inglés no es vital para disfrutar del juego. <BR>Pantalla táctil compatible pero no es necesario. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 101 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Pelaat Raptor tutkia, Survive ja Hunt suurissa kauniita ympäristöjä. <BR>Taistelussa Mecha T-Rex kuuhun matalan painopisteen! <BR>Lukituksen Secret Hub kartta pelata Spinosaurus ja T-Rex. <BR>Säästä muna, kanna sitä, nostaa ja kuoriutuvat se vauva, joka seuraa sinua! <BR>Avata monia räätälöinnit kukistamalla Dinosaurukset ja kerätä DNA mikit. <BR>Koristele Hub (Home) työntämällä esineitä kuten nuotio, pöytä, tuoli, hedelmä talo ja enemmän! <BR>Käytettävä päät teidän voitti Carnivore kilpailijoita, Spinosaurus ja Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skins, 9 päämiehet, 9 Lemmikit, 9 Kunniamerkit, 9 lajin dinosaurukset! <BR><BR>Englanti kieli ei välttämätöntä nauttia pelistä. <BR>Kosketusnäyttö yhteensopiva, mutta ei välttämätöntä. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 101 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Vous jouez comme un Raptor à explorer, survivre et Hunt dans des environnements magnifiques. <BR>Bataille contre un Mecha T-Rex sur la lune en faible gravité! <BR>Déverrouillez la carte secrète Hub à jouer en tant que Spinosaurus et T-Rex. <BR>Enregistrer un œuf, le transporter, soulever et faire éclore dans un bébé qui vous suivra! <BR>Débloquez de nombreux personnalisations en battant dinosaures et la collecte de micros d'ADN. <BR>Décorez votre Hub (Accueil) en appuyant sur des objets tels que feu de camp, table, chaise, maison fruits et plus encore! <BR>Porter la tête de vos rivaux vaincus Carnivore, Spinosaurus et Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skins, 9, 9 chefs Animaux, 9 Décorations, 9 espèces de dinosaures! <BR><BR>Langue anglaise n'est pas indispensable pour profiter de la partie. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 101 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Vous jouez comme un Raptor à explorer, survivre et Hunt dans des environnements magnifiques. <BR>Bataille contre un Mecha T-Rex sur la lune en faible gravité! <BR>Déverrouillez la carte secrète Hub à jouer en tant que Spinosaurus et T-Rex. <BR>Enregistrer un œuf, le transporter, soulever et faire éclore dans un bébé qui vous suivra! <BR>Débloquez de nombreux personnalisations en battant dinosaures et la collecte de micros d'ADN. <BR>Décorez votre Hub (Accueil) en appuyant sur des objets tels que feu de camp, table, chaise, maison fruits et plus encore! <BR>Porter la tête de vos rivaux vaincus Carnivore, Spinosaurus et Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skins, 9, 9 chefs Animaux, 9 Décorations, 9 espèces de dinosaures! <BR><BR>Langue anglaise n'est pas indispensable pour profiter de la partie. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 101 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Si gioca come un Raptor per esplorare, sopravvivere e Hunt in grandi ambienti belli. <BR>Battaglia contro un Mecha T-Rex sulla luna in bassa gravità! <BR>Sbloccare la mappa Segreto Hub di giocare come Spinosaurus e T-Rex. <BR>Salvare un uovo, portare in giro, sollevare e schiudono in un bambino che ti seguirà! <BR>Sbloccare molte personalizzazioni sconfiggendo Dinosauri e raccogliendo pickup DNA. <BR>Decora il tuo Hub (Home) premendo oggetti come fuoco, tavolo, sedia, casa frutta e molto altro! <BR>Indossare i capi delle vostre rivali Carnivore sconfitti, Spinosaurus e Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Pelli, 9 capi, 9 Animali domestici, 9 Decorazioni, 9 specie di dinosauri! <BR><BR>Lingua inglese non vitale per godersi il gioco. <BR>Touch screen compatibile, ma non necessario. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 101 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>あなたは、情報大の美しい環境で生き残るためには、狩りにラプターとしてプレー。 <BR>低重力での月面メカT-REXとの戦い！ <BR>スピノサウルスとT-Rexのように再生するために秘密のハブ·マップのロックを解除します。 <BR>、卵を保存しそれを持ち歩く、上げてあなたに従います、赤ちゃんにそれを孵化！ <BR>恐竜を倒すとDNAのピックアップを収集することにより、多くのカスタマイゼーションのロックを解除します。 <BR>そのようなキャンプファイヤー、テーブル、椅子、フルーツの家など多くのオブジェクトを押すことによって、あなたのハブ（ホーム）飾り！ <BR>あなたの敗北肉食のライバル、スピノサウルスとティラノサウルスレックスの頭を着用してください！ <BR>9スキン、9ヘッズ、9ペット、9装飾、恐竜の9種！ <BR><BR>英語ゲームを楽しむために不可欠ではない。 <BR>タッチスクリーンの互換性が、必須ではない。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 101 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Du spiller som en Raptor å utforske, overleve og Hunt i store vakre omgivelser. <BR>Kjemp mot en Mecha T-Rex på månen i lav gravitasjon! <BR>Lås opp kartet Secret Hub å spille som Spinosaurus og T-Rex. <BR>Lagre et egg, bære den rundt, heve og klekkes det til en baby som vil følge deg! <BR>Lås opp mange tilpasninger ved å bekjempe Dinosaurs og samle DNA-pickups. <BR>Dekorer Hub (Home) ved å skyve gjenstander som bål, bord, stol, frukt huset og mer! <BR>Slitasje på hodene til dine beseiret Carnivore rivaler, Spinosaurus og Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Husdyr, 9 Dekorasjoner, ni arter av dinosaurer! <BR><BR>Engelske språket ikke viktig å nyte spillet. <BR>Berøringsskjerm kompatibel, men ikke nødvendig. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 101 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Je speelt als een Raptor te verkennen, overleven en Hunt in grote mooie omgevingen. <BR>Strijd tegen een Mecha T-Rex op de maan in de lage zwaartekracht! <BR>Ontgrendelen van de kaart Secret Hub om te spelen als Spinosaurus en T-Rex. <BR>Red een ei, dragen het rond, verzorg en broeden er een baby die je zal volgen! <BR>Unlock vele aanpassingen door het verslaan van Dinosaurussen en het verzamelen van DNA-pickups. <BR>Versier je Hub (Home) door op objecten zoals kampvuur, tafel, stoel, fruit huis en nog veel meer! <BR>Draag de hoofden van je verslagen Carnivore rivalen, Spinosaurus en Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Huisdieren, 9 Decoraties, 9 soorten dinosaurussen! <BR><BR>Engels taal niet van vitaal belang om het spel te genieten. <BR>Touch screen compatible maar niet noodzakelijk. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 101 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Grasz jako Raptor zbadać, przetrwać i Hunt w dużych pięknych środowisk. <BR>Bitwa przeciwko Mecha T-Rex na Księżycu w niskiej grawitacji! <BR>Odblokować mapę Tajne Hub grać jak Spinosaurus i T-Rex. <BR>Zapisz jajko, go nosić, podnosić i wylęgają go do dziecka, że będzie za tobą! <BR>Odblokować wiele pokonując dostosowywać Dinozaury i zbierania przetworniki DNA. <BR>Udekoruj Hub (HOME) przez naciśnięcie obiektów, takich jak ognisko, stół, krzesło, domu owoców i więcej! <BR>Nosić głowy swoimi Carnivore, pokonanych rywali Spinosaurus i Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skóry Głowy, 9, 9, 9 Zwierzęta Dekoracje, 9 gatunków dinozaurów! <BR><BR>Język angielski nie ważne, aby cieszyć się grą. <BR>Ekran dotykowy kompatybilny, ale nie jest to konieczne. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 101 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Du spelar som en Raptor att utforska, Överleva och Hunt i stora vackra miljöer. <BR>Slaget mot en Mecha T-Rex på månen i låg gravitation! <BR>Lås upp hemliga Hub kartan för att spela som Spinosaurus och T-Rex. <BR>Spara ett ägg, bära runt, höja och kläcka den till en bebis som kommer att följa dig! <BR>Lås upp många anpassningar genom att besegra Dinosaurs och samla DNA pickups. <BR>Dekorera din Hub (Home) genom att trycka in föremål såsom lägereld, bord, stol, frukt hus och mycket mer! <BR>Ha huvudet på dina besegrade Carnivore rivaler, Spinosaurus och Tyrannosaurus Rex! <BR>9 Skinn, 9 Heads, 9 Husdjur, 9 Dekorationer, 9 arter av dinosaurier! <BR><BR>Engelska språket inte nödvändigt att njuta av spelet. <BR>Pekskärm förenlig men inte nödvändigt. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 101 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_14.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
