<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00221_00">

  <appVersion>2.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>5658544</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Fanny Pixel Paint, ein Pixeln nach Zahlen für die ganze Familie. Sie erhalten die Vollversion von Fanny PP, kostenfrei zum Download. Wichtig ist allerdings, dass Sie nur einen Speicherplatz für Ihre erstellten Bilder zur Verfügung haben. Um zu testen ob Fanny-PP für Sie in Frage kommt können Sie es kostenlos downloaden und so lange damit arbeiten bzw. spielen wie Sie möchten. <BR><BR>1) Fanny-PP stellt ihnen 2 kostenlose Pixeln nach Zahlen Vorlagen zur Verfügung. Weitere Vorlagen, sowie ein Upgrade auf 10 Speicherplätze, können Sie als DLC downloaden.<BR><BR>2) Importieren Sie Bilder über die Kamera.<BR><BR>3) Exportieren Sie die von Ihnen erstellten Bilder in ein Fotoalbum. Ein Re-Import bzw. Import aus einem Album ist nicht möglich. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 5526 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Kamera<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Spanisch/Französisch<BR><BR>2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Fanny Pixel Paint, a paint (pixels) by numbers for the whole family. You get the full version of Fanny PP, free to download. Important is that you have only one memory place for your created images. To test whether Fanny-PP is right for you, you can download it for free and work as long or play with it as you like.<BR><BR>1) Fanny-PP provides you with 2 free pixels by numbers templates. More templates and a upgrade to 10 memory slots, you can download as DLC.<BR><BR>2) Import images from the camera.<BR><BR>3) Export your created images in the photo album of your PlayStation®Mobile-compatible Devices. Therewith you can do whatever you want. A Re-import or the general import of an image from your photo album is not possible. <BR><BR>Package size: 5526 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Camera<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>German/English(United States)/Spanish/French<BR><BR>2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Fanny Pixel Paint, pintar (píxeles) por números para toda la familia. Usted obtiene la versión completa de Fanny PP, descarga gratuita. Lo importante es que usted sólo tiene un único lugar para grabar sus imágenes creadas. Para probar si te gusta Fanny-PP, se puede descargar de forma gratuita y trabajar siempre o disfrutar jugando.<BR><BR>1) Fanny-PP ofrece dos plantillas-pintura por números. Más plantillas y una actualización a 10 ranuras de memoria, se puede descargar como DLC para una pequeña cantidad.<BR><BR>2) Importación de imágenes desde la cámara.<BR><BR>3) Exporta tus imágenes creadas en el álbum de fotos. Con ella puedes hacer lo que quieras. Una Re-importación o la importación de una imagen de su álbum de fotos no es posible. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 5526 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Cámara<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Español/Francés<BR><BR>2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Fanny Pixel Paint, une peinture (pixels) par numéros pour toute la famille. Vous obtenez la version complète de Fanny PP, à télécharger gratuitement. L'important est que vous n'avez qu'une seule place pour enregistrer vos images créées. Pour tester si vous aimez Fanny-PP, vous pouvez le télécharger gratuitement et travailler aussi longtemps ou jouer avec, comme vous le souhaitez.<BR><BR>1) Fanny-PP vous offre 2 templates - peinture par numéros. Plus de templates (modèles) et une mise à niveau de 10 emplacements de mémoire, vous pouvez télécharger en DLC.<BR><BR>2) Importer des images de l'appareil photo.<BR><BR>3) Exportez vos images créées dans l'album photo. Une (Re-)importation d'une image de votre album photo n'est pas possible. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 5526 Ko - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Appareil photo<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Espagnol/Français<BR><BR>2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Entertainment"/><genre value="Apps:Photo"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
