<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00002_00">
 <appVersion>1.04</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>26528544</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[FlickHockeyは1人称視点の3Dエアホッケーシミュレーションゲームです。まるで本物のエアホッケーのようにリアルで、正確な「指」さばきが要求されます。<br><br>ゲームプレイモードは2種類あります。通常のポイントゲームでは、3、5、7点を先取した方が勝ちとなり、時間制限付きゲームでは1、2、3分の中から選び、制限時間内に多くのポイントを取った方が勝ちとなります。<br><br>AIとの対戦の場合は、どちらのモードでも3段階の難易度を選ぶことができます。もちろん、フレンドとの直接対決を楽しむことも可能。殿堂入りを果たせるか、実力を試してみてください。<br><br>機能：<br><br>美しい3Dグラフィック<br>60fpsでなめらかなゲームプレイ<br>リアルなエアホッケーのサウンドエフェクト<br>3段階のAI難易度<br>2プレイヤーモード（1つのデバイスで上下分割画面で対戦）<br><br>コンテンツ容量:26 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1-2人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語/日本語<br><br>著作権等:<br>(c) 2010 - 2012 Spinning Head Software Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Flick Hockey is an Air Hockey Simulation game with a 3D First Person Viewpoint that gets you as close to the real thing as possible while keeping your fingers intact.<br><br>2 choices of Game Play modes are provided. A standard points game where you can play to 3, 5 or 7 points, or a timed game where you can play for 1, 2 or 3 minutes and attempt to score as many points as possible in the chosen amount of time.  <br><br>Play either mode against an AI Opponent with a choice of 3 difficulty level, or play head to head against your friends and see if you are good enough to enter the Hall of Fame.<br><br>Featuring:<br><br>Gorgeous 3D Graphics.<br>Silky Smooth 60fps Game Play<br>Real Air Hockey Sound Effects<br>3 AI Difficulty Levels<br>2 Player Mode (Uses a 3D Top Down View on the same device)<br><br>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1-2Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese<br><br>(c) 2010 - 2012 Spinning Head Software Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Hockey à Maillet est un jeu de simulation d'Air Hockey avec vue à la première personne 3D, qui offre une expérience des plus réalistes tout en préservant vos doigts.  <br><br>Vous avez le choix entre 2 modes de jeu. Une partie classique en 3, 5 ou 7 points, ou une partie limitée à 1, 2 ou 3 minutes lors de laquelle vous devrez marquer autant de points que possible dans le temps imparti. <br><br>Disputez l'un de ces 2 modes contre un adversaire IA, avec un choix de 3 niveaux de difficulté, ou affrontez vos amis et tentez de gagner votre place au Panthéon.<br><br>Le jeu comporte :<br><br>De beaux graphismes 3D<br>Une jouabilité 60fps ultra-fluide<br>De véritables effets sonores d'Air Hockey<br>3 niveaux de difficulté IA<br>Un mode 2 joueurs (via une vue 3D du dessus sur le même appareil)<br><br>Taille du paquet: 26 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1-2joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Japonais<br><br>(c) 2010 - 2012 Spinning Head Software Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Flick Hockey è un gioco di air hockey con una visuale 3D in prima persona: ti sembrerà di giocare sul serio, ma preservando le tue dita.<br><br>2 modalità di gioco a disposizione. Cimentati in una partita standard a punteggio (3, 5 o 7 punti), o in una partita a tempo; in quest'ultima avrai 1, 2 o 3 minuti per provare a segnare quanti più punti possibile prima dello scadere del tempo.<br><br>Gioca contro un avversario IA, scegliendo tra 3 livelli di difficoltà, o sfida i tuoi amici e prova ad entrare nell'albo d'onore.<br><br>Caratteristiche:<br><br>Fantastica grafica 3D<br>Gioca a 60 fotogrammi al secondo<br>Effetti sonori di air hockey realistici<br>3 livelli di difficoltà IA<br>Modalità a 2 giocatori (usa una visuale sotto sopra sullo stesso dispositivo)<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 26 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1-2giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Giapponese<br><br>(c) 2010 - 2012 Spinning Head Software Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Flick Hockey es un juego de simulación de aerohockey con una cámara 3D en primera persona para que te dé la sensación de que estás ahí mismo, con la acción, pero sin poner en peligro tus dedos.<br><br>Hay dos modos de juego, uno con puntos estándar, en el que puedes jugar a 3, 5 o 7 puntos, y otro contrarreloj, en el que tendrás que conseguir el mayor número de puntos en el tiempo elegido (1, 2 o 3 minutos).<br><br>Juega a cualquier modo con la IA como contrincante, en cualquiera de los tres niveles de dificultad, o bien a un cara a cara contra tus amigos para ver si eres digno de entrar en el Salón de la fama.<br><br>Características:<br><br>Gráficos en 3D increíbles.<br>Un juego de 60 FPS pulido y que parece real.<br>Auténticos efectos de sonido del aerohockey.<br>3 niveles de dificultad de la IA.<br>2 modos de juego (con una vista cenital en 3D en el mismo dispositivo).<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 26 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1-2jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Japonés<br><br>(c) 2010 - 2012 Spinning Head Software Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Flick Hockey ist ein Air-Hockey-Spiel in 3-D-Frist-Person-Perspektive, das dich so nah wie nur möglich ins Spielgeschehen hineinzieht, ohne dir die Finger zu brechen.<br><br>2 unterschiedliche Spielmodi stehen zur Verfügung. Das Standard-Punktspiel auf 3, 5, oder 7 Punkte oder das Zeitspiel über 1, 2, oder 3 Minuten, in denen du so viele Punkte wie möglich erzielen musst.<br><br>Spiele entweder gegen einen KI-Gegner in 3 verschiedenen Schwierigkeitsgraden oder gegen einen deiner Freunde, um herauszufinden, ob du dich für die Ruhmeshalle qualifizieren kannst.<br><br>Besondere Eigenschaften:<br><br>Klasse 3-D-Grafiken<br>Butterweiche 60fps-Spielmechanik<br>Echte Air-Hockey-Soundeffekte<br>3 KI-Schwierigkeitsgrade<br>2-Spielermodus (3-D-Ansicht von oben auf demselben Gerät)<br><br>Paketgröße: 26 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1-2Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Japanisch<br><br>(c) 2010 - 2012 Spinning Head Software Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Flick Hockey is an Air Hockey Simulation game with a 3D First Person Viewpoint that gets you as close to the real thing as possible while keeping your fingers intact.<br><br>2 choices of Game Play modes are provided. A standard points game where you can play to 3, 5 or 7 points, or a timed game where you can play for 1, 2 or 3 minutes and attempt to score as many points as possible in the chosen amount of time.  <br><br>Play either mode against an AI Opponent with a choice of 3 difficulty level, or play head to head against your friends and see if you are good enough to enter the Hall of Fame.<br><br>Featuring:<br><br>Gorgeous 3D Graphics.<br>Silky Smooth 60fps Game Play<br>Real Air Hockey Sound Effects<br>3 AI Difficulty Levels<br>2 Player Mode (Uses a 3D Top Down View on the same device)<br><br>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1-2Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Japanese<br><br>(c) 2010 - 2012 Spinning Head Software Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Hockey à Maillet est un jeu de simulation d'Air Hockey avec vue à la première personne 3D, qui offre une expérience des plus réalistes tout en préservant vos doigts.  <br><br>Vous avez le choix entre 2 modes de jeu. Une partie classique en 3, 5 ou 7 points, ou une partie limitée à 1, 2 ou 3 minutes lors de laquelle vous devrez marquer autant de points que possible dans le temps imparti. <br><br>Disputez l'un de ces 2 modes contre un adversaire IA, avec un choix de 3 niveaux de difficulté, ou affrontez vos amis et tentez de gagner votre place au Panthéon.<br><br>Le jeu comporte :<br><br>De beaux graphismes 3D<br>Une jouabilité 60fps ultra-fluide<br>De véritables effets sonores d'Air Hockey<br>3 niveaux de difficulté IA<br>Un mode 2 joueurs (via une vue 3D du dessus sur le même appareil)<br><br>Taille du programme: 26 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1-2joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Japonais<br><br>(c) 2010 - 2012 Spinning Head Software Ltd.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Sports"/>
  <genre value="Games:Simulation"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
