<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00267_00">

  <appVersion>1.20</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>53246288</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Monsters dukkede pludselig i den idylliske landsby.<BR>Anmodning om straf kommer i Witch Emil.<BR>Hvem er med dem, der truer freden?<BR><BR>Lad besejrede den lilla sten til at indkalde et monster ved at udnytte et stort antal våben og sten og magi!<BR>Dette er en traditionel action RPG-stil actionspil.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 Opdateringen indhold.<BR>   * Tilføjet "SP scenen".<BR>     Det bliver muligt at spille efter clearing spillet.<BR>   * Tilføjet en galleri mode.<BR>     Det vil blive udvalgt efter clearing spillet.<BR>   * Tilføjet en gemme data sletning proces.<BR>     Slet menu vises ved △ knappen eller lang tap gemme skærmen til valg af data.<BR>   * Tilføjet en ny post.<BR>   * Magic og en parameter for et monster blev justeret.<BR>   * BGM blev justeret. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 51 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Monster plötzlich im idyllischen Dorf.<BR>Anfragen von Straf kommt Emil Hexe.<BR>Wer ist mit denen, die den Frieden bedrohen?<BR><BR>Lassen Sie besiegte die lila Stein, um ein Monster durch die Verwendung einer Vielzahl von Waffen und Stein und Magie beschwören!<BR>Dies ist eine herkömmliche Action-RPG-Stil Action-Spiel.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 der Aktualisierungsinhalt.<BR> * Hinzugefügt wurde die "SP stage".<BR>   Es wird möglich, nach dem Löschen das Spiel zu spielen.<BR> * Added eine Galerie-Modus.<BR>   Es wird nach dem Löschen des Spiels gewählt werden.<BR> * Es wurde ein Datenlöschvorgang zu speichern.<BR>   Löschen Menü wird durch Taste △ oder lang Tippen Sie auf Speichern Datenauswahlbildschirm angezeigt.<BR> * Ein neues Element hinzugefügt.<BR> * Magie und ein Parameter von einem Monster wurden angepasst.<BR> * BGM wurden angepasst. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 51 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Suddenly appeared monsters in the idyllic village.<BR>Request of punitive comes to witch Emil.<BR>Who is with those who threaten the peace?<BR><BR>Let's overthrow purple stone which makes full use of large number of weapons and devil stones and magic, and summons a monster!<BR>This is a conventional action RPG-style action game.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 The update contents.<BR>  * Added the "SP stage".<BR>    It becomes possible to play after clearing the game.<BR>  * Added a gallery mode.<BR>    It will be selected after clearing the game.<BR>  * Added a save data deletion process.<BR>    Delete menu is displayed by △ button or long tap save data selection screen.<BR>  * Added an new item.<BR>  * Magic and a parameter of a monster were adjusted.<BR>  * BGM were adjusted. <BR><BR>Package size: 51 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Monsters aparecieron de repente en el pueblo idílico.<BR>Solicitud de punitiva trata de bruja Emil.<BR>¿Quién está con los que amenazan la paz?<BR><BR>Let derrotó la piedra púrpura para convocar a un monstruo por la utilización de un gran número de armas y piedra y la magia!<BR>Esta es una acción convencional al estilo de juego de acción RPG.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 El contenido de actualización.<BR> * Se ha añadido la "etapa SP".<BR>   Se convierte en la posibilidad de jugar después de eliminar el juego.<BR> * Se ha añadido un modo de galería.<BR>   Se seleccionó después de eliminar el juego.<BR> * Se ha añadido un proceso de guardar los datos de eliminación.<BR>   Eliminar menú se muestra por botón o mucho toque △ excepto pantalla de selección de datos.<BR> * Se ha añadido un nuevo elemento.<BR> * La magia y un parámetro de un monstruo se a <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 51 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Monsters ilmestyi yhtäkkiä idyllisessä kylässä.<BR>Pyyntö on rankaiseva tulee noita Emil.<BR>Kuka on niiden kanssa, jotka uhkaavat rauhaa?<BR><BR>Olkoon kukisti violetti kivi kutsua hirviö käyttämällä useita aseita ja kivi ja taikaa!<BR>Tämä on tavanomainen toiminta RPG-tyylinen toimintapeli.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 päivitys sisältöä.<BR>   * Lisätty "SP vaiheessa".<BR>     On mahdollista pelata selvittämisen jälkeen pelin.<BR>   * Lisätty galleriaan tilassa.<BR>     Se valitaan selvittämisen jälkeen pelin.<BR>   * Lisätty tallentaa tietoja poisto prosessi.<BR>     Delete valikko näytetään △ -painiketta tai pitkä kosketa tallenna tietoja valintanäyttöön.<BR>   * Lisätty uusi kohde.<BR>   * Magic ja parametri hirviö säädettiin.<BR>   * Taustamusiikin oikaistiin. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 51 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Monstres soudainement apparu dans le village idyllique.<BR>Demande d'punitive se agit de sorcière Emil.<BR>Qui est avec ceux qui menacent la paix?<BR><BR>Soit défait la pierre violette de convoquer un monstre en utilisant un grand nombre d'armes et de la pierre et de la magie!<BR>Ce est un jeu d'action classique d'action RPG de style.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 Le contenu de mise à jour.<BR> * Ajout de la "phase de SP".<BR>   Il devient possible de jouer après l'élimination du jeu.<BR> * Ajout d'un mode de galerie.<BR>   Il sera choisi après avoir effacé le jeu.<BR> * Ajout d'un processus de suppression sauvegarder les données.<BR>   Supprimer menu est affiché par bouton ou taper du △ enregistrer écran de sélection de données.<BR> * Ajout d'un nouvel élément.<BR> * Magie et un paramètre d'un monstre ont été ajustés.<BR> * BGM ont été ajustés. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 51 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Monsters apparso improvvisamente nel villaggio idilliaco.<BR>Richiesta di punitiva viene a strega Emil.<BR>Chi è con coloro che minacciano la pace?<BR><BR>Let sconfitto la pietra viola di evocare un mostro utilizzando un gran numero di armi e pietre e magia!<BR>Questo è un gioco d'azione RPG in stile azione convenzionale.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 I contenuti di aggiornamento.<BR> * Aggiunta la "fase SP".<BR>   Diventa possibile giocare dopo aver eliminato la partita.<BR> * Aggiunta una modalità galleria.<BR>   Verrà selezionato dopo aver eliminato il gioco.<BR> * Aggiunto un salvataggio dei dati di processo di eliminazione.<BR>   Elimina menu viene visualizzato premendo il pulsante o lungo tap △ salva schermo di selezione dei dati.<BR> * Aggiunto un nuovo elemento.<BR> * Magia e un parametro di un mostro sono stati adeguati.<BR> * BGM sono stati <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 51 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[のどかな村に突如現れたモンスター達…<BR>見習い魔法使いエミルに討伐の依頼が舞い込む。<BR>平和を脅かす者とは一体…？<BR><BR>数々の武器/魔石/魔法を駆使して<BR>次々とモンスターを召喚する「紫岩」を撃破せよ！<BR>オーソドックスなアクションRPG風のアクション。<BR><BR>Ver 1.20　アップデート内容<BR>　・SPステージを追加しました。<BR>　　ゲームクリア後にプレイできるようになります。<BR>　・ギャラリーモードを追加しました。<BR>　　ゲームクリア後から選択可能になります。<BR>　・セーブデータ削除処理を追加しました。<BR>　　セーブデータ選択画面で△ボタンかロングタップで削除メニューが表示されます。<BR>　・新たにアイテムを追加しました。<BR>　・一部の魔法とモンスターのパラメータを調整しました。<BR>　・一部のBGMを調整しました。<BR>　<BR>Ver 1.01　アップデート内容<BR>　・PlayStation®Vita TV（PlayStation®TV）に対応しました。<BR>　・新規入手アイテムに「New!」を表示するようにしました。<BR>　・一部の魔法とモンスターのパラメータを調整しました。<BR>　・データセーブ処理を調整しました。<BR>　・いくつかの不具合を修正しました。<BR>　・一部の画像を調整したものに変更しました。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 51 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Monstre dukket plutselig i den idylliske landsbyen.<BR>Anmodning fra straff kommer til heks Emil.<BR>Hvem er med dem som truer freden?<BR><BR>Let beseiret den lilla stein for å innkalle et monster ved å benytte et stort antall våpen og stein og magi!<BR>Dette er en vanlig handling RPG-stil actionspill.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 Oppdaterings innholdet.<BR>   * Lagt til "SP scenen".<BR>     Det blir mulig å spille etter avregning spillet.<BR>   * Lagt et galleri modus.<BR>     Det vil bli valgt etter avregning spillet.<BR>   * Lagt til en lagre data sletting prosessen.<BR>     Slett Menyen vises ved △ knappen eller lang springen save data valgskjermen.<BR>   * Lagt til et nytt element.<BR>   * Magic og en parameter av et monster ble justert.<BR>   * BGM ble justert. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 51 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Monsters verscheen plotseling in het idyllische dorpje.<BR>Verzoek van bestraffende gaat om heks Emil.<BR>Wie is met degenen die de vrede bedreigen?<BR><BR>Laat versloeg de paarse steen aan een monster op te roepen door gebruik te maken van een groot aantal wapens en steen en magie!<BR>Dit is een conventionele actie RPG-stijl actie spel.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 De inhoud updaten.<BR>  * Toegevoegd de "SP podium".<BR>    Het wordt mogelijk om te spelen na het wissen van het spel.<BR>  * Toegevoegd een gallery mode.<BR>    Het zal worden geselecteerd na het wissen van het spel.<BR>  * Toegevoegd een data opslaan verwijdering proces.<BR>    Delete menu wordt weergegeven door △ knop of lange tap save data selectie scherm.<BR>  * Toegevoegd een nieuw item.<BR>  * Magic en een parameter van een monster werden aangepast.<BR>  * BGM werden aangepast. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 51 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Potwory pojawiła się nagle w idyllicznym miasteczku.<BR>Zapytaj o MORALNE przychodzi czarownica Emila.<BR>Kto jest z tymi, którzy zagrażają pokojowi?<BR><BR>Niech pokonał fioletowy kamień przywołać potwora, wykorzystując dużą ilość broni i kamienia i magii!<BR>To jest konwencjonalnym stylu RPG gra akcji.<BR><BR>Ver1.20 zawartość aktualizacji.<BR>   * Dodano "etap SP".<BR>     Możliwe staje się grać po usunięciu gry.<BR>   * Dodano tryb galerii.<BR>     Zostanie on wybrany po usunięciu gry.<BR>   * Dodano zapisywania danych proces usuwania.<BR>     Usuń menu jest wyświetlane przez przycisk lub długie kurek △ zapisać ekranie wyboru danych.<BR>   * Dodano nową pozycję.<BR>   * Magia i parametr potwora zostały skorygowane.<BR>   * BGM zostały skorygowane. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 51 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Japoński<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Monsters dök plötsligt i den idylliska byn.<BR>Begäran om straff kommer till häxa Emil.<BR>Vem är med dem som hotar freden?<BR><BR>Låt besegrade den lila stenen att kalla ett monster genom att utnyttja ett stort antal vapen och sten och magi!<BR>Detta är en konventionell åtgärd RPG-stil actionspel. <BR><BR>Ver1.20 innehållet uppdateringen.<BR>   * Lagt till "SP scenen".<BR>     Det blir möjligt att spela efter att rensa spelet.<BR>   * Lade ett galleri läge.<BR>   Det kommer att väljas ut efter rensa spelet.<BR> * Lade till en spara data raderingen.<BR>   Radera menyn visas genom △ knappen eller lång kran spardataurval skärmen.<BR> * Lade till ett nytt objekt.<BR> * Magi och en parameter för ett monster justerades.<BR> * BGM justerades. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 51 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Inukage Games<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:RPG"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
