<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00150_00">

  <appVersion>2.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>26465632</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Et action-puslespil hvori du hjælper en ung skattejæger, med at stjæle store mængder af skatte fra velbevogtede slotte.<BR>Led dem på deres vej til sikkerhed, undgå fælder og skattenes vogtere.<BR>Jo kortere tid det tager dig at lede skattejægerne, desto højere bliver din score. Og tag dig i agt for manden med leen.<BR><BR>BØRN NU OM DAGE!<BR>Unge Timmy og Susie elsker deres godnathistorier om skattejægere og vilde eventyr. <BR>I nattens mulm og mørke lister de ud af huset, og tager på eventyr for at plyndre det nærmeste slot...<BR>og de kommer i et hav af problemer.<BR><BR>RED DEM!<BR>Hjælp dem ud af deres knibe, ved at hjælpe dem med at stjæle de beskidte penge og flygte fra slottets dyb... <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 26 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Ein Action-Puzzle-Spiel, in dem du jungen Schatzjägern hilfst, große Mengen eines Schatzes aus sehr gut bewachten Burgen zu stehlen.<BR>Führe sie auf ihrem Weg in die Sicherheit und umgehe Fallen und die Schatzwächter.<BR>Je weniger Zeit du als Führer der Schatzjäger verbrauchst, desto höher ist dein Punktestand. Und pass auf den grimmigen Schnitter auf.<BR><BR>DIE KINDER HEUTZUTAGE!<BR>Der junge Timmy und die kleine Susie lieben ihre Gute-Nacht-Geschichten über Schatzjäger und wilde Abenteuer.<BR>Also schleichen sie mitten in der Nacht auf Zehenspitzen aus dem Haus und begeben sich auf ein Abenteuer: Sie haben vor, die nächstgelegene Burg zu überfallen...<BR>und finden sich in einer Welt des Chaos wieder.<BR><BR>ZU HILFE!<BR>Hilf ihnen aus ihrer Zwangslage, indem du unrechtmäßig Schätze raubst, und entkommt gemeinsam <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 26 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[An action-puzzle game in which you help a young treasure hunter steal vast quantities of treasure from well-guarded castles. <BR>Lead them on their way to safety, avoiding traps and the treasure guards. <BR>The less time you take guiding the treasure hunter, the higher your score. And watch out for the Grim Reaper.<BR><BR>KIDS THESE DAYS!<BR>Young Timmy and Susie love their bedtime stories about treasure hunters and wild adventures. <BR>So, in the dead of night they tiptoe out of the house and set off on an adventure to raid the nearest castle... <BR>and find themselves in a world of trouble.<BR><BR>TO THE RESCUE!<BR>Help them in their predicament by guiding them to steal their ill-gotten gains and escape from the depths of the castle... <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[An action-puzzle game in which you help a young treasure hunter steal vast quantities of treasure from well-guarded castles. <BR>Lead them on their way to safety, avoiding traps and the treasure guards. <BR>The less time you take guiding the treasure hunter, the higher your score. And watch out for the Grim Reaper.<BR><BR>KIDS THESE DAYS!<BR>Young Timmy and Susie love their bedtime stories about treasure hunters and wild adventures. <BR>So, in the dead of night they tiptoe out of the house and set off on an adventure to raid the nearest castle... <BR>and find themselves in a world of trouble.<BR><BR>TO THE RESCUE!<BR>Help them in their predicament by guiding them to steal their ill-gotten gains and escape from the depths of the castle... <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[An action-puzzle game in which you help a young treasure hunter steal vast quantities of treasure from well-guarded castles. <BR>Lead them on their way to safety, avoiding traps and the treasure guards. <BR>The less time you take guiding the treasure hunter, the higher your score. And watch out for the Grim Reaper.<BR><BR>KIDS THESE DAYS!<BR>Young Timmy and Susie love their bedtime stories about treasure hunters and wild adventures. <BR>So, in the dead of night they tiptoe out of the house and set off on an adventure to raid the nearest castle... <BR>and find themselves in a world of trouble.<BR><BR>TO THE RESCUE!<BR>Help them in their predicament by guiding them to steal their ill-gotten gains and escape from the depths of the castle... <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[An action-puzzle game in which you help a young treasure hunter steal vast quantities of treasure from well-guarded castles. <BR>Lead them on their way to safety, avoiding traps and the treasure guards. <BR>The less time you take guiding the treasure hunter, the higher your score. And watch out for the Grim Reaper.<BR><BR>KIDS THESE DAYS!<BR>Young Timmy and Susie love their bedtime stories about treasure hunters and wild adventures. <BR>So, in the dead of night they tiptoe out of the house and set off on an adventure to raid the nearest castle... <BR>and find themselves in a world of trouble.<BR><BR>TO THE RESCUE!<BR>Help them in their predicament by guiding them to steal their ill-gotten gains and escape from the depths of the castle... <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Un juego de rompecabezas de acción en el que debes ayudar a un joven cazador de tesoros a robar grandes cantidades de tesoros de castillos muy bien vigilados. Guíale en su camino hacia un lugar seguro evitando trampas y a los guardianes del tesoro. <BR>Cuanto menos tardes en guiar al cazador de tesoros, más puntos tendrás. Y ten cuidado con la Muerte. <BR><BR>¡ESTA JUVENTUD!<BR>A los pequeños Timmy y Susie les encantan sus cuentos para dormir sobre cazadores de tesoros y locas aventuras. Así que, al filo de la noche, salen de casa de puntillas y parten a una aventura para saquear el castillo más cercano... y se meten en un montón de problemas. <BR><BR>¡AL RESCATE!<BR>Ayúdales a salir de sus apuros guiándoles para que roben lo que han conseguido con malas artes y escapen de las profundidades del castillo... <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 26 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Toiminta-arvoituspeli, jossa autat nuorta aarteenmetsästäjää varastamaan kasoittain aarteita hyvin vartioiduista linnoista.  <BR>Johda heitä matkalla kohti turvaa, ja välttele ansoja sekä aarteiden vartijoita.  <BR>Mitä vähemmän aikaa käytät aarteenmetsästäjän opastamiseen, sitä korkeammat pisteet saat. Varothan myös Viikatemiestä!<BR><BR>  NYKYAJAN NUORET! <BR>Nuoret Timmy ja Susie rakastavat iltasatuja aarteenmetsästäjistä ja villeistä seikkailuista.<BR> Satujen innoittamina he hiippailevat ulos talosta keskellä yötä löytääkseen seikkailun tunkeutumalla läheiseen linnaan… ja päätyvät todellisiin vaikeuksiin.  <BR><BR>KOHTI PELASTUSTA! <BR>Auta heitä ahdingossa opastamalla heidät ensin varastettavan saaliinsa luo, ja sitten ulos linnan syvyyksistä… <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 26 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Un jeu de mystère et d'action dans lequel tu aides un jeune chasseur de trésor à voler une grande quantité de richesses dans des châteaux bien gardés. Conduis-le sur le chemin de la sécurité en lui évitant les pièges et les gardiens de trésor. Moins tu mettras de temps à guider le chasseur de trésor, plus tu marqueras de points. Et attention à la Grande Faucheuse.<BR><BR>LES ENFANTS D'AUJOURD'HUI !<BR>Les jeunes Timmy et Susie adorent les histoires de chasseurs de trésor et de folles aventures avant de s'endormir.<BR>Ainsi, au milieu de la nuit, ils sortent de la maison sur la pointe des pieds et s'en vont piller le château le plus proche... pour se retrouver en pleine tourmente.<BR><BR>AU SECOURS !<BR>Aide-les à se sortir de là en se faufilant avec leurs biens mal acquis pour s'échapper des entrailles du chât <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 26 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Un jeu de mystère et d'action dans lequel tu aides un jeune chasseur de trésor à voler une grande quantité de richesses dans des châteaux bien gardés. Conduis-le sur le chemin de la sécurité en lui évitant les pièges et les gardiens de trésor. Moins tu mettras de temps à guider le chasseur de trésor, plus tu marqueras de points. Et attention à la Grande Faucheuse.<BR><BR>LES ENFANTS D'AUJOURD'HUI !<BR>Les jeunes Timmy et Susie adorent les histoires de chasseurs de trésor et de folles aventures avant de s'endormir.<BR>Ainsi, au milieu de la nuit, ils sortent de la maison sur la pointe des pieds et s'en vont piller le château le plus proche... pour se retrouver en pleine tourmente.<BR><BR>AU SECOURS !<BR>Aide-les à se sortir de là en se faufilant avec leurs biens mal acquis pour s'échapper des entrailles du chât <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 26 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Un gioco d'azione e rompicapo in cui bisogna aiutare un giovane cacciatore di tesori a rubare enormi quantità di tesoro da castelli ben sorvegliati. <BR>Portali in salvo, evitando le trappole e le guardie del tesoro. <BR>Meno tempo impieghi a guidare il cacciatore di tesori, più alto sarà il tuo punteggio. E attento alla Grande Mietitrice.<BR><BR>I RAGAZZI DI OGGI!<BR>I piccoli Timmy e Susie amano i loro racconti della buonanotte sui cacciatori di tesori e sulle grandi avventure. <BR>Perciò, nel cuore della notte, escono di casa in punta di piedi per fare irruzione nel castello più vicino... <BR>e trovarsi in un mare di guai.<BR><BR>IN SALVO!<BR>Aiutali nelle difficoltà, guidandoli a rubare ciò che è stato preso in modo illecito e a scappare dalle profondità del castello... <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 26 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[厳重に守られたお城から大量の宝物を盗もうとする小さなトレジャーハンター達の手助けをするアクションパズルゲーム。<BR>数々の罠や宝の番人たちを避けながら、ハンター達を安全な場所に導いてください。<BR>より短時間でトレジャーハンターを誘導できれば、高スコアが得られます。死神に気をつけてください。<BR><BR>今どきの子ども達!<BR>幼いティミーとスージーは、お休み前にトレジャーハンターやワイルドな冒険の物語を聞くのが大好き。<BR>ついに二人は、こっそりと家を抜け出し、近所のお城に侵入する冒険を始めます…<BR>気づくとそこは、トラブルだらけの世界でした。<BR><BR>救出を!<BR>不正に蓄えられた財宝を盗んで城の奥深くから脱出できるよう、窮地に陥った二人を誘導して助けてあげましょう… <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 26 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Et action-puslespill der du hjelper en ung skattejeger med å stjele store mengder skatter fra godt bevoktede slott.<BR>Led dem til sikkerhet og unngå fellene og skattevokterne.<BR>Jo kortere tid du bruker på å hjelpe skattejegeren, jo høyere poengsum får du. Og se opp for Mannen med ljåen.<BR><BR>UNGER NÅ FOR TIDEN!<BR>Unge Timmy og Susie elsker godnatthistorier om skattejegere og ville eventyr.<BR>Så i ly av natten lister de seg ut av huset og legger i vei på eventyr på et tokt til nærmeste slott ...<BR>Snart står de til knes i trøbbel.<BR><BR>TIL UNNSETNING!<BR>Nå er de i knipe! Hjelp dem med å stjele de forbudte skattene og flykte fra slottets dyp ... <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 26 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Een actie-puzzelspel waarbij je een jonge schatrover helpt om grote schatten uit goed bewaakte kastelen te stelen. <BR>Breng hem of haar in veiligheid en vermijd vallen en de schatbewaarders. <BR>Hoe minder tijd je nodig hebt om de schatrover de weg te wijzen, hoe beter je scoort. En kijk uit voor magere Hein.<BR><BR>DE JEUGD VAN TEGENWOORDIG!<BR>Kleine Timmy en Susie houden bij het slapen gaan van verhaaltjes over schatrovers en wilde avonturen.<BR>En dus sluipen ze midden in de nacht het huis uit en beginnen een avontuur door het dichtstbijzijnde kasteel te overvallen... <BR>waarbij ze enorm in de problemen komen.<BR><BR>GA ZE REDDEN!<BR>Help ze uit hun hachelijke situatie door ze de weg te wijzen om hun buit te stelen en uit de diepten van het kasteel te ontsnappen... <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 26 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Ett actionfyllt pusselspel där du hjälper en ung skattjägare att stjäla stora skatter från välbevakade borgar. <BR>För dem i säkerhet genom att undvika fällor och de som vaktar skatterna. <BR>Ju snabbare du guidar skattjägaren, desto högre poäng får du. Se upp för liemannen. <BR><BR>DAGENS BARN!<BR>Lilla Timmy och Susie älskar nattsagor som handlar om skattjägare och vilda äventyr. <BR>Så, mitt i mörka natten smyger de ut från huset och ger sig iväg på ett äventyr för att plundra närmsta borg...<BR>och hamna i trubbel. <BR><BR>TILL UNDSÄTTNING!<BR>Hjälp dem i deras svårigheter genom att få dem att stjäla sina illegalt uppnådda vinster och fly undan borgens djup... <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 26 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright Hiive LLC<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
