<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00164_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>15914256</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Chicken! Chicken!  Er en meget sød puslespil. Flyvende Høns holdes i et lille bur værftet, og vi skal gøre, er at redde de stakkels kyllinger, æg og beskytte deres afkom. <BR>     Klik på den samme farve af buret lås og nøgle, vil være i stand til at sætte ud hønen og kyllingen løber fra side til side, på begge sider af kyllingen vil være den næste til at gå efter de æg, så er du nødt til at styre kurven nedenunder for at fange æggene Nå, inden for en fast periode, fik flere æg, jo højere score, oh ~ Dette kan synes let, men så hvis du ønsker at få gode karakterer er stadig meget vanskeligt, oh. <BR>    Buji (kylling lyde) ~ Buji (kylling lyde) ~ ~ Jeg ønsker en lykkelig spil <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 16 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! ist ein sehr schönes Puzzle-Spiel. Die kleine gelbe Chicken, die fliegen kann, wird im Käfig geschlossen und unsere Aufgabe besteht darin, diese kleine arme Chicken zu retten und ihre Eier zu schützen.<BR>　Kicken Sie den Schloss und Schlüssel, deren Farben gleich mit dem Käfig ist, dann können Sie diese Chicken befreien, dann werden diese Chicken nach zwei Seite laufen, dann werden sie Eier legen, hier sollen sie den Korb unten kontrollieren, um die Eier zu begreifen. In der fixierten Zeit, je mehr Eier Sie haben, desto hoher Punkte haben. Es scheint einfach zu sein, aber wenn Sie gute Leistung haben wollen, ist es auch schwierig.<BR>    Buji~ Buji ~ Ich wünsche Ihnen ein glückliches Spiel~ <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 16 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! is an adorable puzzle game. Volant chicken are shut in the cage, and what we need to do is to rescue the poor chicken and protect their eggs.<BR>　 Click the lock and key of the same color with cage, and the chicken can get out; then the chicken will run both sides to lay eggs, at this time you have to control the bottom of the basket to catch the egg; in the fixed time, more egg to catch, the higher scores to get ~ it seems easy, however, it is very difficult if you want to get good grades.<BR>    Buji (Chicken Squawk) ~ Buji (Chicken Squawk) ~enjoy your game~ <BR><BR>Package size: 16 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! is an adorable puzzle game. Volant chicken are shut in the cage, and what we need to do is to rescue the poor chicken and protect their eggs.<BR>　 Click the lock and key of the same color with cage, and the chicken can get out; then the chicken will run both sides to lay eggs, at this time you have to control the bottom of the basket to catch the egg; in the fixed time, more egg to catch, the higher scores to get ~ it seems easy, however, it is very difficult if you want to get good grades.<BR>    Buji (Chicken Squawk) ~ Buji (Chicken Squawk) ~enjoy your game~ <BR><BR>Package size: 16 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! is an adorable puzzle game. Volant chicken are shut in the cage, and what we need to do is to rescue the poor chicken and protect their eggs.<BR>　 Click the lock and key of the same color with cage, and the chicken can get out; then the chicken will run both sides to lay eggs, at this time you have to control the bottom of the basket to catch the egg; in the fixed time, more egg to catch, the higher scores to get ~ it seems easy, however, it is very difficult if you want to get good grades.<BR>    Buji (Chicken Squawk) ~ Buji (Chicken Squawk) ~enjoy your game~ <BR><BR>Package size: 16 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! is an adorable puzzle game. Volant chicken are shut in the cage, and what we need to do is to rescue the poor chicken and protect their eggs.<BR>　 Click the lock and key of the same color with cage, and the chicken can get out; then the chicken will run both sides to lay eggs, at this time you have to control the bottom of the basket to catch the egg; in the fixed time, more egg to catch, the higher scores to get ~ it seems easy, however, it is very difficult if you want to get good grades.<BR>    Buji (Chicken Squawk) ~ Buji (Chicken Squawk) ~enjoy your game~ <BR><BR>Package size: 16 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Chicken! Chicken! Es una especie de juego de rompecabezas muy lindo. Las gallinas voladores se cierran en una pequeña jaula, y lo que tenemos que hacer solamente es rescatar a estas pobres gallinas, también proteger a los huevos de gallina.<BR>    Haga clic en la cerradura y la llave que tengan el mismo color de la jaula, así usted será capaz de sacar las gallinas y después ellas correrán hacia ambos lados, allí podrán poner huevos, en este momente usted tiene que controlar la canasta debajo para coger los huevos, dentro de un limitado tiempo, más huevos recibidos, más alta es la puntuación, Esto parece muy fácil, pero si quieres obtener buenas notas, todavía será muy difícil.<BR>    Buji (sonidos de gallina) ~ Buji (sonidos de gallina) ~ ~ Que un feliz juego <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 16 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! Onko erittäin söpö pulmapeli. Flying Kanat pidetään pieni häkki piha, ja meidän on tehtävä on pelastaa nämä köyhät poikaset, munat ja suojella jälkeläisiä. <BR>     Valitse sama väri häkin lukko ja avain, voi laittaa ulos kanaa ja kanan kestää puolelta toiselle, molemmin puolin kana on seuraava mennä sen jälkeen munat, niin sinun täytyy hallita kori alla kiinni munat No, tietyn ajan kuluessa, sai enemmän munia, korkeammat pisteet, oh ~ Tämä voi tuntua helpolta, mutta sitten jos haluat saada hyviä arvosanoja on edelleen erittäin vaikeaa, oh. <BR>Buji (kana ääniä) ~ estoton (kana ääniä) ~ ~ Toivotan hyvää peli <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 16 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! c’est un jeu du puzzle très adorable. Le poulet qui peut voler est fermé dans la cage, et pour nous , il faut sauver les pauvres poulets et protéger leurs œufs.<BR>Laisser aller les poulets après cliquer la serrure et la clef de même couleur, et puis les poulet courent vers les deux côtés, ils vont pondre l’œuf après arriver au côté, en ce moment là, il vous faut contrôler le panier afin de prendre les œufs. Dans le délai fixé, le plus vous prenez les œufs, le plus vous prenez les notes. Il a l’air simple, mais si vous voulez obtenir la bonne note, il a encore la difficulté.<BR>Buji(cocorico)~  Buji(cocorico)~je vous souhaite avoir un bon temps de jeu ~ <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 16 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! c’est un jeu du puzzle très adorable. Le poulet qui peut voler est fermé dans la cage, et pour nous , il faut sauver les pauvres poulets et protéger leurs œufs.<BR>Laisser aller les poulets après cliquer la serrure et la clef de même couleur, et puis les poulet courent vers les deux côtés, ils vont pondre l’œuf après arriver au côté, en ce moment là, il vous faut contrôler le panier afin de prendre les œufs. Dans le délai fixé, le plus vous prenez les œufs, le plus vous prenez les notes. Il a l’air simple, mais si vous voulez obtenir la bonne note, il a encore la difficulté.<BR>Buji(cocorico)~  Buji(cocorico)~je vous souhaite avoir un bon temps de jeu ~ <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 16 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! è un gioco intelligente molto carino. I pulcini volanti sono conservati in una gabbia per uccelli, la cosa che dobbiamo fare è quella di salvare questi poveri pulcini e proteggere le loro uova.<BR><BR>Fare clic sulla serratura e chiave con lo stesso colore della gabbia, sarà in grado di mettere fuori i pulcini, quindi i pulcini possono correre ad entrambi i lati per produrre le uova, allora dovete controllare il carrello sotto per prendere le uova, è il più alto punteggio per le più uove ricevute entro il periodo di tempo fisso~ si sembra facile, ma è molto difficile per ottenere buoni voti.<BR><BR>Buji（suoni dei pulcini）~ Buji（suoni dei pulcini）~Augurare un felice gioco~ <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 16 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken!とてもかわいい益智類ゲームです。飛べるニワトリは鳥かごに閉められて、かわいそうニワトリを救い出してその卵を守りましょう。<BR>　かごと同じ色の錠と鍵をクリックすると、ニワトリが放つできます。ニワトリが両側に向って走って卵を産まれます。この時、下のかごを制御して卵をしっかり受け取ります。 固定の時間の内で、もっと多く卵が受け取ると、高い点数ができますよ~簡単に見れるが良い成績を得たいと、やはり難しいですよ。<BR>Buji（ニワトリの叫び声）~ Buji（ニワトリの叫び声）~ゲームを楽しめましょう~ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 16 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Chicken! Chicken! Er en veldig søt puslespill. Flying Kyllinger blir holdt i et lite bur verksted, og vi trenger å gjøre er å redde disse stakkars kyllinger, egg og beskytte sitt avkom. <BR>     Klikk samme farge av buret lås og slå, vil være i stand til å sette ut kyllingen og kyllingen vil gå fra side til side, på begge sider av kylling vil bli den neste til å gå etter at eggene, så må du kontrollere kurv under til å fange eggene vel, innen en fastsatt periode, fikk flere egg, jo høyere score, oh ~ Dette kan virke enkelt, men så hvis du ønsker å få gode karakterer er fortsatt svært vanskelig, oh. <BR>    Buji (kylling lyder) ~ Buji (kylling lyder) ~ ~ Jeg ønsker en lykkelig spill <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 16 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Chicken! Chicken! Is een zeer leuke puzzel spel. Vliegende Kippen worden bewaard in een kleine kooi tuin, en we hoeven te doen is om deze arme kuikens, eieren te redden en hun nageslacht te beschermen. <BR>     Klik op de dezelfde kleur van de kooi achter slot en grendel, staat de kip te blussen zal zijn en de kip loopt van links naar rechts, aan beide zijden van de kip zal de volgende te gaan na de eieren zijn, dan moet je de mand onder controle om de eieren te vangen Nou, binnen een vaste termijn, ontving meer eieren, hoe hoger de score, oh ~ Dit lijkt misschien makkelijk, maar dan als je wilt om goede cijfers halen is nog steeds erg moeilijk, oh. <BR>    Buji (kip geluiden) ~ Buji (kip geluiden) ~ ~ Ik wens een gelukkig spel <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 16 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Chicken!Chicken! En väldigt söt pusselspel. Flygande Kycklingar hålls i en liten bur gård, och vi måste göra är att rädda dessa stackars kycklingar, ägg och skydda sin avkomma. <BR>     Klicka på samma färg på buren lås och nyckel, kommer att kunna sätta ut hönan och kycklingen kommer att löpa från sida till sida, på båda sidor av kyckling kommer att bli nästa att gå efter äggen, då måste man styra korgen under för att fånga ägg Jo, inom en fastställd tid, fick fler ägg, ju högre poäng, oh ~ det kan verka enkelt, men sedan om du vill få bra betyg är fortfarande mycket svårt, åh. <BR>    Buji (kyckling ljud) ~ Buji (kyckling ljud) ~ ~ Jag önskar en glad lek <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 16 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Casual"/><genre value="Games:Family"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
