<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00115_00">

  <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>2834080</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[[Feature] <BR>-Det er en tæller, der kan være et navn på op til seks. <BR>-Du kan gemmes som en skabelon et sæt af navn, du, du vil gendanne. <BR>-Count kan også fraregnes samt tilføje. <BR>-Den håndterer også negativt tal ved at ændre den nedre grænseværdi. <BR>-Desuden knapper, der ikke har brug for en der kan bruges komfortabelt ved at forhindre klart en fejl skærmen ved, du vil skjule. <BR><BR>[Brug Scene] <BR>-Eller tælle trafikmængden, greven hos mænd og kvinder i alle aldre og forskellige knap opdeler passer. <BR>-For eksempel, snesevis af sport og spil. <BR>-At stemme for improvisation spørgeskema til fest <BR>Multi-counter kan bruges til at spille en aktiv rolle i alle aspekter af livet. <BR><BR>[FORHOLDSREGLER] <BR>-Vær opmærksom på, at det ikke giver dig mulighed for at overtage numrene tilstedeværende, blev talt. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 2768 KB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[[Feature]<BR>-Es ist ein Zähler, der ein beliebiger Name sein kann bis zu sechs.<BR>-Sie können als Vorlage eine Reihe von Namen, die Sie wiederherstellen möchten gespeichert werden.<BR>-Count können sowie das Hinzufügen subtrahiert werden.<BR>-Es ist auch für negative Zahl durch Ändern der untere Grenzwert.<BR>-Darüber hinaus können Tasten, die nicht brauchen ein komfortabel durch die Verhinderung eindeutig verwendet werden,eine Fehlfunktion der Bildschirm durch, dass Sie sich zu verstecken.<BR><BR>[Verwenden Scene]<BR>-Oder zählt das Verkehrsaufkommen, teilt die Zählung bei Männern und Frauen aller Altersgruppen und unterschiedliche Taste, um den Passanten.<BR>-Zum Beispiel, zahlreiche Sport-und Spiele.<BR>-To für Improvisation Fragebogen für Partei zu stimmen <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 2768 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[[Feature]<BR>-It is a counter that can be any name up to six.<BR>-You can be saved as a template a set of name you, you want to restore.<BR>-Count can also be subtracted as well as adding.<BR>-It also handles negative number by changing the lower limit value.<BR>-In addition, buttons that do not need a can be used comfortably by preventing clearly, a malfunction the screen by that you want to hide.<BR><BR>[Use Scene]<BR>-Or count the traffic volume, the count in men and women of all ages and different button divides the passer.<BR>-For example, scores of sports and games.<BR>-To vote for improvisation questionnaire for party<BR>Multi-counter can be used to play an active part in all aspects of life.<BR><BR>[PRECAUTIONS]<BR>-Please keep in mind that it does not allow you to take over the numbers present, were counted. <BR><BR>Package size: 2768 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[[Reportaje]<BR>-Es un contador que puede ser cualquier nombre de hasta seis años.<BR>-Puede ser guardado como una plantilla de un conjunto de nombre de usted, que desea restaurar.<BR>-Count también se pueden restar así como la adición.<BR>-También maneja número negativo cambiando el valor límite inferior.<BR>-Además, los botones que no necesitan una se puede utilizar cómodamente mediante la prevención de claridad,un mal funcionamiento de la pantalla que desea ocultar.<BR><BR>[Use escena]<BR>-O se cuenta el volumen de tráfico, el recuento de los hombres y mujeres de todas las edades y diferentes botones divide el pasador.<BR>-Por ejemplo, resultados de deportes y juegos.<BR>-Para votar por cuestionario para la fiesta de la improvisación <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 2768 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[[Ominaisuus] <BR>-Se on laskuri, joka voi olla mikä tahansa nimi jopa kuusi. <BR>-Voit tallentaa mallina joukon nimi, jonka haluat palauttaa. <BR>-Lukumäärä voi myös vähentää sekä lisäämällä. <BR>-Se hoitaa myös negatiivinen luku muuttamalla alempi raja-arvo. <BR>-Lisäksi painikkeita, jotka eivät tarvitse voidaan käyttää mukavasti estämällä selvästi, toimintahäiriön näytön, jonka haluat piilottaa. <BR><BR>[Kohtaushaku] <BR>-Tai laskea liikennemäärä, määrä miehillä ja naisilla kaikenikäisille ja eri painike jakaa ohikulkija. <BR>-Esimerkiksi tulokset urheilu ja pelit. <BR>-Voit äänestää improvisaatio kyselylomake puolue <BR>Multi-laskuri voidaan pelata aktiivisesti kaikilla elämänalueilla. <BR><BR>[VAROTOIMET] <BR>-Ole hyvä pitää mielessä, että se ei anna sinun vallata numerot hetkellä laskettiin. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 2768 Kt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[[Feature]<BR>-Il est un compteur qui peut être n'importe quel nom jusqu'à six personnes.<BR>Vous pouvez être enregistré comme modèle un ensemble de nom que vous, vous voulez restaurer.<BR>-Comte peut aussi être soustraite ainsi que l'ajout.<BR>-Il gère également nombre négatif en modifiant la valeur limite inférieure.<BR>-En outre, les boutons qui n'ont pas besoin d'un peut être utilisé confortablement en prévenant clairement,un dysfonctionnement de l'écran par ce que vous voulez masquer.<BR><BR>[Utiliser scène]<BR>-Ou compter le volume de trafic, le nombre d'hommes et de femmes de tous âges et de différents boutons divise le passeur.<BR>-Par exemple, des dizaines de sports et de jeux.<BR>-Pour voter pour l'improvisation questionnaire pour la fête <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 2768 Ko - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[[REPORTAGE]<BR>-Si tratta di un contatore che può essere qualsiasi nome fino a sei.<BR>-Tu puoi essere salvato come modello un insieme di nome, che si desidera ripristinare.<BR>-Count può essere sottratto, oltre ad aggiungere.<BR>-Si occupa anche di numero negativo modificando il valore limite inferiore.<BR>-Inoltre, pulsanti che non necessitano di una di comodo uso impedendo chiaramente,un malfunzionamento dello schermo che si desidera nascondere.<BR><BR>[Usa Scena]<BR>-Oppure conta il volume di traffico, il numero di uomini e donne di tutte le età e il pulsante diverso divide il passante.<BR>-Per esempio, decine di sport e giochi.<BR>-Per votare questionario improvvisazione per il partito <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 2768 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[[特徴]<BR>・最大6つまで任意の名前を付けられるカウンターです。<BR>・つけた名前のセットをテンプレートとして保存、復元することができます。<BR>・カウントは加算するだけでなく減算することもできます。<BR>・下限値を変更することで負の数も扱えます。<BR>・また、いらないボタン類は非表示にすることによって画面をスッキリ、誤動作を防いで快適に使用することができます。<BR><BR>[活用場面]<BR>・交通量をカウントしたり、通行人をボタン分けして老若男女別にカウント。<BR>・スポーツやゲームの得点などに。<BR>・パーティなどの即興アンケートの投票用に<BR>マルチカウンターは生活のあらゆる場面で活躍することができます。<BR><BR>[使用上の注意]<BR>・現状、カウントした数値を引き継ぐことはできませんのでご注意ください。<BR><BR>[その他]<BR>・バグ報告や要望などは作者掲示板やツイッター等によろしくお願いします。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 2768 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[[Funksjon] <BR>-Det er en teller som kan være en hvilken som helst navn på opp til seks. <BR>-Du kan lagres som en mal et sett med navn du, du ønsker å gjenopprette. <BR>-Count kan også trekkes samt å legge til. <BR>-Den håndterer også negativt tall ved å endre den nedre grenseverdien. <BR>-I tillegg, knapper som ikke trenger en kan brukes komfortabelt ved å hindre klart, en funksjonsfeil på skjermen ved at du ønsker å skjule. <BR><BR>[Bruk Scene] <BR>-Eller telle trafikkvolumet, opptellingen hos menn og kvinner i alle aldre og ulike knapp deler passer. <BR>-For eksempel score av sport og spill. <BR>-For å stemme på improvisasjon spørreskjema for fest <BR>Multi-counter kan brukes til å spille en aktiv rolle i alle aspekter av livet. <BR><BR>[FORHOLDSREGLER] <BR>-Vær spesielt oppmerksom på at den ikke tillater deg å ta over tallene <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 2768 KB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[[Feature] <BR>-Het is een teller die elke naam kan oplopen tot zes. <BR>-Je kan worden opgeslagen als een sjabloon een set van naam, die u wilt terugzetten. <BR>-Count kan ook worden afgetrokken het toevoegen. <BR>-Het behandelt ook negatief getal door de lagere grenswaarde veranderen. <BR>-Bovendien, knoppen die niet op het scherm hoeft een kan gemakkelijk worden gebruikt door duidelijk voorkomen, een storing door die u wilt verbergen. <BR><BR>[Gebruik Scene] <BR>-Of tel het verkeersvolume, de telling bij mannen en vrouwen van alle leeftijden en verschillende knop verdeelt de voorbijganger. <BR>-Bijvoorbeeld scores van sport en spel. <BR>-Om te stemmen voor improvisatie vragenlijst voor partij <BR>Multi-teller kan worden gebruikt om een ​​actieve rol te spelen in alle aspecten van het leven. <BR><BR>[VOORZORGSMAATREGELEN] <BR>-Ho <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 2768 KB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[[Feature] <BR>-Det är en räknare som kan vara ett namn på upp till sex. <BR>-Du kan sparas som en mall ett antal namn som du, du vill återställa. <BR>-Count kan också räknas bort och lägger till. <BR>-Den hanterar också negativt tal, genom att ändra det lägre gränsvärdet. <BR>-Dessutom, knappar som inte behöver en kan användas bekvämt genom att förhindra klart, ett fel på skärmen genom att du vill dölja. <BR><BR>[Använd Scene] <BR>-Eller räkna trafikvolymen, räkningen hos män och kvinnor i alla åldrar och olika knapp delar förbipasserande. <BR>-Till exempel, massor av sport och spel. <BR>-För att rösta på improvisation frågeformulär för fest <BR>Multi-räknare kan användas för att spela en aktiv roll i alla aspekter av livet. <BR><BR>[FÖRSIKTIGHETSÅTGÄRDER] <BR>-Kom ihåg att det inte tillåter dig att ta över de nummer som finns, rä <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 2768 KB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 reats All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Lifestyle"/><genre value="Apps:Utilities"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_14.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_16.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_17.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_18.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
