<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00273_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>141942128</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness er et vanvittigt og fantastisk air hockey spil! Zoo dyr forvolder caos og din mission er ... slå dem i en air hockey konkurrence! Kan du genoprette freden i byen zoologisk have?<BR><BR>FUNKTIONER<BR>- 3 kopper<BR>- Power-ups<BR>- 15 skøre dyr<BR>- Fuld Controll røre eller lege med højre analoge!<BR>- Og meget mere venter dig i Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 136 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Spansk<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness ist eine verrückte und erstaunliche Air-Hockey-Spiel! Die Zootiere sind wreaking caos und Ihre Mission ist ... schlugen sie in einer Air-Hockey-Wettbewerb! Könnten Sie den Frieden in der Stadt Zoo wieder herzustellen?<BR><BR>FEATURES<BR>- 3 Tassen<BR>- Einschalten<BR>- 15 verrückte Tiere<BR>- Full controll Note oder spielen Sie mit der rechten Analog!<BR>- Und vieles mehr warten auf Sie in Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 136 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness is a crazy and amazing air hockey game! The zoo animals are wreaking caos and your mission is... beat them in an air hockey competition! Could you restore peace in the city zoo?<BR><BR>FEATURES <BR>- 3 cups<BR>- Power-ups<BR>- 15 crazy animals<BR>- Full controll touch or play with right analog!<BR>- And much more await you in Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Package size: 136 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness es un juego de air hockey increíblemente loco. Los animales del zoo están causando el caos y tu misión será... ¡vencerlos en una competición de airhockey! Podrás restaurar la paz en el zoo de la ciudad?<BR><BR>CARACTERÍSTICAS<BR>- 3 copas<BR>- Power-ups<BR>- Control total con la táctil o juega con el analógico derecho.<BR>- Y ucho más te espera en Air HocheyZ <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 136 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness on hullu ja hämmästyttävä ilmakiekkopeli!Eläintarhaeläimet ovat wreaking caos ja tehtäväsi on ... ehkä ne ilmakiekko kilpailuun! Voisitko palauttaa rauhan kaupungin eläintarhassa?<BR><BR>Ominaisuudet<BR>- 3 kupillista<BR>- Lisävoimia<BR>- 15 crazy eläimet<BR>- Full controll kosketuksen tai pelata oikealla analoginen!<BR>- Ja paljon muuta odottavat sinua Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 136 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti/Espanja<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness est un jeu de fou et étonnant air hockey! Les animaux de zoo causent des caos et votre mission est ... les battre dans une compétition de hockey de l'air! Pourriez-vous rétablir la paix dans le zoo de la ville?<BR><BR>CARACTÉRISTIQUES<BR>- 3 tasses<BR>- Mises sous tension<BR>- 15 animaux déjantés<BR>- Controll pleine tactile ou jouer avec analogique droit!<BR>- Et bien plus encore vous attendent dans Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 136 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness è un gioco di hockey pazzo e incredibile! Gli animali dello zoo stanno seminando caos e la vostra missione è ... li battere in un concorso air hockey! Potrebbe riportare la pace nella città zoo?<BR><BR>CARATTERISTICHE<BR>- 3 tazze<BR>- Potenziamento<BR>- 15 animali pazzi<BR>- Touch controll completo o giocare con analogico destro!<BR>- E molto altro ti aspettano in Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 136 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ：狂気の動物園は、狂気、素晴らしいエアホッケーゲームです！動物園の動物は、CAOSをwreakingされているとあなたの使命は...エアホッケー競争の中で彼らを倒すされます！あなたは、市内の動物園での平和を回復できますか？<BR><BR>特徴<BR>- 3カップ<BR>- パワーアップ<BR>- 15クレイジー動物<BR>- フルcontroll touchや右アナログで遊びます！<BR>- そして、はるかには、エアHockeyZであなたを待っています！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 136 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness er en gal og fantastisk air hockey game! Zoo dyr skaper kaos og din oppgave er ... slå dem i en air hockey konkurranse! Kan du gjenopprette fred i byens dyrehage?<BR><BR>SPESIFIKASJONER<BR>- 3 kopper<BR>- Power-ups<BR>- 15 sprø dyr<BR>- Full kontroll berøring eller leke med høyre analoge!<BR>- Og mye mer venter deg i Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 136 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Spansk<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness is een gekke en verbazingwekkende air hockey spel! De dierentuin dieren worden ravage caos en je missie is ... sloeg ze in een air hockey wedstrijd! Kunt u de vrede in de dierentuin te herstellen?<BR><BR>KENMERKEN<BR>- 3 kopjes<BR>- Power-ups<BR>- 15 crazy dieren<BR>- Volledige control touch of speel met rechter analoge!<BR>- En nog veel meer wachten op u in Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 136 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels/Spaans<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness jest szalone i niesamowite gry cymbergaja! Zoo zwierzęta są siejąc caos i Twoim zadaniem jest ... ich pokonać w konkursie cymbergaja! Czy możesz przywrócić pokój w zoo miasta?<BR><BR>CECHY<BR>- 3 szklanki<BR>- Dopalacze<BR>- 15 Szalone zwierząt<BR>- Pełna dotykowy controll lub grać z prawej analogowych!<BR>- I wiele więcej czeka na Ciebie w Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 136 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski/Hiszpański<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>AIR HOCKEYZ: Zoo of Madness är en galen och fantastisk air hockey spel! De djurparksdjur är wreaking caos och ditt uppdrag är ... slå dem i en air hockey tävling! Kan du återställa fred i stadens zoo?<BR><BR>DRAG<BR>- 3 koppar<BR>- Power-ups<BR>- 15 galna djur<BR>- Full controll touch eller spela med högra analoga!<BR>- Och mycket mer väntar dig i Air HockeyZ! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 136 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska/Spanska<BR><BR>Development by Angel Garcia 'rtypex' Music by Pau Damià Riera and Carles Gumí<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Sports"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
