<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00207_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>120094336</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Mouse Bounce, en verden, hvor osten er valuta og tyvene ser meget anderledes. <BR><BR>Med en uudslukkelig cheddar trang vores mus er brudt ind i banken, stjålet og spist sin rimelige andel af verdens valuta. Nu må han gøre en hurtig flugt. <BR><BR>- Hop op til store højder, der indsamler et bjerg af ost undervejs. <BR>- Dodge politiet. Din cheddar vane er ikke gået ubemærket hen. <BR>- Styr din rute op verden ved at flytte platforme til at skabe nye veje. <BR>- Kæmp mod andre spillere! Online high scores og resultater viser, hvor god en tyv, du er. <BR>- Kjole til at imponere med over 20 forskellige kostumer at låse op. <BR><BR>Alt dette og meget mere i Mouse Bounce! <BR><BR>Følg os på Twitter .... @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 115 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Bevægelsessensor<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Maus Bounce, eine Welt, in der Käse ist Währung und Diebe ganz anders aussehen. <BR><BR>Mit einem unstillbaren Verlangen Cheddar unsere Maus hat sich in der Bank aufgebrochen, gestohlen und gegessen seinen fairen Anteil der Weltwährung . Jetzt muss er einen Kurzurlaub zu machen. <BR><BR>- Wechseln bis zu großen Höhen sammeln einen Berg von Käse auf dem Weg. <BR>- Ausweichen der Polizei. Ihre Cheddar Gewohnheit nicht unbemerkt geblieben. <BR>- Die Welt kontrollieren Sie Ihre Route durch bewegliche Plattformen, neue Wege zu schaffen. <BR>- Treten Sie gegen andere Spieler! Online-Highscores und Erfolge zeigen, wie gut ein Dieb Sie sind. <BR>- Kleid mit über 20 verschiedenen Kostümen zu entsperren beeindrucken. <BR><BR>All dies und mehr in Maus-Bounce! <BR><BR>Folgen Sie uns auf Twitter .... @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 115 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Bewegungssensor<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Mouse Bounce, a world where cheese is currency and thieves look very different.<BR><BR>With an unquenchable cheddar craving our mouse has broken into the bank, stolen and eaten his fair share of the worlds currency. Now he must make a quick getaway.<BR><BR>- Jump up to great heights collecting a mountain of cheese along the way.<BR>- Dodge the police. Your cheddar habit hasn’t gone unnoticed. <BR>- Control your route up the world by moving platforms to create new paths.<BR>- Compete against other players! Online high scores and achievements show how good of a thief you are.<BR>- Dress to impress with over 20 different costumes to unlock.<BR><BR>All this and more in Mouse Bounce!<BR><BR>Follow us on Twitter …. @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Package size: 115 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Mouse Bounce, a world where cheese is currency and thieves look very different.<BR><BR>With an unquenchable cheddar craving our mouse has broken into the bank, stolen and eaten his fair share of the worlds currency. Now he must make a quick getaway.<BR><BR>- Jump up to great heights collecting a mountain of cheese along the way.<BR>- Dodge the police. Your cheddar habit hasn’t gone unnoticed. <BR>- Control your route up the world by moving platforms to create new paths.<BR>- Compete against other players! Online high scores and achievements show how good of a thief you are.<BR>- Dress to impress with over 20 different costumes to unlock.<BR><BR>All this and more in Mouse Bounce!<BR><BR>Follow us on Twitter …. @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Package size: 115 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Mouse Bounce, a world where cheese is currency and thieves look very different.<BR><BR>With an unquenchable cheddar craving our mouse has broken into the bank, stolen and eaten his fair share of the worlds currency. Now he must make a quick getaway.<BR><BR>- Jump up to great heights collecting a mountain of cheese along the way.<BR>- Dodge the police. Your cheddar habit hasn’t gone unnoticed. <BR>- Control your route up the world by moving platforms to create new paths.<BR>- Compete against other players! Online high scores and achievements show how good of a thief you are.<BR>- Dress to impress with over 20 different costumes to unlock.<BR><BR>All this and more in Mouse Bounce!<BR><BR>Follow us on Twitter …. @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Package size: 115 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Mouse Bounce, a world where cheese is currency and thieves look very different.<BR><BR>With an unquenchable cheddar craving our mouse has broken into the bank, stolen and eaten his fair share of the worlds currency. Now he must make a quick getaway.<BR><BR>- Jump up to great heights collecting a mountain of cheese along the way.<BR>- Dodge the police. Your cheddar habit hasn’t gone unnoticed. <BR>- Control your route up the world by moving platforms to create new paths.<BR>- Compete against other players! Online high scores and achievements show how good of a thief you are.<BR>- Dress to impress with over 20 different costumes to unlock.<BR><BR>All this and more in Mouse Bounce!<BR><BR>Follow us on Twitter …. @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Package size: 115 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Ratón de rebote, un mundo donde el queso es la moneda y los ladrones se ven muy diferentes. <BR><BR>Con un deseo insaciable cheddar nuestro ratón se ha roto en el banco, robado y comido su parte justa de la moneda mundos. Ahora él debe hacer una escapada rápida. <BR><BR>- Ir hasta grandes alturas recoger una montaña de queso en el camino. <BR>- Regate a la policía. Su hábito cheddar no ha pasado desapercibido. <BR>- Controle su recorrido hasta el mundo por plataformas móviles para crear nuevos caminos. <BR>- Compite contra otros jugadores! Resultados y logros altos en línea muestran lo bueno de un ladrón que eres. <BR>- Vístete para impresionar con más de 20 trajes diferentes para desbloquear. <BR><BR>Todo esto y más en el ratón Bounce! <BR><BR>Síguenos en Twitter .... @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 115 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Sensor de movimiento<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Hiiri Bounce, maailma, jossa juusto on valuutta ja varkaat näyttää hyvin erilaiselta. <BR><BR>Kanssa sammumaton cheddar himo meidän hiiri on murtautunut pankkiin, varastettu ja syönyt hänen osuutensa maailman valuutta. Nyt hänen täytyy tehdä nopea pako. <BR><BR>- Hypätä suureen menestykseen kerätä vuori juustoa matkan varrella. <BR>- Dodge poliisille. Sinun cheddar tapa ei ole jäänyt huomaamatta. <BR>- Ohjaa reitti ylös maailmaa liikkuvia alustoja luoda uusia polkuja. <BR>- Kilpaile muita pelaajia vastaan​​! Online huipputuloksia ja saavutuksia näyttää kuinka hyvä varas olet. <BR>- Dress vaikutuksen yli 20 eri pukuja avata. <BR><BR>Kaikki tämä ja enemmän Hiiri Bounce! <BR><BR>Seuraa meitä Twitterissä .... @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 115 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Liikeohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Souris Bounce, un monde où le fromage est la monnaie et les voleurs l'air très différent. <BR><BR>Avec un cheddar soif inextinguible notre souris a fait irruption dans la banque, volé et mangé sa juste part de la monnaie des mondes. Maintenant, il faut faire une petite escapade. <BR><BR>- Aller jusqu'à de grandes hauteurs collecte une montagne de fromage le long du chemin. <BR>- Dodge la police. Votre cheddar habitude n'est pas passé inaperçu. <BR>- Contrôlez votre voie dans le monde de plates-formes mobiles pour créer de nouveaux chemins. <BR>- Affrontez d'autres joueurs! Scores et réalisations élevées en ligne montrent comment bien d'un voleur vous êtes. <BR>- Habillez-vous pour impressionner avec plus de 20 costumes différents à débloquer. <BR><BR>Tout cela et plus dans Souris Bounce! <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 115 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Détection de mouvements<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Souris Bounce, un monde où le fromage est la monnaie et les voleurs l'air très différent. <BR><BR>Avec un cheddar soif inextinguible notre souris a fait irruption dans la banque, volé et mangé sa juste part de la monnaie des mondes. Maintenant, il faut faire une petite escapade. <BR><BR>- Aller jusqu'à de grandes hauteurs collecte une montagne de fromage le long du chemin. <BR>- Dodge la police. Votre cheddar habitude n'est pas passé inaperçu. <BR>- Contrôlez votre voie dans le monde de plates-formes mobiles pour créer de nouveaux chemins. <BR>- Affrontez d'autres joueurs! Scores et réalisations élevées en ligne montrent comment bien d'un voleur vous êtes. <BR>- Habillez-vous pour impressionner avec plus de 20 costumes différents à débloquer. <BR><BR>Tout cela et plus dans Souris Bounce! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 115 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Détecteur de mouvements<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Mouse Bounce, un mondo in cui il formaggio è la valuta e ladri aspetto molto diverso. <BR><BR>Con un cheddar desiderio inestinguibile nostro mouse si è rotto in banca, rubato e mangiato la sua giusta quota di moneta mondi. Ora deve fare una rapida fuga. <BR><BR>- Vai fino a grandi altezze raccolta una montagna di formaggio lungo la strada. <BR>- Dodge la polizia. Il tuo cheddar abitudine non è passato inosservato. <BR>- Controlla il tuo percorso il mondo spostando piattaforme per creare nuovi percorsi. <BR>- Competi contro altri giocatori! Online punteggi più alti e risultati mostrano come bene di un ladro siete. <BR>- Vestito per impressionare con oltre 20 costumi diversi da sbloccare. <BR><BR>Tutto questo e molto altro nel topo Bounce! <BR><BR>Seguici su Twitter .... @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 115 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Sensore di movimento<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>マウスバウンス、チーズは、通貨で、泥棒は非常に違って見える世界。 <BR><BR>抑えられないチェダー渇望とのマウスが、銀行に分割盗まれ、世界の通貨の彼の公正な取り分を食べました。今、彼は素早く逃走を行う必要があります。 <BR><BR>- 道に沿って、チーズの山を収集する偉大な高みにまでジャンプします。 <BR>- ダッジ警察。あなたのチェダー習慣が見過ごされていません。 <BR>- 新しいパスを作成するためにプラットフォームを移動することによって、世界を、あなたのルートを制御します。 <BR>- 他のプレイヤーと対戦！オンラインハイスコアと成果はあなたが泥棒のように良い示しています。 <BR>- ドレスはロックを解除する20以上のさまざまな衣装で感動させる。 <BR><BR>このすべてとマウスバウンスでより！ <BR><BR>... Twitterでフォローする。 @CatTrapStudios <BR>www.facebook.com/cattrapstudios Facebook上で私たちのような... <BR>ウェブサイトでご覧になれます... www.cattrapstudios.com <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 115 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- モーションセンサー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Mus Bounce, en verden der ost er valuta og tyver ser veldig annerledes. <BR><BR>Med ukuelig cheddar craving vår mus har brutt seg inn i banken, stjålet og spist sin rettferdige andel av verdens valuta. Nå må han gjøre en rask getaway. <BR><BR>- Hopp opp til store høyder samle et fjell av ost underveis. <BR>- Dodge politiet. Din cheddar vane har ikke gått ubemerket hen. <BR>- Styr din rute opp verden ved å flytte plattformer for å lage nye veier. <BR>- Konkurrer mot andre spillere! Online høye poengsummer og prestasjoner viser hvor godt av en tyv du er. <BR>- Dress å imponere med over 20 forskjellige kostymer å låse opp. <BR><BR>Alt dette og mer i Mouse Bounce! <BR><BR>Følg oss på Twitter .... @CatTrapStudios <BR>Som oss på Facebook ... www.facebook.com/cattrapstudios <BR>Ta en titt på nettsiden ... www.cattrapstudios.com <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 115 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Bevegelsessensor<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Muis Bounce, een wereld waar de kaas is munt en dieven er heel anders uit. <BR><BR>Met een onlesbare cheddar verlangen onze muis heeft ingebroken in de bank, gestolen en opgegeten zijn deel van de wereld munt. Nu moet hij een snelle ontsnapping te maken. <BR><BR>- Spring omhoog tot grote hoogten te verzamelen een berg van kaas langs de weg. <BR>- Ontwijk de politie. Uw cheddar gewoonte is niet onopgemerkt gebleven. <BR>- Bedien uw route de wereld door de bewegende platforms om nieuwe wegen te creëren. <BR>- Speel tegen andere spelers! Online hoge scores en achievements te laten zien hoe goed van een dief bent. <BR>- Dress to impress met meer dan 20 verschillende kostuums te ontgrendelen. <BR><BR>Dit alles en meer in Muis Bounce! <BR><BR>Volg ons op Twitter .... @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 115 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Bewegingssensor<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Mysz Bounce, świat, w którym ser jest waluta i złodzieje wyglądać zupełnie inaczej. <BR><BR>Z głodu cheddar nieugaszony złamał nasze myszy do banku, ukradł i zjadł swój sprawiedliwy udział w walucie światów. Teraz musi zrobić szybki wypad. <BR><BR>- Przełącz się na duże wysokości zbiorowego góra sera po drodze. <BR>- Dodge policja. Twój cheddar nawyk nie przeszedł niezauważony. <BR>- Kontroluj swoją drogę do świata przez ruchome platformy do tworzenia nowych ścieżek. <BR>- Zmierz się z innymi graczami! Online wysokie wyniki i osiągnięcia pokazują, jak dobry złodziej jesteś. <BR>- Sukienka zaimponować z ponad 20 różnych strojów do odblokowania. <BR><BR>Wszystko to i więcej w Mouse Bounce! <BR><BR>Śledź nas na Twitterze .... CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 115 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Czujnik ruchu<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Musen Bounce, en värld där ost är valuta och tjuvar ser mycket annorlunda ut. <BR><BR>Med en outsläcklig cheddar begäret vår musen har brutit sig in i banken, stulna och ätit sin beskärda del av världens valutor. Nu måste han göra en snabb tillflyktsort. <BR><BR>- Hoppa upp till höga höjder som samlar ett berg av ost på vägen. <BR>- Dodge polisen. Din cheddar vana har inte gått obemärkt förbi. <BR>- Styr din rutt upp världen genom att flytta plattformar för att skapa nya vägar. <BR>- Tävla mot andra spelare! Online höga poäng och resultat visar hur bra en tjuv du är. <BR>- Klänning att imponera med över 20 olika kostymer att låsa upp. <BR><BR>Allt detta och mer i mus Bounce! <BR><BR>Följ oss på Twitter .... @CatTrapStudios <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 115 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Rörelsesensor<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>© Cat Trap Studios 2014<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
