<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00158_00">

  <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.20</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>206644528</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Så er det sommer! I en verden, hvor mennesker og youkai lever side om side, må de unge præstinder, Kaede, Sanae og Yuu, nu på deres andet år, fortsætte deres eventyr og slås mod de drilagtige youkai i dette rhytm action-spil med stemmer.<BR><BR>Bemærk:<BR><BR>* Dette er et rhytm action-spil med stemmer. Al stemme er japansk, og alle tekster kan indstilles til at blive vist på engelsk.<BR><BR>* Engelsk support er tilgængelig via e-mail og twitter. Besøg vores webside for at få mere at vide. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 198 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Der Sommer ist da! In einer Welt, in der Menschen und Youkai zusammenleben, setzen Kaede, Sanae und Yuu, Schreinmädchen im zweiten Studienjahr, ihre Abenteuer fort und kämpfen gegen boshafte Youkai in diesem komplett synchronisierten Action-Rhythmusspiel.<BR><BR>Hinweis:<BR><BR>* Dies ist ein komplett synchronisiertes Action-Rhythmusspiel. Alle Stimmen sind auf Japanisch und alle Texte können auf Englisch angezeigt werden.<BR><BR>* Englischer Support steht über E-Mail und Twitter zur Verfügung. Besuche unsere Webseite für mehr Information. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 198 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Summer is here! In a world where humans and youkai coexist, the young shrine maidens, now sophomores, Kaede, Sanae and Yuu continue their adventures fighting against mischievous youkai in this fully voiced action rhythm game.<BR><BR>Notice:<BR><BR>* This is a fully voiced action rhythm game. All voices are in Japanese, and all texts can be set to be displayed in English.<BR><BR>* English support is available via e-mail and twitter. Visit our webpage for more information. <BR><BR>Package size: 198 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[¡Ha llegado el verano! En un mundo donde coexisten humanos y espíritus, las jóvenes sacerdotisas Sanae, Kaede y Yuu, ahora estudiantes de segundo año, continúan sus aventuras luchando contra los traviesos espíritus en este juego de acción rítmica completamente doblado.<BR><BR>Advertencia:<BR><BR>* Éste es un juego de acción rítmica completamente doblado. Todas las voces están en japonés, y los textos se pueden configurar para que aparezcan en inglés.<BR><BR>* Hay soporte en inglés disponible para este juego, via correo electrónico y twitter. Visite nuestra página web para mayor información. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 198 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Kesä on täällä! Ihmisten ja Youkai:n kansoittamassa maailmassa nuoret pyhäkköneidot Kaede, Sanae ja Yuu, jotka ovat nyt toisen vuoden opiskelijoita, jatkavat seikkailujaan taistellen pahoja Youkai:ta vastaan tässä täysin puhutussa toimintarytmipelissä.<BR><BR>Huom:<BR><BR>* Tämä on täysin puhuttu toimintarytmipeli. Kaikki puhe on japaniksi ja kaikki teksti voidaan valita näytettäväksi englanniksi.<BR><BR>* Englanninkielinen tuki on saatavilla sähköpostin ja twitterin kautta. Viraille verkkosivuilla saadaksesi lisää tietoa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 198 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[L'été est arrivé! Dans un monde où les humains et les youkai coexistent, les jeunes prêtresses du sanctuaire, Kaede, Sanae et Yuu, étudiantes en deuxième année,  continuent leurs aventures et luttent contre les méchants youkai dans ce jeu d'action rythmique entièrement vocal.<BR><BR>Notice:<BR><BR>* Ceci est un jeu de rythme et d'action entièrement vocal. Toutes les voix sont en japonais et tous les textes peuvent être configurés pour être affichés en anglais.<BR><BR>* Support en anglais disponible via e-mail et twitter. Visitez notre site web pour plus d'informations. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 198 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[E 'estate! In un mondo in cui gli esseri umani e spiriti convivono, giovane sacerdotesse Sanae, Kaede e Yuu, studente del secondo anno, continuano le loro avventure combattendo gli spiriti malvagi in questo gioco di azione ritmica completamente vocale.<BR><BR>Attenzione:<BR><BR>* Questo è un gioco di azione ritmica completamente vocale. Tutte le voci sono in giapponese, e testi possono essere impostati ad apparire in inglese.<BR><BR>* Il supporto è disponibile in inglese per questo gioco, via email e Twitter. Visita il nostro sito per ulteriori informazioni. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 198 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[夏が来た！人間と妖怪が存在している世界に、山奥にある巫女学校２年生になった楓、沙苗とゆうが、いたずらする妖怪との戦いが続くフルボイス巫女みこリズム弾幕ゲーム。<BR><BR>ここは人間と動物、そして多種多彩な妖怪たちが共生する世界。<BR><BR>２年生になった楓、沙苗とゆうが、巫女学校の生活にもなれてきて。<BR><BR>可愛い後輩の面倒も見れるようになり、頼もしく成長している。<BR><BR>そして、夏休みが始まる、毎日を勉強だけで終わるのはもったいないので、みんなで楽しい思い出を作ろうといろんな場所に出かける。<BR><BR>もちろん、妖怪は相変わらずイタズラしているので、結局戦いの続く日常が待っていた。<BR><BR>※　当作品のサポートはメールやtwitterにで行っております。詳細にはホームページを御覧ください。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 198 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Sommeren er her! I en verden hvor mennesker og youkai bor sammen, de unge alterjomfruene, som nå går på andre år, Kaede, Sanae og Yuu fortsetter sine eventyr hvor de kjemper mot rampete youkai i dette stemmebaserte rytmiske actionspillet.<BR><BR>Obs:<BR><BR>* Dette er et stemmebasert og rytmisk actionspill. Alle stemmene er på japansk, og du kan velge å vise alle tekstene på engelsk.<BR><BR>* Engelsk støtte er tilgjengelig via e-post og twitter. Besøk nettstedet vårt for mer informasjon. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 198 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Het is zomer! In een wereld waarin mensen en youkai samenleven, zetten de jonge tempelmaagden Kaede, Sanae en Yuu, nu tweedejaars, hun avontuurlijke strijd tegen ondeugende youkai voort in dit volledig ingesproken actie ritmegame.<BR><BR>Let op:<BR><BR>* Dit is een volledig ingesproken actie ritmegame. Alle stemmen zijn in het Japans en alle teksten kunnen in het Engels worden weergegeven.<BR><BR>* Engelse ondersteuning is via e-mail en Twitter beschikbaar. Bezoek onze website voor meer informatie. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 198 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Lato nadeszło! W świecie, gdzie ludzie i youkai współegzystują, młode kapłanki, obecnie uczennice drugiego roku, Kaede, Sanae i Yuu kontynuują swoje przygody zwalczając złośliwe youkai w tej w pełni odegranej przez aktorów grze rytmicznej.<BR><BR>Uwaga:<BR><BR>* Jest to w pełni odegrana przez aktorów gra rytmiczna. Wszystkie wypowiedzi są po japońsku, a wszystkie teksty mogą być wyświetlane po angielsku.<BR><BR>* Wsparcie po angielsku dostępne jest poprzez e-mail i twittera. Więcej informacji znajdziesz odwiedzając naszą stronę internetową. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 198 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Japoński<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Sommaren är här! I en värld där människor och youkai-demoner lever tillsammans fortsätter de unga studenterna Kaede, Sanae och Yuu, som nu går i andra ring, sina äventyr genom att bekämpa onda youkai-demoner i ett röstbaserat action-rytmspel.<BR><BR>Observera:<BR><BR>* Detta är ett röstbaserat action-rytmspel. Alla röster är på japanska och alla texter kan ställas in att visas på engelska.<BR><BR>* Engelsk support finns tillgänglig via e-post och twitter. Besök vår webbsida för mer information. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 198 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>(c) xinoro 2010-2013. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:MusicRhythm"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
