<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00268_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>178644368</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Dying er sjovt. Er du klar til at dø igen og igen?<BR><BR>Du er en pingvin, der har vakt i et laboratorium. Ligner nogen har set dig, men noget gik galt og laboratoriet eksploderede.<BR>Din mission er at flygte fra det sted ved hjælp af 24 niveauer fyldt med fælder, pumper og frem for alt, umulige spring.<BR>Du behøver kun at trykke på en knap. Men husk på, at det vigtigste er at beslutte, hvornår at hoppe eller se en pøl af blod ofte.<BR><BR>Features:<BR>- Simple Control. Du behøver kun at trykke på en knap.<BR>- 24 djævelske niveauer, hvoraf nogle er en hyldest til de gamle konsoller.<BR>- Comic stil illustrationer fortælle historien mellem niveauerne.<BR>- Tilslutning på Twitter og Facebook. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 171 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Spansk<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Sterben macht Spaß. Sind Sie bereit, immer und immer wieder sterben?<BR><BR>Sie sind ein Pinguin, der in einem Labor geweckt hat. Sieht aus wie jemand gesehen, aber etwas schief gelaufen ist und das Labor explodiert.<BR>Ihre Mission ist, von dem Ort, mit 24 Ebenen mit Fallen, Pumpen und vor allem, nicht sprung gefüllt entkommen.<BR>Sie müssen nur eine Taste drücken. Aber denken Sie daran, dass die wichtigste Sache ist, zu entscheiden, wann zu springen oder zu sehen Blutlachen häufig.<BR><BR>Eigenschaften:<BR>- Einfache Steuerung. Sie müssen nur eine Taste drücken.<BR>- 24 teuflischen Ebenen, von denen einige sind eine Hommage an alte Konsolen.<BR>- Comic-Stil Illustrationen erzählen hier zwischen den Ebenen.<BR>- Anbindung an Twitter und Facebook. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 171 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Dying is funny. Are you prepared to die one time and again on Run Run and Die?<BR><BR>You are a penguin that woke up in a lab. It seems that someone has been experimenting with you but something failed and the lab exploded. <BR>Your only mission is escape of this place across the 24 for levels full of traps, bombs and impossible jumps.<BR>You only need press a button. Easy right? But keep in mind that the most important is decide when jump or you will see a bloody penguin frecuently.<BR><BR>Features:<BR>- Very simple control. You only need press a button or touch the screen.<BR>- 24 devilish levels some of them are a tribute to old consoles.<BR>- Spikes, bombs, lasers and robots are waiting for you to... erased you.<BR>- Illustrations with comic style tell the history between levels.<BR>- Connected Twitter and Facebook. <BR><BR>Package size: 171 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Morir es divertido. Estás preparado para morir una y otra vez en Run Run and Die?<BR><BR>Eres un pingüino que ha despertado en un laboratorio. Parece que alguien ha experimentado contigo pero algo falló y el laboratorio explotó.<BR>Tu única misión es escapar del lugar através de 24 niveles llenos de trampas, bombas y sobretodo, saltos imposibles.<BR>Solo necesitarás pulsar un botón. Pero ten en cuenta que lo más importante es decidir cuando saltar o verás charcos de sangre frecuentemente.<BR><BR>Características:<BR>- Control muy sencillo. Solo necesitas pulsar un botón o hacer uso de la pantalla táctil.<BR>- 24 endiablados niveles, algunos de los cuales son un tributo a antiguas consolas.<BR>- Ilustraciones de estilo cómic contarán la historia entre nivel y nivel.<BR>- Conectividad con Twitter y Facebook. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 171 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Dying on hauskaa. Oletko valmis kuolemaan uudestaan ja uudestaan?<BR><BR>Olet pingviini, joka on herättänyt laboratoriossa. Näyttää siltä, että joku on nähnyt sinua, mutta jokin meni pieleen ja lab räjähti.<BR>Sinun tehtäväsi on paeta paikkaan käyttämällä 24 tasoa täynnä ansoja, pumppuja ja ennen kaikkea mahdotonta hyppyjä.<BR>Sinun tarvitsee vain painaa nappia. Mutta pitää muistaa, että tärkeintä on päättää, milloin hypätä tai nähdä altaissa veren usein.<BR><BR>Ominaisuudet:<BR>- Yksinkertainen hallinta. Sinun tarvitsee vain painaa nappia.<BR>- 24 pirullinen tasoilla, joista osa on kunnianosoitus vanhoja konsolit.<BR>- Comic style kuvat kertovat tarinan eri tasojen välillä.<BR>- Yhteydet Twitter ja Facebook. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 171 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti/Espanja<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Mourir est amusant. Êtes-vous prêt à mourir encore et encore?<BR><BR>Vous êtes un pingouin qui a réveillé dans un laboratoire. On dirait que quelqu'un vous a vu, mais quelque chose a mal tourné et le laboratoire explosé.<BR>Votre mission est d'échapper à l'endroit à l'aide de 24 niveaux remplis de pièges, de pompes et surtout, des sauts impossibles.<BR>Vous avez seulement besoin d'appuyer sur un bouton. Mais gardez à l'esprit que la chose la plus importante est de décider quand sauter ou voir des mares de sang fréquemment.<BR><BR>Caractéristiques:<BR>- Simple Control. Vous avez seulement besoin d'appuyer sur un bouton.<BR>- 24 niveaux diaboliques, dont certains sont un hommage aux anciennes consoles.<BR>- Illustrations de style BD racontent l'histoire entre les niveaux.<BR>- Connectivité à Twitter et Facebook. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 171 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Morire è divertente. Sei pronto a morire più e più volte?<BR><BR>Sei un pinguino che ha risvegliato in un laboratorio. Sembra che qualcuno ti ha visto, ma qualcosa è andato storto e il laboratorio esploso.<BR>La vostra missione è quella di fuggire dal luogo utilizzando 24 livelli pieni di trappole, pompe e soprattutto, salti impossibili.<BR>È sufficiente premere un pulsante. Ma tenere a mente che la cosa più importante è quello di decidere quando passare o vedere le pozze di sangue frequentemente.<BR><BR>Caratteristiche:<BR>- Controllo semplice. È sufficiente premere un pulsante.<BR>- 24 livelli diabolici, alcuni dei quali sono un omaggio a vecchie console.<BR>- Illustrazioni stile comico raccontano la storia tra i livelli.<BR>- Connettività a Twitter e Facebook. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 171 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>瀕死のは楽しいです。あなたは何度も何度も死ぬ準備ができていますか？<BR><BR>あなたは、実験室で目覚めたペンギンです。誰かがあなたを見ているように見えるが、何かが間違っていたとの研究室が爆発した。<BR>あなたの使命は、トラップ、ポンプおよび上記のすべて、不可能な飛躍で満たさ24レベルを使用して場所から脱出することです。<BR>あなただけのボタンを押す必要があります。しかし、最も重要なことは、頻繁に血液のプールをジャンプしたり、参照するタイミングを決定することであることに留意してください。<BR><BR>特徴：<BR>- シンプルなコントロール。あなただけのボタンを押す必要があります。<BR>- 古いコンソールへのオマージュであるそのうちのいくつかは24悪魔のようなレベル。<BR>- コミックスタイルのイラストがレベル間の話をする。<BR>- TwitterやFacebookのへの接続。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 171 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Dying er gøy. Er du klar til å dø om og om igjen?<BR><BR>Du er en pingvin som har vekket i et laboratorium. Ser ut som noen har sett deg, men noe gikk galt og lab eksploderte.<BR>Ditt oppdrag er å flykte fra stedet ved hjelp av 24 nivåer fylt med feller, pumper og fremfor alt, umulig sprang.<BR>Du trenger bare å trykke på en knapp. Men husk at det viktigste er å bestemme når man skal hoppe eller se dammer av blod ofte.<BR><BR>Spesifikasjoner:<BR>- Enkel Control. Du trenger bare å trykke på en knapp.<BR>- 24 utfordrende nivåer, hvorav noen er en hyllest til gamle konsoller.<BR>- Comic stil illustrasjoner fortelle historien mellom nivåene.<BR>- Tilkobling til Twitter og Facebook. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 171 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk/Spansk<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Sterven is leuk. Ben je klaar om over en weer sterven?<BR><BR>Je bent een pinguïn die ontwaakt in een laboratorium. Het lijkt erop dat iemand heeft gezien, maar ging er iets mis en het lab explodeerde.<BR>Jouw missie is om te ontsnappen aan de plaats met behulp van 24 levels vol met valstrikken, pompen en vooral onmogelijke sprongen.<BR>U hoeft alleen maar op een knop drukt. Maar houd in gedachten dat het allerbelangrijkste is om te beslissen wanneer te springen of te zien plassen bloed vaak.<BR><BR>Cenmerken:<BR>- Simple Control. U hoeft alleen maar op een knop drukt.<BR>- 24 duivelse niveaus, waarvan sommige zijn een eerbetoon aan de oude consoles.<BR>- Comic stijl illustraties vertellen het verhaal tussen de niveaus.<BR>- Connectiviteit met Twitter en Facebook. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 171 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels/Spaans<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Umieranie jest zabawa. Czy jesteś gotowy na śmierć w kółko?<BR><BR>Jesteś pingwina, który obudził w laboratorium. Wygląda na to, że ktoś widział cię, ale coś poszło nie tak i laboratorium eksplodował.<BR>Twoim zadaniem jest uciec z miejsca za pomocą 24 poziomów wypełnionych pułapek, pomp, a przede wszystkim, niemożliwe skoków.<BR>Wystarczy tylko nacisnąć przycisk. Ale należy pamiętać, że najważniejsze jest, aby zdecydować, kiedy skakać lub zobaczyć kałuże krwi często.<BR><BR>Cechy:<BR>- Proste sterowanie. Wystarczy tylko nacisnąć przycisk.<BR>- 24 trudnych poziomów, z których niektóre są hołdem dla starych konsol.<BR>- Comic ilustracji w stylu opowiedzieć historię pomiędzy poziomami.<BR>- Łączność z Twitter i Facebook. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 171 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski/Hiszpański<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Döende är roligt. Är du redo att dö om och om igen?<BR><BR>Du är en pingvin som har väckt i ett laboratorium. Ser som om någon har sett dig, men något gick fel och arbetskraft exploderat.<BR>Ditt uppdrag är att fly från platsen med hjälp av 24 nivåer fyllda med fällor, pumpar och framför allt, omöjliga språng.<BR>Du behöver bara trycka på en knapp. Men tänk på att det viktigaste är att bestämma när man ska hoppa eller se pooler av blod ofta.<BR><BR>Funktioner:<BR>- Simple Control. Du behöver bara trycka på en knapp.<BR>- 24 grymma nivåer, varav en del är en hyllning till gamla konsoler.<BR>- Illustrerad komisk stil berätta historien mellan nivåerna.<BR>- Anslutning till Twitter och Facebook. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 171 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska/Spanska<BR><BR>Copyright (c) Angel Garcia and Pau Damià Riera<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
