<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00156_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>5656272</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Brug af denne software, kan du logge ind på din instagram konto, se andre brugere til at dele billeder, adgang til brugerens personlige rum, se billeder kommentarer og så videre. Lad din PlayStation(R)Vita er ikke længere bare et spil. Under fritid, gennemse de nyeste dele billeder, se på andre mennesker gør. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 5524 KB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Melden Sie Ihr Instagram-Konto an und verwenden Sie diese Software Instagram auf dem PlayStation(R)Vita, dann können Sie die Bilder schauen, die von den anderen teilhaben lassen werden, und auch persönliche Zone des Benutzers besuchen sowie Kommentare zu den Bildern sehen. Ihr PlayStation(R)Vita ist nicht mehr nur ein Spielgerät. In der Freizeit können Sie die neuesten Fotos durchsuchen und wissen, was andere Leute tun. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 5524 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[You can login your instagram account on this software, view pictures shared by other users, visit personal zone, and view comments of photos etc. Your PlayStation(R)Vita would be no longer just a game console. You could browse latest photos and what others are doing during leisure time. <BR><BR>Package size: 5524 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[You can login your instagram account on this software, view pictures shared by other users, visit personal zone, and view comments of photos etc. Your PlayStation(R)Vita would be no longer just a game console. You could browse latest photos and what others are doing during leisure time. <BR><BR>Package size: 5524 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[You can login your instagram account on this software, view pictures shared by other users, visit personal zone, and view comments of photos etc. Your PlayStation(R)Vita would be no longer just a game console. You could browse latest photos and what others are doing during leisure time. <BR><BR>Package size: 5524 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[You can login your instagram account on this software, view pictures shared by other users, visit personal zone, and view comments of photos etc. Your PlayStation(R)Vita would be no longer just a game console. You could browse latest photos and what others are doing during leisure time. <BR><BR>Package size: 5524 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Podría iniciar en su cuenta de instagram, tanto ve las fotos compartidas de otros usuarios, como accede al espacio personal de ellos y revisa los comentarios de fotos mediante el uso del software.En los tiempos libres, eso hace que no sólo sea un juego, sino que también es una herramienta que pasa las compartidas fotos corrientes y sabe lo que hace de los demás. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 5524 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Ohjelmiston käytöstä, voit kirjautua Instagram tilille, nähdä muiden käyttäjien jakaa kuvia, pääsyn käyttäjän henkilökohtaista tilaa, katsella valokuvia kommentteja ja niin edelleen. Anna PlayStation(R)Vita ei ole enää vain peli. Vapaa-aikana selata uusimpia jakaa valokuvia, katso muut ihmiset tekevät. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 5524 Kt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Via ce logiciel, vous pouvez vous connecter à votre compte de l’Instagram, voir les photos partagées par les autres utilisateurs, accéder à l'espace personnel de l'utilisateur, voir les commentaires des photos et ainsi de suite, ce qui laissez votre PlayStation(R)Vita ne plus être seulement un vidéo jeux. Pendant votre temps libre, découvrez les dernières photos de profil, regardez ce que les autres font. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 5524 Ko - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Via ce logiciel, vous pouvez vous connecter à votre compte de l’Instagram, voir les photos partagées par les autres utilisateurs, accéder à l'espace personnel de l'utilisateur, voir les commentaires des photos et ainsi de suite, ce qui laissez votre PlayStation(R)Vita ne plus être seulement un vidéo jeux. Pendant votre temps libre, découvrez les dernières photos de profil, regardez ce que les autres font. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 5524 Ko - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Usando questo software, Lei può entrare nel Suo conto instegram, consultare le foto conddivise con gli altri utenti, visitare lo spazio personale del conto, consultare i commenti delle foto, ecc. Il Suo PlayStation(R)Vita non sarà una macchina di gioco solo. Nel tempo libero, può consultare le ultime foto conddivise e sapere cose gli altri stanno facendo. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 5524 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このソフトウェアを利用してインスタグラムを登録、ほかのユーザがシェアした写真を見る、ユーザのインスタグラムに訪問する、写真のコメントに見ることが出来る。あなたのPlayStation(R)Vitaはを単なるゲーム機にさせない。休暇時間に最近更新した写真をシェアして、ほかの人がやっていることを了解しよう。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 5524 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Bruk av denne programvaren, kan du logge deg på instagram-konto, se andre brukere å dele bilder, tilgang til brukerens personlige plass, vise bilder kommentarer og så videre. La din PlayStation(R)Vita er ikke lenger bare et spill. Under fritid, bla de nyeste dele bilder, se på andre mennesker gjør. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 5524 KB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Het gebruik van deze software, u kunt je Instagram-account bezoeken, naar foto's van andere gebruikers te bekijken, bezoek persoonlijke ruimte van de gebruiker, foto's bekijken commentaar.Laat uw PlayStation(R)Vita is niet langer alleen een spel machine. Tijdens de vrije tijd, bladeren door de nieuwste foto's te delen, kijk naar wat andere mensen ann het doen. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 5524 KB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Användning av denna programvara kan du logga in på ditt instagram-konto, se andra användare att dela bilder, få tillgång till användarens personliga utrymme, granska foton kommentarer och så vidare. Låt din PlayStation(R)Vita är inte längre bara ett spel. På fritiden bläddra i de senaste dela foton, titta på andra människor gör. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 5524 KB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Photo"/><genre value="Apps:Lifestyle"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
