<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00255_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>61872224</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Hidtil uset ny fornemmelse af 3D puslespil optradte! !<BR>For at give osten i hamstere ved betjening af kranen at gore en vej og Michibike ost!<BR><BR>Vip og bare greb! ?<BR>Ved betjening af kranen i controlleren at sekventere objektet (plade eller firkantet, trekant, osv) Kaero!<BR>Det game over uden at vare helt hamster er slut, nar de foretager en hensynslos made.<BR>Fordi mange gange kan udfordre, sa lad os prove en rakke Forming.<BR>Hurtigt samle vejen, Formal hvert trin ☆ 3 en!<BR><BR>&lt;Spil klar punkt!&gt;<BR>・Det er muligt at besejre objektet Placering kranen fra siden!<BR>・Hamstere aske en minut er nede!<BR>・Objekt drejes ved ramt hjornet!<BR>・Den Watareru hvis multiplicere broen, hvor der ikke er noget gulv!<BR>・Hurtigt og fuldfore vejen ☆ er fuld Nowak! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 60 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>The 3D puzzle game of the new sense comes up more!<BR>You operate a crane to give a hamster cheese and make a way, and lead it to the cheese!<BR><BR>You catch it and carry it, and incline it?<BR>You operate a crane with a controller, and sort an object (including a board and a quadrangle, the triangle)!<BR>It is game over without a hamster being able to finish passing when I make an absurd way.<BR>Because I can challenge it many times, I will try various how to compose.<BR>You assemble a way quickly, and aim at each stage ☆ three!<BR><BR>&lt;Ein Punkt des klaren Spiels!&gt;<BR>・ Ich kann einen Gegenstand niederschlagen, als ich einen Kran von der Seite geschlagen habe!<BR>・ Bezuglich des Hamsters, fur einen Kasten wird ausgestiegen!<BR>・ Der Gegenstand wird durch das Schlagen der Ecke gedreht!<BR>・ Ich kann den Platz ohne einen Fusbo <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 60 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>3D puzzle game of unprecedented new sense comes up! ! <BR>Make a way by operating the crane to provide a cheese hamsters Derive cheese! <BR><BR>Tilt Carrying Grasp! ? <BR>The Kaero sequence (or square plate, such as a triangle) objects by operating the crane in the controller! <BR>Hamster's game over not completely over it and make a reckless way. <BR>It is possible to challenge many times, let's try a different way of constructing. <BR>Assemble the road quickly, and Aim for one each stage ☆ 3! <BR><BR>&lt;Point of the game clear! &gt; <BR>・It is possible to defeat the object if it strikes a crane from the side! <BR>・Hamster is down to one minute box! <BR>・Object is rotated by hit the corner! <BR>・The possible to across it, multiply the bridge where there is no floor! <BR>・Get full it is ☆ and to complete the road soon! <BR><BR>Package size: 60 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>!El rompecabezas 3D del nuevo sentido sube mas!<BR>!Hace funcionar una grua para dar un queso del hamster y hacer un camino y llevarlo al queso!<BR><BR>ﾂｿLo agarra y lo lleva y lo inclina?<BR>!Hace funcionar una grua con un regulador y clasifica un objeto (incluso un consejo y un cuadrilatero, el triangulo)!<BR>Es animoso terminado sin un hamster siendo capaz de terminar de pasar cuando hago un camino absurdo.<BR>Como lo puedo desafiar muchas veces, intentare vario como formar.<BR>!Reune un camino rapidamente y apunta en cada etapa ☆ tres!<BR><BR>＜!Un punto del juego claro!＞<BR>・ !Puedo derribar un objeto cuando golpee una grua del lado!<BR>・ !En cuanto al hamster, para una caja se quita!<BR>・ !El objeto se gira golpeando la esquina!<BR>・ !Puedo cruzar el lugar sin un suelo si construyo un puente!<BR>・ !☆ mucho de lo consigue temp <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 60 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Ennennakematon uudenlaista 3D puzzle peli ilmestyi! !<BR>Jotta juusto hamsterit toimimalla nosturin tehda tie- ja Michibike juustoa!<BR><BR>Kallista kuljettavia tarttui! ?<BR>Toimimalla nosturi ohjain sekvensoitava esine (levy tai nelio, kolmio jne) Kaero!<BR>Se peli yli olematta taysin hamsteri on yli tehtaessa holtiton tavalla.<BR>Koska monta kertaa voi haastaa, yritetaan erilaisia Muotoilu.<BR>Nopeasti kokoonpano tie, Tavoite kussakin vaiheessa ☆ 3 yksi!<BR><BR>＜Game selkea lahtokohta!＞<BR>・ On mahdollista voittaa objektin sijoittaminen nosturin sivulta!<BR>・ Hamsterit laatikko yksi minuutti on alaspain!<BR>・ Object pyoritetaan osui takana!<BR>・ Watareru jos kertomalla silta, jossa ei ole lattiaa!<BR>・ Nopeasti ja loppuun tie ☆ on taynna Nowak! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 60 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Le jeu de puzzle 3D du nouveau sens se lève plus !<BR>Vous faites marcher une grue pour donner un fromage de hamster et avancer et le mener au fromage !<BR><BR>Vous l'attrapez et le portez et l'inclinez ?<BR>Vous faites marcher une grue avec un contrôleur et classez un objet (en incluant une planche et un quadrilatère, le triangle) !<BR>C'est le jeu fini sans un hamster étant capable de finir de passer quand je fais une voie absurde.<BR>Puisque je peux le défier plusieurs fois, j'essaierai différent comment composer.<BR>Vous rassemblez une voie vite et visez chaque stade ☆ trois !<BR><BR>&lt;Un point du jeu clair !&gt;<BR>・ I can knock down an object when I hit a crane from the side!<BR>・ As for the hamster, for one box is got off!<BR>・ The object is turned by hitting the corner!<BR>・ I can cross the place without a floor if I build <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 60 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Il gioco d'enigma in 3 D del nuovo senso arriva piu!<BR>Fa funzionare una gru per dare un formaggio di criceto e fare strada e condurlo al formaggio!<BR><BR>Lo prende e lo porta e lo inclina?<BR>Fa funzionare una gru con un controllore e classifica un oggetto (compreso un'asse e un quadrangolo, il triangolo)!<BR>E il gioco finito senza un criceto che e capace di finire di passare quando faccio una strada assurda.<BR>Perche posso sfidarlo molte volte, provero vario come comporre.<BR>Riunisce una strada rapidamente e mira a ogni stadio ☆ tre!<BR><BR>＜Un punto del gioco chiaro!＞<BR>・ Posso atterrare un oggetto quando ho colpito una gru dalla parte!<BR>・ Quanto al criceto, per una scatola e sceso!<BR>・ L'oggetto e girato colpendo l'angolo!<BR>・ Posso attraversare il posto senza un pavimento se costruisco un ponte!<BR>・ ☆ molto di lo o <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 60 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>かつてない新感覚の３Ｄパズルゲームが登場！！<BR>ハムスターにチーズを与えるためにクレーンを操作して道を作り、チーズに導け！<BR><BR>掴んで運んで傾けて！？<BR>コントローラーでクレーンを操作してオブジェクト(板や四角形、三角形など)を並び替えろ！<BR>無茶な道を作るとハムスターが渡りきれずにゲームオーバーだ。<BR>何度もチャレンジできるので、様々な組み方を試してみよう。<BR>素早く道を組み立て、各ステージ☆３つを目指せ！<BR><BR>＜ゲームクリアのポイント！＞<BR>・クレーンを横からぶつけると物体を倒すことができるぞ！<BR>・ハムスターはボックス１つ分は降りられるぞ！<BR>・物体は角をぶつけることで回転させられるぞ！<BR>・床がないところは橋をかければ渡れるぞ！<BR>・早く道を完成させると☆がいっぱい貰えるぞ！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 60 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Enestaende ny folelse av 3D puslespill spillet dukket opp! !<BR>A gi osten i hamstere ved a operere kranen for a gjore en vei og Michibike ost!<BR><BR>Tilt og gjennomforing grep! ?<BR>Ved a operere kranen i kontrolleren for a sekvensere objekt (plate eller firkant, trekant, etc.) Kaero!<BR>Det game over uten a vare helt hamster er over nar du gjor en hensynslos mate.<BR>Fordi mange ganger kan utfordre, la oss prove en rekke Forming.<BR>Raskt montering av veien, Aim hvert trinn ☆ tre ett!<BR><BR>&lt;Spillet klart synspunkt!&gt;<BR>・Det er mulig a beseire objektet Plassering av kran fra siden!<BR>・Hamstere boksen ett minutt er nede!<BR>・Objekt roteres ved truffet hjornet!<BR>・Den Watareru hvis multiplisere brua der det er ingen gulvet!<BR>・Raskt og for a fullfore veien ☆ er full Nowak! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 60 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Ongekend nieuw gevoel van 3D-puzzel spel verscheen! !<BR>Om de kaas in hamsters geven door het bedienen van de kraan op een weg en Michibike kaas te maken!<BR><BR>Kantelen en uitvoeren pakte! ?<BR>Door het bedienen van de kraan in de controller om het object (plaat of vierkant, driehoek, etc.) Kaero sequentie!<BR>Het spel over zonder volledig hamster is dan bij het maken van een roekeloze manier.<BR>Omdat vele malen kunnen uitdagen, laten we proberen een verscheidenheid aan vormen.<BR>Snel monteren van de weg, Richt elke fase ☆ 3 een!<BR><BR>&lt;Spel duidelijk punt van!&gt;<BR><BR>・Het is mogelijk om het object te verslaan plaatsen van de kraan van de kant!<BR>・Hamsters doos een minuut is naar beneden!<BR>・Object wordt gedraaid door druk op de hoek!<BR>・De Watareru als de brug te vermenigvuldigen waar er geen vloer!<BR>・Snel en te voltooie <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 60 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Bezprecedensowa nowe poczucie 3D gra logiczna pojawił! !<BR>Aby dać ser u chomików przez obsługi żurawia do drogi i ser Michibike!<BR><BR>Pochylenie i przewożących złapał! ?<BR>Przez obsługi żurawia w kontrolerze do sekwencjonowania obiektu (płyta lub kwadrat, trójkąt, itp) Kaero!<BR>To gra nad bez całkowicie Chomik jest na przy podejmowaniu lekkomyślny sposób.<BR>Ponieważ wiele razy, może kwestionować, spróbujmy różnych Plastycznej.<BR>Szybko montażu drogi, Cel każdego etapu ☆ 3 jeden!<BR><BR>＜Gra wyraźny punkt!＞<BR>・Możliwe jest obejście celu Umieszczenie dźwigu z boku!<BR>・Chomiki box jednej minuty w dół!<BR>・Obiekt jest obracany o trafiła w rogu!<BR>・Watareru jeśli pomnożenie przez most, gdzie nie ma podłogi!<BR>・Szybko i wypełnić ☆ Droga jest pełna Nowak! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 60 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Japoński<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Oovertraffad ny kansla av 3D-pusselspel dok upp! !<BR>For att ge osten i hamstrar genom att manovrera kranen for att gora en vag och Michibike ost!<BR><BR>Luta och bara gripit! ?<BR>Genom att driva kranen i styrenheten att sekvensera objektet (platta eller fyrkant, triangel, etc.) Kaero!<BR>Ar spelet over utan att vara helt hamster ar over nar du gor ett vaghalsigt satt.<BR>Eftersom manga ganger kan utmana, lat oss prova olik<BR><BR>&lt;Spel tydlig punkt!&gt;<BR>・Det ar mojligt att besegra objektet Placering av kranen fran sidan!<BR>・Hamstrar rutan en minut ar nere!<BR>・Object roteras av drabbade hornet!<BR>・Den Watareru om multiplicera bron dar det saknas golv!<BR>・Snabbt och att slutfora vagen ☆ ar full Nowak! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 60 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>c 2014 SAT-BOX<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
