<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00208_00">

  <appVersion>1.08</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>23196688</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Motivet atmosfæren i begyndelsen af ​​1990'erne, og den lodrette rulle Classic (J) STG.<BR>Den opmærksomhed span af spil, som er bygget, også 10 organer i en række forskellige bosskampe.<BR>Den spilbare luftfartøjer af 4 forskellige typer af naturen, alle 5 + 2 trin.<BR>Venligst nyde! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 23 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Das Motiv die Atmosphäre der frühen 1990er Jahre, und die vertikale Bildlauf Classic (J) STG.<BR>Die Aufmerksamkeitsspanne des Spiels, die gebaut wird, auch 10 Stellen, in einer Vielzahl von Boss-Kämpfe.<BR>Die spielbare Flugzeuge von 4 verschiedenen Arten von Natur, alle 5 + 2 Bühne.<BR>Bitte genießen Sie! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 23 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[The motif the atmosphere of the early 1990s, and the vertical scroll Classic (J) STG.<BR>The attention span of the game which is built, also 10 bodies, in a variety of boss battles.<BR>The playable aircraft of 4 different types of nature, all 5 + 2 stage.<BR>Please enjoy! <BR><BR>Package size: 23 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[El motivo de la atmósfera de la década de 1990, y el clásico de desplazamiento vertical (J) STG.<BR>La capacidad de atención del juego que se construye, también 10 cadáveres, en una variedad de combates contra jefes.<BR>El avión jugable de 4 tipos diferentes de la naturaleza, los 5 + 2 etapa.<BR>Por favor, disfrutar! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 23 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Motiivi ilmapiiri 1990-luvun alussa, ja pystyvieritystä Classic (J) STG.<BR>Keskittymiskyky peli, joka on rakennettu, myös 10 elinten, eri pomotaisteluissa.<BR>Pelattavia ilma on 4 erilaista luontoa, kaikki 5 + 2 vaiheessa.<BR>Ole hyvä ja nauti! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 23 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Le motif de l'atmosphère du début des années 1990, et le défilement vertical classique (J) STG.<BR>La durée d'attention du jeu qui est construit, également 10 organismes, dans une variété de combats contre les boss.<BR>L'avion jouable de 4 types différents de la nature, tous les 5 + 2 étage.<BR>S'il vous plaît profiter! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 23 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Il motivo l'atmosfera dei primi anni 1990, e la scorrimento verticale Classic (J) STG.<BR>La capacità di attenzione del gioco che è costruito, anche 10 corpi, in una serie di battaglie con i boss.<BR>L'aereo giocabile di 4 diversi tipi di carattere, tutti 5 + 2 fase.<BR>Si prega di godere! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 23 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[９０年代初頭の雰囲気をモチーフとした、縦スクロールクラシック(Ｊ)ＳＴＧ。<BR>作りこまれたゲーム性、１０体にも及ぶ、多彩なボス戦に注目。<BR>全５＋2ステージを、性質の異なる４種類の自機でプレイ可能。<BR>お楽しみください！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 23 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Motivet atmosfæren i begynnelsen av 1990, og det vertikale rulle Classic (J) STG.<BR>Oppmerksomheten span av spillet som er bygd, også 10 kropper, i en rekke sjefskamper.<BR>Den spillbare fly av 4 forskjellige naturtyper, alle 5 + 2 scenen.<BR>Vennligst nyte! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 23 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Het motief van de sfeer van de vroege jaren 1990, en de verticale schuifbalk Classic (J) STG.<BR>De aandacht overspanning van het spel dat is gebouwd, ook organen 10, in diverse boss gevechten.<BR>De speelbare vliegtuigen uit 4 verschillende types van de natuur, alle 5 + 2 podium.<BR>Veel plezier! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 23 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Motyw atmosfera z początku lat 1990, i przewijania pionowego Classic (J) STG.<BR>Koncentracji uwagi gry, który jest zbudowany, także 10 ciał, w wielu walkach z bossami.<BR>Odtwarzane samolot z 4 różnych rodzajów natury, wszystkie 5 + 2 etapie.<BR>Proszę cieszyć! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 23 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Motivet atmosfären i början av 1990, och den lodräta rullnings Classic (J) STG.<BR>Den uppmärksamhet span av spelet som är byggt, även 10 kroppar, i en mängd olika bosstrider.<BR>De spelbara flygplan av 4 olika naturtyper, alla 5 + 2 skede.<BR>Vänligen njuta! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 23 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska<BR><BR>Team_Redheering<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Shooter"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_18.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_21.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_22.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_16.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
