<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00113_00">

  <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>36760048</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Nøglen til en vellykket slankekur for doven gammel du! <BR><BR>"Munchy Girl Mogumi Easy Diet" er en slankekure app, der hjælper dig med at registrere din vægt og følge din kost. Den er udstyret med sjove illustrationer og rådgivning fra Munchy Girl selv, Mogumi Office Worker, skabt af Etsuko Mizusawa, som også har lavet den populære tegneserie "Hana ingen Zubora Meshi -. Hana s Jiffy Meals" <BR><BR>Brugervenlig! <BR><BR>Input din vægt hver dag, og optage det, du spiste ved at vælge fra rullemenuen. Mogumi vil være at se din fremskridt - eller mangel på samme. Hun vil give dig skræddersyet rådgivning, der passer til din vægt og spise tilstand og pep-talks. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 36 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Der Schlüssel zum erfolgreichen Diät für faule alt Sie! <BR><BR>"Munchy Mädchen Mogumi Easy-Diät" ist eine Diät-App, die Sie Ihr Gewicht aufnehmen und folgen Sie Ihrem Diät hilft. Es bietet Spaß Abbildungen und Beratung von der Munchy Mädchen selbst, Mogumi der Büroangestellter, erstellt von Etsuko Mizusawa, der auch aus der beliebten Comic-Serie "Hana no Zubora Meshi -. Hana Jiffy Meals" <BR><BR>Benutzerfreundlich! <BR><BR>Geben Sie Ihr Gewicht jeden Tag und notieren, was Sie, indem Sie aus dem Pull-Down-Menü gegessen haben. Mogumi werden sehen Ihre Fortschritte - oder deren Fehlen. Sie wird Ihnen maßgeschneiderte Beratung, die Ihr Gewicht und Essen Zustand und pep-Gespräche passt. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 36 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[The key to successful dieting for lazy old you!<BR><BR>“Munchy Girl Mogumi’s Easy Diet” is a dieting app that helps you record your weight and follow your diet. It features fun illustrations and advice from the Munchy Girl herself, Mogumi the Office Worker, created by Etsuko Mizusawa, who also made the popular comic series “Hana no Zubora Meshi--Hana's Jiffy Meals.”<BR><BR>User friendly!<BR><BR>Input your weight every day and record what you ate by choosing from the pull-down menu. Mogumi will be watching your progress – or lack thereof. She will give you tailor-made advice that fits your weight and eating condition and pep-talks. <BR><BR>Package size: 36 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[La clave para una dieta exitosa para perezosos edad que tengas! <BR><BR>"Easy Diet de Munchy Chica Mogumi" es una aplicación de la dieta que le ayuda a grabar su peso y seguir su dieta. Cuenta con divertidas ilustraciones y consejos de la Munchy Chica sola, Mogumi el Oficinista, creado por Etsuko Mizusawa, quien también hizo la popular serie cómica "Hana no Zubora Meshi - de Hana Jiffy comidas." <BR><BR>Fácil de usar! <BR><BR>Ingrese su peso todos los días y grabar lo que comió eligiendo en el menú desplegable. Mogumi estará observando su progreso - o falta de ella. Ella le dará consejos a medida que se ajuste a su peso y el estado comiendo y pep-habla. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 36 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Avain onnistuneeseen ruokavalioon laiska vanha olet! <BR><BR>"Munchy Girl Mogumi Easy Diet" on laihduttaminen sovellus, jonka avulla voit tallentaa paino ja seurata ruokavaliota. Siinä on hauskaa piirroksia ja neuvoja Munchy Tyttö itse, Mogumi toimistotyöntekijä, kirjoittaja Etsuko Mizusawa, joka teki myös suositun sarjakuvan "Hana no Zubora Meshi - Hana Jiffy Ateriat." <BR><BR>Käyttäjäystävällinen! <BR><BR>Painosi joka päivä ja tallentaa mitä söit valitsemalla alasvetovalikosta. Mogumi tarkkailevat oman edistymisen - tai sen puutteesta. Hän antaa sinulle räätälöityjä neuvoja, joka sopii paino ja syöminen kunnossa ja PEP-neuvottelut. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 36 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[La clé de la réussite pour un régime paresseux vieux vous! <BR><BR>"Easy Diet Munchy fille Mogumi" est une application qui vous permet de suivre un régime enregistré votre poids et suivez votre régime alimentaire. Il dispose d'illustrations amusantes et conseils de la fille Munchy elle-même, la Mogumi Employé de bureau, créé par Etsuko Mizusawa, qui a également fait la série de bande dessinée populaire "Hana no Zubora Meshi - Jiffy Repas Hana." <BR><BR>Convivial! <BR><BR>Saisissez votre poids tous les jours et d'enregistrer ce que vous avez mangé en choisissant dans le menu déroulant. Mogumi surveillera vos progrès - ou l'absence de celui-ci. Elle vous donnera des conseils sur mesure qui s'adapte à votre poids et l'état de l'alimentation et de pep-talks. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 36 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[La chiave per una dieta di successo per pigri anni hai! <BR><BR>"Easy Dieta Munchy ragazza Mogumi" è un app dieta che ti aiuta a registrare il vostro peso e seguire la vostra dieta. È dotato di illustrazioni divertenti e consigli dal Munchy ragazza stessa, Mogumi l'Office Worker, creato da Etsuko Mizusawa, che ha anche fatto il popolare serie a fumetti "Hana no Zubora Meshi -. Jiffy Meals di Hana" <BR><BR>Facile da usare! <BR><BR>Inserisci il tuo peso ogni giorno e registrare quello che hai mangiato scegliendo dal menu a discesa. Mogumi starà a guardare i tuoi progressi - o la loro mancanza. Lei vi darà consigli su misura che si adatta il vostro peso e la condizione di mangiare e pep-colloqui. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 36 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[ずぼらなあなたもこれがあればダイエット成功！？<BR><BR>『食いしんぼうOL もぐ美のずぼらダイエット』は、人気漫画「花のズボラ飯」作画・水沢悦子先生による書き下ろしのキャラクター・食いしんぼうOL もぐ美がイラストやアドバイスで、あなたのダイエットを応援してくれるレコーディングダイエットアプリです。 <BR><BR>基本操作は簡単！<BR>毎日の体重入力と食事内容をプルダウンから選択するだけ！<BR>入力された体重の増減や食事内容に合わせて、もぐ美から応援のメッセージカードや、ダイエットアドバイスがもらえるよ！<BR><BR>【アプリの特徴】<BR>・ずぼらダイエットでしか見れない！水沢悦子先生書き下ろしのメッセージカードがもらえる！（全30種類）<BR>・【体重】タップ＆入力！と、【食事内容】プルダウンから選択！だけの簡単操作<BR>・グラフで体重の変化を確認できる<BR>・“ひとこと”機能で、日記としても使える！<BR>・栄養士によるアドバイスが読める！<BR>・ダイエット何日目か日数をカウントできる！<BR>・ダイエットに挫折しても日数カウントダウンをリセットできるから、気楽にダイエットできる！<BR>・アプリ起動時に、目標体重までの差が表示されるから励みになる！<BR>・セキュリティコードが設定できるから万が一誰かにアプリを起動されても体重がばれずに済みます <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 36 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Nøkkelen til vellykket slanking for lat gammel du!<BR><BR>"Munchy Jente Mogumi Easy Diet" er en slanking app som hjelper deg å spille inn din vekt og følge dietten din. Den har morsomme illustrasjoner og råd fra Munchy jenta selv, Mogumi Office Worker, skapt av Etsuko Mizusawa, som også laget den populære tegneserien "Hana no Zubora Meshi -. Hana er Jiffy Meals"<BR><BR>Brukervennlig!<BR><BR>Input vekten din hver dag, og ta opp det du spiste ved å velge fra rullegardinmenyen. Mogumi vil bli å se fremgangen din - eller mangelen på dem. Hun vil gi deg skreddersydde råd som passer din vekt og spising tilstand og pep-talks. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 36 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[De sleutel tot succesvolle dieet voor luie oud je! <BR><BR>"Munchy Girl Mogumi Easy Diet" is een dieet app die je helpt om je gewicht te nemen en volg je dieet. Het beschikt over leuke illustraties en advies van de Munchy meisje zelf, Mogumi de Beambte, gecreëerd door Etsuko Mizusawa, die ook de populaire comic serie "Hana geen Zubora Meshi -. Hana's Jiffy maaltijden" <BR><BR>Gebruiksvriendelijk! <BR><BR>Voer uw gewicht elke dag en opnemen wat je gegeten hebt door te kiezen uit het pull-down menu. Mogumi zal kijken naar je vooruitgang - of het ontbreken daarvan. Zij zal u een advies op maat dat uw gewicht en eten staat en pep-gesprekken past geven. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 36 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Nyckeln till framgångsrik bantning för lata gammal du! <BR><BR>"Munchy Girl Mogumi Easy Diet" är en bantning app som hjälper dig att spela in din vikt och följ din kost. Den har roliga illustrationer och råd från Munchy Girl själv, Mogumi Office Worker, skapad av Etsuko Mizusawa, som också gjort den populära tecknade serien "Hana no Zubora Meshi -. Hanas Jiffy Meals" <BR><BR>Användarvänligt! <BR><BR>Fyll i din vikt varje dag och spela in vad du åt genom att välja från rullgardinsmenyn. Mogumi kommer att titta på dina framsteg - eller brist på sådan. Hon kommer att ge dig skräddarsydda råd som passar din vikt och äta skick och pep-samtal. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 36 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>(c) etsuko mizusawa/Sony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:HealthAndFitness"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
