<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00136_00">

  <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>27227184</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel er et tempofyldt spil, hvor du skal kigge efter et hotel med en række meget usædvanlige gæster! Indbyggerne i Monster Hotel kan være en vægelsindet flok, og holde dem søde kommer til at være svært.<BR><BR>Kig efter ulykkelig gæster og trække dem ind i forskellige rum, der opfylder deres behov - shuffle dine monstre rundt for at holde dem alle glade. Jo bedre du gør det sværere bliver det!<BR><BR>Konkurrere om den højeste score på online leaderboards og låse nye monstre, større hoteller og særlige rum, som du fremskridt. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 26 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel ist ein schnelles Spiel, wo Sie muss nach einem Hotel mit einer Vielzahl von sehr ungewöhnlichen Gäste zu kümmern! Die Bewohner der Monster-Hotel ist eine wankelmütige Haufen zu sein, und halten sie süß wird schwierig sein.<BR><BR>Suchen Sie nach unglücklichen Gäste und ziehen Sie sie in verschiedenen Räumen, die ihre Bedürfnisse zu befriedigen - mische deine Monster in der Umgebung, um sie alle glücklich. Je besser Sie tun, desto schwieriger wird es!<BR><BR>Wettbewerb um die höchste Punktzahl auf der Online-Bestenlisten und schalte neue Monster, größeren Hotels und spezielle Zimmer wie Sie Fortschritte. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 26 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel is a fast paced game where you must look after a hotel with a variety of very unusual guests! The inhabitants of Monster Hotel can be a fickle bunch, and keeping them sweet is going to be difficult.<BR><BR>Look for unhappy guests and drag them into different rooms that satisfy their needs - shuffle your monsters around to keep them all happy. The better you do the harder it gets!<BR><BR>Compete for the highest score on the online leaderboards and unlock new monsters, bigger hotels and special rooms as you progress. <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel is a fast paced game where you must look after a hotel with a variety of very unusual guests! The inhabitants of Monster Hotel can be a fickle bunch, and keeping them sweet is going to be difficult.<BR><BR>Look for unhappy guests and drag them into different rooms that satisfy their needs - shuffle your monsters around to keep them all happy. The better you do the harder it gets!<BR><BR>Compete for the highest score on the online leaderboards and unlock new monsters, bigger hotels and special rooms as you progress. <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel is a fast paced game where you must look after a hotel with a variety of very unusual guests! The inhabitants of Monster Hotel can be a fickle bunch, and keeping them sweet is going to be difficult.<BR><BR>Look for unhappy guests and drag them into different rooms that satisfy their needs - shuffle your monsters around to keep them all happy. The better you do the harder it gets!<BR><BR>Compete for the highest score on the online leaderboards and unlock new monsters, bigger hotels and special rooms as you progress. <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel is a fast paced game where you must look after a hotel with a variety of very unusual guests! The inhabitants of Monster Hotel can be a fickle bunch, and keeping them sweet is going to be difficult.<BR><BR>Look for unhappy guests and drag them into different rooms that satisfy their needs - shuffle your monsters around to keep them all happy. The better you do the harder it gets!<BR><BR>Compete for the highest score on the online leaderboards and unlock new monsters, bigger hotels and special rooms as you progress. <BR><BR>Package size: 26 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel es un juego de ritmo rápido en el que debe cuidar de un hotel con una variedad de invitados muy inusual! Los habitantes de Monster hotel puede ser un grupo inconstante, y mantenerlos dulce va a ser difícil.<BR><BR>Busque clientes insatisfechos y arrastrarlos a diferentes habitaciones que satisfagan sus necesidades - barajar sus monstruos alrededor para mantener a todos felices. Cuanto mejor lo hagas más difícil se hace!<BR><BR>Compite por la puntuación más alta en las tablas de clasificación online y desbloquear nuevos monstruos, grandes hoteles y habitaciones especiales a medida que avanza. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 26 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Hirviö Hotel on nopeatempoinen peli, jossa sinun täytyy huolehtia hotelli erilaisia ​​hyvin epätavallinen vieraita!Asukkaat Monster Hotelli voi olla oikullinen nippu, ja pitää ne makea tulee olemaan vaikeaa.<BR><BR>Etsi onneton vieraille ja vedä ne eri huoneisiin, jotka täyttävät heidän tarpeensa - shuffle hirviöitä ympärille pitää ne kaikki onnellisia.Paremmin teet vaikeampi se saa!<BR><BR>Kilpaile korkeimmat pisteet verkossa pistetaulukot ja avata uusia hirviöitä, suurimpien hotellien ja erityinen huoneita edetessä. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 26 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Monstre Hôtel est un jeu rapide où vous devez prendre soin d'un hôtel avec une variété de clients très inhabituelles! Les habitants de Monster Hôtel peuvent être un tas capricieux, et les garder doux va être difficile.<BR><BR>Rechercher des clients mécontents et faites-les glisser dans des pièces différentes qui répondent à leurs besoins - mélangez vos monstres autour de tous les garder heureux. Le mieux que vous faites le plus c'est difficile!<BR><BR>Compétition pour le meilleur score sur les classements en ligne et débloquer de nouveaux monstres, grands hôtels et des chambres spéciales que vous progressez. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 26 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Monstre Hôtel est un jeu rapide où vous devez prendre soin d'un hôtel avec une variété de clients très inhabituelles! Les habitants de Monster Hôtel peuvent être un tas capricieux, et les garder doux va être difficile.<BR><BR>Rechercher des clients mécontents et faites-les glisser dans des pièces différentes qui répondent à leurs besoins - mélangez vos monstres autour de tous les garder heureux. Le mieux que vous faites le plus c'est difficile!<BR><BR>Compétition pour le meilleur score sur les classements en ligne et débloquer de nouveaux monstres, grands hôtels et des chambres spéciales que vous progressez. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 26 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Mostro Hotel è un gioco veloce in cui si deve badare a un albergo con una varietà di ospiti molto particolari! Gli abitanti di mostro hotel può essere un po 'volubile, e tenerli dolce sta per essere difficile.<BR><BR>Cercare gli ospiti infelici e trascinarli in stanze diverse che soddisfano le loro esigenze - mischiare i tuoi mostri in giro per tenerli tutti felici. Il meglio che fai più diventa difficile!<BR><BR>Gareggia per il punteggio più alto sul classifiche online e sbloccare nuovi mostri, grandi alberghi e camere speciali come si procede. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 26 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[モンスターホテルはホテルの店長になり切り、様々な変わったお客様の管理をするというペースの速いゲームです！モンスターホテルに住んでいる者たちは気まぐれな方たちで、みんなを満足させるのはなかなか難しいでしょう。<BR><BR>不満で違う部屋へ勝手に移動してしまうお客に注意。そうなる前にお客のモンスターたちを移動させ、満足させよう。だが、うまくやればやるほどゲームの難易度も上昇！<BR><BR>ハイスコアとオンラインランキングのトップを目指し、新しいモンスター、もっと大きいホテル、特別な部屋などを手に入れよう。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 26 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel er et fartsfylt spill hvor du må lete etter et hotell med en rekke svært uvanlige gjester! Innbyggerne i Monster Hotel kan være en ustadig haug, og holde dem søte kommer til å bli vanskelig.<BR><BR>Se etter ulykkelige gjester og dra dem inn i forskjellige rom som tilfredsstiller deres behov - shuffle dine monstre rundt for å holde dem alle glade. Jo bedre du gjør det vanskeligere det blir!<BR><BR>Konkurrer om den høyeste poengsummen på ledertabellene online og låse opp nye monstre, større hoteller og spesielle rom som du avanserer. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 26 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel is een snel spel waar je moet kijken na een hotel met een verscheidenheid van zeer ongewone gasten! De inwoners van Monster Hotel kan een grillig bos zijn, en houden ze lief is zal moeilijk worden.<BR><BR>Kijk voor ontevreden gasten en sleep ze naar verschillende kamers die aan hun behoeften voldoen - shuffle je monsters rond om ze allemaal tevreden te houden. Hoe beter je het doet hoe moeilijker het wordt!<BR><BR>Strijden om de hoogste score op de online leaderboards en speel nieuwe monsters, grotere hotels en speciale kamers als je vooruitgang. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 26 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Monster Hotel är ett snabbt tempo spel där du måste leta efter ett hotell med en mängd mycket ovanliga gäster! Invånarna i Monster hotell kan vara en flyktig gäng, och hålla dem söta kommer att bli svårt.<BR><BR>Leta efter nöjda gäster och dra dem till olika rum som tillfredsställer deras behov - blanda dina monster runt för att hålla dem nöjda. Ju bättre du gör desto svårare blir det!<BR><BR>Tävla om den högsta poängen på nätet topplistorna och låsa upp nya monster, större hotell och speciella rum som du framsteg. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 26 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013, 2014 Xmpt Games Limited.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
