<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00138_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>166317840</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Menneskeheden er forsvundet i en alternativ version af Tokyo, og de dyr, der er tilbage, kæmper for livet. <BR>Der er kun ét mål – "Overlevelse". <BR>Alle former for dyr sætter livet på spil her i denne kamp for at overleve. <BR>Vælg dit yndlingsdyr blandt de 40 tilgængelige dyr, og gør alt, hvad du kan, for at overleve!<BR>Dyrenes kamp for overlevelse starter nu på PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 159 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[In einem alternativen Tokio, in dem die Menschheit bereits nicht mehr existiert, kämpfen die verbliebenen Tiere um ihr Leben. <BR>"Überleben" ist das einzige Ziel.<BR>Jedes Tier riskiert bei diesem Überlebenskampf sein Leben. <BR>Wähle aus über 40 Tieren dein Lieblingstier aus und versuche alles, was in deiner Macht steht, um nicht zu sterben!<BR>Der Überlebenskampf der Tiere beginnt jetzt bei PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 159 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Set in an alternate Tokyo where mankind has vanished, the animals that remain have to fight to stay alive. <BR>There is only one goal, "survival". <BR>Every kind of animal can be found risking its life here, in this struggle for lilfe. <BR>Choose your favorite animal out of over 40 available and do everything in your power to survive!<BR>The animals' fight for survival starts now on the PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Package size: 159 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Ambientado en un Tokio alternativo en el que la humanidad ha desaparecido, los animales supervivientes tienen que luchar para seguir con vida.<BR>Sólo hay un objetivo, la "supervivencia".<BR>Aquí encontrarás todo tipo de animales arriesgando su vida, luchando por sobrevivir.<BR>¡Escoge a tu animal favorito entre los más de 40 disponibles y haz todo lo que puedas para sobrevivir!<BR>¡La lucha de los animales por la supervivencia empieza ahora en PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 159 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Vaihtoehtoiseen Tokioon sijoittuva peli, missä ihmiskunta on kadonnut ja jäljelle jääneet eläimet taistelevat henkensä puolesta. <BR>Pelissä on vain yksi tavoite, selviytyminen. <BR>Jokainen eläin riskeeraa elämänsä kamppaillessaan selviytymisensä puolesta.<BR>Valitse suosikkieläimesi 40 eri vaihtoehdosta ja tee kaikkesi pitääksesi sen hengissä!<BR>Eläinten henkiinjäämiskamppailu alkaa nyt PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 159 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Dans un Tokyo où toute forme d'humanité s'est éteinte, les animaux doivent se battre pour rester en vie.<BR>Ils n'ont qu'un seul objectif : "survivre".<BR>Toutes les espèces animales s'affrontent dans ce même but.<BR>Choisissez votre animal préféré parmi les 40 espèces disponibles et faites tout ce qui est en votre pouvoir pour survivre !<BR>La lutte commence dès aujourd'hui sur PlayStation®Mobile ! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 159 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[In una Tokyo alternativa nella quale l'umanità è scomparsa, gli animali rimasti lottano per la vita.<BR>L'unico obiettivo è la sopravvivenza.<BR>Animali di ogni razza e genere combattono in questa guerra senza quartiere.<BR>Scegli il tuo animale preferito fra gli oltre 40 disponibili, e fai tutto ciò che è in tuo potere per sopravvivere!<BR>Il confronto finale tra gli animali inizia ora  su PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 159 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[人類が忽然と姿を消した東京を舞台に、動物たちのサバイバルが今、幕をあける<BR><BR>目的はただひとつ、『生きのびること』。<BR><BR>さまざまな動物たちが自らの命をかけ、この地で生存競争を繰り広げている。<BR><BR>40種類以上の動物の中から、好きな動物を選択し、あらゆる手をつくして生き延びろ！<BR><BR>動物たちのサバイバルがPlayStation®Mobileで今、始まる！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 159 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[I dette alternative universet har mennenskene forsvunnet fra Tokyo, og dyrene som er igjen må kjempe for å overleve.<BR>Kun ett mål; overlevelse!<BR>Her finner du alle slags dyr som risikerer livet sitt for å overleve.<BR>Velg ditt favorittdyr blant 40 forskjellige dyr, og gjør alt du kan for å overleve.<BR>Dyrenes kamp for overlevelse starter nå på PlayStation®Mobile. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 159 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[In een alternatieve versie van Tokio is de rol van de mensheid uitgespeeld. De overgebleven dieren vechten hier om de macht. <BR>Je hebt maar één doel: overleven. <BR>Elke diersoort waagt hier zijn leven in een wanhopige strijd om te overleven. <BR>Kies je favoriete dier uit 40 soorten en zet alles op alles om niet ten onder te gaan!<BR>De overlevingsstrijd begint nu op PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 159 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[I en framtida version av Tokyo har mänskligheten försvunnit och djuren som är kvar kämpar för sina liv.<BR>Det finns bara ett mål: "överlevnad". <BR>Alla djurarter här riskerar sina liv – i kampen för att få behålla dem.<BR>Välj ditt favoritdjur, bland över 40 tillgängliga, och gör allt i din makt för att överleva!<BR>Djurens kamp för att överleva börjar nu – på PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 159 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>© 2013 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
