<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00178_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>112954080</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Have det sjovt og nyde din kost med ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie!<BR><BR>"ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie Easy Diet" er en app til at registrere og støtte dine kostvaner med skulle illustrere og råd fra ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie der har været længe tilbedt siden sin fødsel i 1909.<BR><BR>Brugervenlig!<BR><BR>Input din vægt hver dag, og optage det, du spiste ved at vælge fra rullemenuen. Du kan få support beskeder og kost råd fra ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie som svar på din tilstand og indholdet af din kost!<BR><BR>features:<BR>· 30 Originale budskabskort kun tilgængelig med "ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie Easy Diet"!<BR>· Brugervenlig! Bare input din vægt ved at trykke på tallene, og optage det, du spiste ved at vælge fra rullemenuen.<BR>· Grafisk oversigt over ændringer i din vægt. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 108 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Viel Spaß und genießen Sie Ihre Ernährung mit ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE!<BR><BR>"ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE Easy-Diät" ist eine App, mit illustations und Ratschläge von ROSE O'Neill KEWPIE, die lange seit seiner Geburt im Jahre 1909 wurde angebetet hat, aufnehmen und unterstützen Sie Ihre Ernährungsgewohnheiten.<BR><BR>Benutzerfreundlich!<BR><BR>Geben Sie Ihr Gewicht jeden Tag und notieren, was Sie, indem Sie aus dem Pull-Down-Menü gegessen haben. Sie können Support-Meldungen und Diät-Tipps von ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE in Reaktion auf Ihren Zustand und die Inhalte Ihrer Diät! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 108 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Have fun and enjoy your diet with ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE!<BR><BR>"ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE’s Easy Diet" is an app to record and support your dietary habits with illustations and advice from ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE who has been long adored since its birth in 1909.<BR><BR>User friendly!<BR><BR>Input your weight every day and record what you ate by choosing from the pull-down menu. You can get support messages and diet advice from ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE in response to your condition and the contents of your diet!<BR><BR>Features:<BR>・30 Original message cards only available with "ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE’s Easy Diet“!<BR>・User friendly! Just input your weight by tapping the numbers, and record what you ate by choosing from the pull-down menu.<BR>・Graphical overview of changes in your weight. <BR><BR>Package size: 108 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Divertirse y disfrutar de su dieta con ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE!<BR><BR>"Easy Diet de ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE" es una aplicación para registrar y apoyar sus hábitos alimenticios con illustations y consejos de ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE que ha sido adorados mucho desde su nacimiento en 1909.<BR><BR>Fácil de usar!<BR><BR>Ingrese su peso todos los días y grabar lo que comió eligiendo en el menú desplegable. Usted puede obtener los mensajes de apoyo y consejo de la dieta de ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE en respuesta a su condición y el contenido de su dieta! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 108 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Pidä hauskaa ja nauti ruokavaliota ROSE O'Neill Kewpie!<BR><BR>"ROSE O'Neill Kewpie Easy Diet" on app tallentaa ja tukea ruokailutottumuksiin kanssa illustations ja neuvoja ROSE O'Neill Kewpie joka on pitkään ihailtu, koska sen syntymän vuonna 1909.<BR><BR>Käyttäjäystävällinen!<BR><BR>Painosi joka päivä ja tallentaa mitä söit valitsemalla alasvetovalikosta. Voit saada tukea viestejä ja ruokavalio neuvoja ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie vastauksena kunnossa ja sisällön ruokavalio!<BR><BR>ominaisuudet:<BR>· 30 Alkuperäinen viesti kortteja saatavana vain "ROSE O'Neill Kewpie Easy Diet"!<BR>· Käyttäjäystävällinen! Vain syöttö painosi napauttamalla numeroita ja tallentaa mitä söit valitsemalla alasvetovalikosta.<BR>· Graafisen muutoksia painon. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 108 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Amusez-vous et profitez de votre régime alimentaire avec ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE!<BR><BR>"Easy Diet ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE" est une application pour enregistrer et soutenir vos habitudes alimentaires avec Illustations et conseils de ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE qui a été longtemps adoré depuis sa naissance en 1909.<BR><BR>Convivial!<BR><BR>Saisissez votre poids tous les jours et d'enregistrer ce que vous avez mangé en choisissant dans le menu déroulant. Vous pouvez obtenir des messages de soutien et des conseils de régime de ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE en réponse à votre état et le contenu de votre régime! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 108 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Buon divertimento e godetevi la vostra dieta con ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie!<BR><BR>"Easy Dieta ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie" è un app per registrare e sostenere le vostre abitudini alimentari con illustations e consigli ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie che è stato a lungo adorato dalla sua nascita nel 1909.<BR><BR>Facile da usare!<BR><BR>Inserisci il tuo peso ogni giorno e registrare quello che hai mangiato scegliendo dal menu a discesa. È possibile ottenere messaggi di sostegno e consigli di dieta da ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie in risposta alla sua condizione e il contenuto della vostra dieta! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 108 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[ローズオニールキューピーと一緒に、気楽に楽しくダイエットをしよう！<BR>  <BR>『ローズオニールキューピーのゆるゆるダイエット』は、1909年の誕生以来長く愛され続けているキューピーがイラストやアドバイスで、あなたのダイエットを応援してくれるレコーディングダイエットアプリです。<BR>  <BR>基本操作は簡単！<BR>毎日の体重入力と食事内容をプルダウンから選択するだけ！<BR>入力された体重の増減や食事内容に合わせて、ローズオニールキューピーから応援のメッセージカードや、ダイエットアドバイスがもらえます！<BR>  <BR>【アプリの特徴】<BR>・『ローズオニールキューピーのゆるゆるダイエット』でしか手に入らない描き下ろしメッセージカードがもらえる！（全30種類）<BR>・【体重】タップ＆入力！と、【食事内容】プルダウンから選択！だけの簡単操作<BR>・グラフで体重の変化を確認できる<BR>・“ひとこと”機能で、日記としても使える！<BR>・栄養士によるアドバイスが読める！<BR>・ダイエット何日目か日数をカウントできる！<BR>・ダイエットに挫折しても日数カウントダウンをリセットできるから、気楽にダイエットできる！<BR>・アプリ起動時に、目標体重までの差が表示されるから励みになる！<BR>・セキュリティコードが設定できるから万が一誰かにアプリを起動されても体重がばれずに済みます <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 108 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Ha det gøy og nyte din diett med ROSE O'NEILL kewpie!<BR><BR>"ROSE O'NEILL kewpie Easy Diet" er en app for å ta opp og støtte dine kostvaner med illustations og råd fra ROSE O'NEILL kewpie som har vært lenge beundret siden sin fødsel i 1909.<BR><BR>Brukervennlig!<BR><BR>Input vekten din hver dag, og ta opp det du spiste ved å velge fra rullegardinmenyen. Du kan få støtte meldinger og kosthold råd fra ROSE O'NEILL kewpie som svar på din tilstand og innholdet i kostholdet ditt!<BR><BR>funksjoner:<BR>· 30 opprinnelige meldingen kort bare tilgjengelig med "ROSE O'NEILL kewpie Easy Diet"!<BR>· Brukervennlig! Bare innspill vekten din ved å trykke på tallene, og registrere hva du spiste ved å velge fra rullegardinmenyen.<BR>· Grafisk oversikt over endringer i vekten. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 108 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Veel plezier en geniet van uw dieet met ROSE O'NEILL Kewpie!<BR><BR>"ROSE O'NEILL kewpie Easy Diet" is een app om op te nemen en ondersteuning van uw voedingsgewoonten met illustations en advies van ROSE O'NEILL kewpie die al lang vereerd sinds haar geboorte in 1909.<BR><BR>Gebruiksvriendelijk!<BR><BR>Voer uw gewicht elke dag en opnemen wat je gegeten hebt door te kiezen uit het pull-down menu. U kunt ondersteuning berichten en voeding advies krijgen van ROSE O'NEILL kewpie in reactie op uw conditie en de inhoud van uw dieet! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 108 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Have fun and enjoy your diet with ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE!<BR><BR>"ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE’s Easy Diet" is an app to record and support your dietary habits with illustations and advice from ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE who has been long adored since its birth in 1909.<BR><BR>User friendly!<BR><BR>Input your weight every day and record what you ate by choosing from the pull-down menu. You can get support messages and diet advice from ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE in response to your condition and the contents of your diet!<BR><BR>Features:<BR>・30 Original message cards only available with "ROSE O'NEILL KEWPIE’s Easy Diet“!<BR>・User friendly! Just input your weight by tapping the numbers, and record what you ate by choosing from the pull-down menu.<BR>・Graphical overview of changes in your weight. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 108 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>ⒸROKI / ⒸSony Digital Entertainment<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:HealthAndFitness"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
