<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00015_00">
 <appVersion>1.05</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>13724704</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[アンダーラインはハイペースで中毒的な言葉遊びゲームです。入り乱れて変化し続ける文字のグリッドから言葉を見つけなければいけません。<br><br><br>文字が落ちてくる中、言葉を作ってグリッドからタイルを消していきます。グリッドがいっぱいになるか時間をかけすぎるとゲームオーバー！速く、上手にやることでスペシャルマルチプライヤーやボーナスが報酬として与えられます。スペシャルタイルは列を消すことや、「空白」文字として機能すること、またはスコアを倍にしてランキングのトップを競うことができます。ゲーム内で獲得するコインを使い、グリッドを消し、タイルをシャッフルし、スタートダッシュを与えるか時間を止める武器を購入しましょう。<br><br>ゲームプレイには以下のモードがあります：<br><br>クラシック―文字が画面上部から絶え間なく落ちてきて、長く生き残り良い得点を出すほど速度が上がります。マルチプライヤーやボーナスタイルを獲得、ボーナス連鎖でボードをクリアし、より高得点を出しましょう。<br><br>タイムアタック―クラシックモードにひねりを加えたようなものです。時計が常にチクタク鳴り、言葉を作ることで切らさないようにしなければいけません。言葉が長いほど時間が増えます。どれだけ生き残れるでしょうか？<br><br>ワードサーチ―このモードでは、文字のグリッドで始まり、2分以内にできる限り多くの言葉を見つけないといけません。言葉を取り除くたびに、新たな文字に置き換えられます。<br><br>全てのチャレンジをクリアして全トロフィーを解除できるでしょうか？<br><br>コンテンツ容量:14 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1-2人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)<br><br>著作権等:<br>Copyright (C) 2012 Albino Pixel Limited. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Underline is a fast-paced, addictive word game where you must find words in a jumbled and ever changing grid of letters.<br><br>Create words and clear the tiles off the grid while the letters drop, don't let the grid fill up or take too long otherwise its game over! You are rewarded for speed and skill with special multipliers and bonuses. These special tiles can clear rows, act as a 'blank' letter, or multiply your score as you compete to top the leaderboard. Use the coins you earn in-game to buy weapons which clear the grid, shuffle the tiles, give you a head start or even freeze time.<br><br>Gameplay is split over a number of modes including: <br><br>Classic - letters will constantly drop from the top of the screen getting faster the longer you last and the better you play. Earn multipliers and bonus tiles to clear the board with bonus chains and earn higher scores.<br><br>Time Attack - this is like Classic mode but with a twist, the clock is always ticking and you must try and keep it topped up by playing words; the longer the word the more time added to your clock. How long will you last?<br><br>Wordsearch- in this mode you start with a solid grid of letters and you have two minutes to find as many words as possible, each time you remove a word it will be replaced with fresh letters.<br><br>Can you complete all the challenges and unlock all the trophies?<br><br>Package size: 14 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1-2Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Albino Pixel Limited. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Underline vous fait jouer avec les mots avec son gameplay furieux et addictif qui vous demande de trouver des mots dans une grille de lettres en désordre et changeante.<br><br>Créez des mots pour vider la grille de ses tuiles pendant que des lettres tombent et la remplissent. La partie prendra fin si vous laissez la grille se remplir complètement ou si vous prenez trop de temps, alors attention  ! Votre vitesse et dextérité seront récompensées par l’intermédiaire de bonus spéciaux et autres multiplicateurs. Ces tuiles spéciales peuvent vider des lignes entières, faire office de tuiles “joker”, ou simplement multiplier votre score et vous propulser au sommet des classements. Utilisez les pièces que vous gagnez lors de vos parties pour acheter des armes capables de vider entièrement la grille, mélanger les tuiles,  vous donner de l’avance et même arrêter le temps.<br><br>Le jeu se compose de différents modes, tels que  :<br><br>Classique : des lettres tombent continuellement depuis le haut de l’écran et accélèrent à mesure que vous progressez. Gagnez des multiplicateurs ou des tuiles bonus, videz la grille en faisant des chaînes bonus et faites monter votre score.<br><br>Contre la montre : similaire au mode classique à cela près que le temps vous est compté. Un compte à rebours décompte le temps qu’il vous reste et vous devez constamment le remplir en créant des mots. Plus le mot sera long, plus le temps ajouté au compteur sera grand. Combien de temps tiendrez-vous  ?<br><br>Recherche de mots : dans ce mode, vous commencez avec une grille pré-remplie et vous avez deux minutes pour trouver autant de mots que possible. À chaque mot retiré, de nouvelles lettres apparaissent à sa place.<br><br>Êtes-vous capable de terminer tous les défis et débloquer tous les trophées ?<br><br>Taille du paquet: 14 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1-2joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Albino Pixel Limited. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Underline è un puzzle game a base di parole dal ritmo mozzafiato e incredibilmente appassionante in cui dovrai trovare nuove parole in una griglia di lettere che cambia in continuazione.<br><br>Scrivi le parole e svuota le caselle della griglia sotto una pioggia di lettere, non permettere che la griglia si riempia e agisci velocemente per non perdere il gioco! Sarai premiato per la tua velocità e abilità con moltiplicatori e bonus speciali. Questi premi speciali possono liberare righe di caselle, fungere da “spazio vuoto” o moltiplicare il tuo punteggio per aiutarti ad raggiungere la vetta della classifica. Usa le monete che guadagni nel corso del gioco per comprare armi per svuotare la griglia, mescolare le caselle, acquisire un vantaggio e persino bloccare il tempo.<br><br>Il gioco è suddiviso in diverse modalità, tra cui: <br><br>Classica: le lettere cadono costantemente dall’alto dello schermo, guadagnando velocità man mano che giochi più a lungo e con maggiore difficoltà. Guadagna moltiplicatori e bonus per svuotare la griglia con catene bonus e raggiungere punteggi più alti.<br><br>Sfida contro il tempo: simile alla modalità Classica ma con un elemento in più; l’orologio segna il tempo e tu devi cercare di non farlo esaurire creando delle parole: più lunga è una parola e più tempo verrà aggiunto al tuo orologio. Per quanto riuscirai a durare?<br><br>Parole intrecciate: in questa modalità parti con una griglia piena di lettere e hai due minuti per trovare più parole possibili; ogni volta che rimuovi una parola, questa sarà sostituita da nuove lettere.<br><br>Sarai in grado di completare tutte le sfide e sbloccare tutti i trofei?<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 14 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1-2giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Albino Pixel Limited. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Underline es un adictivo juego de palabras en el que debes encontrar palabras en una desordenada cuadrícula de letras que cambia constantemente.<br><br>Crea palabras y elimina las fichas de la cuadrícula mientras las letras van cayendo, ¡pero no dejes que la cuadrícula se llene ni tardes demasiado tiempo o la partida terminará! Según tu velocidad y habilidad, se te recompensará con multiplicadores y bonificaciones especiales. Estas fichas especiales pueden eliminar filas enteras, hacer de comodín o multiplicar tu puntuación para ayudarte a llegar a lo alto de la clasificación. Utiliza las monedas que ganes en el juego para comprar armas que despejan la cuadrícula, barajan las fichas, te dan ventaja al principio de la partida o incluso que paran el tiempo.<br><br>La mecánica de juego se divide en varios modos, como por ejemplo: <br><br>Clásico: las letras caen constantemente desde la parte superior de la pantalla, y aumentan la velocidad de caída a medida que aguantas más tiempo y juegas mejor. Gana multiplicadores y bonificaciones para despejar el tablero con cadenas y así ganar más puntos.<br><br>Contrarreloj: es como el modo Clásico pero con el añadido de que el reloj siempre está contando atrás, y debes crear palabras para ganar tiempo; cuanto más larga sea la palabra, más tiempo añadirás al reloj. ¿Cuánto tiempo aguantarás?<br><br>Buscar palabras: en este modo empiezas con la cuadrícula llena de letras, y tienes dos minutos para intentar encontrar tantas palabras como puedas. Cada vez que encuentres una palabra, aparecerán letras nuevas para sustituir las anteriores.<br><br>¿Podrás completar todos los desafíos y desbloquear todos los trofeos?<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 14 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1-2jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Albino Pixel Limited. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Underline ist ein flottes, fesselndes Wortspiel, bei dem man Begriffe in einem ungeordneten, sich ständig ändernden Buchstabenfeld finden muss.<br><br>Erzeuge Wörter und mach die Felder frei, während die Buchstaben fallen. Die Felder dürfen nicht komplett gefüllt werden und wenn du nicht schnell genug bist, dann ist das Spiel für dich vorbei! Für Schnelligkeit und Können wirst du mit besonderen Multiplikatoren und Bonussen belohnt. Diese speziellen Spielsteine können Reihen freimachen, als „Blanko-Buchstabe“ dienen oder deine Punktzahl im Kampf um die Spitzenposition in der Bestenliste multiplizieren. Mit den Münzen, die du im Spiel erhältst, kannst du Waffen kaufen, um das Spielfeld freizumachen, die Spielsteine zu mischen, dir einen Vorsprung zu verschaffen oder sogar die Zeit anzuhalten.<br><br>Das Spielerlebnis ändert sich je nach Spielmodus:<br><br>Klassisch: Buchstaben fallen ständig vom oberen Bildschirmrand und werden schneller, je länger man durchhält und desto besser man spielt. Erlange Multiplikatoren und Bonussteine, um das Spielfeld mit Bonusketten freizumachen und mehr Punkte zu erzielen.<br><br>Zeitangriff: Das ist wie der klassische Modus, aber die Zeit läuft dir davon. Mehr Zeit erhältst du durch Wörter. Je länger die Wörter, desto mehr Zeit erlangst du. Wie lange hältst du durch?<br><br>Wortsuche: Bei diesem Modus beginnt man mit einem Spielfeld, auf dem schon Buchstaben sind. Innerhalb von zwei Minuten muss man so viele Wörter wie möglich finden. Jedes entfernte Wort wird durch neue Buchstaben ersetzt.<br><br>Kannst du alle Herausforderungen meistern und alle Trophäen freischalten?<br><br>Paketgröße: 14 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1-2Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Albino Pixel Limited. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Underline is a fast-paced, addictive word game where you must find words in a jumbled and ever changing grid of letters.<br><br>Create words and clear the tiles off the grid while the letters drop, don't let the grid fill up or take too long otherwise its game over! You are rewarded for speed and skill with special multipliers and bonuses. These special tiles can clear rows, act as a 'blank' letter, or multiply your score as you compete to top the leaderboard. Use the coins you earn in-game to buy weapons which clear the grid, shuffle the tiles, give you a head start or even freeze time.<br><br>Gameplay is split over a number of modes including: <br><br>Classic - letters will constantly drop from the top of the screen getting faster the longer you last and the better you play. Earn multipliers and bonus tiles to clear the board with bonus chains and earn higher scores.<br><br>Time Attack - this is like Classic mode but with a twist, the clock is always ticking and you must try and keep it topped up by playing words; the longer the word the more time added to your clock. How long will you last?<br><br>Wordsearch- in this mode you start with a solid grid of letters and you have two minutes to find as many words as possible, each time you remove a word it will be replaced with fresh letters.<br><br>Can you complete all the challenges and unlock all the trophies?<br><br>Package size: 14 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1-2Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Albino Pixel Limited. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Underline vous fait jouer avec les mots avec son gameplay furieux et addictif qui vous demande de trouver des mots dans une grille de lettres en désordre et changeante.<br><br>Créez des mots pour vider la grille de ses tuiles pendant que des lettres tombent et la remplissent. La partie prendra fin si vous laissez la grille se remplir complètement ou si vous prenez trop de temps, alors attention  ! Votre vitesse et dextérité seront récompensées par l’intermédiaire de bonus spéciaux et autres multiplicateurs. Ces tuiles spéciales peuvent vider des lignes entières, faire office de tuiles “joker”, ou simplement multiplier votre score et vous propulser au sommet des classements. Utilisez les pièces que vous gagnez lors de vos parties pour acheter des armes capables de vider entièrement la grille, mélanger les tuiles,  vous donner de l’avance et même arrêter le temps.<br><br>Le jeu se compose de différents modes, tels que  :<br><br>Classique : des lettres tombent continuellement depuis le haut de l’écran et accélèrent à mesure que vous progressez. Gagnez des multiplicateurs ou des tuiles bonus, videz la grille en faisant des chaînes bonus et faites monter votre score.<br><br>Contre la montre : similaire au mode classique à cela près que le temps vous est compté. Un compte à rebours décompte le temps qu’il vous reste et vous devez constamment le remplir en créant des mots. Plus le mot sera long, plus le temps ajouté au compteur sera grand. Combien de temps tiendrez-vous  ?<br><br>Recherche de mots : dans ce mode, vous commencez avec une grille pré-remplie et vous avez deux minutes pour trouver autant de mots que possible. À chaque mot retiré, de nouvelles lettres apparaissent à sa place.<br><br>Êtes-vous capable de terminer tous les défis et débloquer tous les trophées ?<br><br>Taille du programme: 14 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1-2joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Albino Pixel Limited. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
  <genre value="Games:Arcade"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
