<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPQA00107_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>242592112</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Betreten Sie die Welt von Märchen und Spaß! Gehen Sie mit Hänsel und Gretel auf ein Abenteuer, dass Sie noch nie zuvor erlebt haben. Basierend auf Grimms Märchen wirbeln die im Wald verloren gegangenen Kinder die Geschichten durcheinander und durchleben sie neu in einer Serie von Rätseln. Helfen Sie Hänsel und Gretel, der bösen Hexe zu entkommen, dabei aber auch jede Menge Süßigkeiten zu ergattern. Die Kinder müssen sicher durch Fallen und Gefahren jedes Levels gelotst werden. Mit Kleverness und der richtigen Nutzung der Stärken von Hänsel und Gretel können Sie sie sicher durch die einzelnen Schwierigkeitsstufen bringen. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 232 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>Copyright © XPEC Entertainment INC. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Enter the world of fairy tales and fun! Embark on an adventure with Hansel and Gretel in a world like you’ve never experienced before. Based on the Grimm Fairy Tales, The Lost Kids turns the age old fairy tales on their heads and gives them new life through a series of episodic puzzle quests. Help Hansel and Gretel avoid the evil witch while trying to get the sweets. Pitfalls and dangers abound as you strategize how to lead the Lost Kids through each level. Use your smarts to level up by utilizing the different strengths of Hansel and Gretel. <BR><BR>Package size: 232 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright © XPEC Entertainment INC. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>¡Ingresa al mundo de los cuentos de hadas y de la diversión! Embárcate en una aventura con Hansel y Gretel en un mundo como nunca has experimentado antes. Basado en los cuentos de hadas de Grimm, Los Niños Perdidos cambian los viejos cuentos de hadas y dan una nueva vida a través de una serie de misiones de rompecabezas episódicos. Ayuda a Hansel y Gretel a evitar la malvada bruja mientras que intenta conseguir los dulces. Los escollos y peligros abundan en cuanto tú elaboras estrategias de cómo llevar a los niños perdidos a través de cada nivel. Usa tu inteligencia para subir de nivel mediante la utilización de las diferentes fortalezas de Hansel y Gretel. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 232 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>Copyright © XPEC Entertainment INC. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Entrez dans le monde des contes de fées et de l'amusement ! Embarquez-vous dans une aventure avec Hansel et Gretel dans un monde où vous n'avez jamais vécu auparavant. Basé sur les Contes de Fées de Grimm. Les Enfants Perdus transforme les contes de fées historiques et leur donne une nouvelle vie à travers d'une série de recherches épisodiques de casse-têtes.  Aidez Hansel et Gretel a éviter la méchante sorcière tout en essayant d'obtenir les bonbons. Les pièges et les dangers abondent pendant que vous élaborer des stratégies pour mener les Enfants Perdus à travers chaque niveau. Employez votre intelligence pour monter de niveau en utilisant les différentes forces de Hansel et de Gretel. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 232 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright © XPEC Entertainment INC. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Entra nel mondo delle storie delle fate e divertiti! Imbarcati per l'avventuta con Hansel e Gretel in un modo che non hai mai provato fino ad ora. Basato su racconto fantastico dei fratelli Grimm, i Bimbi Sperduti modificano le vecchie storie di streghe nella loro mente e danno loro una nuova vita attraverso una serie di ricerca attraverso puzzle episodici. Aiuta Hanesel e Gretel a evitare la strega malvagia mentre tentano di raggiungere i dolci. Insidie e pericoli abbondano mentre tu studi strategie per condurre i Bimbi Sperduti attraverso ciascun livello. Utilizza la tua intelligenza per salire di livello utilizzando i differenti punti forti di Hansel and Gretel. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 232 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>Copyright © XPEC Entertainment INC. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>フェアリーテイルズの世界へようこそ！<BR>ヘンゼルとグレーテルと一緒に、今まで感じたことのない冒険に旅立とう！<BR><BR>グリム童話をベースとし、The Lost Kidsは以前のフェアリーテイルズにひと味加えた、エピソード型迷路クエストです。<BR><BR>ヘンゼルとグレーテルがお菓子を探している時、邪悪な魔女に捕まらないように手助けをし、<BR>罠や危険を顧みず、道に迷っている子どもたちを導こう！<BR>あなたの知恵で、ヘンゼルとグレーテルの長所をどんどん伸ばそう！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 232 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright © XPEC Entertainment INC. All rights reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:BrainTraining"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
