<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00213_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>11457072</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - en tid til at klæde op, skære græskar og samle herlige mængder af slik! For at indsamle nok slik, en gang rundt i nabolaget vil bare ikke gøre - du kommer til at bruge flere forskellige kostumer at trække det ud. <BR><BR>  - Klassisk eventyrspil sjovt. <BR>  - Udforsk en munter, interaktiv verden og løse gåder. <BR>  - Søg dit hus og nabolaget for, hvad du behøver at gøre kostumer. <BR>  - Carve din egen græskar. <BR>  - Go trick-or-behandling, og indsamle det søde, søde slik. <BR><BR>Lad intet stoppe dig fra at få din rimelig andel - og meget mere! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 11 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - eine Zeit, sich zu verkleiden, schnitzen Kürbisse und sammeln glorreichen Mengen von Süßigkeiten! Um genügend Süßigkeiten sammeln, einmal in der Nachbarschaft einfach nicht tun - Sie gehen zu verschiedenen Kostüme brauchen, um es auszuziehen. <BR><BR>  - Klassisches Adventure-Spiel Spaß. <BR>  - Entdecken Sie eine unbe, interaktive Welt und Rätsel lösen. <BR>  - Suchen Sie Ihr Haus und die Nachbarschaft für das, was Sie brauchen, um Kostüme zu machen. <BR>  - Schnitzen Sie Ihren eigenen Kürbis. <BR>  - Gehen Trick-or-Behandlung und sammeln diese süße, süße Süßigkeiten. <BR><BR>Lassen Sie nichts stoppen Sie davon ab, Ihren gerechten Anteil - und mehr! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 11 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - a time to dress up, carve pumpkins and amass glorious amounts of candy! In order to collect enough candy, once around the neighborhood just won't do - you are going to need several different costumes to pull it off.<BR><BR> - Classic adventure game fun.<BR> - Explore a lighthearted, interactive world and solve puzzles.<BR> - Search your house and the neighborhood for what you need to make costumes.<BR> - Carve your own pumpkin.<BR> - Go trick-or-treating and collect that sweet, sweet candy.<BR><BR>Let nothing stop you from getting your fair share - and more! <BR><BR>Package size: 11 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - un tiempo para vestir, tallar calabazas y acumular cantidades gloriosos de caramelo! Con el fin de recoger suficientes dulces, una vez por el barrio no va a hacer - usted va a necesitar varios trajes diferentes para llevarlo a cabo. <BR><BR>  - Classic divertido juego de aventuras. <BR>  - Explorar un mundo interactivo alegre y resolver puzzles. <BR>  - Busca en tu casa y el barrio por lo que necesita para hacer trajes. <BR>  - Tallar su propia calabaza. <BR>  - Go-truco o trato y recoger ese dulce, dulce de caramelo. <BR><BR>No dejes que nada te impida conseguir su parte justa - y mucho más! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 11 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - aika pukeutua, veistää kurpitsat ja koota loistava määriä karkkia! Jotta kerätä tarpeeksi karkkia, kun ympäri lähiseutua vain ei tehdä - olet menossa tarvitsevat useita erilaisia ​​pukuja vetää se pois. <BR><BR>  - Klassinen seikkailupeli hauskaa. <BR>  - Tutki hilpeä, interaktiivinen maailma ja ratkaista arvoituksia. <BR>  - Etsi talosi ja naapuruston mitä sinun täytyy tehdä pukuja. <BR>  - Carve oma kurpitsa. <BR>  - Go temppu-tai-hoitoon ja kerätä lisää suloista karkkia. <BR><BR>Älä anna minkään estää sinua saamasta oman osansa - ja enemmän! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 11 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - un temps de s'habiller, sculpter des citrouilles et amasser des quantités glorieux de bonbons! Afin de recueillir suffisamment de sucre, une fois dans le quartier ne veut tout simplement pas faire - vous allez avoir besoin de plusieurs costumes différents pour le retirer. <BR><BR>  - Classique amusant jeu d'aventure. <BR>  - Explorez un monde interactif léger et résoudre des énigmes. <BR>  - Cherchez dans votre maison et le quartier pour ce que vous devez faire des costumes. <BR>  - Découper votre propre citrouille. <BR>  - Aller trick-or-treat et de recueillir que doux, bonbon sucré. <BR><BR>Que rien ne vous empêche de faire votre juste part - et plus encore! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 11 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - un tempo per vestire, intagliare zucche e accumulare quantità gloriosi di caramelle! Al fine di raccogliere abbastanza caramelle, una volta che tutto il quartiere proprio non lo farà - si sta per bisogno di diversi costumi differenti per tirarlo fuori. <BR><BR>  - Classico gioco divertente avventura. <BR>  - Esplora un mondo interattivo spensierato e risolvere enigmi. <BR>  - Ricerca la vostra casa e il quartiere per ciò che è necessario fare i costumi. <BR>  - Carve tua zucca. <BR>  - Go trick-or-treat e raccogliere quel dolce, dolce caramella. <BR><BR>Che nulla ti impedisce di ottenere la vostra parte equa - e molto altro! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 11 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>ああ、ハロウィン - 時間は、ドレスアップカボチャを彫るとお菓子の栄光の量を蓄積するために！かつて近所の周りだけで行うことはありません、十分なキャンディーを収集するために - あなたはそれをやってのけるためにいくつかのさまざまな衣装を必要としています。 <BR><BR>  - クラシックアドベンチャーゲームの楽しみ。 <BR>  - 気軽に、インタラクティブな世界を探検しパズルを解く。 <BR>  - あなたが衣装を作るために必要なもののためにあなたの家や近所を検索します。 <BR>  - あなた自身のカボチャを彫る。 <BR>  - トリックまたは治療を行って、その甘い、甘いお菓子を集める。 <BR><BR>何があなたの公正な取り分を得ることからあなたを停止しないしましょう​​ - ともっと！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 11 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - en tid for å kle seg, skjære gresskar og samle strålende mengder godteri! For å samle inn nok godteri, en gang rundt i nabolaget bare ikke vil gjøre - er du kommer til å trenge flere forskjellige kostymer å trekke den av. <BR><BR>  - Klassisk eventyrspill moro. <BR>  - Utforsk en munter, interaktiv verden og løse gåter. <BR>  - Søk huset og nabolaget for hva du trenger for å lage kostymer. <BR>  - Skjære dine egne gresskar. <BR>  - Gå trick-or-behandling og samle den søte, søte drops. <BR><BR>La noe stoppe deg fra å få en god del - og mer! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 11 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - een tijd om te kleden, carve pompoenen en vergaren glorieuze hoeveelheden snoep! Om voldoende snoep te verzamelen, een keer door de buurt gewoon niet doen - je gaat naar verschillende kostuums nodig om het af te trekken. <BR><BR>  - Classic adventure game plezier. <BR>  - Ontdek een luchtige, interactieve wereld en puzzels op te lossen. <BR>  - Zoek uw huis en de buurt voor wat je nodig hebt om kostuums te maken. <BR>  - Carve je eigen pompoen. <BR>  - Ga trick-or-behandeling en het verzamelen van dat zoete, zoete snoep. <BR><BR>Laat niets te stoppen van het krijgen van uw billijk aandeel - en nog veel meer! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 11 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - czas, aby ubierać się, rzeźbić dynie i zgromadzić wspaniałych ilości cukierków! W celu zebrania wystarczającej ilości słodyczy, raz po okolicy po prostu nie zrobi - będziesz potrzebować kilka różnych kostiumów wyciągnąć go. <BR><BR>  - Klasyczna gra zręcznościowa zabawa. <BR>  - Poznaj się beztroska, interaktywny świat i rozwiązywać zagadki. <BR>  - Znajdź swój dom i okolicę na to, czego potrzebujesz, aby kostiumy. <BR>  - Carve swoją dynię. <BR>  - Idź trick-or-leczenia i zbierać ten słodki, słodki cukierek. <BR><BR>Niech nic nie powstrzyma cię od zaczyna swój sprawiedliwy udział - i wiele więcej! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 11 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Ahh, Halloween - en tid att klä upp, tälja pumpor och samla härliga mängder av godis! För att samla in tillräckligt med godis, en gång runt kvarteret bara inte kommer att göra - du kommer att behöva flera olika kostymer för att dra bort det. <BR><BR>  - Klassiskt äventyrsspel kul. <BR>  - Utforska en lättsam, interaktiv värld och lösa pussel. <BR>  - Sök ditt hus och grannskapet för det du behöver för att göra kostymer. <BR>  - Rista din egen pumpa. <BR>  - Gå bus eller godis och samla den söta, söta godis. <BR><BR>Låt ingenting hindra dig från att få din beskärda del - och mycket mer! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 11 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Adventure"/><genre value="Games:Family"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Fear.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
