<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00007_00">
 <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>19572656</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="ja">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[『快感足つぼマッサージ』は、女の子の足つぼをキモチよくマッサージし、ほぐしてあげるゲームです。<br>画面上で指定される女の子のつぼを、あなたの指でグリグリとマッサージしてあげてください。<br>つぼをほぐしてステージクリアすると、色々なポーズで別のつぼを求めてきますので、どんどん刺激していきましょう。<br>同じ場所でもマッサージのしかたで得点が変わるのがプレイのコツ。ハイスコアを出せばご褒美ポーズを見せてくれるので、<br>時間切れに注意しながら女の子のつぼをほぐしてしていきましょう！<br><br>・500枚以上の撮影データで再現されたリアルなモジモジ感！<br>・スコアに応じて女の子のお宝画像が！<br>・女の子のモジモジボイス入り！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:19 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<br><br>著作権等:<br>Copyright (C) 2012 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage)is a game to rub around pinky spots of a girl's leg, and to make a girl happy. <br>The girl will point wanted spots, then give your fingers to massage (rub around it).<br>When the girl becomes happy, other spots will be asked by various poses. <br>So, you can make her happier.<br>Even in the same spot, your way to rub (massage) changes the score.<br>When you get high scores, the girl show you various poses as bonus.<br>Challenge how much you can make her happy.<br>・Over 500 taking a picture data reproduces realistic squirming!<br>・The special image, the score and more!<br>・In the bashfully girl voice!<br><br>Package size: 19 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/Japanese<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) est un jeu de frotter les taches rosâtres autour de la jambe d'une jeune fille, et de faire une petite fille heureuse.<br>La jeune fille va pointer endroits voulus, puis donnez vos doigts pour masser (frotter autour de lui).<br>Quand la jeune fille devient heureux, d'autres taches seront posées par diverses poses.<br>Ainsi, vous pouvez lui faire plus heureux.<br>Même au même endroit, le chemin se frotter (massage) modifie le score.<br>Lorsque vous obtenez des scores élevés, la jeune fille vous montrer des poses variées en prime.<br>Défiez combien vous pouvez vous rendre heureuse.<br><br>· Plus de 500 prenant une photo reproduit les données réalistes tortiller!<br>· L'image spéciale, le score et plus encore!<br>· Dans la voix fille timide!<br><br>Taille du paquet: 19 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) è un gioco di strofinare intorno macchie mignolo della gamba di una ragazza, e per fare una ragazza felice.<br>La ragazza punterà punti desiderati, poi dare le dita per massaggio (strofinare intorno ad esso).<br>Quando la ragazza diventa felice, altri punti verrà chiesto da varie pose.<br>Quindi, si può farla più felice.<br>Anche nello stesso punto, il vostro modo di strofinare (massaggio) cambia il punteggio.<br>Quando si ottiene punteggi più alti, la ragazza visualizzare varie pose come bonus.<br>Sfida quanto si può renderla felice.<br><br>· Oltre 500 prendendo un dati di immagine riproduce realistico dimenarsi!<br>· L'immagine particolare, il punteggio e di più!<br>· Nella voce ragazza timidamente!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 19 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) es un juego de frotar alrededor de los puntos rosados de la pierna de una chica, y hacer que una chica feliz.<br>La chica se señalan los puntos deseados, a continuación, dar masaje a los dedos (frotar alrededor de él).<br>Cuando la niña llega a ser felices, otros lugares se le preguntará por varias actitudes.<br>Por lo tanto, usted puede hacer más feliz.<br>Incluso en el mismo lugar, a tu manera de frotar (masaje) cambia la puntuación.<br>Cuando usted consigue altas calificaciones, la chica le mostrará varias poses como bonus.<br>Desafía a la cantidad que puede hacerla feliz.<br><br>· Más de 500 datos tomando un cuadro realista reproduce retorcerse!<br>· La imagen especial, la puntuación y mucho más!<br>· En la voz tímidamente chica!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 19 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) ist ein Spiel um pinky Stellen eines Mädchens Bein zu reiben, und um ein Mädchen glücklich.<br>Das Mädchen wird darauf wanted Flecken, dann geben Sie Ihre Finger zu massieren (rub um ihn herum).<br>Als das Mädchen glücklich wird, werden andere Flecken von verschiedenen Posen gestellt werden.<br>So können Sie sie glücklicher machen.<br>Auch an der gleichen Stelle, ändert Ihren Weg zu reiben (Massage) die Partitur.<br>Wenn Sie hohe Punktzahlen zu bekommen, zeigen das Mädchen Ihnen verschiedene als Bonus darstellt.<br>Fordern Sie, wie viel Sie sie glücklich machen.<br><br>· Mehr als 500 der Aufnahme eines Bildes wiedergibt realistische winden!<br>· Das besondere Bild, die Gäste und vieles mehr!<br>· In der verschämt Mädchen Stimme!<br><br>Paketgröße: 19 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage)is a game to rub around pinky spots of a girl's leg, and to make a girl happy. <br>The girl will point wanted spots, then give your fingers to massage (rub around it).<br>When the girl becomes happy, other spots will be asked by various poses. <br>So, you can make her happier.<br>Even in the same spot, your way to rub (massage) changes the score.<br>When you get high scores, the girl show you various poses as bonus.<br>Challenge how much you can make her happy.<br><br>・Over 500 taking a picture data reproduces realistic squirming!<br>・The special image, the score and more!<br>・In the bashfully girl voice!<br><br>Package size: 19 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/Japanese<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) est un jeu de frotter les taches rosâtres autour de la jambe d'une jeune fille, et de faire une petite fille heureuse.<br>La jeune fille va pointer endroits voulus, puis donnez vos doigts pour masser (frotter autour de lui).<br>Quand la jeune fille devient heureux, d'autres taches seront posées par diverses poses.<br>Ainsi, vous pouvez lui faire plus heureux.<br>Même au même endroit, le chemin se frotter (massage) modifie le score.<br>Lorsque vous obtenez des scores élevés, la jeune fille vous montrer des poses variées en prime.<br>Défiez combien vous pouvez vous rendre heureuse.<br><br>· Plus de 500 prenant une photo reproduit les données réalistes tortiller!<br>· L'image spéciale, le score et plus encore!<br>· Dans la voix fille timide!<br><br>Taille du programme: 19 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Casual"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_16.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Sex.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
