<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00319_00">

  <appVersion>2.10</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>4262192</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Endelig for Twitter "UserStream" tilsvarende app optrådte!<BR><BR>Driften<BR>Venstre pind: Timeline rulle hurtigt, bevæger på tidspunktet for billedvisning<BR>Højre pind: Skalaen på tidspunktet for display billede<BR>□ knap: Hent på tidspunktet for display billede<BR><BR>og funktioner<BR>Tweet (",." Eller "、。" Mulige linjeskift)<BR>Multiple billede vedhæftet Tweets<BR>Fast sætning funktion (automatisk tilføje tegn til tweet slutningen)<BR>Retweet, Foretrukne, og slette sin, svar<BR>tweet Slet<BR>LinkShare (citat RT, billede citation, anden URL)<BR>At åbne linket i en browser<BR>billede download<BR><BR>Og visning af brugeroplysninger<BR>Tweet, favorit, header, Se profil<BR><BR>※ Denne app vil formidlingen af stor kapacitet. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 4163 KB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Schließlich von Twitter "UserStream" entsprechende App erschienen!<BR><BR>-Betrieb<BR>Linker Stick: Timeline schnelles Scrollen, Bewegen zum Zeitpunkt der Bildanzeige<BR>Rechter Stick: Skala zur Zeit Anzeigebild<BR>□ Taste: Download zum Zeitpunkt Anzeigebild<BR><BR>und Funktionen<BR>Tweet (",." Oder "、。" Mögliche Zeilenumbruch)<BR>Multiple Bildanhang Tweets<BR>Festen Satz Funktion (automatische fügen jedes Zeichen, um das Ende tweet)<BR>Retweet, Favoriten, und löschen ihre, antworten<BR>Tweet löschen<BR>Linkshare (Zitat RT, Bildzitat, andere URL)<BR>Um den Link in einem Browser öffnen<BR>Bild-Download<BR><BR>Und Anzeige von Benutzerinformationen<BR>Tweet, Lieblings, header, Profil ansehen<BR><BR>※ Diese App wird die Kommunikation mit großer Kapazität. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 4163 KB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Finally of Twitter "UserStream" corresponding app appeared!<BR><BR>-Operation<BR>Left stick: Timeline fast scrolling, moving at the time of image display<BR>Right stick: The scale at the time of display image<BR>□ button: Download at the time of display image<BR><BR>And functions<BR>Tweet (",." Or "、。" Possible line break)<BR>Multiple image attachment Tweets<BR>Fixed sentence function (automatic add any character to tweet the end)<BR>Retweet, Favorites, and delete its, reply<BR>Tweet Delete<BR>LinkShare (quote RT, image citation, other URL)<BR>To open the link in a browser<BR>Image download<BR><BR>And display of user information<BR>Tweet, favorite, header, View Profile<BR><BR>※ This app will the communication of large capacity. <BR><BR>Package size: 4163 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Finalmente de Twitter "UserStream" correspondiente aplicación apareció!<BR><BR>-Operación<BR>Palo izquierdo: Cronología desplazamiento rápido, moviéndose en el momento de presentación de la imagen<BR>Palo derecho: La escala a la hora imagen de la pantalla de<BR>□ botón: Descargar en el momento de la imagen de la pantalla<BR><BR>y funciones<BR>Tweet (",." O "、。" Salto de línea Posible)<BR>Archivo adjunto de imagen múltiple Tweets<BR>Función sentencia fija (automático añadir cualquier carácter tweet final)<BR>Retweet, Favoritos, y borrar su, contestación<BR>Tweet Eliminar<BR>LinkShare (cita RT, la imagen de la citación, otra URL)<BR>Para abrir el enlace en un navegador<BR>descarga de imagen<BR><BR>Y visualización de la información del usuario<BR>Tweet, favorito, cabecera, Ver Perfil<BR><BR>※ Esta aplicación va a la comunicación de gran capacidad. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 4163 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Lopuksi Twitter "UserStream" vastaten app ilmestyi!<BR><BR>asemien välinen toiminto<BR>Vasen stick: Timeline nopea vieritys, liikkuvat aikaan kuvan näyttö<BR>Oikea stick: asteikko aikaan näytön kuva<BR>□ -painike: Lataa aikaan näytön kuva<BR><BR>ja toiminnot<BR>Tweet (",." Or "、。" Mahdolliset rivinvaihto)<BR>Useita kuvaliitteen Tweets<BR>Kiinteä lause toiminto (automaattinen lisätä merkin piipittää loppuun)<BR>Retweet, suosikit, ja poistaa sen, vastata<BR>Tweet Poista<BR>LinkShare (lainaus RT, kuva lainaus, muut URL)<BR>Voit avata linkin selaimessa<BR>lataa kuva<BR><BR>Ja näyttö käyttäjän tiedot<BR>Tweet, suosikki, header, Kirjattu<BR><BR>※ Tämä sovellus viestintää suuren kapasiteetin. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 4163 Kt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Enfin de Twitter "UserStream" correspondant app est apparu!<BR><BR>-operation<BR>Joystick gauche: Chronologie défilement rapide, se déplacer au moment de l'affichage de l'image<BR>Bâton de droite: L'échelle à l'image en temps d'affichage des<BR>□ bouton: Télécharger l'image au moment de l'affichage de<BR><BR>et fonctions<BR>Tweet (",." Ou pause "、。" Ligne possible)<BR>Multiples points de fixation d'image Tweets<BR>Fonction de peine fixe (automatique ajouter un caractère de tweeter la fin)<BR>Retweet, Favoris, et supprimer son, répondent<BR>Tweet Supprimer<BR>LinkShare (citation RT, l'image citation, autre URL)<BR>Pour ouvrir le lien dans un navigateur<BR>téléchargement d'images<BR><BR>Et l'affichage des informations de l'utilisateur<BR>Tweet, favori, tête, Voir le profil<BR><BR>※ Cette application va de la communication de grande capacité. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 4163 Ko - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Infine di Twitter "UserStream" corrispondente app è apparso!<BR><BR>-Funzionamento<BR>Bastone Sinistra: Timeline scorrimento veloce, si muove a tempo di visualizzazione delle immagini<BR>Levetta destra: La scala al momento visualizzazione immagine di<BR>□ bottone: Scarica all'epoca immagine visualizzazione<BR><BR>e FUNZIONI<BR>Tweet (",." O "、。" Interruzione possibile linea)<BR>Immagine allegata multipla Tweets<BR>Funzione frase fissa (automatica aggiungere qualsiasi carattere di tweet alla fine)<BR>Retweet, Preferiti e cancellare il suo, rispondono<BR>Tweet Elimina<BR>LinkShare (citazione RT, immagine citazione, altro URL)<BR>Per aprire il link in un browser<BR>Immagine scaricare<BR><BR>E visualizzazione delle informazioni dell'utente<BR>Tweet, favorito, intestazione, Connesso<BR><BR>※ Questa applicazione la comunicazione di grande capacità. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 4163 KB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>遂にTwitterの「UserStream」対応アプリが登場！<BR><BR>・操作<BR>左スティック : タイムライン高速スクロール、画像表示時に移動<BR>右スティック : 画像表示時に拡大縮小 <BR>□ボタン :　画像表示時にダウンロード<BR><BR>・機能<BR>ツイート（「,.」もしくは「、。」で改行可能）<BR>複数画像添付ツイート<BR>固定文機能（ツイート末尾に任意の文字を自動追加）<BR>Retweet、Favorites、及びその削除、reply<BR>ツイート削除<BR>リンクシェア（引用RT、画像引用、その他URL）<BR>リンクをブラウザでオープン<BR>画像ダウンロード<BR><BR>・ユーザー情報の表示<BR>ツイート、お気に入り、ヘッダー、プロフィールの表示<BR><BR>※本アプリは大容量の通信をします。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 4163 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Endelig på Twitter "UserStream" tilsvarende app dukket opp!<BR><BR>Driften<BR>Venstre spak: Tidslinje rask rulling, flytte på tidspunktet for bildevisning<BR>Høyre pinne: Skalaen på tidspunktet for visningen av bildet<BR>□ knapp: Last ned samtidig med skjerm bilde<BR><BR>og funksjoner<BR>Tweet (",." Eller "、。" Mulig linjeskift)<BR>Multiple bildevedlegg Tweets<BR>Fast setning funksjon (automatisk legge alle tegn til å tweet slutten)<BR>Retweet, Favoritter, og slette sin, svare<BR>Tweet Slett<BR>Linkshare (sitat RT, image sitat, annet URL)<BR>Å åpne koblingen i en nettleser<BR>Bilde nedlasting<BR><BR>Og visning av brukerinformasjon<BR>Tweet, favoritt, header, Loggført<BR><BR>※ Denne applikasjonen vil kommunikasjon av stor kapasitet. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 4163 KB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Tot slot van Twitter "UserStream" bijbehorende app verschenen!<BR><BR>-Operation<BR>Linker joystick: Timeline snel scrollen, bewegen op het moment van de beeldweergave<BR>Rechter joystick: De schaal op het moment van de beeldweergave<BR>□ knop: Download bij de beeldweergave van<BR><BR>en functies<BR>Tweet (",." Or "、。" Mogelijke line break)<BR>Attachment meerdere image Tweets<BR>Vaste zin-functie (automatische toevoegen karakter aan het einde tweet)<BR>Retweet, favorieten, en haar verwijderen, beantwoorden<BR>Tweet Verwijder<BR>LinkShare (citaat RT, het citaat, andere URL)<BR>Om de link in een browser te openen<BR>afbeelding downloaden<BR><BR>En weergave van informatie voor de gebruiker<BR>Tweet, favoriet, header, Bekijk profiel<BR><BR>※ Deze app zal de communicatie van grote capaciteit. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 4163 KB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Wreszcie pojawiła się na Twitterze "UserStream" odpowiada aplikacja!<BR><BR>-operacja<BR>Lewy drążek: Timeline przewijanie, przesuwając w czasie wyświetlania obrazu<BR>Prawy drążek: waga w czasie wyświetlania obrazu<BR>Przycisk □: Pobierz w czasie wyświetlania obrazu<BR><BR>i funkcje<BR>Tweet (",." A "、。" Przerwa Możliwe linia)<BR>Obraz Tweety wielokrotnego mocowania<BR>Funkcja Fixed zdanie (automatyczne dodać dowolny znak tweet koniec)<BR>Prześlij dalej, Ulubione, a usunięcie jej, odpowiadać<BR>Tweet Usuń<BR>LinkShare (cytat RT, obraz cytat, inne URL)<BR>Aby otworzyć link w przeglądarce<BR>pobierz zdjęcie<BR><BR>I wyświetlanie informacji o użytkowniku<BR>Tweet, ulubione, nagłówek, Pokaż profil<BR><BR>※ Ta aplikacja będzie przekazywanie dużej pojemności. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 4163 KB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Slutligen av Twitter "UserStream" motsvarande app dök upp!<BR><BR>-funktionen<BR>Vänster stick: Tidslinje snabb bläddring, rör sig med tiden för bildvisning<BR>Höger pinne: Skalan vid tidpunkten för visningsbild<BR>□ knapp: Hämta vid tidpunkten för visningsbild<BR><BR>och funktioner<BR>Tweet (",." Eller "、。" Möjlig radbrytning)<BR>Flerbilds fastsättning Tweets<BR>Fast meningen funktion (automatisk lägga alla tecken att tweet slutet)<BR>Retweet, favoriter, och ta bort den, svara<BR>tweet Radera<BR>Linkshare (citat RT, bild stämning, andra URL)<BR>Om du vill öppna länken i en webbläsare<BR>bild nedladdning<BR><BR>Och visning av användarinformation<BR>Tweet, favorit, sidhuvud, Loggat<BR><BR>※ Denna app kommer kommunikationen med stor kapacitet. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 4163 KB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>(C) 2015 Matsudamper<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:SocialNetworking"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_18.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_22.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_16.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_17.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_21.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_14.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_19.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_20.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
