<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00187_00">

  <appVersion>2.26</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>158837008</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Spiller som en RAPTOR at udforske, jagt og overleve i store smukke omgivelser!<BR>Kæmp mod en Mecha T-Rex på månen i lav tyngdekraft!<BR>Lås Secret Hub til at spille som en Spinosaurus og T-REX!<BR>Redde en EGG, HATCH og hæve den på din egen BABY Raptor!<BR>Dekorere dit Hub (hjemme), låse kæledyr og Tilpas din Raptors hud FARVER og hatte!<BR>Tænd RAGDOLL MODE for at flop, tur og backflip på kollidere!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Kæledyr, 9 Dekorationer, 10 arter af dinosaurer!<BR>MULTIPLAYER! (efter oplåsning lava kort)<BR>Hunt og med rigtige spillere som Raptors Jorden rundt i en KÆMPE GRATIS ROAM kort udforske!<BR>Og meget mere skjulte ekstraelementer på multiplayer! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 152 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR>Support til online spil med flere spillere: Ja (2-32 spillere)<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Spielen wie ein RAPTOR zu erforschen, zu jagen und zu überleben in großen schönen Umgebungen!<BR>Kampf gegen eine Mecha T-Rex auf dem Mond in geringer Schwerkraft!<BR>Entriegeln Sie das Geheimnis Hub als SPINOSAURUS und T-REX zu spielen!<BR>Retten ein Ei, Luke und heben Sie sie in Ihre eigene BABY Raptor!<BR>Dekorieren Sie Ihr Hub (home), entsperren Haustiere und Fertigen Sie Ihren Raptors Haut COLOURS und HATS!<BR>Schalten Sie RAGDOLL MODE auf Flop, Reise und backflip auf kollidieren!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Haustiere, 9 Dekorationen, 10 Arten von Dinosauriern!<BR>Mehrspieler! (nach der Entriegelung Lava Karte)<BR>Jagd und erkunden Sie mit echten Spielern Raptors in der ganzen Welt in einem HUGE Freien Modus Karte!<BR>Und vieles mehr versteckten Extras auf Multiplayer! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 152 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR>Online-Unterstützung für Multiplayer-Spiel: Ja (2-32 Spieler)<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>PLAY AS A RAPTOR to explore, hunt and survive in large beautiful environments!<BR>Battle against a Mecha T-Rex on the moon in low gravity!<BR>Unlock the Secret Hub to play as a SPINOSAURUS and T-REX!<BR>Rescue an EGG, HATCH and raise it into your own BABY Raptor!<BR>DECORATE your Hub (home), unlock PETS and CUSTOMISE your Raptors skin COLOURS and HATS!<BR>Turn on RAGDOLL MODE to flop, trip and backflip upon colliding!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Decorations, 10 species of DINOSAURS!<BR>And lots more hidden extras! <BR><BR>Package size: 152 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2-32 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>PLAY AS A RAPTOR to explore, hunt and survive in large beautiful environments!<BR>Battle against a Mecha T-Rex on the moon in low gravity!<BR>Unlock the Secret Hub to play as a SPINOSAURUS and T-REX!<BR>Rescue an EGG, HATCH and raise it into your own BABY Raptor!<BR>DECORATE your Hub (home), unlock PETS and CUSTOMISE your Raptors skin COLOURS and HATS!<BR>Turn on RAGDOLL MODE to flop, trip and backflip upon colliding!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Decorations, 10 species of DINOSAURS!<BR>MULTIPLAYER! (after unlocking lava map)<BR>Hunt and explore with real players as Raptors around the WORLD in one HUGE FREE ROAM map!<BR>And lots more hidden extras on multiplayer! <BR><BR>Package size: 152 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2-32 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>PLAY AS A RAPTOR to explore, hunt and survive in large beautiful environments!<BR>Battle against a Mecha T-Rex on the moon in low gravity!<BR>Unlock the Secret Hub to play as a SPINOSAURUS and T-REX!<BR>Rescue an EGG, HATCH and raise it into your own BABY Raptor!<BR>DECORATE your Hub (home), unlock PETS and CUSTOMISE your Raptors skin COLOURS and HATS!<BR>Turn on RAGDOLL MODE to flop, trip and backflip upon colliding!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Decorations, 10 species of DINOSAURS!<BR>MULTIPLAYER! (after unlocking lava map)<BR>Hunt and explore with real players as Raptors around the WORLD in one HUGE FREE ROAM map!<BR>And lots more hidden extras on multiplayer! <BR><BR>Package size: 152 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2-32 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>PLAY AS A RAPTOR to explore, hunt and survive in large beautiful environments!<BR>Battle against a Mecha T-Rex on the moon in low gravity!<BR>Unlock the Secret Hub to play as a SPINOSAURUS and T-REX!<BR>Rescue an EGG, HATCH and raise it into your own BABY Raptor!<BR>DECORATE your Hub (home), unlock PETS and CUSTOMISE your Raptors skin COLOURS and HATS!<BR>Turn on RAGDOLL MODE to flop, trip and backflip upon colliding!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Pets, 9 Decorations, 10 species of DINOSAURS!<BR>MULTIPLAYER! (after unlocking lava map)<BR>Hunt and explore with real players as Raptors around the WORLD in one HUGE FREE ROAM map!<BR>And lots more hidden extras on multiplayer! <BR><BR>Package size: 152 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2-32 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>JUGAR COMO RAPTOR para explorar, cazar y sobrevivir en grandes entornos hermosos!<BR>Batalla contra un Mecha T-Rex en la Luna en baja gravedad!<BR>Desbloquear el Hub secreto para jugar como un SPINOSAURUS y T-REX!<BR>Rescata a un huevo, portilla y elevarla a su propio bebé Raptor!<BR>Decora tu Hub (casa), desbloquear PETS y Personaliza tu COLORES y HATS piel Raptors!<BR>Activar el modo de trapo para flop, viaje y voltereta hacia atrás al chocar!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Jefes, 9 Mascotas, 9 Decoraciones, 10 especies de dinosaurios!<BR>MULTIJUGADOR! (después de desbloquear el mapa de lava)<BR>Hunt y explorar con jugadores reales como Raptors de todo el mundo en una enorme mapa ROAM GRATIS!<BR>Y muchos extras más ocultos en multijugador! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 152 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR>Asistencia para juegos de varios jugadores en línea: Sí (2-32 jugadores)<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Pelaa RAPTOR tutkia, metsästää ja hengissä suuri kaunis ympäristöissä!<BR>Taistelua Mecha T-Rex kuuhun matalan painopisteen!<BR>Vapauta Secret Hub pelata Spinosaurus ja T-REX!<BR>Pelastus muna, HATCH ja nosta sen omaan BABY Raptor!<BR>Sisustaa Hub (koti), avata lemmikkejä ja mukauta Raptors ihon COLOURS ja HATS!<BR>Kytke RAGDOLL MODE floppi, matkan ja backflip törmätessään!<BR>9 Skins, 9 päämiehet, 9 Lemmikkieläimet, 9 Kunniamerkit, 10 lajin dinosaurukset!<BR>MULTIPLAYER! (avaamisen jälkeen lava kartta)<BR>Hunt ja tutkia todellisia pelaajia, kuten Raptors ympäri maailmaa yhdessä VALTAVA ILMAISEKSI ROAM kartalla!<BR>Ja paljon muuta piilotettu extrat moninpelin! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 152 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR>Monen pelaajan pelin verkkotuki: Kyllä  (2-32 pelaajaa)<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Jouez comme un RAPTOR à explorer, chasser et survivre dans des environnements magnifiques!<BR>Bataille contre un Mecha T-Rex sur la lune en faible gravité!<BR>Déverrouillez le Hub secret à jouer comme un Spinosaurus et T-REX!<BR>Sauver un œuf, HATCH et l'élever dans votre propre bébé Raptor!<BR>Décorez votre Hub (la maison), et déverrouiller ANIMAUX MODIFIER votre Raptors COULEURS de la peau et des chapeaux!<BR>Allumez RAGDOLL MODE pour flop, voyage et backflip sur la collision!<BR>Skins 9, 9, 9 chefs Animaux, 9 Décorations, 10 espèces de dinosaures!<BR>MULTIJOUEUR! (après le déverrouillage de lave carte)<BR>Hunt et d'explorer avec de vrais joueurs que Raptors à travers le monde en une immense carte de ROAM GRATUIT!<BR>Et beaucoup plus extras cachés sur multijoueur! <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 152 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR>Mode multijoueur en ligne : Oui (2-32 joueurs)<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Jouez comme un RAPTOR à explorer, chasser et survivre dans des environnements magnifiques!<BR>Bataille contre un Mecha T-Rex sur la lune en faible gravité!<BR>Déverrouillez le Hub secret à jouer comme un Spinosaurus et T-REX!<BR>Sauver un œuf, HATCH et l'élever dans votre propre bébé Raptor!<BR>Décorez votre Hub (la maison), et déverrouiller ANIMAUX MODIFIER votre Raptors COULEURS de la peau et des chapeaux!<BR>Allumez RAGDOLL MODE pour flop, voyage et backflip sur la collision!<BR>Skins 9, 9, 9 chefs Animaux, 9 Décorations, 10 espèces de dinosaures!<BR>MULTIJOUEUR! (après le déverrouillage de lave carte)<BR>Hunt et d'explorer avec de vrais joueurs que Raptors à travers le monde en une immense carte de ROAM GRATUIT!<BR>Et beaucoup plus extras cachés sur multijoueur! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 152 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR>Assistance en ligne pour jeu multijoueur : Oui (2-32 joueurs)<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Gioca come un RAPTOR da esplorare, caccia e sopravvivere in ambienti di grandi dimensioni belle!<BR>Battaglia contro un Mecha T-Rex sulla luna in bassa gravità!<BR>Sbloccare il Segreto Hub di giocare come un SPINOSAURUS e T-REX!<BR>Salvare un uovo, HATCH ed aumentare nella vostra BAMBINO Raptor!<BR>Decorare la vostra Hub (casa), sbloccare ANIMALI e Personalizza la tua pelle Raptors COLORI e CAPPELLI!<BR>Attivare la modalità ragdoll per flop, viaggio e backflip su collisione!<BR>9 Pelli, 9 capi, 9 Animali domestici, 9 Decorazioni, 10 specie di dinosauri!<BR>MULTIPLAYER! (dopo aver sbloccato la mappa lava)<BR>Hunt e di esplorare con giocatori reali come Raptors in tutto il mondo in un enorme vagano liberi mappa!<BR>E molto di più extra nascosti sul multiplayer! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 152 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR>Supporto giochi multiplayer online: Sì (2-32 giocatori)<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>、狩りを探索し、大規模な美しい環境で生き残るためにRAPTORとしてプレー！<BR>低重力で月にメカT-REXとの戦い！<BR>スピノサウルスとT-REXとして再生するシークレットハブのロックを解除！<BR>EGG、ハッチを救出し、独自のBABYラプターにそれを上げます！<BR>あなたのハブ（ホーム）を飾る、ペットのロックを解除し、あなたのラプターズ皮膚COLOURSとHATSをカスタマイズ！<BR>ラグドールモードをオンには、衝突時の旅行やバク転、フロップに！<BR>9スキン、9ヘッズ、9ペット、9デコレーション、恐竜の10種！<BR>マルチプレイ！ （溶岩マップのロックを解除した後）<BR>ハントと一つの巨大な無料ROAMマップで世界中の猛禽のような本物のプレイヤーと探検！<BR>とマルチにたくさんより多くの隠されたエキストラを！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 152 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR>オンラインマルチプレイ: 2～32人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Spiller som en RAPTOR å utforske, jakte og overleve i store vakre omgivelser!<BR>Kjemp mot en Mecha T-Rex på månen i lav gravitasjon!<BR>Lås opp Secret Hub å spille som en Spinosaurus og T-REX!<BR>Redde et EGG, luke og heve den til din egen BABY Raptor!<BR>Innred Hub (hjemme), låse opp PETS og tilpass Raptors hud FARGER og HATS!<BR>Slå på Ragdoll MODE å floppe, tur og backflip på å kollidere!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Husdyr, 9 Dekorasjoner, 10 arter av dinosaurer!<BR>MULTIPLAYER! (etter opplåsing lava kartet)<BR>Hunt og utforske med ekte spillere som Raptors verden rundt i ett KJEMPESTOR FRI ROAM kartet!<BR>Og mye mer skjulte statister på multiplayer! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 152 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR>Støtte for online flerspiller: Ja (2-32 spillere)<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Speel als een Raptor te verkennen, jagen en te overleven in grote mooie omgevingen!<BR>Strijd tegen een Mecha T-Rex op de maan in de lage zwaartekracht!<BR>Ontgrendelen van de Secret Hub te spelen als een SPINOSAURUS en T-REX!<BR>Rescue een ei, HATCH en verhogen het in uw eigen baby Raptor!<BR>Versier je Hub (thuis), ontgrendelen PETS en Pas uw Raptors huid KLEUREN en hoeden!<BR>Schakel RAGDOLL MODE om flop, reis en backflip op botsen!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 huisdieren, 9 Decoraties, 10 soorten dinosaurussen!<BR>MULTIPLAYER! (na het ontgrendelen lava kaart)<BR>Hunt en verken met echte spelers Raptors rond de wereld in een ENORME GRATIS ROAM kaart!<BR>En nog veel meer verborgen extra's op multiplayer! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 152 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR>Ondersteuning voor online multiplayergame: Ja (2-32 spelers)<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Graj jako RAPTOR zbadać, polować i przetrwać w dużych pięknych środowiskach!<BR>Bitwa przeciwko Mecha T-Rex na księżycu w niskiej grawitacji!<BR>Odblokuj Secret Hub grać jako SPINOZAUR i T-REX!<BR>Uratuj Jajko, właz i podnieść ją do własnego BABY Raptor!<BR>Udekoruj Hub (HOME), odblokować ZWIERZĘTA i Dostosuj Raptors KOLORY skóry i kapelusze!<BR>Włącz RAGDOLL MODE aby flop, podróż i backflip po kolizji!<BR>9 Skins, 9, 9 Zwierzaki szefowie, 9, 10 gatunków Dekoracje dinozaury!<BR>Multiplayer! (po odblokowaniu lawy mapę)<BR>Hunt i odkrywania prawdziwych graczy jak Raptors dookoła świata w jeden wielki darmo wędrować mapie!<BR>I wiele więcej ukrytych dodatków na multiplayer! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 152 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR>Tryb online dla wielu graczy: tak (2-32 graczy)<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Spela som en RAPTOR att utforska, jaga och överleva i stora vackra miljöer!<BR>Slaget mot en Mecha T-Rex på månen i låg gravitation!<BR>Lås upp hemliga Hub att spela som en Spinosaurus och T-REX!<BR>Rädda ett ägg, kläcks och höja den till ditt eget barn Raptor!<BR>Dekorera dina Hub (hem), låsa PETS och Skräddarsy din Raptors huden FÄRGER och hattar!<BR>Slå på RAGDOLL MODE att floppen, resa och backflip på kolliderar!<BR>9 Skins, 9 Heads, 9 Husdjur, 9 Dekorationer, 10 arter av dinosaurier!<BR>FLERA! (efter upplåsning lava karta)<BR>Hunt och utforska med riktiga spelare som Raptors Runt om i världen i en ENORM fri roam karta!<BR>Och mycket mer dolda kostnader på multiplayer! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 152 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR>Stöd för onlinespel med flera spelare: Ja (2-32 spelare)<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Adventure"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_17.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_14.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
