<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00168_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>13578400</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[QChat er en instant messaging-software, du kan chatte med dine venner hvor som helst, når som helst. <BR>features: <BR>En ven online status displayet, kan du kender en ven online eller offline. <BR>2 baseret på brugernavnet søgning, tilføje kontakter. <BR>3 og chatte med venner, som i øjeblikket kun understøtter tekst chat. <BR>4 beskeder gemt lokalt. Automatiske beskeder sendes og modtages gemmes lokalt. <BR>5 chatrum. I chatten, chatte med brugere fra hele verden sammen. <BR>6 leveres med vejret plugin. Du kan altid tjekke vejrforholdene. <BR>Bemærk: <BR>Understøtter ikke offline-beskeder og ikke online venner til at chatte, ikke den anden modtage beskeder. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 13 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - forenklet/Kinesisk - traditionelt<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[QChat ist ein sofortiges Nachrichtenübermittlungssoftware, Sie können jederzeit mit ihren Freunden chatten.<BR><BR>Funktionen:<BR>1. Freunde Online-Statusanzeige, dann können Sie wissen, ob Ihre Freunde Online oder Offline.<BR>2. Nach den Namen suchen und Kontakte hinzufügen<BR>3. Chatten mit den Freunden, jetzt unterstützt diese Software nur Text-Chat<BR>4. Nachrichten lokal speichern. Die gesendeten und akzeptierten Nachrichten können automatisch lokal gespeichert.<BR>5. Funktion von Chatraum. Im Chatraum kann man mit den Benutzern aller Welt kommunizieren.<BR>6. Eigene Wetter-Plugin. Sie können den Wetterzustand jederzeit nachschauen.<BR><BR>Achtung:<BR>1. Es unterstützt keine  Offline-Nachrichten. Wenn Sie mit den nicht Online-Freunden chatten, können sie keine Nachrichten empfangen. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 13 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch/Vereinfachtes Chinesisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[QChat is an instant messaging software, with which you can chat with your friends anytime and anywhere.<BR>Function:<BR>1. Online-state of friends is displayed. You can know whether your friends are online or offline.<BR>2. Searching the user name to add contact.<BR>3. Chatting with friends. Only text chatting is available at present.<BR>4. Messages are stored locally. Messages sent and received are automatically stored locally. <BR>5. Function of chatting room. In chatting room, you can chat with users from all over the world. <BR>6. The weather plugin is embedded. You can check the weather condition at any time. <BR>Notes: <BR>Do not support offline messages for the time being. When chatting with offline friends, your messages cannot reach to them. <BR><BR>Package size: 13 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[QChat is an instant messaging software, with which you can chat with your friends anytime and anywhere.<BR>Function:<BR>1. Online-state of friends is displayed. You can know whether your friends are online or offline.<BR>2. Searching the user name to add contact.<BR>3. Chatting with friends. Only text chatting is available at present.<BR>4. Messages are stored locally. Messages sent and received are automatically stored locally. <BR>5. Function of chatting room. In chatting room, you can chat with users from all over the world. <BR>6. The weather plugin is embedded. You can check the weather condition at any time. <BR>Notes: <BR>Do not support offline messages for the time being. When chatting with offline friends, your messages cannot reach to them. <BR><BR>Package size: 13 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[QChat is an instant messaging software, with which you can chat with your friends anytime and anywhere.<BR>Function:<BR>1. Online-state of friends is displayed. You can know whether your friends are online or offline.<BR>2. Searching the user name to add contact.<BR>3. Chatting with friends. Only text chatting is available at present.<BR>4. Messages are stored locally. Messages sent and received are automatically stored locally. <BR>5. Function of chatting room. In chatting room, you can chat with users from all over the world. <BR>6. The weather plugin is embedded. You can check the weather condition at any time. <BR>Notes: <BR>Do not support offline messages for the time being. When chatting with offline friends, your messages cannot reach to them. <BR><BR>Package size: 13 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[QChat is an instant messaging software, with which you can chat with your friends anytime and anywhere.<BR>Function:<BR>1. Online-state of friends is displayed. You can know whether your friends are online or offline.<BR>2. Searching the user name to add contact.<BR>3. Chatting with friends. Only text chatting is available at present.<BR>4. Messages are stored locally. Messages sent and received are automatically stored locally. <BR>5. Function of chatting room. In chatting room, you can chat with users from all over the world. <BR>6. The weather plugin is embedded. You can check the weather condition at any time. <BR>Notes: <BR>Do not support offline messages for the time being. When chatting with offline friends, your messages cannot reach to them. <BR><BR>Package size: 13 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Simplified Chinese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[QChat es un software de mensajería instantánea, puedes chatear con tus amigos en cualquier lugar y cualquier momento.<BR>Características: <BR>1. Visualización de estado en línea de amigos,usted puede saber un amigo esta en línea o fuera de línea.<BR>2.Puede agregar contactos de acuerdo con la búsqueda de nombre de usuario.<BR>3.Para chatear con los amigos,de este momento sólo estan disponible de textos.<BR>4.La historia de mensajes se guarda por almacenamiento local.Los mensajes enviados y recibidos se guarda automaticamente en.<BR>5.Sala de charla.En la sala de charla,puede chatear con con usuarios de todo el mundo.<BR><BR>Atención:<BR>Ahora no admite mensajes fuera de línea,el mensaje que mandas a los amigos que estan fuera de línea,ellos no van a recibirlos. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 13 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés/Chino simplificado/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[QChat on pikaviestiohjelma ohjelmisto, voit keskustella ystäviesi kanssa missä ja milloin tahansa. <BR>ominaisuudet: <BR>- Kaverit Online tila näyttö, voit tietää ystävä online-tai offline. <BR>- Perustuu käyttäjätunnus haku, yhteystietojen lisäämisen. <BR>- Jutella ystävien kanssa, tukee tällä hetkellä vain tekstiä chat. <BR>- Tallennetut viestit paikallisesti. Automaattinen lähetetyt ja vastaanotetut viestit tallennetaan paikallisesti. <BR>- Chat. Chat-huoneessa, keskustella käyttäjiä ympäri maailmaa yhdessä. <BR>- Oma sää plugin. Voit aina tarkistaa sääolosuhteet. <BR>Huom: <BR>Ei tue offline-viestien eikä verkossa ystäviä keskustella, muut saa viestejä. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 13 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Kiina - yksinkertaistettu/Kiina - perinteinen<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[QChat est un logiciel de communication immédiate qui vous permet de communiquer avec des amis toujours et partout.<BR>Fonctions :<BR>1. vous pouvez savoir si les amis sont en ligne ou non selon leurs conditions.<BR>2. vous pouvez enrichir le carnet de correspondance en cherchant leurs noms d’usager.<BR>3. vous pouvez bavarder avec les amis en écrivant.<BR>4. vous pouvez mettre en réserve les informations. Les informations envoyées et reçues seront réservées automatiquement dans votre ordinateur.<BR>5. vous pouvez communiquer avec les usagers venant du monde entier dans la chambre de communication.<BR>6. vous pouvez consulter le temps tous les moments avec un logiciel adjoint.<BR>Notes :<BR>1. ce logiciel ne permet pas de communiquer si vous n’ êtes pas en ligne, vos amis ne recevront pas vos messages. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 13 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[QChat est un logiciel de communication immédiate qui vous permet de communiquer avec des amis toujours et partout.<BR>Fonctions :<BR>1. vous pouvez savoir si les amis sont en ligne ou non selon leurs conditions.<BR>2. vous pouvez enrichir le carnet de correspondance en cherchant leurs noms d’usager.<BR>3. vous pouvez bavarder avec les amis en écrivant.<BR>4. vous pouvez mettre en réserve les informations. Les informations envoyées et reçues seront réservées automatiquement dans votre ordinateur.<BR>5. vous pouvez communiquer avec les usagers venant du monde entier dans la chambre de communication.<BR>6. vous pouvez consulter le temps tous les moments avec un logiciel adjoint.<BR>Notes :<BR>1. ce logiciel ne permet pas de communiquer si vous n’ êtes pas en ligne, vos amis ne recevront pas vos messages. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 13 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois simplifié/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QChat è un software di comunicazione istantanea, è possible di chattare con i tuoi amici in qualsiasi momento ovunque. <BR>Caratteristiche: <BR>1 indicare lo stato online di amico, è possibile di conoscere un amico online o offline.<BR>2 ricercare secondo il nome utente, ed aggiungere i contatti.<BR>3 chiacchierare con gli amici, supportare attualmente la chat testuale solamente.<BR>4 messaggi memorizzati localmente, messaggi inviati e ricevuti vengono memorizzati in locale automaticamente.<BR>5 la funzione della stanza di chat, chattare con utenti di tutto il mondo insieme nella stanza di chat.<BR>Notare:<BR>non supportare i messaggi offline temporaneamente, la parte altra non può ricevere i messaggi quando chiacchierare con gli amici offline. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 13 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese/Cinese semplificato/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[QChatはリアルタイム通信ソフトウェアで、随時随所に友たちとチャットすることができます。<BR>機能：<BR>1.友たちオンラインの状態表示、友たちはオンラインまたはオフラインが分かる。<BR>2.ユーザ名で検索して友たちを添加します。<BR>3.友人とチャットします。現在は文字チャットだけできます。<BR>4.消息ローカル保存します。発送・接収のメッセージは自動的ローカルに保存します。<BR>5.チャットルーム機能。チャットルームの中で、全世界のユーザと一緒にチャットします。<BR>6.天気プラグインがあります。いつでも天気情況を調べることができます。<BR>注意：<BR>1.オフラインメッセージをサポートしていません。オンラインの友たちとチャットすると、相手に届きません。<BR>2.ご提案を楽し見にしています。我々は必ずできるだけ早く検討して改善します。dfsupport@126.com <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 13 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語/中国語(簡体字)/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[QChat er en instant messaging-programvare, du kan chatte med vennene dine hvor som helst, når som helst. <BR>funksjoner: <BR>- Venner Online status skjerm, kan du kjenne en venn online eller offline. <BR>- Basert på brukernavnet ditt, legge til kontakter. <BR>- Chat med venner, foreløpig kun støtter tekstchat. <BR>- Meldinger som er lagret lokalt. Automatiske meldinger som sendes og mottas lagres lokalt. <BR>- Chat rom. I chatterommet, chatte med brukere fra hele verden sammen. <BR>- Egen vær plugin. Du kan alltid sjekke værforholdene. <BR>Merk: <BR>Støtter ikke offline meldinger, og ikke online-venner til å chatte, den andre ikke motta meldinger. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 13 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - Forenklet/Kinesisk - Tradisjonell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[QChat is een instant messaging software, u kunt chatten met je vrienden overal en altijd. <BR>kenmerken: <BR>1 vriend online status display kunt u een vriend online of offline kennen. <BR>2 op basis van de naam van het zoekgedrag, het toevoegen van contacten. <BR>3 en ​​chatten met vrienden, op dit moment ondersteunt alleen tekst chatten. <BR>4 berichten lokaal opgeslagen. Automatische berichtjes verstuurd en ontvangen worden lokaal opgeslagen. <BR>5 chatrooms. In de chatroom, chatten met gebruikers uit de hele wereld bij elkaar. <BR>6 komt met het weer plugin. U kunt altijd de weersomstandigheden. <BR>Opmerking: <BR>Is offline berichten, en niet online vrienden te chatten geen ondersteuning, de andere niet ontvangen van berichten. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 13 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Chinees - Vereenvoudigd/Chinees - Traditioneel<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[QChat är ett snabbmeddelandeprogram, kan du chatta med dina vänner var som helst, när som helst. <BR>Funktioner: <BR>- Vänner Online status display, kan du känna en kompis online eller offline. <BR>- Baserat på användarnamnet söka, lägga till kontakter. <BR>- Chatta med vänner, för närvarande endast stöd för textchatt. <BR>- Meddelanden lagras lokalt. Automatiska meddelanden som skickas och tas emot lagras lokalt. <BR>- Chatta rum. I chattrum, chatta med användare från hela världen tillsammans. <BR>- Egen väder plugin. Du kan kontrollera väderförhållandena. <BR>notera: <BR>Stöder inte offline-meddelanden, och inte online-vänner att chatta, inte den andra emot meddelanden. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 13 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Kinesiska - förenklad/Kinesiska - traditionell<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Apps:Communication"/><genre value="Apps:Entertainment"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
