<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00007_00">

  <appVersion>2.01</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>49564112</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="ja"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) er et spil, der handler om at massere de lyserøde områder på en piges ben for at gøre hende glad. <BR>Pigen vil pege på områder og bede dig om at massere dem.<BR>Når pigen er tilfreds, vil hun bede om andre områder i forskellige stillinger. <BR>Så du kan gøre hende endnu gladere.<BR>Din måde at massere samme område på kan ændre din score.<BR>Når du får highscores, vil pigen vise dig forskellige stillinger som bonus.<BR>Prøv at se, hvor glad du kan gøre hende.<BR><BR>・Over 500 billeder får pigen til at vride sig realistisk!<BR>・Det særlige billede, scoren og meget andet!<BR>・Med en herlig pigestemme! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 48 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Bevægelsessensor<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) ist ein Spiel um pinky Stellen eines Mädchens Bein zu reiben, und um ein Mädchen glücklich.<BR>Das Mädchen wird darauf wanted Flecken, dann geben Sie Ihre Finger zu massieren (rub um ihn herum).<BR>Als das Mädchen glücklich wird, werden andere Flecken von verschiedenen Posen gestellt werden.<BR>So können Sie sie glücklicher machen.<BR>Auch an der gleichen Stelle, ändert Ihren Weg zu reiben (Massage) die Partitur.<BR>Wenn Sie hohe Punktzahlen zu bekommen, zeigen das Mädchen Ihnen verschiedene als Bonus darstellt.<BR>Fordern Sie, wie viel Sie sie glücklich machen.<BR>----------------------------<BR>Aufgrund der vielen Anfrage für ein Upgrade, haben wir beschlossen, Version 2 freizugeben.<BR>Fünf Add-ons von verschiedenen Kostümen zusätzlich zu den bestehenden Original-Spiele. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 48 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Bewegungssensor<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Japanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) is a game to rub around pinky spots of a girl's leg, and to make a girl happy. <BR>The girl will point wanted spots, then give your fingers to massage (rub around it).<BR>When the girl becomes happy, other spots will be asked by various poses. <BR>So, you can make her happier.<BR>Even in the same spot, your way to rub (massage) changes the score.<BR>When you get high scores, the girl show you various poses as bonus.<BR>Challenge how much you can make her happy.<BR>----------------------------<BR>Because of many request for upgrade, we have decided to release version 2. <BR>Five add-ons of different costumes in addition to the existing original games. <BR><BR>*You can play the first stage "at no additional charge". <BR> Enjoy the upgraded Pinky spots leg massage! <BR><BR>Package size: 48 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) is a game to rub around pinky spots of a girl's leg, and to make a girl happy. <BR>The girl will point wanted spots, then give your fingers to massage (rub around it).<BR>When the girl becomes happy, other spots will be asked by various poses. <BR>So, you can make her happier.<BR>Even in the same spot, your way to rub (massage) changes the score.<BR>When you get high scores, the girl show you various poses as bonus.<BR>Challenge how much you can make her happy.<BR>----------------------------<BR>Because of many request for upgrade, we have decided to release version 2. <BR>Five add-ons of different costumes in addition to the existing original games. <BR><BR>*You can play the first stage "at no additional charge". <BR> Enjoy the upgraded Pinky spots leg massage! <BR><BR>Package size: 48 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) is a game to rub around pinky spots of a girl's leg, and to make a girl happy. <BR>The girl will point wanted spots, then give your fingers to massage (rub around it).<BR>When the girl becomes happy, other spots will be asked by various poses. <BR>So, you can make her happier.<BR>Even in the same spot, your way to rub (massage) changes the score.<BR>When you get high scores, the girl show you various poses as bonus.<BR>Challenge how much you can make her happy.<BR>----------------------------<BR>Because of many request for upgrade, we have decided to release version 2. <BR>Five add-ons of different costumes in addition to the existing original games. <BR><BR>*You can play the first stage "at no additional charge". <BR> Enjoy the upgraded Pinky spots leg massage! <BR><BR>Package size: 48 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) is a game to rub around pinky spots of a girl's leg, and to make a girl happy. <BR>The girl will point wanted spots, then give your fingers to massage (rub around it).<BR>When the girl becomes happy, other spots will be asked by various poses. <BR>So, you can make her happier.<BR>Even in the same spot, your way to rub (massage) changes the score.<BR>When you get high scores, the girl show you various poses as bonus.<BR>Challenge how much you can make her happy.<BR>----------------------------<BR>Because of many request for upgrade, we have decided to release version 2. <BR>Five add-ons of different costumes in addition to the existing original games. <BR><BR>*You can play the first stage "at no additional charge". <BR> Enjoy the upgraded Pinky spots leg massage! <BR><BR>Package size: 48 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage)  es un juego de frotar alrededor de los puntos rosados ​​de la pierna de una chica, y hacer que una chica feliz.<BR>La chica se señalan los puntos deseados, a continuación, dar masaje a los dedos (frotar alrededor de él).<BR>Cuando la niña llega a ser felices, otros lugares se le preguntará por varias actitudes.<BR>Por lo tanto, usted puede hacer más feliz.<BR>Incluso en el mismo lugar, a tu manera de frotar (masaje) cambia la puntuación.<BR>Cuando usted consigue altas calificaciones, la chica le mostrará varias poses como bonus.<BR>Desafía a la cantidad que puede hacerla feliz.<BR>----------------------------<BR>Debido a que muchos de solicitud para la actualización, hemos decidido lanzar la versión 2.<BR>Cinco complementos de trajes diferentes, además de los juegos originales existentes. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 48 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Sensor de movimiento<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Pinky Spots (leg massage) on peli, jossa otat tytön jalan käteesi ja teet hänestä onnellisen. <BR>Tyttö osoittaa haluamaansa kohtaa, jota sinun on hierottava sormillasi (pistettävä ne sen ympärille).<BR>Kun tyttö on tyytyväinen, muita kohtia osoitetaan eri asennoissa. <BR>Voit siis tehdä hänestä entistä onnellisemman.<BR>Jopa samassa kohdassa erilainen hierontatyyli voi muuttaa pisteitäsi.<BR>Huipputuloksen saadessasi tyttö esittelee erilaisia asentoja bonuksena.<BR>Haasta itsesi tekemään hänestä mahdollisimman onnellinen.<BR><BR>・Yli 500 kuvan tiedot tekevät kiemurtelusta realistista!<BR>・Erityinen kuva, tulos ja muuta!<BR>・Kainon tyttömäinen ääni! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 48 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Liikeohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) est un jeu de frotter les taches rosâtres autour de la jambe d'une jeune fille, et de rendre une fille heureuse.<BR>La jeune fille va pointer endroits voulus, puis donnez vos doigts pour masser (frotter autour de lui).<BR>Quand la jeune fille devient heureux, d'autres taches seront posées par diverses poses.<BR>Ainsi, vous pouvez lui faire plus heureux.<BR>Même au même endroit, le chemin se frotter (massage) modifie le score.<BR>Lorsque vous obtenez des scores élevés, la jeune fille vous montrer des poses variées en prime.<BR>Défiez combien vous pouvez vous rendre heureuse.<BR>----------------------------<BR>En raison de la demande de nombreux de mise à niveau, nous avons décidé de publier la version 2.<BR>Cinq modules de costumes différents, en plus des jeux existants d'origine. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 48 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Détection de mouvements<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) est un jeu de frotter les taches rosâtres autour de la jambe d'une jeune fille, et de rendre une fille heureuse.<BR>La jeune fille va pointer endroits voulus, puis donnez vos doigts pour masser (frotter autour de lui).<BR>Quand la jeune fille devient heureux, d'autres taches seront posées par diverses poses.<BR>Ainsi, vous pouvez lui faire plus heureux.<BR>Même au même endroit, le chemin se frotter (massage) modifie le score.<BR>Lorsque vous obtenez des scores élevés, la jeune fille vous montrer des poses variées en prime.<BR>Défiez combien vous pouvez vous rendre heureuse.<BR>----------------------------<BR>En raison de la demande de nombreux de mise à niveau, nous avons décidé de publier la version 2.<BR>Cinq modules de costumes différents, en plus des jeux existants d'origine. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 48 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Détecteur de mouvements<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage)è un gioco di strofinare intorno macchie mignolo della gamba di una ragazza, e per fare una ragazza felice.<BR>La ragazza punterà punti desiderati, poi dare le dita per massaggio (strofinare intorno ad esso).<BR>Quando la ragazza diventa felice, altri punti verrà chiesto da varie pose.<BR>Quindi, si può farla più felice.<BR>Anche nello stesso punto, il vostro modo di strofinare (massaggio) cambia il punteggio.<BR>Quando si ottiene punteggi più alti, la ragazza visualizzare varie pose come bonus.<BR>Sfida quanto si può renderla felice.<BR>----------------------------<BR>A causa delle molte richieste per l'aggiornamento, abbiamo deciso di rilasciare la versione 2.<BR>Cinque componenti aggiuntivi di costumi diversi, oltre ai giochi originali esistenti. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 48 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Sensore di movimento<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Giapponese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[『快感足つぼマッサージ』は、女の子の足つぼをキモチよくマッサージし、ほぐしてあげるゲームです。<BR>画面上で指定される女の子のつぼを、あなたの指でグリグリとマッサージしてあげてください。<BR>つぼをほぐしてステージクリアすると、色々なポーズで別のつぼを求めてきますので、どんどん刺激していきましょう。<BR>同じ場所でもマッサージのしかたで得点が変わるのがプレイのコツ。ハイスコアを出せばご褒美ポーズを見せてくれるので、時間切れに注意しながら女の子のつぼをほぐしていきましょう！<BR>----------------------------<BR>皆様のご好評にお応えして、バージョン2へアップデート！<BR>従来のオリジナルゲームに加えて、5つの衣装によるステージを用意しました。<BR><BR>※最初のステージは「追加課金なし」でお楽しみ頂けるようにいたしました。<BR>今後ともよろしくお願いします！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 48 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- モーションセンサー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) er et spill der du gnir rundt rosa flekker på ben til ei jente, for å gjøre henne glad.<BR>Jenta peker på den rosa flekken hun vil at du skal gni rundt, og gir deg så fingre som du skal bruke til å massere med (rundt flekken, ikke på).<BR>Når jenta blir glad vil du se flere flekker som du kan gni rundt ved at hun bytter posering. Gjør dette og hun blir enda gladere.<BR>Du kan få bedre poengsum ved å gni på andre måter, selv om det er et sted du har allerede fullført.<BR>Får du en rekord, blir du belønnet med en bonus der hun bytter poseringer.<BR>Se hvor glad du gjøre henne.<BR><BR><BR>・Du kan ta over 500 bilder for å reprodusere en mer realistisk åling.<BR>・Med bedre bilder får du høyere poeng.<BR>・Spillet har en sky jentestemme <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 48 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Bevegelsessensor<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Pinky spots  (leg massage) is een spel te wrijven rond pinky plekjes van het been van een meisje, en een meisje gelukkig te maken.<BR>Het meisje zal wijzen wilde plekken, dan geef je vingers om massage (wrijven eromheen).<BR>Toen het meisje gelukkig wordt, zullen andere plekken worden gevraagd door verschillende poses.<BR>Dus, kun je haar gelukkiger maken.<BR>Zelfs op dezelfde plek, je weg te wrijven (massage) verandert de score.<BR>Wanneer je hoge scores, het meisje laten zien verschillende poses als bonus.<BR>Daag hoeveel je van haar gelukkig kan maken.<BR>-<BR>Door de vele aanvragen voor een upgrade, hebben we besloten om versie 2 vrij te geven.<BR>Vijf add-ons van verschillende kostuums in aanvulling op de bestaande originele games.<BR><BR>* U kunt de eerste toneelstuk "zonder extra kosten <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 48 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Bewegingssensor<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[I spelet Pinky spots (leg massage) ska du massera de skära punkterna på en tjejs ben – och göra henne lycklig. <BR>Tjejen kommer att peka på de önskade punkterna, sedan ska du massera (gnugga) runt dem.<BR>Då tjejen blir lycklig kommer andra punkter att dyka upp i olika poser.<BR>Så att du kan göra henne ännu lyckligare.<BR>Till och med när det gäller samma punkt kan ditt sätt att gnugga (massera) förändra din poäng.<BR>Då du får höga poäng visar tjejen dig olika poser som bonus.<BR>Utmana dig själv om hur lycklig du kan göra henne.<BR><BR>・ Över 500 bilddata reproducerar realistisk förtjusning!<BR>・ Specialbilder, poäng, med mera!<BR>・ Med en blyg tjejröst! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 48 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Rörelsesensor<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2012-13 Mobile Internet Technology Co., LTD. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_16.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Sex.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_14.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_16.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_17.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_18.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
