<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00162_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>10378112</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Meget klassisk ræsonnement spil, vil spillet tilfældigt generere fire forskellige ordrenummer, vi gætte disse fire numre, hver gætte fire figurer og i hvilken rækkefølge, i alt 10 chancer. Hvis du gætter rigtigt vil bede [? A? B], hvor A repræsenterer numrene og placeringer er korrekte nummer, B repræsenterer antallet er korrekt, men antallet af forkert position. Så vidt muligt med det mindste antal gange for at gætte det rigtige nummer. <BR>     Det korrekte svar er 1234, for eksempel, hvis gæt 2354, så vil du blive bedt om: 1A2B, fordi "4" og deres placering er korrekte, "2", "3" ciffer er korrekt, men placeringen er ikke korrekt. <BR>     Spil med venner, antallet af sammenligning og inden for 10 minutter, der gættede multi ~ <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 10 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Sehr klassische Schlussspiele, durch sie zufällig vier verschiedene laufenden Nummern generiert wird. Wir sollten diese vier Nummern und ihre Reihenfolge vermuten und haben insgesamt 10 Chancen. Wenn Sie nicht richtig raten, wird das Spiel [?A?B] zeigen, A bedeutet die Zahl der richtiger Nummern und ihrer korrekten Reihenfolgen. A bedeutet die Zahl der richtiger Nummern und der falschen Reihenfolgen. Bitte erraten Sie die korrekte Anzahl mit Mindestanzahl.  <BR>    Beispielsweise würde die richtige Antwort 1234 sein und wenn Sie 2354 erraten, wird es 1A2B zeigen, weil die Zahl und Reihenfolge von ,,4" korrekt sind, die Zahl von ,,2" und ,,3" richtig aber die Reihenfolge falsch ist. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 10 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[A very classic mystery game: The game will randomly generate four different ordered numbers and we have to guess these four numbers and its order, totally 10 chances to guess. If the guess is wrong, there is a hint [?A?B], of which A means the number of correct number and position, B means the number of correct number but wrong position. Guess the correct number to the best of one's abilities with the least amount of times.<BR>　　For example, the correct answer is 1234, if one guesses 2354, there will be a hint: 1A2B, because the number “4” is correct in both number and position and number “2” and “3” is of correct number but wrong position. <BR>　　Play with your friends and compare with each other! Who can guess the answer more times within 10 minutes? <BR><BR>Package size: 10 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[A very classic mystery game: The game will randomly generate four different ordered numbers and we have to guess these four numbers and its order, totally 10 chances to guess. If the guess is wrong, there is a hint [?A?B], of which A means the number of correct number and position, B means the number of correct number but wrong position. Guess the correct number to the best of one's abilities with the least amount of times.<BR>　　For example, the correct answer is 1234, if one guesses 2354, there will be a hint: 1A2B, because the number “4” is correct in both number and position and number “2” and “3” is of correct number but wrong position. <BR>　　Play with your friends and compare with each other! Who can guess the answer more times within 10 minutes? <BR><BR>Package size: 10 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[A very classic mystery game: The game will randomly generate four different ordered numbers and we have to guess these four numbers and its order, totally 10 chances to guess. If the guess is wrong, there is a hint [?A?B], of which A means the number of correct number and position, B means the number of correct number but wrong position. Guess the correct number to the best of one's abilities with the least amount of times.<BR>　　For example, the correct answer is 1234, if one guesses 2354, there will be a hint: 1A2B, because the number “4” is correct in both number and position and number “2” and “3” is of correct number but wrong position. <BR>　　Play with your friends and compare with each other! Who can guess the answer more times within 10 minutes? <BR><BR>Package size: 10 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[A very classic mystery game: The game will randomly generate four different ordered numbers and we have to guess these four numbers and its order, totally 10 chances to guess. If the guess is wrong, there is a hint [?A?B], of which A means the number of correct number and position, B means the number of correct number but wrong position. Guess the correct number to the best of one's abilities with the least amount of times.<BR>　　For example, the correct answer is 1234, if one guesses 2354, there will be a hint: 1A2B, because the number “4” is correct in both number and position and number “2” and “3” is of correct number but wrong position. <BR>　　Play with your friends and compare with each other! Who can guess the answer more times within 10 minutes? <BR><BR>Package size: 10 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[El juego de razonamiento muy clásico, el juego genera aleatoriamente 4 números de diferentes órdenes, suponemos estos cuadro números, tenemos 10 oportunidades para suponer los 4 números y sus órdenes. Si no podemos acertar, se muestra [?A?B], A significa el número con la ubicación correcta, B significa el número con la ubicación incierta. Acertar los números con las oportunidades lo menos posible.<BR>　Por ejemplo la respuesta es 1234, si se supone 2354, se mostrará1A2B, es que el número¨4¨tiene la correcta ubicación, pero el número ¨2¨ y ¨3¨ tienen ubicación incorrecta.<BR>　Jugar con los amigos, vamos a ver quién acerta más veces dentro de 10 minutos. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 10 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Hyvin klassinen päättely peli, peli satunnaisesti tuottaa neljä eri tilausnumero, me kai nämä neljä numeroa, joista jokainen arvaa neljä numeroa ja missä järjestyksessä, yhteensä 10 yritystä. Jos arvaa oikean kysyy [?? B], jossa edustaa numerot ja paikat ovat oikea määrä, B edustaa numero on oikea, mutta määrä väärään asentoon. Niin pitkälle kuin mahdollista ainakin monta kertaa arvata oikea numero. <BR>    Oikea vastaus on 1234, esimerkiksi, jos arvaus 2354, niin sinulta kysytään: 1A2B, koska "4" numeroita ja ovat oikein, "2", "3" numero on oikea, mutta sijainti ei ole oikein. <BR>     Pelata kavereiden kanssa, määrä verrattuna ja 10 minuutin jotka arvannut multi ~ <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 10 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Un jeu de raisonnement très classique. Il existe quatre chiffres aléatoires dans l’ordre et nous les devinent. Nous possédons de dix chances en vue de deviner les quatre chiffres ainsi que leur ordre. Le jeu indique [?A?B] si nous faisons des fautes dont le A représente le nombre des chiffres et positions corrects, dont le B représente le nombre des chiffres et positions faux. Essayez de prendre les fois les plus moins possible.<BR>　　Au moment où la réponse correcte est 1234, le jeu indique 1A2B si vous devinez 2354 comme le chiffre 4 et sa position sont corrects, les chiffres 2, 3 sont corrects avec positions fausses.<BR>　　Jouez avec des amis et prenez une comparaison en dix minutes. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 10 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Un jeu de raisonnement très classique. Il existe quatre chiffres aléatoires dans l’ordre et nous les devinent. Nous possédons de dix chances en vue de deviner les quatre chiffres ainsi que leur ordre. Le jeu indique [?A?B] si nous faisons des fautes dont le A représente le nombre des chiffres et positions corrects, dont le B représente le nombre des chiffres et positions faux. Essayez de prendre les fois les plus moins possible.<BR>　　　Au moment où la réponse correcte est 1234, le jeu indique 1A2B si vous devinez 2354 comme le chiffre 4 et sa position sont corrects, les chiffres 2, 3 sont corrects avec positions fausses.<BR>　　　Jouez avec des amis et prenez une comparaison en dix minutes. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 10 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Gioco molto classico di ragionamento, il gioco genererà quattro numero diverso d’ordine casualmente, indoviniamo questi quattro numeri, ognuno indoviniamo quattro cifre e l’ordine, ci sono 10 opportunità totale. Si dimostra [?A?B] se non è corretto di indovinare, tra qui A rappresenta il numero corretto delle cifre e posizioni, B rappresenta il numero delle cifre corrette e posizioni errate, indovinare il numero corretto con il minor numero di volte per quanto possible. <BR><BR>Per esempio, la risposta corretta è 1234, si dimostra 1A2B se indovinare 2354, perchè “4” è corretto sia per la cifra che per la posizione, “2”“3”sono corretti per le cifre, ma la posizione non è corretta. <BR><BR>Gioca con gli amici, e confrontare il più numero di indovinare entro 10 minuti ~ <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 10 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[これはとても経典の推理ゲームです。ランダムに四つの秩序ある数字を推測して、十回のチャンスでこの四つの数字とその整列順序を推理できます。当てられない場合に[?A?B]の提示があります。その中で、Aは数字と位置がすべて正しい個数で、Bは数字が正しいが位置が正しくない個数です。できるだけ最少の回数で正しい数字を当てます。<BR>　例えば、正確な解答は1234の場合、2354と推理すれば、1A2Bという提示が出てきます。「4」の数字と位置が正しく、「2」と「3」 の数字が正しいが、位置が正しくありません。<BR>　友達と一緒に遊んで、10分以内に誰の当てた回数は一番多いですか～ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 10 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Veldig klassisk resonnement spillet, vil spillet tilfeldig generere fire forskjellige ordrenummer, antar vi at disse fire tall, hver gjette fire tall og i hvilken rekkefølge, totalt 10 sjanser. Hvis du gjetter riktig vil be [? A? B], hvor A er tallene og plasseringene er riktig nummer, B representerer nummeret er riktig, men antall feil posisjon. Så langt som mulig med minst antall ganger for å gjette riktig nummer. <BR>     Det riktige svaret er 1234, for eksempel, hvis gjetning 2354, vil du bli bedt om: 1A2B, fordi "4" tall og steder er riktige, er "2", "3" siffer korrekt, men plasseringen er ikke riktig. <BR>     Spill med venner, antall sammenligning og innen 10 minutter som gjettet multi ~ <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 10 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Zeer klassieke redenering spel, zal het spel willekeurig genereren vier verschillende ordernummer, denk dat we deze vier nummers, elke denk vier cijfers en in welke volgorde, in totaal 10 kansen. Als u raden recht vraagt ​​[? A? B], waarbij A de aantallen en locaties juiste aantal, B het nummer correct is, maar het aantal verkeerde positie. Zoveel mogelijk met het minst aantal keren op het juiste aantal raden. <BR>     Het juiste antwoord is 1234, bijvoorbeeld als de gok 2354, dan wordt u gevraagd: 1A2b, omdat "4" en-locaties correct zijn, correct "2", "3" cijfer is maar de locatie is niet correct. <BR>     Speel met vrienden, het aantal vergelijking en binnen 10 minuten die meerdere geraden ~ <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 10 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Mycket klassiskt resonemang spelet, kommer spelet att slumpmässigt generera fyra olika ordernummer, vi antar att dessa fyra nummer, var och gissa fyra siffror och i vilken ordning, totalt 10 chanser. Om du gissar rätt kommer att fråga [? A? B], där A står för siffrorna och platser är rätt nummer, B representerar numret är korrekt, men antalet felaktigt läge. Så långt som möjligt med minsta antal gånger för att gissa rätt nummer. <BR>     Rätt svar är 1234, till exempel om den gissningen 2354, då du kommer att bli tillfrågad: 1A2B, eftersom "4" och-plats är korrekta, är "2", "3" siffra rätt, men platsen är inte korrekt.<BR>     Spela med vänner, antalet jämförelse och inom 10 minuter som gissat multi ~ <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 10 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright(c)2013 DF Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
