<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00122_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.11</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>134213440</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA["Gennem denne firkantede papverden rejser en ædel og frygtløs ridder ad papstien for at finde skræmte småbørn, nødstedte ungmøer og fra tid til anden en prinsesse, som han kan redde.<BR>På hans vej venter usigelige farer – afskyelige monstre, helvedes ild og mørke, endeløse faldgruber – som DU skal overvinde".<BR><BR>I denne verden af papir er elementerne på din side! Hvis en drage spærrer vejen, skal du bare tænde en tændstik, og *puf* så er dragen væk! Hvis der er en irriterende væg, klipper du den bare væk med en saks. Kan du undgå fælderne, så du ikke ender som papmaché?<BR><BR>Spilleren kan spille syv episke missioner. Utallige finurlige fjender vil forsøge at besejre din ridderfigur. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 128 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Finsk/Dansk/Norsk/Svensk<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA["Ein stattlicher, furchtloser Ritter bereist Papierpfade in einer Welt ganz aus Pappe, immer auf der Suche nach verängstigten Waisen, holden Jungfrauen in Not und Prinzessinnen, die gerettet werden wollen. <BR>Auf seinem Pfad lauern unsagbare Gefahren – abscheuliche Monster, Höllenfeuer und finstere, bodenlose Abgründe – denen DU dich stellen musst.“<BR><BR>CardBoard Castle ist ein Denkspiel, das deine Reflexe auf die Probe stellt und Stunden voller Herausforderungen in einer abgedrehten mittelalterlichen Welt bietet. Alles was du tun musst, ist deine grauen Zellen in Wallung zu bringen und unserem furchtlosen Helden beim Besiegen seiner Feinde zu helfen.<BR><BR>Kannst du den fiesen Fallen ausweichen, um nicht als Pappmaché zu enden? <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 128 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Dänisch/Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch/Niederländisch/Norwegisch/Finnisch/Schwedisch/Japanisch<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA["In his cardboard cut-out world, a noble fearless knight travels his cardboard cut-out trail in search of frightened orphans, damsels in distress, and the occasional princess to save.<BR>On his path lurk unspeakable dangers - hideous monsters, hellfire, and dark bottomless pits - that YOU have to overcome."<BR><BR>CardBoard Castle is a game of puzzles and reflexes offering hours of exciting challenges in a madcap medieval world. All you have to do is power up your brainbox and help our intrepid hero vanquish his enemies.<BR><BR>In this paper world, the elements are on your side! If a dragon blocks your path, simply strike a match, and.. Poof! No more dragon! If a wall is proving tiresome, simple snip it down with scissors. Can you avoid the pitfalls and not wind up as papier-maché? <BR><BR>Package size: 128 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA["In his cardboard cut-out world, a noble fearless knight travels his cardboard cut-out trail in search of frightened orphans, damsels in distress, and the occasional princess to save.<BR>On his path lurk unspeakable dangers - hideous monsters, hellfire, and dark bottomless pits - that YOU have to overcome."<BR><BR>CardBoard Castle is a game of puzzles and reflexes offering hours of exciting challenges in a madcap medieval world. All you have to do is power up your brainbox and help our intrepid hero vanquish his enemies.<BR><BR>In this paper world, the elements are on your side! If a dragon blocks your path, simply strike a match, and.. Poof! No more dragon! If a wall is proving tiresome, simple snip it down with scissors. Can you avoid the pitfalls and not wind up as papier-maché? <BR><BR>Package size: 128 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA["In his cardboard cut-out world, a noble fearless knight travels his cardboard cut-out trail in search of frightened orphans, damsels in distress, and the occasional princess to save.<BR>On his path lurk unspeakable dangers - hideous monsters, hellfire, and dark bottomless pits - that YOU have to overcome."<BR><BR>CardBoard Castle is a game of puzzles and reflexes offering hours of exciting challenges in a madcap medieval world. All you have to do is power up your brainbox and help our intrepid hero vanquish his enemies.<BR><BR>In this paper world, the elements are on your side! If a dragon blocks your path, simply strike a match, and.. Poof! No more dragon! If a wall is proving tiresome, simple snip it down with scissors. Can you avoid the pitfalls and not wind up as papier-maché? <BR><BR>Package size: 128 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA["In his cardboard cut-out world, a noble fearless knight travels his cardboard cut-out trail in search of frightened orphans, damsels in distress, and the occasional princess to save.<BR>On his path lurk unspeakable dangers - hideous monsters, hellfire, and dark bottomless pits - that YOU have to overcome."<BR><BR>CardBoard Castle is a game of puzzles and reflexes offering hours of exciting challenges in a madcap medieval world. All you have to do is power up your brainbox and help our intrepid hero vanquish his enemies.<BR><BR>In this paper world, the elements are on your side! If a dragon blocks your path, simply strike a match, and.. Poof! No more dragon! If a wall is proving tiresome, simple snip it down with scissors. Can you avoid the pitfalls and not wind up as papier-maché? <BR><BR>Package size: 128 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>Danish/German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian/Dutch/Norwegian/Finnish/Swedish/Japanese<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA["Un noble e intrépido caballero surca su mundo, hecho de recortes de papel, en busca de huérfanos aterrorizados, damiselas en apuros y la típica princesa a la que salvar.<BR>Por el camino le esperan peligros inimaginables, horripilantes monstruos, el fuego del infierno y agujeros negros sin fondo que TÚ tendrás que ayudarle a superar".<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle es un juego de puzles y reflejos que ofrece horas de desafíos increíbles en un genuino mundo medieval. Lo único que tienes que hacer es poner ese cerebro en marcha y ayudar a nuestro intrépido héroe a derrotar a sus enemigos. <BR><BR>En este mundo de recortes de papel, los elementos están de tu lado. ¿Estás preparado/a para esquivar las trampas y no acabar como papel maché? <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 128 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Danés/Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano/Holandés/Noruego/Finlandés/Sueco/Japonés<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA["Jalo ja peloton ritari matkustaa pahvista luodussa maailmassa ja etsii avuttomia orpoja, neitoja hädässä ja pelastettavia prinsessoja.<BR>Ritarin tiellä vaanii sanoin kuvaamattomia vaaroja - karmivia hirviöitä, tulimyrskyjä ja pohjattomia kuiluja - jotka SINUN on selätettävä."<BR><BR>CardBoard Castle on pulma- ja toimintapeli, joka tarjoaa tuntien verran haasteita hurjassa keskiaikaisessa maailmassa. Rasita älynystyröitäsi ja auta urheaa sankariamme kukistamaan vihollisensa.<BR><BR>Käytä paperimaailman elementtejä hyödyksesi! Jos lohikäärme on tielläsi, sytytä vain tulitikku ja... Puff! Ei enää lohikäärmettä! Jos joku seinä alkaa käydä hermoillesi, leikkaa se saksilla. Pystytkö selättämään esteet vai päädytkö selluloosaksi?<BR><BR>Voit pelata seitsemän eri eeppistä tehtävää. Lukemato määrä omituisia vihollisi <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 128 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Ranska/Espanja/Saksa/Italia/Hollanti/Suomi/Tanska/Norja/Ruotsi<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA["Dans ce monde fait de carton découpé, un noble chevalier sans peur parcourt son chemin de carton à la recherche d'orphelins effrayés, de demoiselles en détresse et de l’habituelle princesse à sauver.<BR>Sur son chemin veillent d'indicibles dangers - des monstres hideux, des feux infernaux, et de sombres fosses sans fonds - que VOUS devez surmonter."<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle est un jeu de puzzles et de réflexes, offrant des heures de défis excitants dans un univers médiéval déjanté. Tout ce que vous devez faire est de vous remuer les méninges et aider notre intrépide héros à vaincre ses ennemis.<BR><BR>Dans ce monde de papier, les éléments sont de votre côté!Pouvez-vous éviter les fosses et ne pas finir en papier-mâché? <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 128 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Danois/Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien/Néerlandais/Norvégien/Finnois/Suédois/Japonais<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[“Nel suo mondo di cartone, un nobile ed impavido cavaliere percorre dei sentieri alla ricerca di orfani impauriti, damigelle in pericolo e principesse da salvare.<BR>Sul suo percorso incombono pericoli tremendi: mostri orribili, fuoco infernale e voragini scure e senza fondo, che TU dovrai superare”.<BR><BR>CardBoard Castle è un gioco di puzzle che mette alla prova i tuoi riflessi, offrendoti ore di eccitanti battaglie in uno stravagante paesaggio medievale. Tutto ciò che occorre è essere intelligenti ed aiutare il nostro intrepido eroe a sconfiggere i suoi nemici.<BR><BR>In questo mondo di cartone, gli elementi sono dalla tua parte! Se un drago blocca il tuo cammino, accendi semplicemente un fiammifero e… Ta-da! Niente più drago! Riuscirai anche ad evitare le trappole e non finire come cartapesta? <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 128 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Danese/Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano/Olandese/Norvegese/Finlandese/Svedese/Giapponese<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[「彼のこのダンボールを切り抜いた世界で、崇高で勇敢な騎士が恐怖におののく孤児たち、困っている少女や、時々王女たちを救うための探索において彼のダンボールで切り抜いた道を旅します。<BR>彼の進む道にはあなたが乗り越えなければならない、凶悪な怪物、地獄の炎、暗黒の底なし穴などの筆舌に尽くしがたい危険が待ち構えています。」<BR><BR>カードボード・キャッスルは向こう見ずな中世の世界で何時間にも及ぶチャレンジを提供するパズルと対決のゲームです。すべてあなたに必要なことは自分の頭脳を強化し、勇敢なヒーローが敵を打ち負かすのを支援することです。<BR><BR>この紙の世界において、各エレメントはあなたが持っています! もしドラゴンがあなたの道を塞ぐのなら、マッチを擦り、... 「プー」と吹くと! もうドラゴンはいません! もし壁にうんざりしたなら、それをはさみでチョキンと切るだけです。落とし穴を回避し、紙粘土みたいにならないようにできますか? <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 128 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>デンマーク語/ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語/オランダ語/ノルウェー語/フィンランド語/スウェーデン語/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA["I denne pappfigurverdenen reiser en edel og fryktløs ridder rundt på leting etter vettskremte foreldreløse barn, jomfruer i nød og en og annen prinsesse som han kan redde.<BR>Men på hans vei lurer ubeskrivelige farer - grusomme monstre, skjærsild og mørke avgrunner - som DU må komme deg forbi."<BR><BR>I denne pappverdenen har du elementene på din side! Dersom en drage står i veien, er det bare å tenne en fyrstikk, og så ... Bang - drage borte! Støter du på en vrien mur, kan du bare klippe den bort med en saks. Klarer du å unngå fallgruvene så du ikke ender som pappmasjé?<BR><BR>Du har sju episke oppdrag foran deg - med utallige fiender som vil prøve å beseire ridderen din. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 128 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Fransk/Spansk/Tysk/Italiensk/Hollandsk/Finsk/Dansk/Norsk/Svensk<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA["In een kartonnen wereld gaat een onverschrokken ridder op pad. Kan hij de arme wezen, de vrouwen in nood en de prinsessen redden?<BR>Talloze afschuwelijke gevaren liggen op hem te wachten: gruwelijke monsters, hellevuur en duistere, bodemloze afgronden. En alleen JIJ kunt hem helpen."<BR><BR>CardBoard Castle is een spel vol puzzels en uitdagingen dat zich afspeelt in een knotsgekke, middeleeuwse wereld. Zet je hersens aan het werk en help onze dappere held met het verslaan van zijn vijanden.<BR><BR>In deze wereld van papier staan de elementen aan jouw kant! Als een draak je de weg verspert, steek je gewoon een lucifer aan en… poef! Weg is de draak! Staat er een muur in de weg? Knip hem dan gewoon aan flarden met je schaar. Kun jij alle valkuilen vermijden en voorkomen dat je eindigt als papier-maché? <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 128 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Frans/Spaans/Duits/Italiaans/Nederlands/Fins/Deens/Noors/Zweeds<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[“I sin egna pappersvärld reser en ädel riddare på sin egna pappersstig på jakt efter skrämda föräldralösa barn, nödställda ungmöer och någon sessa här och där som behöver räddas.<BR>På vägen lurar obeskrivliga faror - ohyggliga monster, helveteseldar och becksvarta bottenlösa hål - som DU måste ta dig förbi.<BR><BR>I denna pappersvärld är elementen på din sida! Står en drake i din väg? Tänd en tändsticka, och ... poff! Draken är väck! Har du en sån där tröttsam vägg framför dig? Använd en sax för att klippa den i bitar. Kan du väja för fallgroparna och undfly ett öde som papier-maché?<BR><BR>Spelarens äventyr sträcker sig över sju episka uppdrag. Oräkneliga, udda fiender kommer att göra sitt bästa för att besegra riddaren du tagit rollen som. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 128 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Franska/Spanska/Tyska/Italienska/Holländska/Finska/Danska/Norska/Svenska<BR><BR>Cardboard Castle PSM (c) 2013, AMA &amp; Mando Productions<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
