<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00175_00">

  <appVersion>2.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>67460768</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Galop, hoppe og ragdoll i en stor smuk kort! Vind skøre belønninger til din hest!<BR><BR>Frie roam Horse Simulator med ragdoll fysik.<BR>Trav, Galop, Gallop og hoppe rundt en Big Beautiful kort.<BR>Udforsk en strand, Ice vulkan, grotter, bjerge, skov og campingpladsen.<BR>Tal med hest NPC'er at vinde belønninger til din hest.<BR>Tilpas din heste hud og manke farve.<BR>Aktiver mods for at tilføje ekstra sjov til spillet, såsom lav tyngdekraft og mega skubbe.<BR>Flip, flop og slip omkring den fantastiske miljø med din ragdoll fysik hest!<BR><BR>6 maj 2015: Version 2.0: Spil genskabt, nyt kort, bedre grafik, ragdoll fysik og meget mere! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 65 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Gallop, springen und Ragdoll in einem großen schönen Karte! Gewinnen Sie verrückt Belohnung für Ihr Pferd!<BR><BR>Free Roam Pferde Simulator mit Ragdoll Physik.<BR>Trab, Galopp, Galopp und Springen um eine große schöne Karte.<BR>Entdecken Sie einen Strand, Ice Vulkan, Höhlen, Berge, Wald und Campingplatz.<BR>Sprechen Sie Pferd NPCs, um dir Belohnungen für Ihr Pferd zu gewinnen.<BR>Fertigen Sie Ihre Pferde und Mähne Haut Farbe.<BR>Aktivieren Sie Mods für zusätzlichen Spaß an dem Spiel, wie niedrige Schwerpunkt und mega drängen hinzuzufügen.<BR>Flip, Flop und Drop um die erstaunliche Umgebung mit Ragdoll Physik Pferd!<BR><BR>6. Mai 2015: Version 2.0: Spiel neu gemacht, neue Karte, bessere Grafik, Ragdoll Physik und vieles mehr! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 65 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Gallop, jump and ragdoll in a big beautiful map! Win crazy rewards for your horse!<BR><BR>Free roam Horse Simulator with Ragdoll Physics.<BR>Trot, Canter, Gallop and Jump around a Big Beautiful map.<BR>Explore a beach, Ice volcano, caves, mountains, forest and campsite.<BR>Talk to horse NPC’s to win rewards for your horse.<BR>Customise your horses skin and mane colour.<BR>Activate mods to add extra fun to the game, such as low gravity and mega pushing.<BR>Flip, flop and drop around the amazing environment with your ragdoll physics horse!<BR><BR>6 May 2015 : Version 2.0 : Game remade, new map, better graphics, ragdoll physics and lots more! <BR><BR>Package size: 65 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Gallop, jump and ragdoll in a big beautiful map! Win crazy rewards for your horse!<BR><BR>Free roam Horse Simulator with Ragdoll Physics.<BR>Trot, Canter, Gallop and Jump around a Big Beautiful map.<BR>Explore a beach, Ice volcano, caves, mountains, forest and campsite.<BR>Talk to horse NPC’s to win rewards for your horse.<BR>Customise your horses skin and mane colour.<BR>Activate mods to add extra fun to the game, such as low gravity and mega pushing.<BR>Flip, flop and drop around the amazing environment with your ragdoll physics horse!<BR><BR>6 May 2015 : Version 2.0 : Game remade, new map, better graphics, ragdoll physics and lots more! <BR><BR>Package size: 65 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Gallop, jump and ragdoll in a big beautiful map! Win crazy rewards for your horse!<BR><BR>Free roam Horse Simulator with Ragdoll Physics.<BR>Trot, Canter, Gallop and Jump around a Big Beautiful map.<BR>Explore a beach, Ice volcano, caves, mountains, forest and campsite.<BR>Talk to horse NPC’s to win rewards for your horse.<BR>Customise your horses skin and mane colour.<BR>Activate mods to add extra fun to the game, such as low gravity and mega pushing.<BR>Flip, flop and drop around the amazing environment with your ragdoll physics horse!<BR><BR>6 May 2015 : Version 2.0 : Game remade, new map, better graphics, ragdoll physics and lots more! <BR><BR>Package size: 65 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Gallop, jump and ragdoll in a big beautiful map! Win crazy rewards for your horse!<BR><BR>Free roam Horse Simulator with Ragdoll Physics.<BR>Trot, Canter, Gallop and Jump around a Big Beautiful map.<BR>Explore a beach, Ice volcano, caves, mountains, forest and campsite.<BR>Talk to horse NPC’s to win rewards for your horse.<BR>Customise your horses skin and mane colour.<BR>Activate mods to add extra fun to the game, such as low gravity and mega pushing.<BR>Flip, flop and drop around the amazing environment with your ragdoll physics horse!<BR><BR>6 May 2015 : Version 2.0 : Game remade, new map, better graphics, ragdoll physics and lots more! <BR><BR>Package size: 65 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Galope, salto y muñeco de trapo en un mapa grande hermoso! Gana recompensas locos para su caballo!<BR><BR>Roam Free Horse Simulador con Ragdoll Physics.<BR>Trote, galope, galope y salto alrededor de un mapa grande hermosa.<BR>Explorar una playa, el volcán de hielo, cuevas, montañas, bosques y camping.<BR>Hable con caballo NPC para ganar recompensas por su caballo.<BR>Personaliza tu piel caballos y color melena.<BR>Activar mods para agregar más diversión al juego, como la baja gravedad y de mega empujar.<BR>Tirón, fracaso y soltar todo el entorno increíble con su caballo física ragdoll!<BR><BR>06 de mayo 2015: Versión 2.0: rehecha Juego, nuevo mapa, mejores gráficos, la física ragdoll y mucho más! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 65 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Laukka, hypätä ja ragdoll in iso kaunis kartalla! Voita hullu palkintoja hevonen!<BR><BR>Free Roam Horse Simulator kanssa ragdoll fysiikan.<BR>Trot, Canter, Laukka ja hypätä noin Big Beautiful kartan.<BR>Tutki ranta, Ice tulivuori, luolia, vuoria, metsää ja leirintäalue.<BR>Puhu hevosen NPC voittaa palkintoja oman hevosen.<BR>Mukauta hevoset ihon ja harja väri.<BR>Aktivoi modeja lisätä ylimääräistä hauska peli, kuten alhainen vakavuuden ja mega työntämällä.<BR>Flip, flop ja pudota ympäri hämmästyttävä ympäristön kanssa ragdoll fysiikan hevonen!<BR><BR>06 toukokuu 2015: Versio 2.0: Game uusittava, uusi kartta, parempaa grafiikkaa, ragdoll fysiikan ja paljon muuta! <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 65 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Gallop, saut et ragdoll dans une grande et belle carte! Gagner des récompenses folles pour votre cheval!<BR><BR>Free Roam Cheval Simulator avec Ragdoll Physics.<BR>Trot, Canter, Gallop et Jump autour d'un Big Beautiful carte.<BR>Explorez une plage, volcan de glace, grottes, montagnes, forêt et camping.<BR>Parlez-en à cheval PNJ de gagner des récompenses pour votre cheval.<BR>Personnalisez votre peau et la couleur des chevaux crinière.<BR>Activer mods d'ajouter l'amusement supplémentaire pour le jeu, tels que la faible gravité et méga poussant.<BR>Flip, flop et déposer autour de l'environnement incroyable avec votre cheval de la physique ragdoll!<BR><BR>6 mai 2015: Version 2.0: refait du jeu, nouvelle carte, de meilleurs graphismes, la physique ragdoll et beaucoup plus! <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 65 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Gallop, saut et ragdoll dans une grande et belle carte! Gagner des récompenses folles pour votre cheval!<BR><BR>Free Roam Cheval Simulator avec Ragdoll Physics.<BR>Trot, Canter, Gallop et Jump autour d'un Big Beautiful carte.<BR>Explorez une plage, volcan de glace, grottes, montagnes, forêt et camping.<BR>Parlez-en à cheval PNJ de gagner des récompenses pour votre cheval.<BR>Personnalisez votre peau et la couleur des chevaux crinière.<BR>Activer mods d'ajouter l'amusement supplémentaire pour le jeu, tels que la faible gravité et méga poussant.<BR>Flip, flop et déposer autour de l'environnement incroyable avec votre cheval de la physique ragdoll!<BR><BR>6 mai 2015: Version 2.0: refait du jeu, nouvelle carte, de meilleurs graphismes, la physique ragdoll et beaucoup plus! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 65 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Gallop, saltare e ragdoll in una grande bella mappa! Vinci premi pazzo per il vostro cavallo!<BR><BR>Free Roam Cavallo simulatore di Ragdoll Physics.<BR>Trot, Canter, Galoppo e saltare intorno una grande bella mappa.<BR>Esplorare una spiaggia, vulcano di ghiaccio, grotte, montagne, foreste e camping.<BR>Parlate con il cavallo NPC per vincere premi per il tuo cavallo.<BR>Personalizza la tua cavalli pelle e il colore criniera.<BR>Attivare mods per aggiungere divertimento in più al gioco, come la bassa gravità e mega spingere.<BR>Rifletti, flop e rilasciare intorno l'ambiente incredibile con il tuo cavallo fisica ragdoll!<BR><BR>6 Maggio 2015: Versione 2.0: rifatto gioco, nuova mappa, grafica migliore, fisica ragdoll e molto altro ancora! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 65 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>ギャロップ、大きな美しいマップでジャンプとラグドール！あなたの馬のために狂気の報酬を獲得！<BR><BR>ラグドール物理学とフリーローミング馬シミュレータ。<BR>トロット、キャンター、ギャロップ、ビッグビューティフルマップの周りのジャンプ。<BR>ビーチ、氷火山、洞窟、山、森やキャンプ場を探検。<BR>あなたの馬のための報酬を獲得するために、馬NPCのに相談してください。<BR>あなたの馬の皮とたてがみの色をカスタマイズ。<BR>このような低重力やメガ押しのようなゲームに余分な楽しみを追加する改造をアクティブにします。<BR>、フリップフロップとあなたのラグドール物理学の馬で素晴らしい環境の周りにドロップ！<BR><BR>2015年5月6日：バージョン2.0：ゲームのリメイク、新マップ、より良いグラフィックス、ラグドール物理学とたくさんもっと！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 65 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Galopp, hoppe og ragdoll i en stor, vakker kartet! Vinn sprø belønning for hesten din!<BR><BR>Gratis roam Horse Simulator med Ragdoll Physics.<BR>Trav, Canter, Galopp og hoppe rundt en stor vakker kartet.<BR>Utforsk en strand, Ice vulkan, grotter, fjell, skog og campingplass.<BR>Snakk med hesten NPC er å vinne premier for hesten.<BR>Tilpass hester hud og manke farge.<BR>Aktiver mods å legge ekstra moro til spillet, for eksempel lavt tyngdepunkt og mega presser.<BR>Flip, flop og slippe rundt fantastisk miljø med ragdoll fysikk hest!<BR><BR>6 mai 2015: Versjon 2.0: Spillet gjenskapt, nytt kart, bedre grafikk, ragdoll fysikk og mye mer! <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 65 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Galop, springen en ragdoll in een grote mooie kaart! Win gekke beloning voor uw paard!<BR><BR>Free Roam Paard Simulator met Fysica Ragdoll.<BR>Draf, galop, galop en Jump rond een grote mooie kaart.<BR>Ontdek een strand, Ice vulkaan, grotten, bergen, bos en de camping.<BR>Praat met paard NPC's om beloningen te winnen voor uw paard.<BR>Pas uw paarden huid en manen kleur.<BR>Activeer mods om extra plezier toe te voegen aan het spel, zoals een laag zwaartepunt en mega duwen.<BR>Tik, plof en neerzetten rond de geweldige omgeving met uw ragdoll physics paard!<BR><BR>6 mei 2015: Versie 2.0: Game remade, nieuwe kaart, betere graphics, ragdoll physics en nog veel meer! <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 65 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Galop, skakać i ragdoll w dużym pięknym mapie! Wygraj nagrody za szalony koń!<BR><BR>Bezpłatne wędrować Jazda Simulator z fizyki ragdoll.<BR>Kłus, Canter, galop i skakać wokół duży piękny mapie.<BR>Przeglądaj Ice plażowej, wulkan, jaskinie, góry, las i kemping.<BR>Porozmawiaj z konia NPC do wygrania nagrody dla konia.<BR>Dostosuj swoje konie i kolor skóry grzywa.<BR>Aktywuj modów, aby dodać dodatkowe zabawy do gry, takie jak niskiej grawitacji i mega pchania.<BR>Flip flop i upuść wokół wspaniałego środowiska z ragdoll fizyki konia!<BR><BR>06 maja 2015: Wersja 2.0: przerobiony gry, nowa mapa, lepszą grafikę, fizykę ragdoll i wiele więcej! <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 65 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Galopp, hoppa och ragdoll i en stor vacker karta! Vinn galna belöningar för din häst!<BR><BR>Gratis roam Horse Simulator med ragdoll fysik.<BR>Trav, Galopp, galopp och hoppa runt en stor härlig karta.<BR>Utforska en strand, is vulkan, grottor, berg, skog och camping.<BR>Prata med häst NPC att vinna belöningar för din häst.<BR>Skräddarsy din hästar huden och mane färg.<BR>Aktivera mods att lägga till extra roligt att spelet, såsom låg allvar och mega driver.<BR>Flip, misslyckande och släppa runt den fantastiska miljö med ragdoll fysik häst!<BR><BR>6 maj 2015: Version 2.0: Spel omgjord, ny karta, bättre grafik, ragdoll fysik och mycket mer! <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 65 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>(C) 2014 StephenAllen<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Simulation"/><genre value="Games:RPG"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_19.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_20.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_21.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_22.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_23.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_24.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_25.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_26.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_27.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
