<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00034_00">
 <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>29892176</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[「SwitchGalaxy」へようこそ。PlayStation®Mobileでも例を見ないスピード感満点ゲームで、宇宙を猛烈なスピードで駆け抜けよう。<br> <br>「SwitchGalaxy」は、美しいビジュアル要素と高品質のオーディオが楽しめると同時に、そのスピード感が恐ろしくクセになるアーケードゲーム。障害物や敵の間を駆け抜けながら宇宙を横断し、Dakur Technology のためにタンタラムを集めよう。銀河の向こうにある彼らの研究所には最新のテクノロジーが待っている。宇宙船のアップグレードに必要なクレジットを集め、トラック上に落ちているアイテムを拾ってベストタイムをゲットしたり最高の報酬を手に入れよう。<br> <br>それでも物足りなければ、サバイバルモードを試してみよう。命は１つしかないのに、永遠に続くゲーム。あなたはどれだけ生き残れる？<br> <br>特徴<br>• スピード感たっぷりの流れるようなゲームプレイ<br>• ミッションベースのストーリーモード<br>• 高品質のグラフィックスとオーディオ<br>• 終わりのないチャレンジ – サバイバルモード<br>• 反射的アクションを可能にするシンプルなコントロール<br>• アップグレード可能な宇宙船やスキン<br><br>コンテンツ容量:29 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<br><br>著作権等:<br>(C) Atomicom Limited 2013. Switch Galaxy is the trademark of Atomicom Limited. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Welcome to Switch Galaxy, the fastest gaming experience on PlayStation®Mobile that will have you blazing across the galaxy at breakneck speeds.<br> <br>Switch Galaxy is an insanely addictive, fast-paced arcade challenge with gorgeous visuals and high quality audio. Weave your way past obstacles and enemies as you travel across the galaxy collecting Tantalum for Dakur Technology. Reach their research base on the other side of the Galaxy and you will be rewarded with their latest technology. Collect credits to spend on ship upgrades and look out for pick-ups on the track that will give you an advantage to get the best times and highest rewards.<br><br>If you're eager for another challenge then try out the survival mode. With one life and infinity in front of you, how long can you last?<br><br>Features<br>• High-speed, fluid gameplay<br>• Mission based story mode<br>• High quality graphics and audio<br>• Infinitely challenging survival mode<br>• Simple controls for reflex-action<br>• Upgradeable Ship and skins<br><br>Package size: 29 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>(C) Atomicom Limited 2013. Switch Galaxy is the trademark of Atomicom Limited. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Bienvenue dans Switch Galaxy, l'expérience de jeu la plus rapide sur PlayStation®Mobile qui vous transportera à une vitesse vertigineuse à travers la galaxie.<br>Switch est un jeu de rapidité totalement addictif, au rythme de graphismes et de son époustouflants, avec un gameplay fantastique. Switch Galaxy est incroyablement addictif, un défi d'arcade au rythme rapide avec des effets visuels magnifiques et un son de haute qualité. Faufilez-vous à travers les obstacles et les ennemis de façon à voyager à travers la Galaxie et de collecter la Tantale pour Dakur Technology. Atteignez leur base de recherche de l'autre côté de la Galaxie et vous serez récompensé avec leur technologie de pointe. Recueillez des crédits à dépensez les dans des mises à niveau des navires. Collectez des bonus qui vous permettront de gagner du temps et d’obtenir les récompenses les plus élevées.<br>Si vous devenez accro essayez le mode survie. Avec une seule vie et l'infini devant vous, combien de temps allez-vous tenir?<br><br>Caractéristiques : <br>• Haute-vitesse, gameplay fluide<br>• Une misson basée sur le mode histoire<br>• Graphismes et son de haute qualité<br>• Mode survie infiniment difficile<br>• Commandes simples pour des actions réflexes<br>• Mises à jour des navires et des apparences<br><br>Taille du paquet: 29 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>(C) Atomicom Limited 2013. Switch Galaxy is the trademark of Atomicom Limited. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Benvenuto a Switch Galaxy, l'esperienza ludica più scavezzacollo disponibile su PlayStation®Mobile. Sfreccia nella galassia a velocità inaudite!<br>  <br>Switch Galaxy ti prende e non ti molla più: una sfida in puro stile arcade, ultra-veloce e con una qualità grafica e sonora da paura. Lanciati a perdifiato per la galassia alla conquista del Tantalum, in nome di Dakur Technology, facendo il pelo a ostacoli e nemici. Raggiungi tutto d'un pezzo i laboratori di Dakur Technology all'altro lato della galassia per avere accesso alle loro tecnologie. Accumula crediti da poter spendere per migliorare l'astronave e tieni gli occhi aperti lungo il tracciato: troverai vari aiuti per ottenere tempi e ricompense migliori.<br>Se fremi dalla voglia di una sfida ancora più tosta, prova Sopravvivenza. Una sola vita e l'infinito che ti aspetta... pensi di andare lontano?<br> <br>Aspetti salienti:<br>• Un'esperienza di gioco che scorre a velocità inaudite<br>• Una storia che si sviluppa di missione in missione<br>• Una qualità grafica e sonora da paura<br>• Sopravvivenza, per una sfida letteralmente infinita<br>• Un sistema di controllo che agevola i tuoi riflessi<br>• Un'astronave ottimizzabile sia in aspetto che prestazioni<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 29 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<br><br>(C) Atomicom Limited 2013. Switch Galaxy is the trademark of Atomicom Limited. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Bienvenido a Switch Galaxy, el juego mas velóz en PlayStation®Mobile que te hará cruzar la galaxia a una velocidad vertiginosa contra el tiempo.<br><br>Switch Galaxy es un juego de velocidad muy adictivo con alta calidad de audio e increíbles gráficos. Abrete camino entre las naves enemigas y los obstáculos mientras viajas por la galaxia recolectando el material Tantalum para la Ciudad Dakur. Llega a su estación de investigación al otro extremo de la Galaxia y serás recompensado con su última tecnología. Recolecta créditos que puedes usar para mejorar tu nave; presta atención y  agarra los pick-ups que aparecen en la vía, éstos son clave para obtener mejores tiempos y mayores recompensas.<br>Si quieres aventurarte por otro desafío juega el Modo Supervivencia (Survival Mode). En ésta modalidad tienes una sola vida, cuánto puedes sobrevivir?<br><br>Características:<br>• Juego de alta velocidad<br>• Modo Misión y Modo Supervivencia<br>• Opciones para mejorar tu nave<br>• Alta calidad de gráficos y audio<br>• Horas de diversión<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 29 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<br><br>(C) Atomicom Limited 2013. Switch Galaxy is the trademark of Atomicom Limited. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Willkommen bei Switch Galaxy, dem schnellsten Gaming-Erlebnis auf PlayStation®Mobile - mit halsbrecherischer Geschwindigkeit durch die Galaxie.<br><br>Switch Galaxy ist eine süchtig machende, extrem schnelle Arcade-Herausforderung mit fantastischer Grafik und hoher Audioqualität. Schlängeln Sie sich zwischen Hindernissen und Feinden hindurch und sammeln Sie dabei „Tantalum“ für die Firma Dakur Technology. Wenn Sie    die Forschungsstation auf der anderen Seite der Galaxie erreichen, bekommen Sie die neueste Technologie als Belohnung. Sammeln Sie Credits für Schiff-Upgrades und achten Sie auf Pick-ups auf der Strecke, welche Ihnen helfen werden, die besten Zeiten zu erreichen und die höchsten Belohnungen zu bekommen.<br>Wenn Sie eine neue Herausforderung wollen, dann probieren Sie den Survival-Modus. Mit nur einem Leben und Unendlichkeit vor Ihnen - wie weit werden Sie kommen?<br><br>Features<br>• Hochgeschwindigkeits-Gameplay<br>• Missionsbasierter Storymodus<br>• Hochwertige Grafik und Audio<br>• Unendlicher herausfordernder Survival-Modus<br>• Einfaches Kontroll-System für Reflexhandlungen<br>• Erweiterbares Schiff und verschiedene Skins<br><br>Paketgröße: 29 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<br><br>(C) Atomicom Limited 2013. Switch Galaxy is the trademark of Atomicom Limited. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Welcome to Switch Galaxy, the fastest gaming experience on PlayStation®Mobile that will have you blazing across the galaxy at breakneck speeds.<br> <br>Switch Galaxy is an insanely addictive, fast-paced arcade challenge with gorgeous visuals and high quality audio. Weave your way past obstacles and enemies as you travel across the galaxy collecting Tantalum for Dakur Technology. Reach their research base on the other side of the Galaxy and you will be rewarded with their latest technology. Collect credits to spend on ship upgrades and look out for pick-ups on the track that will give you an advantage to get the best times and highest rewards.<br><br>If you're eager for another challenge then try out the survival mode. With one life and infinity in front of you, how long can you last?<br><br>Features<br>• High-speed, fluid gameplay<br>• Mission based story mode<br>• High quality graphics and audio<br>• Infinitely challenging survival mode<br>• Simple controls for reflex-action<br>• Upgradeable Ship and skins<br><br>Package size: 29 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<br><br>(C) Atomicom Limited 2013. Switch Galaxy is the trademark of Atomicom Limited. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Bienvenue dans Switch Galaxy, l'expérience de jeu la plus rapide sur PlayStation®Mobile qui vous transportera à une vitesse vertigineuse à travers la galaxie.<br>Switch est un jeu de rapidité totalement addictif, au rythme de graphismes et de son époustouflants, avec un gameplay fantastique. Switch Galaxy est incroyablement addictif, un défi d'arcade au rythme rapide avec des effets visuels magnifiques et un son de haute qualité. Faufilez-vous à travers les obstacles et les ennemis de façon à voyager à travers la Galaxie et de collecter la Tantale pour Dakur Technology. Atteignez leur base de recherche de l'autre côté de la Galaxie et vous serez récompensé avec leur technologie de pointe. Recueillez des crédits à dépensez les dans des mises à niveau des navires. Collectez des bonus qui vous permettront de gagner du temps et d’obtenir les récompenses les plus élevées.<br>Si vous devenez accro essayez le mode survie. Avec une seule vie et l'infini devant vous, combien de temps allez-vous tenir?<br><br>Caractéristiques : <br>• Haute-vitesse, gameplay fluide<br>• Une misson basée sur le mode histoire<br>• Graphismes et son de haute qualité<br>• Mode survie infiniment difficile<br>• Commandes simples pour des actions réflexes<br>• Mises à jour des navires et des apparences<br><br>Taille du programme: 29 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<br><br>(C) Atomicom Limited 2013. Switch Galaxy is the trademark of Atomicom Limited. All Rights Reserved<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Racing"/>
  <genre value="Games:Arcade"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
