<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00274_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>148728112</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="de"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Bekæmpe endeløse horder af levende døde og monstre som en pirat eller en Royal Navy! Shoot ' em, blast'em, beat 'em.<BR><BR>Indsamle bomber og skat kister og dræbe snesevis af monstre og udøde at slå din rang!<BR><BR>Sætte bomber taktisk for at få ultimative combos.<BR><BR>Seks spilbare figurer (knappen Åbn bar) med forskellige evner. Som slowmotion funktion for nøjagtig dræber.<BR><BR>Tre atmosfæriske og forskellige arenaer!<BR><BR>Åh, vi nævner at du tegner tusindvis at dø? <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 142 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Kämpfen Sie als Pirat oder als Royal Navy gegen endlose Horden von Untoten und Monstern! Shoot 'em, blast 'em, Beat' em. <BR><BR>Sammeln Sie Bomben und Schatzkisten ein und töten Sie dutzende von Monstern und Untote um Ihren Rank zu überbieten! <BR><BR>Setzten Sie Bomben taktisch ein, um Ultimative Combos zu erhalten.<BR><BR>Sechs spielbare Charaktere (Freischaltbar) mit unterschiedlichen Fähigkeiten. Z. b. Zeitlupenfunktion für präzise kills.<BR><BR>Drei Atmosphärische und Unterschiedliche Arenen!<BR><BR>Oh, haben wir schon erwähnt, dass Sie tausende male sterben werden? <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 142 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Fight endless hordes of undead and monsters as a pirate or a Royal Navy! Shoot ' em, blast'em, beat 'em.<BR><BR>Collect bombs and treasure chests and kill dozens of monsters and undead to beat your rank!<BR><BR>Put bombs tactically to get ultimate combos.<BR><BR>Six playable characters (Open button bar) with different abilities. Such as slow motion function for accurate kills.<BR><BR>Three atmospheric and different arenas!<BR><BR>Oh, we did mention that you draw thousands to die? <BR><BR>Package size: 142 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Lucha interminables hordas de muertos vivientes y monstruos como un pirata o de la marina real. Disparar ' em, blast'em, Batirlos.<BR><BR>Recoge bombas y cofres del tesoro y matar a docenas de monstruos y zombies para vencer su rango!<BR><BR>Pon bombas tácticamente para conseguir a combos de ultimate.<BR><BR>Seis personajes jugables (barra de botones abiertos) con capacidades diferentes. Como la función de cámara lenta para mata precisa.<BR><BR>Tres ámbitos atmosféricos y diferentes!<BR><BR>¿Mencionamos que dibujar miles de personas a morir? <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 142 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Taistella loputtoman laumoista undead ja hirviöitä merirosvo tai kuninkaallisen laivaston! Ampua ' em, blast'em, beat 'em.<BR><BR>Kerätä pommit ja ne. ja tappaa kymmeniä hirviöitä ja undead voittamaan sijoitus!<BR><BR>Laita pommeja taktisesti saada lopullinen yhdistelmä.<BR><BR>Kuusi pelattavaa hahmoa (Avaa bar) eri kykyjä. Kuten hidastettuna toiminnon tarkka tappaa.<BR><BR>Kolme ilmakehän ja eri areenoilla!<BR><BR>Voi me mainita vetävät tuhansia kuolla? <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 142 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Combattre des hordes de morts-vivants et monstres comme un pirate ou un Marine royale ! Shoot ' em, blast'em, battre.<BR><BR>Recueillir des bombes et coffres au Trésor et tuer des dizaines de monstres et morts-vivants pour battre votre rang !<BR><BR>Mettre des bombes sur le plan tactique pour obtenir des combos ultimes.<BR><BR>Six personnages jouables (barre de boutons ouverts) avec des capacités différentes. Comme la fonction ralenti pour tue précis.<BR><BR>Trois différents et atmosphériques des arènes !<BR><BR>Ah, nous avons mentionné que vous dessinez des milliers à mourir ? <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 142 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Combattere le infinite orde di non morti e mostri come un pirata o un Royal Navy! Shoot ' em, blast'em, batterlo.<BR><BR>Raccogliere le bombe e scrigni del tesoro e uccidere decine di mostri e non morti per battere il tuo rank!<BR><BR>Mettere bombe tatticamente per ottenere combo finale.<BR><BR>Sei personaggi giocabili (pulsante Open bar) con diverse abilità. Quale funzione rallentatore per accurata uccide.<BR><BR>Tre arene atmosferiche e diversi!<BR><BR>Ti ricordiamo che attirano migliaia di morire? <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 142 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>アンデッドの無限の大群を戦うと、海賊や、高貴な海軍としてモンスター ！撮影 ' em、blast'em、それらを打ちます。<BR><BR>収集爆弾と宝箱とあなたのランクをビートに何十ものモンスターやアンデッドを殺す ！<BR><BR>究極のコンボを得る戦術的に爆弾を置きます。<BR><BR>6 再生可能な文字 (開いているボタンバー) 異なる能力を持つ。正確なを殺すのためのスローモーション機能など<BR><BR>3 つの大気と異なるアリーナ ！<BR><BR>ああ、私たち死ぬ数千人を描くことを言及しましたか？ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 142 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Kjempe endeløse horder av vandøde og monstre som en pirat eller en Royal Navy! Shoot ' em, blast'em, beat 'em.<BR><BR>Samle bomber og skatten kister og drepe dusinvis av monstre og vandøde å slå din rang!<BR><BR>Satt bomber taktisk for å få endelig kombinasjoner.<BR><BR>Seks spillbare karakterer (knappen åpne bar) med ulike muligheter. Som slow motion-funksjon for nøyaktig dreper.<BR><BR>Tre atmosfæriske og ulike arenaer!<BR><BR>Oh, vi nevne at du tegner tusenvis å dø? <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 142 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Eindeloze undead hordes vechten en monsters als een piraat of een Royal Navy! Schieten ' em, blast'em, beat 'em.<BR><BR>Verzamel bommen en schat kisten en doden tientallen monsters en ondoden om te verslaan uw rang!<BR><BR>Plaats bommen tactisch om uiteindelijke combo's.<BR><BR>Zes bespeelbare personages (Open knoppenbalk) met verschillende capaciteiten. Zoals slow motion functie voor nauwkeurige doodt.<BR><BR>Drie atmosferische en verschillende arena's!<BR><BR>Oh, wij heb al gezegd dat u tekent duizenden om te sterven? <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 142 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Walczyć niekończące się hordy nieumarłych i potwory jako pirata lub Royal Navy! Strzelać ' em, blast'em, beat 'em.<BR><BR>Zbieraj bomby i skarb skrzynie i zabić dziesiątki potworów i nieumarłych, aby pokonać ranking!<BR><BR>Umieścić bomby taktycznie, aby uzyskać ostateczny combo.<BR><BR>Sześć grywalnych postaci (przycisk Otwórz pasek) z różnych umiejętności. Jak powolny ruch funkcja precyzyjne zabija.<BR><BR>Trzy atmosfery i różnych aren!<BR><BR>Aha mamy wspomina się, że można wyciągnąć tysiące umrzeć? <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 142 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Slåss oändliga horder av odöda och monster som en pirat eller en Royal Navy! Shoot ' em, blast'em, beat 'em.<BR><BR>Samla bomber och skatt kistor och döda massor av monster och odöda att slå din rank!<BR><BR>Sätta bomber taktiskt för att få ultimat combos.<BR><BR>Sex spelbara karaktärer (knappen Öppna bar) med olika förmågor. Som slow motion-funktion för korrekt dödar.<BR><BR>Tre atmosfäriska och olika arenor!<BR><BR>Åh, vi nämnde att du ritar tusentals att dö? <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 142 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>2015(C) LostVision Studios Stefan Krauß<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Action"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
