<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00151_00">

  <appVersion>1.11</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>15710272</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Udtrykker taknemmelighed for den første levering årsdagen for " Vacc-Balls -Chin"<BR>Du skal konfrontere det med mennesker i verden.<BR><BR>■Spilintroduktion<BR>I dette nuttede maskot-hovedbrudsspil går spillerne efter den bedste score ved at dyrke de farverige Vacc-Balls, der indeholder unge vacciner, og stille dem op. Jo flere du samler, jo højere bliver din score, og jo mere stiger du i niveau!<BR><BR>■Grundlæggende spil<BR>Når du stiller tre eller flere af den samme type Vacc-Ball op lodret, vandret eller diagonalt, vil vaccinen inde i dem vokse. Åbn for nye baner, og forøg din score ved at samle flere og flere.<BR>Når skærmen bliver helt fyldt med Vacc-Balls, er spillet forbi.<BR>Men det stopper ikke der! Hvis du har den særlige "MidoRich"-vaccine, kan du genstarte spillet på samme bane og med samme score <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 15 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR>Support til online spil med flere spillere: Ja (2 spillere)<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Das Ausdrücken am ersten Lieferungsjahrestag für .Vacc-Ball-Kinn von Dankbarkeit.<BR>Konfrontieren Sie es bitte mit Leuten in der Welt. <BR><BR>■Game-Einführung<BR>In diesem niedlichen Maskottchenpuzzlespiel zielen Spieler für das hohe Spielergebnis durch das Starten, das Anstellen und das Anbauen der bunten Vacc-Bälle, die junge Impfstoffe enthalten.<BR><BR>■Basic-Spiel<BR>Wenn Sie 3 oder mehr des gleichen Vacc-Balles horizontal senkrecht in einer Reihe aufstellen, oder diagonal, der Impfstoff in wird wachsen. Eröffnen Sie neue Niveaus und erhöhen Sie Ihr Spielergebnis, indem Sie sich immer mehr sammeln.<BR>Wenn sich der Bildschirm mit Vacc-Bällen zur Spitze füllt, ist es vorbei bereit.<BR>Aber Spiel über ist nicht das Ende! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 15 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR>Online-Unterstützung für Multiplayer-Spiel: Ja (2 Spieler)<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Expressing gratitude on the first delivery anniversary for 「Vacc-Balls-Chin」<BR>Please confront it with people in the world. <BR><BR>■Game Introduction<BR>In this cute mascot puzzle game, players aim for the high score by launching, lining up, and growing the colorful Vacc-Balls that contain young vaccines. <BR><BR>■Basic Play<BR>When you line up 3 or more of the same Vacc-Ball vertically, horizontally, or diagonally, the vaccine inside will grow. Open new levels and increase your score by collecting more and more.<BR>When the screen fills to the top with Vacc-Balls, it's game over.<BR>The Battle Nutrients on the right side of the screen will fill up as you create chains of 2 and 3 and clear them. The Nutrients are ready when it's full!<BR>You can now play in Battle Mode. <BR><BR>Package size: 15 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Expressing gratitude on the first delivery anniversary for 「Vacc-Balls-Chin」<BR>Please confront it with people in the world. <BR><BR>■Game Introduction<BR>In this cute mascot puzzle game, players aim for the high score by launching, lining up, and growing the colorful Vacc-Balls that contain young vaccines. <BR><BR>■Basic Play<BR>When you line up 3 or more of the same Vacc-Ball vertically, horizontally, or diagonally, the vaccine inside will grow. Open new levels and increase your score by collecting more and more.<BR>When the screen fills to the top with Vacc-Balls, it's game over.<BR>The Battle Nutrients on the right side of the screen will fill up as you create chains of 2 and 3 and clear them. The Nutrients are ready when it's full!<BR>You can now play in Battle Mode. <BR><BR>Package size: 15 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Expressing gratitude on the first delivery anniversary for 「Vacc-Balls-Chin」<BR>Please confront it with people in the world. <BR><BR>■Game Introduction<BR>In this cute mascot puzzle game, players aim for the high score by launching, lining up, and growing the colorful Vacc-Balls that contain young vaccines. <BR><BR>■Basic Play<BR>When you line up 3 or more of the same Vacc-Ball vertically, horizontally, or diagonally, the vaccine inside will grow. Open new levels and increase your score by collecting more and more.<BR>When the screen fills to the top with Vacc-Balls, it's game over.<BR>The Battle Nutrients on the right side of the screen will fill up as you create chains of 2 and 3 and clear them. The Nutrients are ready when it's full!<BR>You can now play in Battle Mode. <BR><BR>Package size: 15 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Expressing gratitude on the first delivery anniversary for 「Vacc-Balls-Chin」<BR>Please confront it with people in the world. <BR><BR>■Game Introduction<BR>In this cute mascot puzzle game, players aim for the high score by launching, lining up, and growing the colorful Vacc-Balls that contain young vaccines. <BR><BR>■Basic Play<BR>When you line up 3 or more of the same Vacc-Ball vertically, horizontally, or diagonally, the vaccine inside will grow. Open new levels and increase your score by collecting more and more.<BR>When the screen fills to the top with Vacc-Balls, it's game over.<BR>The Battle Nutrients on the right side of the screen will fill up as you create chains of 2 and 3 and clear them. The Nutrients are ready when it's full!<BR>You can now play in Battle Mode. <BR><BR>Package size: 15 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR>Online multiplayer game support: Yes (2 Players)<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Expresando su gratitud por la primera entrega aniversario " Vacc-Balls -Chin"<BR>Por favor, se enfrenta con la gente en el mundo.<BR><BR>■Introducción del partido de ¦<BR>En este partido del rompecabezas de mascota lindo, los jugadores apuntan hacia el puntaje alto se iniciando, formar fila, y crear las Vacc - pelotas lleno de color que contienen vacunas jóvenes. Cuanto más usted colecciona, el más alto su puntaje y más grande su nivel el!<BR><BR>■la obra dramática básica<BR>Cuando usted forra 3 o more de la misma Vacc - pelota verticalmente, horizontalmente, o en diagonal, el carril de menor tráfico de vacuna crecerá. Abra nuevos niveles y incremente su puntaje coleccionando más y más.<BR>Cuando la pantalla se llena a la cima con Vacc - pelotas, es el partido desde lo alto. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 15 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR>Asistencia para juegos de varios jugadores en línea: Sí (2 jugadores)<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Ilmaista kiitokseni 「Vacc pallot Chin」 kuluneeksi toimitus <BR> haluta kohdata ihmisiä maailmassa.<BR><BR>■ Pelin Johdanto <BR>Tässä söpö maskotti palapeli Pelin tarkoitus korkeat pisteet käynnistämällä, riviin, ja kasvava värikäs VACC-pallot, jotka sisältävät nuorten rokotteita.Enemmän keräät, sitä korkeammat pisteet ja enemmän tasosi!<BR>■ Basic Play <BR>Kun riviin 3 tai useampi saman VACC-Ball vaakasuoraan, pystysuoraan tai vinottain, rokote sisällä kasvaa. Avaa uusia tasoja ja lisätä pisteet keräämällä enemmän ja enemmän. <BR>Kun näyttö täyttyy alkuun kanssa VACC-pallot, peli päättyy. <BR>Battle ravinteet oikeassa laidassa täyttyy luot ketjujen 2 ja 3 ja poista ne. Ravinteet ovat valmiina, kun se on täynnä! <BR>Nyt voit pelata Battle tilassa. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 15 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR>Monen pelaajan pelin verkkotuki: Kyllä  (2 pelaajaa)<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Exprimant gratitude sur le premier anniversaire de la livraison pour .Vacc-balle-menton.<BR>Let aanpakken met mensen in de wereld.<BR><BR>■Introduction du jeu<BR>cette adorable mascotte jeu de puzzle, les joueurs visent pour le score élevé en lançant, en alignant, et la croissance de l'Vacc-Balls coloré que contiennent les vaccins jeunes.<BR><BR>■Pièce de base<BR>Lorsque vous alignez 3 ou plus du même Vacc-Ball horizontalement, verticalement ou en diagonale, le vaccin l'intérieur va croître. Ouvrir de nouveaux niveaux et augmenter votre score en collectant plus et plus.<BR>Lorsque l'écran remplit au sommet des Balles de Vacc, c'est jeu partout.<BR>Les Éléments nutritifs de la Bataille à droite le côté de l'écran remplira au-dessus comme tu crées des chaînes de 2 et 3 et les éclaircis. <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 15 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR>Mode multijoueur en ligne : Oui (2 joueurs)<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Exprimant gratitude sur le premier anniversaire de la livraison pour .Vacc-balle-menton.<BR>Let aanpakken met mensen in de wereld.<BR><BR>■Introduction du jeu<BR>cette adorable mascotte jeu de puzzle, les joueurs visent pour le score élevé en lançant, en alignant, et la croissance de l'Vacc-Balls coloré que contiennent les vaccins jeunes.<BR><BR>■Pièce de base<BR>Lorsque vous alignez 3 ou plus du même Vacc-Ball horizontalement, verticalement ou en diagonale, le vaccin l'intérieur va croître. Ouvrir de nouveaux niveaux et augmenter votre score en collectant plus et plus.<BR>Lorsque l'écran remplit au sommet des Balles de Vacc, c'est jeu partout.<BR>Les Éléments nutritifs de la Bataille à droite le côté de l'écran remplira au-dessus comme tu crées des chaînes de 2 et 3 et les éclaircis. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 15 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR>Assistance en ligne pour jeu multijoueur : Oui (2 joueurs)<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[La gratitudine che esprime sul primo anniversario di consegna per .Vacc-palla-mento.<BR>Per favore lo confronti con persone nel mondo. <BR><BR>■Introduzione di .Game<BR>In questo gioco di enigma di mascotte grazioso, i giocatori puntano per il risultato alto lanciando, fiancheggiando su, e crescendo le Vacc-palle colorite che contengono i giovani vaccini. Il più che Lei raccoglie, il più alto il Suo risultato e più grande il Suo livello!<BR><BR>■Basic Play<BR>Quando Lei solca su verticalmente 3 o più della stessa Vacc-palla, orizzontalmente o diagonalmente, il vaccino in crescerà. Apra livelli nuovi ed aumenti il Suo risultato raccogliendo sempre più.<BR>Quando lo schermo riempie alla cima con Vacc-palle, è su pronto. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 15 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR>Supporto giochi multiplayer online: Sì (2 giocatori)<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[「ワク玉ちん」配信1周年の感謝の気持ちを込めました。<BR>世界のみんなと遊んで、対戦してください。<BR><BR>■ゲーム紹介<BR>ワクちんを閉じこめた色とりどりの“ワク玉”を、押し上げ、揃え、成長さて、どんどん採取で目指せハイスコア！目指せハイレベル！！<BR>そんなモリモリ遊べる、ゆるキャラパズルゲームです。<BR>更にネット対決やスコアランキングでマイラボの着せ替えアイテムをGETしよう。 <BR><BR>■基本ルール<BR>縦、横、斜めに同じ“ワク玉”を３つ以上揃えると、ワク玉の中のワクちんが成長。採取される事でスコアもレベルもどんどん上昇。<BR>但し、フィールド全部が“ワク玉”で全て埋め尽くしてしまうと、ゲームオーバーになるぞ。<BR>ゲームオーバーになっても大丈夫。特異ワクちんの「ミドリっち」を持っていれば、その時のレベルとその時のスコアからゲームが再開できるので、ハイスコアランキング１位の栄誉も夢じゃない!<BR><BR>２連鎖、３連鎖と連鎖消しを成功させると画面右側の「対決栄養素」が溜まり、満タンになると「対決栄養素」完成！<BR>対決モードのプレイが可能になるぞ。<BR><BR>「ミドリっち」や「対決栄養素」、プレイ中に使える３つのプレイアイテムは、全て“わっコイン”での購入が可能。<BR>　アイテム１「スロー玉」：“ワク玉”の補充スピードが１分間遅くなる<BR>　アイテム２「消し玉」：フィールド上の最多“ワク玉”を強制成長<BR>　アイテム３「解除玉」：LOCKされた“ワク玉”を破壊<BR>でも、アイテムの使用は１レベルでひとつまでだから注意してね。<BR><BR>■マイラボデコレート<BR>毎週開催されるハイスコアランキングの上位者には、マイラボ着せ替えアイテムや対決コメントがもらえるよ。<BR>更に、毎月開催される対決ランキングでは、季節限定マイラボ着せ替えセットが上位者にプレゼント！<BR>ふたつチャンスを逃さないで！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 15 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR>オンラインマルチプレイ: 2人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Å uttrykke takknemlighet på første levering jubileum for " Vacc-Balls -Chin" <BR>kan du konfrontere det med folk i verden.<BR><BR>■Spillintroduksjon<BR>I dette nusselige hjernetrim-spillet må du prøve å høyeste poengesum, ved å skyte vacc-baler som inneholder vaksiner. Jo flere du samler, desto mer poeng får du. Og med en høyere poengsum oppnår du et høyere nivå.<BR><BR>■Grunnleggende<BR>Få tre på rad av samme type vacc-baller, diagonlalt, horisontalt eller vertikalt, og vaksinen inn i ballene begynner å vokse. Lås opp nye nivåer og få en høyere poengsum, ved å samle flere av dem.<BR>Når vacc-ballene når toppen av skjermen er spillet over. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 15 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR>Støtte for online flerspiller: Ja (2 spillere)<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Ik dank de eerste aflevering verjaardag " Vacc-Balls -Kin"<BR>kunt u aanpakken met mensen in de wereld.<BR><BR>■Game Introductie<BR>In dit schattige mascotte puzzelgame, spelers doel voor de hoge score van start, versterking en groei van het kleurrijke Vacc-Balls die jonge vaccins. Hoe meer je er verzamelt, hoe hoger uw score en meer uw niveau!<BR><BR>■Basic spelen!<BR>Wanneer je 3 of meer van dezelfde Vacc-Ball verticaal, horizontaal of diagonaal, het vaccin binnen zal groeien. Open nieuwe levels en verhoog je score door het verzamelen meer en meer.<BR>Wanneer het scherm wordt gevuld aan de top met Vacc-Balls , is het game over. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 15 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR>Ondersteuning voor online multiplayergame: Ja (2 spelers)<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Wdzięczności na rocznicę pierwszej dostawy dla " Vacc-Balls -podbródek"<BR>Proszę skonfrontować ją z ludźmi na świecie.<BR><BR>■Game wprowadzenie, w tym urocze maskotki puzzle, zawodnicy z najlepszymi wynikami w celu rozpoczęcie, ustawiając w jednej linii, a rosnące w kolorowych Vacc-Balls zawierających młoda szczepionek. Tym bardziej, tym wyższy wynik i większy poziom!<BR><BR>■Basic zagrać po linii 3 lub więcej tego samego Vacc-Ball pionowo, poziomo lub po przekątnej, szczepionka wewnątrz będzie rosnąć. Otwórz nowe poziomy i poprawić swój wynik zbierając coraz więcej. Jeśli ekran z monitora zajmuje cały do góry Vacc-Balls , gra się skończy. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 15 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR>Tryb online dla wielu graczy: tak (2 graczy)<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski/Japoński<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Jag uttrycker min tacksamhet på den första leveransen årsdagen för " Vacc-Balls -Chin" <BR>Vänligen konfrontera den med människor i världen.<BR><BR>■ Spelintroduktion<BR>I det här söta pusselmaskotspelet siktar spelarna på toppoängen genom att avfyra, rada upp och odla sina färgglada Vacc-Balls som innehåller unga vaccin. Desto fler du samlar, desto högre poäng och bättre nivå får du!<BR><BR>■ Spelfundament<BR>Då du radar upp tre eller fler av samma Vacc-Balls vertikalt, horisontellt eller diagonalt kommer vaccinet inuti att växa. Nå nya nivåer och öka din poäng genom att samla fler och fler.<BR>Då dina Vacc-Balls når toppen av skärmen är det Game Over. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 15 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR>Stöd för onlinespel med flera spelare: Ja (2 spelare)<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2013 BoobyTrap.,Ltd. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Online.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_13.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_14.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_15.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_16.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_17.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
