<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00269_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>7152288</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Blue, Yellow, Red, Green, Orange, Purple, Black and White drops!<BR>Spin drops to move them! Mix diferent color drops!<BR>Place 4 drops of the same color together in a square disposition!<BR>When the same color drop are forming a square the FREEZE command will make them frozen blocks ready to disapear!<BR>! But beware frozen drops can not be moved and they take time to disapear, so watch out! Also beware of using  the frozen command if there are no same color squares!<BR><BR>As drops are erased the time it takes for a new one to appear decreases!<BR><BR>Will you be able to get a really high score? <BR><BR>Package size: 6985 KB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/Spanish/Japanese<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Gotas Azules, Amarillas, Rojas, Verdes, Naranjas, Moradas, Negras y Blancas!<BR>Gira las gotas para moverlas! combina gotas de distintos colores!<BR>Junta 4 gotas del mismo color en forma de cuadrado!<BR>Cuando se forme un cuadrado de gotas del mismo color el comando de Congelar las congelara para luego hacerlas desaparecer!<BR>Pero cuidado las gotas congeladas no se pueden mover y toman tiempo en desaparecer! También hay que tener precaución en no usar el comando de congelar cuando no hay cuadrados del mismo color!<BR><BR>Mientras mas gotas desaparezcas mas rápido aparecerán las siguientes!<BR><BR>Seras capaz de obtener una alta puntuación! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 6985 KB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Español/Japonés<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>青、黄色、赤、緑、オレンジ色、紫、黒、白！色んな色の雫（ドロップ）！<BR>ドロップを回転！ドロップをミックスかアンミックスか！<BR>四角の形に４つのドロップを集めて！<BR>四角形の集めたドロップは凍結コマンドで凍らせる！<BR>凍結したドロップは消える！<BR>けど！注意！凍結コマンドで凍ったドロップは確かに消えるが時間がかかるそれに凍ったドロップが動けません！あと同じ色の四角形が無い時に凍結コマンドを使うのは注意！<BR><BR>ドロップを消せば消すほど新しいドロップの出る時間が減る！<BR><BR>あなたには高い点数を取れるのかな？ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 6985 KB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/スペイン語/日本語<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2014 M. Alejandro Jiménez All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:Casual"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_11.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_12.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
