<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00184_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>2.00</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>10539232</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>An alien race known as Boops have decided to kidnap you and you are forced to play their addictive strategy game.  To beat their game you must become a master of the puzzle game Tetris otherwise you will go into combat with the Boops.  After each round you will become more powerful and you decide how to power up.  RPT can be played as a puzzle game, a role playing game, or even a mix of both, you decide how to play. <BR><BR>Package size: 11 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>© 2014 by Wesley and Deirdre Crick. All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Une race extraterrestre connue sous le nom Boops ont décidé de vous kidnapper et vous êtes forcé à jouer leur jeu de stratégie addictif. Pour battre leur jeu, vous devez devenir un maître du jeu de puzzle Tetris sinon vous allez aller au combat avec le Boops. Après chaque tour, vous deviendrez plus puissant et vous décider comment mettre en place. RPT peut être joué comme un jeu de puzzle, un jeu de rôle, ou encore un mélange des deux, vous décidez comment jouer. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 11 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>© 2014 by Wesley and Deirdre Crick. All rights reserved<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Puzzle"/><genre value="Games:RPG"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
