<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPQA00104_00">

  <appVersion>1.05</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.20</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>140920912</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="ja"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Grib dit sværd! Et nyt eventyr starter! Fra udviklerne af arkade-kampspillet “Chaos Code” – FK Digital præsenterer – Mononoke Slashdown En siderullende 2D-actionoplevelse, som bringer klassisk nonstop-hack &amp; slash til PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Spil som Kagemaru, og kæmp dig gennem mange monstre for at finde roden til den ondskab, der har gjort alle bevidstløse. <BR>Over 35 forskellige baner, og spillerne kan vælge mellem tre forskellige sværhedsgrader, som imødekommer både gamle og nye actionspillere. <BR><BR>Både grafikken og lyden er renderet i traditionel japansk stil. Grafikken er simpel, men detaljeret på alle banerne, og spillet er hurtigt og flydende. <BR><BR>Det begynder. Er du klar til at betræde ninjaens sti? <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 135 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - traditionelt<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Super Geil! Genussvoll! Ninja-ARPG!<BR>Grenzenlos an Monster und Gespenster anschlagen! <BR>Ein grandiose Aktion-Spiel von der Firma FK DIGITAL, wird auf PlayStation®Mobile präsentiert!<BR><BR>Einfach zu bedienen und leicht zu spielen für Hardcore-Spieler und die leichten Spieler! Der Unbesiegbarkeit zu genießen!  <BR><BR>Farbereiche Grafik in japanischer Stil und ihrer Weltanschauung anpassende Musik.<BR>Mit blitzschnelle Bewegung die Monster zerschlagen und am Ende jedes Kapitels wartet ein Boss-Monster auf die Spieler, die ihrer Spieltechnik zutrauen!<BR>Das Spiel besteht aus mehre Kapitel und hat einen mega-hochen Wiederspielwert.<BR>Benutzt die dienliche Ninja-Aufrüstungen und die prunkvolle Ninja-Techniken, die nach eigenem Freiwahl verstärkt werden. <BR><BR>Stift dein eigenes Nin-Dao auf die Grenze! <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 135 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Japanisch/Traditionelles Chinesisch<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_AU"><description><![CDATA[Unsheathe your sword! A new adventure begins! From the developers of arcade fighting game “Chaos Code” - FK Digital Presents – Mononoke Slashdown A 2D side-scrolling action experience which brings nonstop classic hack &amp; slash to PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Play as Kagemaru and slash through many monsters to find the origin of the evil that has rendered everyone unconscious. <BR>Over 35 different stages, players can select up to 3 different difficulties to choose from which caters to both old and new action game players. <BR><BR>The visuals and the audio are both rendered in a traditional Japanese style. Graphics contain a simple yet detailed appearance which shows in every stage played, and the gameplay is fast and fluid. <BR><BR>It begins. Are you ready to walk down the path of the ninja? <BR><BR>Package size: 135 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_CA"><description><![CDATA[Unsheathe your sword! A new adventure begins! From the developers of arcade fighting game “Chaos Code” - FK Digital Presents – Mononoke Slashdown A 2D side-scrolling action experience which brings nonstop classic hack &amp; slash to PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Play as Kagemaru and slash through many monsters to find the origin of the evil that has rendered everyone unconscious. <BR>Over 35 different stages, players can select up to 3 different difficulties to choose from which caters to both old and new action game players. <BR><BR>The visuals and the audio are both rendered in a traditional Japanese style. Graphics contain a simple yet detailed appearance which shows in every stage played, and the gameplay is fast and fluid. <BR><BR>It begins. Are you ready to walk down the path of the ninja? <BR><BR>Package size: 135 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en_GB"><description><![CDATA[Unsheathe your sword! A new adventure begins! From the developers of arcade fighting game “Chaos Code” - FK Digital Presents – Mononoke Slashdown A 2D side-scrolling action experience which brings nonstop classic hack &amp; slash to PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Play as Kagemaru and slash through many monsters to find the origin of the evil that has rendered everyone unconscious. <BR>Over 35 different stages, players can select up to 3 different difficulties to choose from which caters to both old and new action game players. <BR><BR>The visuals and the audio are both rendered in a traditional Japanese style. Graphics contain a simple yet detailed appearance which shows in every stage played, and the gameplay is fast and fluid. <BR><BR>It begins. Are you ready to walk down the path of the ninja? <BR><BR>Package size: 135 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Unsheathe your sword! A new adventure begins! From the developers of arcade fighting game “Chaos Code” - FK Digital Presents – Mononoke Slashdown A 2D side-scrolling action experience which brings nonstop classic hack &amp; slash to PlayStation®Mobile! <BR><BR>Play as Kagemaru and slash through many monsters to find the origin of the evil that has rendered everyone unconscious. <BR>Over 35 different stages, players can select up to 3 different difficulties to choose from which caters to both old and new action game players. <BR><BR>The visuals and the audio are both rendered in a traditional Japanese style. Graphics contain a simple yet detailed appearance which shows in every stage played, and the gameplay is fast and fluid. <BR><BR>It begins. Are you ready to walk down the path of the ninja? <BR><BR>Package size: 135 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Japanese/Traditional Chinese<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Superb! Refrescante! Ninja drama de acción!<BR>Ilimitado decapitado Los fantasmas y duendes!<BR>FK DIGITAL Ofrecer acción grande、en PlayStation®Mobile Presione parámetros impresionante!<BR><BR>A pesar de que puede ser fácil para empezar disfrutando de un paseo en la sensación refrescante de un mil!<BR><BR>Lujosa y magnífica de arte japonés y Música en visión del mundo<BR>Derrotó a los demonios en figura relámpago, La cruzada de cada capítulo, por último, a la espera de los jugadores del Gran diablo.<BR><BR>Planteada por una amplia gama de barreras, Repetida disfrutar del juego.<BR>Utilice la paciencia, también hay Impresionante de Ninjutsu, Libre de seguir fortaleciendo.<BR>Sólo su propio límite de tolerancia! <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 135 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Japonés/Chino tradicional<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Vedä miekkasi tupesta! Uusi seikkailu alkaa! Arcademaisen Chaos Code -tappelupelin kehittäjä, FK Digital, esittelee sivuttain skrollaavan Mononoke Slashdown -2D-toimintapelin, mikä tarjoaa PlayStation®Mobile tauotonta hack 'n' slash -toimintaa! <BR><BR>Pelaa Kagemaruna ja silvo tiesi läpi useiden hirviöiden löytääksesi pahuuden lähteen, mikä on saanut kaikki vaipumaan tajuttomiksi. Tarjolla on yli 35 eri tasoa, ja pelaa voi valita jopa kolmesta eri vaikeustasosta, jotka sopivat sekä vanhoille että uusille toimintapelien pelaajille. <BR><BR>Grafiikat ja äänet ovat luotu perinteisellä japanilaisella tyylillä. Grafiikat ovat yksinkertaisia mutta tarkkoja, mikä voidaan todistaa jokaisella pelattavalla kentällä. <BR><BR>Niin se alkaa. Oletko valmiina kävelemään ninjan jalanjäljissä? <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 135 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Japani/Englanti/Englanti/Kiina - perinteinen<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr_CA"><description><![CDATA[Exclusivement extradorniaire! Jouez tout votre content ! Ninja scène de combat d’action ! <BR>Décapiter sans frein toutes sorte de démons et monstres !<BR>Une œuvre d’action grandiose offerte par FK DIGITAL est solennellement vous présentée sur PlayStation®Mobile!<BR>N’importe qui peut facilement débuter et jouir d’une sensation à cœur joie de Ikki Tousen(Une personne en valant mille)!<BR>Avec les beaux-arts et la musique magnifiques et splendides du style japonais pour faire ressortir la vue du monde.<BR>Réprimer les monstres avec une geste rapide comme l’éclair, et défaire tous les Roi-démons vous attendant à la fin de chaque chapitre.<BR>Un jeu composé d’un large éventail d'obstacles qui vous permet de le répéter sans cesse et d’en jouir.<BR>Développer à fond et perfectionner à l’extrêmité votre shinobido! <BR><BR>Taille du programme : 135 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<BR><BR>Information sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette d’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Exclusivement extradorniaire! Jouez tout votre content ! Ninja scène de combat d’action ! <BR>Décapiter sans frein toutes sorte de démons et monstres !<BR>Une œuvre d’action grandiose offerte par FK DIGITAL est solennellement vous présentée sur PlayStation®Mobile!<BR>N’importe qui peut facilement débuter et jouir d’une sensation à cœur joie de Ikki Tousen(Une personne en valant mille)!<BR>Avec les beaux-arts et la musique magnifiques et splendides du style japonais pour faire ressortir la vue du monde.<BR>Réprimer les monstres avec une geste rapide comme l’éclair, et défaire tous les Roi-démons vous attendant à la fin de chaque chapitre.<BR>Un jeu composé d’un large éventail d'obstacles qui vous permet de le répéter sans cesse et d’en jouir.<BR>Développer à fond et perfectionner à l’extrêmité votre shinobido! <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 135 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Japonais/Chinois traditionnel<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Unichissimo! Prontissimo! Gioco d’azione di Ninja!<BR>Innumerevoli mostri e diavoli da uccidere!<BR>Grande opera offerta da FK DIGITAL e presentata al PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Chiunque potrà godere facilmente della sensazione di calvalcare!<BR><BR>L’eccellente design d’arte e la musica splendida sublimano la visione del mondo.<BR><BR>Si può annientare con rapidità di un fulmine i mostri e confrontare i grandi Signori che aspettano alla fine dei capitoli.<BR><BR>Un gioco composto da vari passi, i quali si può ripetere come vuole.<BR>Se ne può rafforzare incessantemente senza limite tramite armi convenienti e Ninjutsu brillante.<BR>Approfitta pienamente del tuo shinobido! <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 135 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Giapponese/Cinese tradizionale<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[超絶！爽快！忍者アクション活劇！<BR>魑魅魍魎の群団を斬って斬って斬りまくる！<BR>台湾のFK DIGITALが贈るアクション大作、PlayStation®Mobileに凛々しく推参！<BR><BR>簡単操作で誰でも一騎当千の爽快感！<BR><BR>豪華絢爛な和風美術と音楽が世界観を盛り上げる！<BR>疾風迅雷の体捌きで魍魎共を薙ぎ倒し、各章に待ち受ける巨大なボスを討て！<BR> <BR>多種多様なステージ構成で、何度でも楽しめるゲーム性！<BR>便利な忍具やド派手な忍術で、自身を自由に強化！<BR>自分だけの忍道を極めよう！ <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 135 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/日本語/中国語(繁体字)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Grip sverdet ditt! Det er på tide med et nytt eventyr. Fra utviklerne av "Chaos Code", får vi FK Digitals nyeste siderullende 2D-spill "Monoke Slashdown". Her finner du nådeløs action i klassisk hugg-og-hakk-stil til PlayStation®Mobile.<BR><BR>spill som Lagearu og hugg deg gjennom en mengde monstre for å komme til kjernen av all ondskapen som har gjort alle bevisstløse.<BR>Med over 35 forskjellige nivåer og 3 forskjellige vanskelighetsgrader som er tilpasset både nye og gamle travere innen sjangeren.<BR><BR>Den visuelle og musikalske stilen er i tradisjonell japansk stil. Grafikken spillet bruker er av en enkel, men høyt detaljert art, noe som kan sees i hvert av nivåene. Alt dette i tillegg til en rask og flytende kampmekanikk.<BR><BR>Det hele starter her! Men er du klar til å starte på stien til å bli en nin <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 135 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Japansk/Engelsk/Engelsk/Kinesisk - Tradisjonell<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Haal je zwaard tevoorschijn! Een nieuw avontuur begint! Van de ontwikkelaars van het arcade vechtspel: Chaos Code - FK Digital Presents - Mononoke Slashdown. <BR>Een 2D side-scrolling actie ervaring die nonstop classic hack &amp; slash brengt naar de PlayStation®Mobile. <BR><BR>Speel als Kagemaru en slacht zo veel mogelijk monsters om de oorzaak van het kwaad te vinden dat iedereen bewusteloos heeft gemaakt. <BR><BR>Met meer dan 35 verschillende fases kunnen spelers uit 3 verschillende moeilijkheidsgraden kiezen. Je kan kiezen uit oude en nieuwe actie spelers.<BR><BR>Het beeld en geluid zijn beide gemaakt in een traditionele Japanse stijl. Graphics bevatten een simpele maar toch gedetailleerd verschijning. Dat kan je zien in elke fase die je speelt en de gameplay is snel en vloeiend. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 135 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Japans/Engels/Engels/Chinees - Traditioneel<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Dra ditt svärd! Ett nytt äventyr börjar! Från FK Digital – utvecklarna av arkadspelet "Chaos Code" – kommer Mononoke Slashdown. Ett sidorullande actionäventyr i 2D som ger dig en klassisk hugga och slå-upplevelse utan slut på PlayStation®Mobile!<BR><BR>Spela som Kagemaru och hugg dig genom många monster för att hitta ondskans ursprung, som har gjort alla medvetslösa.<BR>Över 35 olika banor där spelaren kan välja 3 olika svårighetsgrader som passar båda gamla och nya actionspelare.<BR><BR>Grafiken och ljudet renderas i traditionell japansk stil. Grafiken har ett enkelt men detaljerat utseende som syns i varje spelad bana och spelstilen är snabb och flytande.<BR><BR>Det börjar. Är du redo att ge dig ut på ninjans väg? <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 135 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Japanska/Engelska/Engelska/Kinesiska - traditionell<BR><BR>(C) F K Digital<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Action"/><genre value="Games:Arcade"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
