<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPPA00016_00">
 <appVersion>1.03</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>0.99</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>579927344</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[世界を探しても、こんな音楽ゲームは珍しい！ さあ、君もショパンと旅に出よう！<br><br>フレデリック ショパンが、突如、現代によみがえった！その秘密とは？<br>音楽の決闘を勝ち抜こう。ショパンの代表曲12曲を、ポップにアレンジ。<br>しかも、彼の稀代の冒険をハイクオリティ画面のコミックで楽しめる。<br>その背後には、邪悪な陰謀が ・・・ その正体を暴こう！<br><br>君は、音楽の世界を救えるのか？この「ショパンTHEゲーム」では：<br><br>フレデリック ショパンの代表曲12曲を、独自にリミックス。<br>世界中から選び抜いたカラフルな12のロケーション。しかもそこには、実はジョークが。君には、わかるかな？さらに、各ロケーションに探し物が。<br>1時間もの傑作アニメで、ショパンの奇妙な運命を紹介。<br>とにかく、面白い！<br><br>プレイヤーも、グランドピアノのマスターになれるかも！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:554 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)<br><br>著作権等:<br>(C) 2012 Forever Entertainment S. A.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Embark on the quirkiest musical journey that the world has to offer!<br><br>Reveal the secret of Frederic Chopin’s sudden return to life. Battle opponents in challenging musical<br>duels . Play through twelve catchy arrangements of Chopin's greatest classics and enjoy high quality<br>comic picturing his bizarre adventures. Learn the evil plot hidden behind all these events.<br><br>Do you have what it takes to save the world of music?<br><br>What you can expect:<br><br>* 12 catchy and original remixes of Frederic Chopin’s compositions<br>* 12 colorful locations from around the world full of subtle jokes and Easter eggs<br>* An hour of outstanding animated comic picturing the story of Frederic’s bizarre destiny<br>* Tons of great fun<br><br>You too can become master of the grand piano!<br><br>Package size: 554 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>(C) 2012 Forever Entertainment S. A.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Embarque-toi pour un voyage musical complètement fou autour du monde!<br><br>Découvre un plan diabolique derrière retour de Frédéric Chopin<br>dans le monde des vivants. Gagne avec tous les ennemis rencontrés dans les duesl de musique!<br>Joue  12 arrangements accrocheurs de plus grandes œuvres de Chopin et suis les aventures de<br>Frédéric regardant une bande dessinée comique et unique. Découvre les motifs du méchant<br>derrière cette aventure.<br><br>As-tu la force et la capacité pour sauver la musique du monde?<br><br>Qu'est-ce que tu peux attendre:<br><br>* 12 pièces à la base de compositions de Frederick Chopin<br>* 12 emplacements fabuleusement colorés dans le monde entier<br>* Une bande dessinée animée d’une heure pleine d’aventures non conventionnelles de Frederick<br>* Des tons d’ humour à faire mourir de rire<br><br>Toi aussi, tu peux devenir un maître du piano!<br><br>Taille du paquet: 554 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>(C) 2012 Forever Entertainment S. A.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Parti per un viaggio musicale completamente pazzo intorno al mondo!<br><br>Scopri un piano diabolico dietro il ritorno di Frederic Chopin<br>nel mondo dei vivi. Sconfiggi tutti i nemici incontrati nei duelli di musica!<br>Gioca 12 arrangiamenti attraenti di più grandi opere di Chopin e segui avventure di <br>Federico guardando un fumetto animato unico. Scopri i motivi del cattivo<br>dietro questa avventura.<br><br>Hai la forza e la possibilità di salvare la musica del mondo?<br><br>Che cosa ci si può aspettare:<br><br>* 12 pezzi attraenti basati sulle composizioni musicali di FedericoChopin<br>* 12 posti favolosamente colorati in tutto il mondo<br>* Un fumetto  animato di un’ora piena di avventure non convenzionali di Federico<br>* Tonnellate di  umorismo a far morire da ridere<br><br>Anche tu  diventa  un maestro del pianoforte!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 554 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<br><br>(C) 2012 Forever Entertainment S. A.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¡Inicia un alocado viaje musical alrededor del mundo!<br><br>Descubre el diabólico plan oculta tras el regreso de Federico Chopin al mundo de los vivos. ¡Vence a todos los contrincantes en duelos musicales!<br>Toca 12 variaciones de los temas más impresionantes de Chopin y sigue las aventuras de Federico disfrutando de un comic animado. Descubre los motivos del malvado creador de esta aventura. <br><br>¿Tienes suficientes fuerzas y talento para salvar la música del mundo?<br><br>Puedes esperarte: <br><br>* 12 absorbentes variaciones de composiciones de Federico Chopin<br>* 12 pintorescas localizaciones dispersas en todo el mundo<br>* Comic animado, con una hora de duración, que muestra las originales aventuras de Federico<br>* Melodías de humor y risas<br><br>¡Tú también puedes ser un maestro del piano!<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 554 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<br><br>(C) 2012 Forever Entertainment S. A.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Jetzt kannst du eine total verrückte Musikreise rund um die Welt antreten!<br><br>Du entdeckst den teuflischen Plan, der mit der Rückkehr von Fryderyk Chopin in die Welt<br>der Lebenden verbunden ist. Du kannst allen getroffenen Gegner in den musischen Duellen<br>Besiegen!<br>Jetzt kannst du 12 eingängigen Arrangements von den prächtigsten Werken von Fryderyk<br>Chopin spiele und die Abenteuer von Fryderyk Chopin in dem einmaligen Zeichentrickcomic<br>befolgen. Entdecke die Motive des Misstäters, der hinter dieser Abenteuer steht.<br><br>Bist du ausreichend stark und begabt um die Weltmusik zu retten?<br><br>Was sollst du erwarten:<br><br>* 12 engagierenden musischen Werken auf Basis der Kompositionen von Fryderyk Chopin.<br>* 12 außerordentlich bunten Lokalisierungen, die weltweit angeordnet sind.<br>* eine Stunde dauernde Zeichentrickcomic voll von den untypischen Abenteuer von Fryderyk<br>Chopin<br>* Voll von Humor, du wirst dich vor Lachen kugeln.<br><br>Sei ein Klaviermeister!<br><br>Paketgröße: 554 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)<br><br>(C) 2012 Forever Entertainment S. A.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Embark on the quirkiest musical journey that the world has to offer!<br><br>Reveal the secret of Frederic Chopin’s sudden return to life. Battle opponents in challenging musical<br>duels . Play through twelve catchy arrangements of Chopin's greatest classics and enjoy high quality<br>comic picturing his bizarre adventures. Learn the evil plot hidden behind all these events.<br><br>Do you have what it takes to save the world of music?<br><br>What you can expect:<br><br>* 12 catchy and original remixes of Frederic Chopin’s compositions<br>* 12 colorful locations from around the world full of subtle jokes and Easter eggs<br>* An hour of outstanding animated comic picturing the story of Frederic’s bizarre destiny<br>* Tons of great fun<br><br>You too can become master of the grand piano!<br><br>Package size: 554 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>(C) 2012 Forever Entertainment S. A.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Embarque-toi pour un voyage musical complètement fou autour du monde!<br><br>Découvre un plan diabolique derrière retour de Frédéric Chopin<br>dans le monde des vivants. Gagne avec tous les ennemis rencontrés dans les duesl de musique!<br>Joue  12 arrangements accrocheurs de plus grandes œuvres de Chopin et suis les aventures de<br>Frédéric regardant une bande dessinée comique et unique. Découvre les motifs du méchant<br>derrière cette aventure.<br><br>As-tu la force et la capacité pour sauver la musique du monde?<br><br>Qu'est-ce que tu peux attendre:<br><br>* 12 pièces à la base de compositions de Frederick Chopin<br>* 12 emplacements fabuleusement colorés dans le monde entier<br>* Une bande dessinée animée d’une heure pleine d’aventures non conventionnelles de Frederick<br>* Des tons d’ humour à faire mourir de rire<br><br>Toi aussi, tu peux devenir un maître du piano!<br><br>Taille du programme: 554 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>(C) 2012 Forever Entertainment S. A.<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:MusicRhythm"/>
  <genre value="Games:Arcade"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
