<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00178_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>1.21</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>11540656</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[Flap dine vinger til at flyve din drage og gøre kampen mod fjendtlige drager på tværs af en række forskellige miljøer. Kæmp i ruinerne af en gammel by. Flyv mellem træerne i en frodig jungle. Dodge de smeltede ildkugler, der regner ned fra en bryder vulkan. Undgå regn storme og lynnedslag midt skyerne. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 12 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[Flap Your Wings Sie Ihre Drachen fliegen und kämpfen gegen feindliche Drachen in einer Vielzahl von Umgebungen. Kampf in den Ruinen einer antiken Stadt. Fliege unter den Bäumen in einem üppigen Dschungel. Dodge die geschmolzene Feuerbälle, die von einem ausbrechenden Vulkan hinab regnen. Vermeiden Sie regen Stürme und Blitzschlag mitten in den Wolken. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 12 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[Flap your wings to fly your dragon and do battle against enemy dragons across a variety of environments. Fight within the ruins of an ancient city. Fly among the trees in a lush jungle. Dodge the molten fireballs that rain down from an erupting volcano. Avoid rain storms and lightning strikes amidst the clouds. <BR><BR>Package size: 12 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[Mueve tus alas para volar a tu dragón y luchar contra dragones enemigos a través de una variedad de entornos. Lucha en las ruinas de una antigua ciudad. Vuela entre los árboles en un exuberante selva. Esquivar las bolas de fuego de fundición que llueven desde un volcán en erupción. Evite las tormentas de lluvia y relámpagos en medio de las nubes. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 12 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[Läppä siivet lentää lohikäärme ja taistelemaan vihollisen lohikäärmeitä poikki eri ympäristöissä. Fight sisällä rauniot muinainen kaupunki. Lentää keskuudessa puiden rehevän viidakon. Dodge sula tulipalloja, että sataa alas purkautuvan tulivuoren. Vältä sade myrskyt ja salama iskee keskellä pilviä. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 12 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[Battre des ailes pour voler votre dragon et faire la bataille contre les dragons ennemis à travers une variété d'environnements. Lutte dans les ruines d'une ville antique. Voler entre les arbres dans une jungle luxuriante. Dodge les boules de feu en fusion qui pleuvent d'un volcan en éruption. Éviter les tempêtes de pluie et de la foudre dans les nuages​​. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 12 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[Lembo il tuo ali per volare il vostro drago e fare la battaglia contro i draghi nemici attraverso una varietà di ambienti. Lotta tra le rovine di un'antica città. Vola tra gli alberi in una giungla lussureggiante. Dodge le palle di fuoco fuso che piovono da un vulcano in eruzione. Evitare le tempeste di pioggia e fulmini tra le nuvole. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 12 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[あなたのドラゴンを飛行し、さまざまな環境全体で敵のドラゴンとの戦いを行うにはあなたの翼を羽ばたか。古代都市の遺跡内で戦う。緑豊かなジャングルの中で木々の間に飛ぶ。火山噴火から降り注ぐダッジ溶融火の玉。雲の中の雨嵐や落雷を避ける。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 12 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[Klaff dine vinger å fly dragen din og kjemp mot fiendtlige drager på tvers av en rekke miljøer. Kjemp i ruinene av en gammel by. Fly mellom trærne i en frodig jungel. Dodge de smeltede ildkuler som regnet ned fra en vulkan under utbrudd. Unngå regnstormer og lynnedslag blant skyene. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 12 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[Flap dine vinger til at flyve din drage og gøre kampen mod fjendtlige drager på tværs af en række forskellige miljøer. Kæmp i ruinerne af en gammel by. Flyv mellem træerne i en frodig jungle. Dodge de smeltede ildkugler, der regner ned fra en bryder vulkan. Undgå regn storme og lynnedslag midt skyerne. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 12 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[Klapy skrzydła do lotu smoka i walki przeciwko smoki wroga całej różnych środowiskach. Walcz w ruinach starożytnego miasta. Latać między drzewami w bujnej dżungli. Dodge stopione ogniste kule, które spadają z wybuch wulkanu. Uniknąć deszczu i burze uderzeniu pioruna pośród chmur. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 12 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[Vifta med vingarna för att flyga din drake och slåss mot fientliga drakar över en mängd olika miljöer. Kämpa i ruinerna av en gammal stad. Fly bland träden i en frodig djungel. Dodge de smälta eldklot som regnar ner från en vulkan som får utbrott. Undvik regn stormar och blixtnedslag bland molnen. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 12 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright 2014 Michael Oliphant<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Arcade"/><genre value="Games:Family"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_12.png</ratingLogo><contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
