<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00010_00">
 <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>28662672</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[｢お腹が空いていると気分も最悪。ただひたすらハンバーガーにかぶりつきたい、タコスにかじりつきたい、って時があるよね。アフリカのサバンナでHungry Giraffeもおんなじ気持ち。<br><br>体長20フィート、体重1200キロのキリンは毎日生き延びるために大量の食物を食べないと。それなのに困った！おいしい葉っぱは全部食べられちゃった。でも空には沢山のスナックやフルーツ、ジャンクフードが次々と浮かんでいて、今にも届きそう！<br><br>Hungry Giraffeは世界一大きく世界一お腹を空かせた野生動物 。キリンの首を上にクネクネとうまく動かして、いちごやフライドポテト、サンドイッチ、もっとおいしいおやつなどをムシャムシャと食べさせよう。<br><br>でも気をつけて！空には危険もいっぱい。毒や金床、薬なんかも浮かんでいて、用心しないとキリンはまっ逆さまに地面へ…<br><br>Hungry Giraffeは史上最高傑作のキリンえさやりゲーム！プレイしないと損するよ！｣<br><br>コンテンツ容量:28 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)<br><br>著作権等:<br>Hungry Giraffe © 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[It sucks when you’re hungry. Sometimes you just want to bury your face into a burger, or tear into a taco. Out on the African savannah, a Hungry Giraffe feels your pain.<br><br>A 20 foot tall, 1200kg animal like the giraffe needs to chow down on tons of food each day, just to stay alive. But, oh no! All the tastiest leaves have been eaten, while up in the sky endless quantities of snacks, fruit and junk food hover just out of reach!<br><br>Hungry Giraffe features the world’s largest and hungriest even-toed ungulate. Through skilful steering of his neck, you can propel your half-starved giraffe on his twisty-turny upward journey, chomping on strawberries, fries, sandwiches and naughtier treats.<br><br>But beware! The skies are also strewn with hazards. Poison, Anvils and non-prescription Drugs also hover up there, ready to send unwary giraffes plummeting to earth.<br><br>Hungry Giraffe is by FAR the greatest giraffe-feeding game of all time! Dare you miss out?<br><br>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>Hungry Giraffe © 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[C'est terrible d'avoir faim. Parfois, on aimerait pouvoir mordre dans un gros sandwich, ou un panini bien chaud. Dans la savane africaine, il y a une girafe affamée, la Hungry Giraffe, qui connaît ça.<br><br>Avec ses 6 m pour 1,2 tonne, la girafe doit mâcher des tonnes de nourriture chaque jour. Mais, voilà que les feuilles les plus savoureuses ont été mangées, tandis que se balancent dans les branches tout un tas de délices inaccessibles !<br><br>Hungry Giraffe présente l’ongulé à sabot fendu le plus affamé du monde. En pilotant habilement son cou, vous amènerez votre girafe affamée vers les cimes pour avaler frises, frites, sandwichs et autres délicatesses.<br><br>Mais attention ! Le ciel est rempli de dangers. Du poison, des enclumes et des médicaments planent aussi dans les hauteurs, prêts à renvoyer au sol les girafes imprudentes.<br><br>Hungry Giraffe est le meilleur jeu de nourrissage de girafe de tous les temps ! Vous ne pouvez pas le manquer !<br><br>Taille du paquet: 28 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>Hungry Giraffe © 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[È terribile quando si ha fame. A volte hai proprio voglia di azzannare quel panino e inforcare quella spaghettata. Proprio come te, nella savana africana, una Hungry Giraffe prova il tuo stesso dolore.<br><br>Alta 6 metri e pesante 1.200 chili, la giraffa ha bisogno di mangiare un sacco di cibo ogni giorno per sopravvivere. Ma dannazione! Tutte le foglie più prelibate sono già state divorate mentre lassù in cielo una quantità di dolci, frutta e merendine fluttuano appena fuori portata!<br><br>Hungry Giraffe ha come protagonista il più grande e affamato ungulato con un numero di dita pari del mondo. Virando abilmente il suo collo, puoi proiettare la tua famelica giraffa in un viaggio ascensionale tra fragole, patatine fritte, panini e delizie ancora più unte.<br><br>Ma fa' attenzione! I cieli pullulano di pericoli. Veleno, incudini e medicine strambe sono sospese in aria, pronte a rispedire la tua giraffa giù a terra.<br><br>Hungry Giraffe è INDUBBIAMENTE il più grande gioco di tutti i tempi in cui devi sfamare una giraffa! Non puoi perderlo!<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 28 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<br><br>Hungry Giraffe © 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Tener hambre es un asco. A veces lo único que te apetece es meterte un bocadillo entre pecho y espalda. En Hungry Giraffe conocerás a alguien de la sabana africana que siente lo mismo.<br><br>Un animal de 6 metros y 1200 kg como la jirafa necesita comer muchísimo solo para mantenerse con vida. Pero alguien se ha comido las hojas más sabrosas y en el cielo flotan aperitivos, fruta y comida basura, justo donde no puedes alcanzarlos.<br><br>En Hungry Giraffe conocerás al rumiante más grande y hambriento del mundo. Utiliza el largo cuello de la jirafa para desplazarte y comer fresas, patatas fritas, bocadillos y cosas peores.<br><br>¡Cuidado! También hay objetos peligrosos como yunques y medicinas que te enviarán de nuevo a la tierra.<br><br>Hungry Giraffe es con diferencia el mejor juego de alimentación de jirafas de todos los tiempos. ¿Te lo vas a perder?<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 28 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<br><br>Hungry Giraffe © 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Hunger ist Mist: Manchmal will man einfach mal in einen Burger beißen oder ein paar Pommes probieren. Die hungrige Giraffe in der afrikanischen Savanne versteht dich nur allzu gut.<br><br>Ein sechs Meter großes und 1.200 kg schweres Tier wie die Giraffe muss jeden Tag Unmengen von Nahrung zu sich nehmen. Leider sind alle leckeren Blätter schon weggefressen, doch am Himmel hängen massig Snacks, Obst und Junkfood!<br><br>In Hungry Giraffe triffst du auf den größten und hungrigsten Paarhufer der Welt. Steuere geschickt den Hals der Giraffe, um das halb verhungerte Tier mit allerlei Wendungen nach oben zu transportieren, wo es Erdbeeren, Pommes, Sandwiches und weitere Leckereien gibt.<br><br>Aber Vorsicht – am Himmel wimmelt es nur so von Gefahren! Gift, Ambosse und Medikamente lassen leichtsinnige Giraffen schnell wieder auf die Erde plumpsen.<br><br>Hungry Giraffe ist das BESTE Giraffenfütterungsspiel aller Zeiten! Probier es aus!<br><br>Paketgröße: 28 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)<br><br>Hungry Giraffe © 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[It sucks when you’re hungry. Sometimes you just want to bury your face into a burger, or tear into a taco. Out on the African savannah, a Hungry Giraffe feels your pain.<br><br>A 20 foot tall, 1200kg animal like the giraffe needs to chow down on tons of food each day, just to stay alive. But, oh no! All the tastiest leaves have been eaten, while up in the sky endless quantities of snacks, fruit and junk food hover just out of reach!<br><br>Hungry Giraffe features the world’s largest and hungriest even-toed ungulate. Through skilful steering of his neck, you can propel your half-starved giraffe on his twisty-turny upward journey, chomping on strawberries, fries, sandwiches and naughtier treats.<br><br>But beware! The skies are also strewn with hazards. Poison, Anvils and non-prescription Drugs also hover up there, ready to send unwary giraffes plummeting to earth.<br><br>Hungry Giraffe is by FAR the greatest giraffe-feeding game of all time! Dare you miss out?<br><br>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>Hungry Giraffe © 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[C'est terrible d'avoir faim. Parfois, on aimerait pouvoir mordre dans un gros sandwich, ou un panini bien chaud. Dans la savane africaine, il y a une girafe affamée, la Hungry Giraffe, qui connaît ça.<br><br>Avec ses 6 m pour 1,2 tonne, la girafe doit mâcher des tonnes de nourriture chaque jour. Mais, voilà que les feuilles les plus savoureuses ont été mangées, tandis que se balancent dans les branches tout un tas de délices inaccessibles !<br><br>Hungry Giraffe présente l’ongulé à sabot fendu le plus affamé du monde. En pilotant habilement son cou, vous amènerez votre girafe affamée vers les cimes pour avaler frises, frites, sandwichs et autres délicatesses.<br><br>Mais attention ! Le ciel est rempli de dangers. Du poison, des enclumes et des médicaments planent aussi dans les hauteurs, prêts à renvoyer au sol les girafes imprudentes.<br><br>Hungry Giraffe est le meilleur jeu de nourrissage de girafe de tous les temps ! Vous ne pouvez pas le manquer !<br><br>Taille du programme: 28 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>Hungry Giraffe © 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Action"/>
  <genre value="Games:Casual"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
