<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00011_00">
 <appVersion>1.01</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>53850912</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en_GB">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[緊急事態！緊急事態！OMG-Zombies ！レッドフィールドシティが爆発的なゾンビの大量発生に襲われた。おもしろいから理由はどうでもいいんだけど、ゾンビたちは撃たれるとまさに文字通り爆発しゾンビ仲間達に血しぶきを浴びせかける。たった一発の銃弾がチェーンリアクションを引き起こしゾンビたちの内臓が飛び散る！<br><br>どういった経緯でそうなったかは分からないが、ゾンビ大量発生地に到着前に、チーム内でただ一人だけ生き残った君はたった一人で何千ものゾンビに立ち向かわなければならない。<br><br>• 各レベルステージで大量のゾンビを倒しまくろう。レベル数はなんと80以上<br>• それぞれ特徴を持つゾンビの種類は５種類<br>• 沢山のアイテム：70のアップグレード購入可能。獲得できるメダル数324枚<br>• ステータストラッキング、チュートリアル、３種類のエンディング<br><br>コンテンツ容量:52 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br><br>対応言語:<br>英語(アメリカ)<br><br>著作権等:<br>OMG-Zombies! c 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Alert! Alert! OMG-Zombies! The City of Redfield has been hit by an outbreak of exploding zombies! For cool and unimportant reasons these suckers literally explode when shot, showering their zombie brethren with gore and causing chain reactions of showering zombie gibs with just a single bullet!<br><br>For reasons that aren’t important right now, all but one of your team is killed before arriving at the outbreak’s epicentre, leaving YOU to deal with thousands of zombies ALONE.<br><br>• Destroy hordes of zombies across over 80 branching levels<br>• Five zombie classes, each with lethal effects to exploit<br>• Lots of stuff: 70 upgrades to buy and 324 medals to win<br>• Stat tracking, Tutorials and 3 end sequences<br><br>Package size: 52 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>OMG-Zombies! c 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Oh mon Dieu... des zombies ! Dans OMG-Z!, la ville de Redfield est envahie par des hordes de zombies. Pour des raisons scientifiques obscures, une seule balle suffit à tuer ces bons à rien, qui explosent en causant des réactions en chaîne et en recouvrant leurs congénères de sang et de morceaux de chair.<br><br>Pour des raisons qui n’ont aucune importance pour le moment, tous les membres de ton équipe sont tués avant d’arriver sur place, te laissant SEUL face à des milliers de zombies.<br><br>• Détruis des hordes de zombies sur plus de 80 niveaux<br>• 5 classes de zombies possédant chacune des effets dévastateurs à exploiter<br>• 70 améliorations à acheter et 324 médailles à gagner<br>• Suivi des stats, initiations et 3 séquences finales<br><br>Taille du paquet: 52 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>OMG-Zombies! c 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Allerta! Allerta! OMG-Z! La città di Redfield è stata colpita da un'epidemia di zombie esplosivi! Per qualche motivo che non ci interessa, questi scemotti esplodono quando gli spari, inzuppando di sangue i loro fratelli zombie e causando reazioni a catena di budella zombie con un solo proiettile!<br><br>Ma tutti i membri della tua squadra vengono eliminati prima di giungere a destinazione, lasciando TE a gestire migliaia di zombie DA SOLO.<br><br>• Distruggi orde di zombie in 80 livelli ramificati<br>• Cinque classi di zombie con effetti letali da sfruttare<br>• Un sacco di roba: 70 potenziamenti da comprare e 324 medaglie da vincere<br>• Statistiche, tutorial e 3 sequenze finali<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 52 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Inglese(Stati Uniti)<br><br>OMG-Zombies! c 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[¡Alerta! ¡Alerta! OMG-Z! ¡La ciudad de Redfield está siendo atacada por zombis explosivos! Por motivos que ahora no importan, esos bichos explotan si les disparas, salpican de sangre a los demás zombis y causan reacciones en cadena de zombis que también explotan. ¡Y todo con una sola bala!<br><br>Por motivos que no vienen al caso, los demás miembros de tu equipo mueren antes de llegar al destino. ¡Deberás enfrentarte a miles de zombis sin ayuda!<br><br>• Acaba con hordas de zombis en más de 80 niveles ramificados<br>• Cinco clases de zombis con efectos letales que debes aprovechar<br>• Montones de extras: 70 mejoras para comprar y 324 medallas que puedes ganar<br>• Estadísticas, tutoriales y tres escenas finales<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 52 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Inglés(Estados Unidos)<br><br>OMG-Zombies! c 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Alarm! Alarm! OMG-Z! Die Stadt Redfield ist von explodierenden Zombies angegriffen worden! Diese Typen gehen in die Luft, wenn man auf sie schießt, und ihre Kollegen reißen sie gleich mit in die ewigen Jagdgründe. Eine Kugel reicht, um eine verheerende Kettenreaktion auszulösen!<br><br>Leider wird dein gesamtes Team außer dir vor dem Eintreffen getötet und jetzt hast DU ALLEIN es mit Tausenden von Zombies zu tun!<br><br>• Vernichte Horden von Zombies in mehr als 80 verzweigten Levels<br>• Fünf Zombietypen mit jeweils anderen tödlichen Effekten<br>• Hole dir 70 Upgrades und gewinne 324 Medaillen<br>• Stat-Speicherung, Tutorials und drei Endsequenzen<br><br>Paketgröße: 52 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Englisch(USA)<br><br>OMG-Zombies! c 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Alert! Alert! OMG-Zombies! The City of Redfield has been hit by an outbreak of exploding zombies! For cool and unimportant reasons these suckers literally explode when shot, showering their zombie brethren with gore and causing chain reactions of showering zombie gibs with just a single bullet!<br><br>For reasons that aren’t important right now, all but one of your team is killed before arriving at the outbreak’s epicentre, leaving YOU to deal with thousands of zombies ALONE.<br><br>• Destroy hordes of zombies across over 80 branching levels<br>• Five zombie classes, each with lethal effects to exploit<br>• Lots of stuff: 70 upgrades to buy and 324 medals to win<br>• Stat tracking, Tutorials and 3 end sequences<br><br>Package size: 52 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br><br>Supported languages:<br>English(United States)<br><br>OMG-Zombies! c 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Oh mon Dieu... des zombies ! Dans OMG-Z!, la ville de Redfield est envahie par des hordes de zombies. Pour des raisons scientifiques obscures, une seule balle suffit à tuer ces bons à rien, qui explosent en causant des réactions en chaîne et en recouvrant leurs congénères de sang et de morceaux de chair.<br><br>Pour des raisons qui n’ont aucune importance pour le moment, tous les membres de ton équipe sont tués avant d’arriver sur place, te laissant SEUL face à des milliers de zombies.<br><br>• Détruis des hordes de zombies sur plus de 80 niveaux<br>• 5 classes de zombies possédant chacune des effets dévastateurs à exploiter<br>• 70 améliorations à acheter et 324 médailles à gagner<br>• Suivi des stats, initiations et 3 séquences finales<br><br>Taille du programme: 52 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Anglais(États-Unis)<br><br>OMG-Zombies! c 2012 Laughing Jackal LTD<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Shooter"/>
  <genre value="Games:Puzzle"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_13.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_16.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_16.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_8.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_9.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_10.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
