<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<psmMeta npTitleId="NPOA00007_00">
 <appVersion>1.02</appVersion>
 <runtimeVersion>1.00</runtimeVersion>
 <packageSize>29129120</packageSize>
 <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en">
  <localizedMeta locale="ja">
   <description><![CDATA[戦争で捕虜になるってのは最悪だ。だがごくまれに、脱走に気づかないバカな敵がいる。でも武器もなしにどうやって追っ手を回避するって？ 不可能だと思うか？ いやいや、敵がバカすぎる場合は別だ！ 飛び交う銃弾をぬって進み、敵の同士討ちを誘え。敵を利用して軍隊の中を駆け抜けろ。ヘリ、戦車、砲台、お構いなしだ。さあ、復讐の時間が始まるぞ！<br><br>コンテンツ容量:28 MB<br><br>プレイ人数:1人<br><br>対応機能:<br> - タッチスクリーン<br> - コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<br> - モーションセンサー<br><br>対応言語:<br>ドイツ語/英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)/スペイン語/フランス語/イタリア語<br><br>著作権等:<br>Copyright (C) 2012 PomPom Software Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en">
   <description><![CDATA[Being a prisoner of war sucks. But sometimes, just sometimes, your enemy is just stupid enough to let you escape. Armed to the teeth with no weapons whatsoever, how will you evade your captors? Impossible maybe? Not when your enemy is as dimwitted as this mob! Dodge and weave the incoming barrage. Draw their fire causing them to destroy themselves. Help them work their way through their whole army. Helicopters. Tanks. Turrets. All perfectly suited to blowing each other up. Revenge has never been sweeter!<br><br>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 PomPom Software Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr">
   <description><![CDATA[Être prisonnier de guerre n’a rien de drôle. Mais parfois, votre ennemi est assez stupide pour vous laisser vous échapper. Sans aucune arme pour vous défendre, comment échapperez-vous à vos ravisseurs armés jusqu’aux dents ? Cela vous paraît impossible ? Pas quand votre ennemi est attardé comme celui-ci ! Préparez-vous à vous faufiler à travers la pluie de balle de vos adversaires. Arrangez-vous pour qu'ils se détruisent les uns les autres. Frayez-vous un chemin à travers leur armée toute entière.<br><br>Taille du paquet: 28 Mo – Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<br><br>Informations sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette à l’écran<br> - Détecteur de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 PomPom Software Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="it">
   <description><![CDATA[Essere un prigioniero di guerra è estremamente faticoso. Tuttavia, a volte, ma solo a volte, il nemico è abbastanza stupido da lasciarti scappare. Armato di tanta buona volontà ma senza alcun tipo di arma, come riuscirai a sfuggire al controllo dei tuoi carcerieri e a evadere? È forse impossibile? No, se il tuo nemico è scemo come questo branco di caproni! Evadi e sfuggi allo sbarramento del nemico. Fai in modo che il loro stesso fuoco li distrugga e che indietreggino con tutto il loro esercito.<br><br>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 28 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<br><br>Informazioni sulla compatibilità: <br>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1giocatore/i<br><br>Interfacce/sensori supportati<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / Controller su schermo<br> - Sensore di movimento<br><br>Lingue supportate:<br>Tedesco/Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)/Spagnolo/Francese/Italiano<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 PomPom Software Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="es">
   <description><![CDATA[Ser prisionero de guerra no mola nada. Pero a veces, tu enemigo es tan estúpido como para dejarte escapar. Aunque, sin armas de ningún tipo, ¿cómo puedes escapar de tus captores? ¿Te parece imposible? ¡Para nada! Sobre todo si tu enemigo es tan tonto como esta banda. Esquiva y burla el bombardeo enemigo. Desvía su fuego y que acabe con ellos mismos. Haz que se vayan abriendo paso a través de todo su propio ejército.<br><br>Tamaño del paquete: 28 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación<br><br>Información de compatibilidad: <br>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1jugador(es)<br><br>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<br> - Pantalla táctil<br> - Mando / mando en pantalla<br> - Sensor de movimiento<br><br>Idiomas compatibles:<br>Alemán/Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)/Español/Francés/Italiano<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 PomPom Software Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="de">
   <description><![CDATA[Als Kriegsgefangener fühlt man sich ausgelaugt. Aber manchmal ist der Feind dumm genug, dich fliehen zu lassen. Er ist bis an die Zähne bewaffnet, wie willst du deinen Gefangenenwärtern ohne Waffen entkommen? Vielleicht unmöglich? Nicht, wenn der Feind so beschränkt ist wie dieser Mob! Weiche dem ankommenden Sperrfeuer aus. Ziehe das Feuer so, dass sie sich selbst zerstören. Hilf ihnen dabei, ihren Weg durch ihre ganze Armee zu machen.<br><br>Paketgröße: 28 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich<br><br>Kompatibilitätsinformationen: <br>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1Spieler<br><br>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<br> - Bewegungssensor<br><br>Unterstützte Sprachen:<br>Deutsch/Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)/Spanisch/Französisch/Italienisch<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 PomPom Software Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="en_GB">
   <description><![CDATA[Being a prisoner of war sucks. But sometimes, just sometimes, your enemy is just stupid enough to let you escape. Armed to the teeth with no weapons whatsoever, how will you evade your captors? Impossible maybe? Not when your enemy is as dimwitted as this mob! Dodge and weave the incoming barrage. Draw their fire causing them to destroy themselves. Help them work their way through their whole army. Helicopters. Tanks. Turrets. All perfectly suited to blowing each other up. Revenge has never been sweeter!<br><br>Package size: 28 MB - More storage space required for install<br><br>Compatibility information: <br>Number of players for local play: 1Player(S)<br><br>Supported interfaces/sensors<br> - Touchscreen<br> - Controller / On-screen controller<br> - Motion sensor<br><br>Supported languages:<br>German/English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)/Spanish/French/Italian<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 PomPom Software Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
  <localizedMeta locale="fr_CA">
   <description><![CDATA[Être prisonnier de guerre n’a rien de drôle. Mais parfois, votre ennemi est assez stupide pour vous laisser vous échapper. Sans aucune arme pour vous défendre, comment échapperez-vous à vos ravisseurs armés jusqu’aux dents ? Cela vous paraît impossible ? Pas quand votre ennemi est attardé comme celui-ci ! Préparez-vous à vous faufiler à travers la pluie de balle de vos adversaires. Arrangez-vous pour qu'ils se détruisent les uns les autres. Frayez-vous un chemin à travers leur armée toute entière.<br><br>Taille du programme: 28 Mo - Plus d’espace de stockage est requis pour l’installation<br><br>Information sur la compatibilité: <br>Nombre de joueurs pour le jeu local : 1joueur(s)<br><br>Interfaces / capteurs compatibles<br> - Écran tactile<br> - Manette / Manette d’écran<br> - Détection de mouvements<br><br>Langues prises en charge:<br>Allemand/Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)/Espagnol/Français/Italien<br><br>Copyright (C) 2012 PomPom Software Ltd<br><br>]]></description>
  </localizedMeta>
 </localizedMetadataList>
 <genreList>
  <genre value="Games:Action"/>
  <genre value="Games:Arcade"/>
 </genreList>
 <ratingList default="SELF">
  <rating type="ESRB">
   <ratingLogo>ESRB_10.png</ratingLogo>
  </rating>
  <rating type="PEGIEX">
   <ratingLogo>PEGIEX_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>PEGIEX_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
  <rating type="SELF">
   <ratingLogo>SELF_7.png</ratingLogo>
   <contentDescriptor>SELF_Violence.png</contentDescriptor>
  </rating>
 </ratingList>
 <screenShotList>
  <screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot>
  <screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot>
 </screenShotList>
</psmMeta>
