<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<psmMeta npTitleId="NPNA00237_00">

  <appVersion>1.00</appVersion>
  <runtimeVersion>4.03</runtimeVersion>
  <packageSize>128920448</packageSize>
  <localizedMetadataList default_locale="en"><localizedMeta locale="da"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INDHOLD ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHEDER.<BR><BR>Pulling USA er en lastbil og traktor trække simulation spil i fuld 3D-miljø. Med over 30 lastbiler og traktorer og 10 køretøjsklasser, den trækker aldrig ender. Opgrader din bils motor, kompressor / turbolader, systemet brændstof og mere i garagen. Juster vægte og dæktryk til at rumme forskellige baneforhold. Træk på county fair i forskellige dag og nat miljøer eller i den indendørs grand arena. Arbejd din vej op gennem de forskellige konkurrencer tjene penge og point for at vinde. Styr gashåndtaget og kobling perfekt for at få din arena rystemaskine ned sporet. Byg din RPM, motor temp, boost og tage ud ned på sporet med realistiske snavs og røg effekter. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 123 MB - Mere opvaringsplads påkrævet til installation.<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation<BR>Antal spillere til lokalt spil: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Understøttede grænseflader/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskærm<BR>- Controller / skærmcontroller<BR>- Bevægelsessensor<BR><BR>Understøgte sprog:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="de"><description><![CDATA[DIESER INHALT IST NICHT MIT Android™-GERÄTEN KOMPATIBEL.<BR><BR>Pulling USA ist ein LKW und Traktor Pulling Simulation, in einer 3D Umgebung. Mit über 30 Lastwagen und Traktoren sowie 10 Fahrzeugklassen, das Ziehen nie endet. Upgrade-Motor, Kompressor / Turbolader Kraftstoffsystem Ihres Fahrzeugs und in der Garage. Stellen Sie die Gewichte und Reifendruck, den Bereich der Streckenbedingungen anzupassen. Ziehen Sie auf dem Jahrmarkt in unterschiedliche Tag und Nacht-Umgebungen oder in der Innen großen Arena. Arbeiten Sie sich durch die verschiedenen Wettbewerbe, Geld zu verdienen und die Punkte für den Gewinn. Steuern Sie die Züge und perfekt auf Ihre Arena Schüttelmaschine unten die Spur zu kommen. Erstellen Sie Ihre RPM, Motortemperatur , Ladedruck und nehmen Sie auf der Bahn mit realistischen Schmutz und Raucheffekte. <BR><BR>Paketgröße: 123 MB - Mehr Speicherplatz für die Installation erforderlich <BR><BR>Kompatibilitätsinformationen:<BR>Anzahl von Spielern für lokales Spiel: 1 Spieler<BR><BR>Unterstützte Schnittstellen/Sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller/Bildschirm-Controller<BR>- Bewegungssensor<BR><BR>Unterstützte Sprachen:<BR>Englisch(USA)/Englisch(Großbritannien)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="en"><description><![CDATA[THIS CONTENT IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH Android™ DEVICES.<BR><BR>Pulling USA is a truck and tractor pulling simulation game in a full 3D environment. With over 30 trucks and tractors and 10 vehicle classes, the pulling never ends. Upgrade your vehicle's engine, supercharger/turbocharger, fuel system and more at the garage. Adjust the weights and tire pressure to accommodate the range of track conditions. Pull at the county fair in different day and night environments or in the indoor grand arena. Work your way up through the different competitions earning money and points for winning. Control the throttle and clutch perfectly to get your arena shaking machine down the track. Build your RPM, engine temp, boost and take off down the track with realistic dirt and smoke effects. <BR><BR>Package size: 123 MB - More storage space required for install<BR><BR>Compatibility information:<BR>Number of players for local play: 1 Player<BR><BR>Supported interfaces/sensors<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / On-screen controller<BR>- Motion sensor<BR><BR>Supported languages:<BR>English(United States)/English(United Kingdom)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="es"><description><![CDATA[ESTE CONTENIDO NO ES COMPATIBLE CON DISPOSITIVOS Android™.<BR><BR>Pulling USA es un camión y tractor tirando juego de simulación en un entorno completamente en 3D. Con más de 30 camiones y tractores y 10 clases de vehículos, el tirar nunca termina. Actualiza motor, turbocompresor, sistema de combustible de su vehículo supercargador / y más en el garaje. Ajuste el peso y la presión de los neumáticos para adaptarse a la variedad de condiciones de la pista. Tire a la feria del condado en diferentes entornos diurnos y nocturnos o en el gran estadio cubierto. Su forma de trabajo a través de las diferentes competiciones que ganan dinero y puntos para ganar. Controlar el acelerador y embrague perfectamente para obtener su máquina arena temblando por la pista. Construye tu RPM, temperatura del motor, impulso y despegar por la pista de tierra y humo realistas. <BR><BR>Tamaño del paquete: 123 MB. Se requiere más espacio de almacenamiento para la instalación <BR><BR>Información de compatibilidad:<BR>Número de jugadores para juego local: 1 jugador<BR><BR>Interfaces/sensores compatibles<BR>- Pantalla táctil<BR>- Mando / mando en pantalla<BR>- Sensor de movimiento<BR><BR>Idiomas compatibles:<BR>Inglés(Estados Unidos)/Inglés(Reino Unido)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fi"><description><![CDATA[TÄTÄ SISÄLTÖÄ EI VOI KÄYTTÄÄ Android™-LAITTEILLA.<BR><BR>Pulling USA on kuorma-auton ja traktorin vetämällä simulointi peli kokonaan 3D-ympäristössä. Yli 30 kuorma-traktorit ja 10 ajoneuvoluokkien, vetämällä ei lopu koskaan. Päivitä autosi moottoria, ahdin / turboahdin, polttoainejärjestelmä ja enemmän autotalli. Säädä painot ja rengaspaineet mahtuu erilaisia rataolosuhteiden. Vedä läänin messuilla eri päivä ja yö ympäristöjen tai sisätiloissa grand areenalla. Raivaa tiesi läpi eri kilpailujen ansaita rahaa ja pisteitä voittaa. Kaasusäätimellä ja kytkin täydellisesti saat areena ravistinlaitteessa alas radan. Rakenna RPM, moottorin lämpötila, vauhtia ja riisua alas radan realistinen lian ja savun vaikutuksia. <BR><BR>Pakkauksen koko: 123 Mt - Asennukseen vaaditaan enemmän muistia<BR><BR>Yhteensopivuus:<BR>Paikallisen pelin pelaajien lukumäärä: 1  Pelaaja<BR><BR>Tuetut käyttöliittymät/ohjaimet<BR>- Kosketusnäyttö<BR>- Ohjain / Näytöllä näkyvä ohjain<BR>- Liikeohjain<BR><BR>Tuetut kielet:<BR>Englanti/Englanti<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="fr"><description><![CDATA[CE CONTENU N'EST PAS COMPATIBLE AVEC LES PÉRIPHÉRIQUES Android™.<BR><BR>Pulling USA est un camion et un tracteur tirant jeu de simulation dans un environnement 3D. Avec plus de 30 camions et de tracteurs et 10 classes de véhicules, le tirage ne se termine jamais. Mise à niveau moteur, compresseur / turbocompresseur, système de carburant de votre véhicule et plus au garage. Réglez le poids et la pression des pneus pour accueillir la gamme de conditions de piste. Tirez à la foire du comté dans différents environnements de jour et de nuit ou dans la grande salle omnisports. Travailler votre chemin à travers les différentes compétitions gagner de l'argent et des points pour gagner. Contrôler l'accélérateur et d'embrayage parfaitement à obtenir votre arène secouant la machine sur la piste. <BR><BR>Taille du paquet : 123 Mo - Nécessite un plus grand espace de stockage pour l’installation<BR><BR>Informations sur la compatibilité :<BR>Nombre de joueurs pour jeu local : 1 joueur<BR><BR>Interfaces/détecteurs pris en charge<BR>- Écran tactile<BR>- Manette / Manette à l’écran<BR>- Détecteur de mouvements<BR><BR>Langues prises en charge :<BR>Anglais(États-Unis)/Anglais(Royaume-Uni)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="it"><description><![CDATA[QUESTO CONTENUTO NON È COMPATIBILE CON I DISPOSITIVI Android™.<BR><BR>Pulling USA è un camion e trattori tirando gioco di simulazione in un ambiente 3D completo. Con oltre 30 camion e trattori e 10 classi di veicoli, la trazione non finisce mai. Aggiornamento del motore, compressore turbocompressore, sistema del veicolo / carburante e di più al garage. Regolare il peso e la pressione dei pneumatici per accogliere la gamma delle condizioni della pista. Estrarre alla fiera della contea in ambienti giorno e notte differenti o nella grande arena coperta. Il tuo lavoro attraverso i diversi concorsi guadagnare soldi e punti per la vittoria. Controllare l'acceleratore e frizione perfettamente per ottenere la vostra macchina arena scuotendo la pista. Costruisci la tua RPM, temperatura del motore, spinta e prendere giù per la pista con sporcizia effetti realistici. <BR><BR>Dimensioni del pacchetto: 123 MB - Spazio di archiviazione aggiuntivo richiesto per l'installazione<BR><BR>Informazioni sulla compatibilità:<BR>Numero di giocatori per la riproduzione in locale: 1 giocatore<BR><BR>Interfacce/sensori supportati<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / Controller su schermo<BR>- Sensore di movimento<BR><BR>Lingue supportate:<BR>Inglese(Stati Uniti)/Inglese(Regno Unito)<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="ja"><description><![CDATA[このコンテンツはAndroid™端末非対応です。<BR><BR>Pulling USA 完全な3D環境でのシミュレーションゲームを引っ張って、トラックやトラクターである。 30以上のトラックやトラクターと10車両クラスでは、決して終わらない引っ張っ。ガレージであなたの車のエンジン、過給器/ターボチャージャー、燃料システムなどをアップグレードします。トラック条件の範囲に対応するための重みとタイヤの圧力を調整します。別の昼夜の環境でまたは屋内グランドアリーナで郡フェアで引き出します。勝利のためにお金とポイントを獲得異なる競技会を通して、あなたのようにワークアップ。スロットルを制御し、トラックダウンあなたのアリーナ揺れマシンを得るために完全にクラッチ。あなたのRPM、エンジンの一時、ブーストを構築し、現実的な汚れや煙エフェクトをトラックダウン離陸。 <BR><BR>コンテンツ容量: 123 MB <BR><BR>プレイ人数: 1人<BR><BR>対応機能:<BR>- タッチスクリーン<BR>- コントローラーまたは、オンスクリーンコントローラー<BR>- モーションセンサー<BR><BR>対応言語:<BR>英語(アメリカ)/英語(イギリス)<BR><BR>著作権等:<BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="no"><description><![CDATA[DETTE INNHOLDET ER IKKE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Pulling USA er en lastebil og traktorpulling simulering spillet i en full 3D miljø. Med over 30 lastebiler og traktorer og ti kjøretøyklasser, den drar aldri slutter. Oppgradere bilens motor, supercharger / turbolader, drivstoffsystem og mer på garasjen. Justere vekter og dekktrykk å imøtekomme rekke spor forhold. Trekk på fylkesmessen i ulike dag- og natt miljøer eller i innendørs grand arena. Arbeid deg oppover gjennom de forskjellige konkurranser tjene penger og poeng for å vinne. Betjene gass og clutch perfekt å få arenaen risting maskin ned sporet. Bygg din RPM, motor temp, boost og ta av ned sporet med realistiske skitt og røykeffekter. <BR><BR>Pakkestørrelse: 123 MB - Mer lagringsplass er påkrevd for installasjon<BR><BR>Kompabilitetsinformasjon:<BR>Antall spillere for lokal spilling: 1 Spiller<BR><BR>Støttede grensesnitt/sensorer<BR>- Berøringsskjerm<BR>- Kontroller / kontroller på skjermen<BR>- Bevegelsessensor<BR><BR>Støttede språk:<BR>Engelsk/Engelsk<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="nl"><description><![CDATA[DEZE CONTENT IS NIET COMPATIBEL MET Android™-APPARATEN.<BR><BR>Pulling USA is een truck en tractor pulling simulatie spel in een volledige 3D-omgeving. Met meer dan 30 vrachtwagens en tractoren en 10 voertuigklassen, het trekken nooit eindigt. Upgrade motor, supercharger / turbo, brandstof systeem van uw voertuig en meer bij de garage. Pas de gewichten en bandenspanning om het bereik van de track voorwaarden tegemoet te komen. Trek op de kermis in verschillende dag en nacht omgevingen of in het overdekte grote arena. Werk je weg door de verschillende competities geld verdienen en de punten voor het winnen. De controle van de gaspedaal en koppeling perfect om uw arena schudden machine te krijgen over de baan. Bouw je RPM, motor temp, boost en opstijgen van de baan met realistische vuil en rook effecten. <BR><BR>Pakketgrootte: 123 MB - Meer opslagruimte vereist voor installatie<BR><BR>Compatibiliteitsinformatie:<BR>Aantal spelers voor lokaal spelen: 1 speler<BR><BR>Ondersteunde interfaces/sensoren<BR>- Touchscreen<BR>- Controller / schermcontroller<BR>- Bewegingssensor<BR><BR>Ondersteunde talen:<BR>Engels/Engels<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="pl"><description><![CDATA[TA ZAWARTOŚĆ NIE JEST KOMPATYBILNA Z URZĄDZENIAMI Z SYSTEMEM Android™.<BR><BR>Pulling USA jest ciężarówka i ciągnik ciągnie grę symulacyjną, w pełnym środowisku 3D. Z ponad 30 samochodów ciężarowych i ciągników oraz 10 klas pojazdów, ciągnąc nigdy się nie kończy. Uaktualnienie silnika, doładowania turbosprężarki, układu / paliwa Twojego pojazdu i więcej w garażu. Regulacja ciśnienia w oponach i Wag w celu dostosowania zakresu warunków na torze. Wyciągnij na targach county w różnych środowiskach, w dzień iw nocy lub w pomieszczeniach wielkiej arenie. Swój sposób pracy poprzez różne konkursy zarabiają pieniądze i punkty za wygraną. Kontrolować gaz i sprzęgło idealnie by maszyna arena potrząsając dół toru. Zbuduj swój RPM, temp silnika, impuls i startu w dół toru z realistycznych efektów dymu i brudu. <BR><BR>Rozmiar paczki: 123 MB - do instalacji potrzebne jest więcej miejsca w pamięci masowej<BR><BR>Informacje o zgodności:<BR>Liczba graczy podczas rozgrywki lokalnej: 1 Gracz<BR><BR>Obsługiwane interfejsy/czujniki<BR>- Ekran dotykowy<BR>- Kontroler / Kontroler ekranowy<BR>- Czujnik ruchu<BR><BR>Obsługiwane języki:<BR>Angielski/Angielski<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta><localizedMeta locale="sv"><description><![CDATA[DET HÄR MATERIALET ÄR INTE KOMPATIBELT MED Android™-ENHETER.<BR><BR>Pulling USA är en lastbil och traktor drar simulering spel i full 3D-miljö. Med över 30 lastbilar och traktorer och 10 fordonsklasser, drag aldrig tar slut. Uppgradera din fordonets motor, kompressor / turbo, bränslesystemet och mer på garaget. Justera vikter och däcktryck för att rymma de olika spårförhållanden. Dra på county fair i olika dag och natt miljöer eller i inomhus Grand Arena. Arbeta dig upp genom olika tävlingar tjäna pengar och poäng för att vinna. Styr gasspjället och kopplingen perfekt att få din arena skaka maskinen längs spåret. Bygg din RPM, motortemp, boost och ta av ner på spåret med realistiska smuts och rök effekter. <BR><BR>Paketstorlek: 123 MB - Ytterligare utrymme krävs för installation<BR><BR>Kompatibilitetsinformation:<BR>Antal spelare för att spela lokalt: 1 spelare<BR><BR>Gränssnitt/sensorer som stöds<BR>- Pekskärm<BR>- Handkontroll/skärmkontroll<BR>- Rörelsesensor<BR><BR>Språk som stöds:<BR>Engelska/Engelska<BR><BR>Copyright (C) 2014 Bowen Games. All Rights Reserved.<BR><BR>Android is a trademark of Google Inc.<BR><BR>]]></description></localizedMeta></localizedMetadataList>
  <genreList><genre value="Games:Racing"/><genre value="Games:Simulation"/></genreList>
  <ratingList default="SELF"><rating type="PEGIEX"><ratingLogo>PEGIEX_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="SELF"><ratingLogo>SELF_3.png</ratingLogo></rating><rating type="ESRB"><ratingLogo>ESRB_3.png</ratingLogo></rating></ratingList>
  <screenShotList><screenShot>screenshot_1.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_2.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_3.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_4.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_5.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_6.png</screenShot><screenShot>screenshot_7.png</screenShot></screenShotList>

</psmMeta>
